<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>难以集中注意力？科学说这个简单的习惯真的有效- Ynetnews</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/health_science/article/b19tatxhbg</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="ArticleHeaderComponent" class="ArticleHeaderEngComponent1280 selectableShareable for-print" role="header" aria-label="article header"&gt;&lt;p class="mainTitleWrapper"&gt;&lt;h1 class="mainTitle"&gt;Struggling to focus? Science says this simple habit really works&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="subTitleWrapper"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span disabled class="subTitle" contenteditable="false"&gt;A major new study finds physical activity significantly improves concentration; here is why exercise is critical for attention, when to work out for real gains and which workouts work best — spoiler: not running&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 03:01:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE5sQ0pYS0hLcEZDUjVHSVFPOS1nZDZpaUZBVzAzVHA5WlNxTmdfcVp5X2NGMkhNMjlHV0JZMFo2SXoxVkpfY3l3VnI0dzFsVmpFMGlvMkNxOXJxaUgzTC1kelVUaFBnSk9Ha3c</guid></item><item><title>亲爱的Annie ：人们称我为癌症“幸存者” ，但我很沮丧，不想只是克服它- OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/advice/2026/01/dear-annie-people-call-me-a-cancer-survivor-but-im-depressed-and-dont-want-to-just-get-over-it.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZAPLZQ6ZG5FCNMB2MPC4AVT44A"&gt;Dear Annie: I was diagnosed with breast cancer a few months ago. I’ve been through surgery and radiation treatments. According to the oncologists, I should now consider myself a “survivor.” Since I have scars, I’m taking medication for the next 10 years that has potentially really bad side effects, and the chance of reoccurrence is a definite possibility, I don’t feel like a “survivor.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XD4BJ2HF3FBZ5J2CPP5JQHI7O4"&gt; I readily admit that I’m depressed. I maintain that this is a perfectly reasonable reaction to something bad that has upended and changed my whole life for the foreseeable future. I’m not suicidal, and although some mornings are hard, I get up every day, shower, brush my hair and teeth and maintain my usual schedule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XERLV72NB5EBJH7PYWHXBBWHNQ"&gt; The worst thing to me about cancer is that I can’t talk to anyone because I’ve gone from an actual person with thoughts and interests to people only wanting to know about the cancer. It’s all anyone asks about. That being the case, I tried to talk to people about how I feel, but the word “depressed” freaks people out more than “cancer.” Now I just say I’m fine or OK to make others feel comfortable, which applies to my doctors as well. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EVCETBQZUBDAVCVRLFHY22F5KE"&gt; I don’t need medication, and I tried online and in-person group discussions a few times, and they aren’t for me. I’ve noticed the same thing with people who lose a loved one or have something else bad happen -- they aren’t allowed to be depressed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4KTRIQBNONECLLFFZOFPZ2XSEA"&gt; When did it become shameful and something that needs to be fixed when people have a true human emotion to events? Sad things should understandably make us sad -- and maybe depressed? Please note, I’m not talking about people with real diagnosed clinical depression or other mental issues. -- Sad “Survivor”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NSUUG75AIVF2RC2CHTH3J7C6CE"&gt; Dear Sad “Survivor”: The word “survivor” may sound triumphant, yes, but it doesn’t cancel out the fear, pain and lifelong change you’ve endured to get here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XBLJEFBKRFHXZCPE2QWRGL3XAE"&gt; It is a victory to be where you are today, and there’s nothing troubling about feeling conflicted. What is troubling is feeling you have to hide it -- especially from your doctors, who need the full picture, whether it’s pretty or not. You’re allowed to say, “I’m getting through it, but it’s still hard,” and you deserve people in your corner who can hear that without panicking or minimizing it, no matter how uncomfortable it may make them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AKRN73MG2VE67LXA5ZZLBRXBWA"&gt; Healing doesn’t happen overnight. Give yourself permission to feel whatever comes and ask honestly for the support you need. A survivor isn’t someone who feels strong all the time; it’s someone who keeps going despite hardship. By that measure, you absolutely are one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:SFE3ARRPA5AV7LDCAUW5LN3ZYY" data-fusion-component="SFE3ARRPA5AV7LDCAUW5LN3ZYY"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:SFE3ARRPA5AV7LDCAUW5LN3ZYY" data-fusion-component="SFE3ARRPA5AV7LDCAUW5LN3ZYY"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KBS5BB2UAFFXZAS3VFHZOZ5FEI"&gt;Dear Annie: After 15 years, my wife says she is filing for divorce. I’m disabled and don’t drive. I work part time and receive disability money. My wife has always helped me get to and from work because I don’t drive myself, and she also handles our bills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YY5ND5DMORFBBCNY37KUMJE2JM"&gt; I still love her, and I need to know why she has become so bitter toward me. And why did she wait till now, after I sank so much money into this life we’ve been building? What changed? -- Stunned Spouse&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LWPUFL55R5HGLFOQWTESK55EQE"&gt; Dear Stunned Spouse: I’m so sorry. The end of a marriage is always sad, but when you don’t see it coming, it can feel especially blindsiding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4XDI4BKEQBCCLNTPVGL63RHRTE"&gt; Perhaps the question isn’t what suddenly changed but what has built up over a long time. From what you describe, your wife has carried a lot of the day-to-day -- transportation, paying bills, keeping everything afloat -- which can wear a person down. That doesn’t mean this is your fault, but it might explain some of the “bitterness” you’ve picked up on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="E7SMOALE6JECLG2L3WDDCOEMCU"&gt; If she’s willing, ask for an honest conversation. You might not be able to change her mind or salvage the relationship, but getting some answers can help you at least make sense of its ending.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4CW6RMWCIVCHPAVGLW7QR4VF5Q"&gt; In the meantime, focus on building independence where you can -- transportation alternatives, financial management, legal advice. It’s important to start planning how you’ll take care of and protect yourself going forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3NZ6WOLDINBPHLN7MMXO3DMGXU"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Send your questions for Annie Lane to &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:dearannie@creators.com"&gt;&lt;i&gt;dearannie@creators.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6ECHFSPXGNGLHONECDZRWKCEIY"&gt;COPYRIGHT 2023 &lt;a href="http://creators.com/"&gt;CREATORS.COM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2AFBVV95cUxQR2VaZW8zOENZam02Y2IzamFjS0M0Z0Uyc0VBV0JHNjc3b19qdWpsSFR6bFQ3X1NwZkw5ZXhYRDJodXY3dGJFb3JRNnBXT3FYRUpkbWd3Z1owV0IzTm5MdjdQYW5wUVJ6dk9VdncycXlRVGpuSUxYYnVJRmphem9OTUhQbnNQYjI5WGlqZVZsNzNYSzhubTl5enNyTllFMUhNZ0ktbUgyTjc2Rkg0T1ZOSlZGX0RaR2xnamFfams2U0I0TnA4azNid3pJemVHUnN1M25zWlJobmjSAewBQVVfeXFMTW5uLUdCZjdUTFE2WjhnbU1OcV9KSHlzeUIzQ0xqRGZlLUdQSms1WVVfLU5qb1pvWUZIa2pFcFJvYTM2a252bW9wNDB1ZEphTTdoNVA4YW5fS1ZTclNzOWhvTkdTcnpqVDR4Qlh5LWNTTnVRTkJaMkFKU3oyR0xZSUl6SzhKNnd0WXQ3cndETFJpbzk2d2IwNWdEYjVLUzRnc01BNWZjVnc5VGVZTS1RWGFyMnE5c1BOTlFBbVVHOVFIaFR0czhFX2dncWJGbFBBei1qQkotUlZSUXF4aHg3UkpBTVB0dEFEaG1NeEU</guid></item><item><title>加拿大神秘脑部疾病之战-英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c623r47d67lo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;'The answer cannot be nothing': The battle over Canada's mystery brain disease&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 ciiGlA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 kdBCdE"&gt;Joel Gunter,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 eDNgSC"&gt;senior international reporter, New Brunswick&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-9 keGieE"&gt;and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-1" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 ciiGlA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 kdBCdE"&gt;Nadine Yousif,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-1-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 eDNgSC"&gt;senior Canada reporter, New Brunswick&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC Graphic showing a photograph of Dr Marerro against a stylised black, white and yellow background. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;BBC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;b id="five-hundred-people-in-a-small-canadian-province-were-diagnosed-with-a-mystery-brain-disease.-what-would-it-mean-for-the-patients-if-the-disease-was-never-real?" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;Five hundred people in a small Canadian province were diagnosed with a mystery brain disease. What would it mean for the patients if the disease was never real?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In early 2019, officials at a hospital in the small Canadian province of New Brunswick noticed that two patients had contracted an extremely rare brain condition known as Creutzfeldt-Jakob Disease, or CJD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;CJD is both fatal and potentially contagious, so a group of experts was quickly assembled to investigate. Fortunately for New Brunswick, the disease didn't spread. But the story didn't end there. In fact, it was just beginning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Among the experts was Alier Marrero, a soft-spoken, Cuban-born neurologist who had been working in the province for about six years. Marrero would share some worrying information with the other members of the group. He had been seeing patients with unexplained CJD-like symptoms for several years, he said, including young people who showed signs of a rapidly progressing dementia. The number of cases was already more than 20, Marrero said, and several patients had already died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Because of the apparent similarity to CJD, Marrero had been reporting these cases to Canada's Creutzfeldt-Jakob Disease Surveillance System, or CJDSS. But the results had been coming back negative. Marrero was stumped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;More worrying still, he was seeing a dizzying array of symptoms among the patients, according to his notes. There were cases of dementia, weight loss, unsteadiness, jerking movements and facial twitches. There were patients with spasms, visions, limb pain, muscle atrophy, dry skin and hair loss. Many said they were suffering with both insomnia and waking hallucinations. Patients reported excessive sweating and excessive drooling. Several exhibited Capgras Delusion, which causes someone to believe that a person close to them has been replaced by an identical-looking imposter. Others appeared to lose the ability to speak. One patient would report that she had forgotten how to write the letter Q.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero ordered test after test. But he was at a loss. "I just kept seeing new patients, I kept documenting new cases, and I kept seeing new people dying," he recalled. "And an image of a cluster became more clear."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Many of the cluster patients believe industrial poisoning has affected New Brunswick's environment. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Over the coming months, Marrero and the CJDSS scientists began to suspect that instead of a small cluster of CJD patients, the province of New Brunswick might have on its hands a much larger cluster of people suffering from a completely unknown brain disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Over the next five years, Marrero's cluster would balloon from 20 to an astonishing 500. But there came no scientific breakthrough, no new understanding of neurology, no expensive new treatments. Instead, last year, a bombshell research paper authored by several Canadian neurologists and neuroscientists concluded that there was in fact no mystery disease, and that the patients had all likely suffered from previously known neurological, medical, or psychiatric conditions. The New Brunswick cluster was, one of the paper's authors told the BBC, a "house of cards".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;To report this story, the BBC spent time with Marrero and spoke to a dozen of his patients or their relatives — some of whom are telling their story for the first time — as well as key scientists, experts, and government officials, and reviewed hundreds of pages of internal emails and documents obtained by freedom of information requests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;We can reveal that at least one cluster patient has now opted for death via medical assistance in dying — legal in Canada since 2016. The diagnosis on the death certificate, according to the doctor who signed it off, was "degenerative neurological condition of unknown cause". At least one other cluster patient is currently considering assisted dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The research paper published last year could have marked the end of a strange chapter in Canadian science. Except, hundreds of the patients disagree. Defiant, fiercely loyal to Marrero, and backed by passionate patient advocates, they argue that the paper is flawed and reject any notion that the cluster might not be real.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Many believe instead that they have been poisoned by an industrial environmental toxin, and that the government of New Brunswick has conspired against them to cover it up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I'm not a conspiracy theorist type person, at all, but I honestly think it's financially motivated," said Jillian Lucas, one of the patients. "There's all these different levels."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Lucas first met Marrero back in early 2020, after her stepfather, Derek Cuthbertson, an accountant and military veteran, began experiencing cognitive and behavioural problems including sudden rage and loss of empathy. He was referred to Marrero, who ordered a battery of tests but was unable to explain his symptoms. Cuthbertson became one of the early cluster patients — the so-called "original 48".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Lucas had just gone through a divorce and suffered a bad concussion, and she moved back in with her mother and Cuthbertson in their rural community near the city of Moncton. Soon she began experiencing her own symptoms and went to see Marrero for herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"He ran so many tests, so much blood work and scans and spinal taps," Lucas recalled. "We were trying to rule absolutely everything out and we just kept coming up with more questions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Short on answers, Marrero added Lucas to the cluster. Over the coming months, her symptoms worsened and new symptoms appeared. She experienced light sensitivity, tremors, terrible migraines and issues with her memory and ability to speak clearly, she said. She felt unexplained stabbing pains. Cold water felt scalding hot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Jillian Lucas and her stepfather Derek Cuthbertson. Both were diagnosed by Marrero with the mystery illness. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero, though, was attentive and caring. He took her symptoms seriously. "He made me feel seen and that what I was experiencing was important," Lucas wrote in a Facebook post about her struggle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It was a sentiment that seemed to be shared by everyone who saw Marrero. He held their hands during appointments. He remembered them, cried with them. He was "the only one listening to them," said Lori-Ann Roness, one of the cluster patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"He's an incredible human and physician," said Melissa Nicholson, whose mother died last year after being diagnosed with the mystery disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Watching our mom go through it was hard enough," Nicholson said. "But he was such a pillar of support."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In March 2021, with Canada still in the grip of the Covid pandemic, the cluster suddenly became news. New Brunswick's chief medical officer had sent a memo to doctors alerting them to the apparent syndrome and suggesting they contact Marrero with possible cases. The memo leaked and the story hit the papers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero found himself inundated with new patients. But he was also drawing support from the highest levels of Canadian science. The working group set up to respond to the original CJD cases had evolved into a multi-disciplinary group studying the cluster, and the possibility of a mysterious new neurological condition seemed, at times, irresistible to the scientists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's like reading a movie script," emailed one researcher to colleagues, about an early story in the Toronto Star.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We are all in the movie!", a senior federal scientist replied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Dr Marrero at home in New Brunswick. "I kept documenting new cases and I kept seeing new people dying," he said. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;At the heart of the working group was Marrero, along with Dr Michael Coulthart, the head of the CJD Surveillance System; Dr Neil Cashman, a leading Canadian neurologist; Dr Michael Strong, the head of the Canadian Institutes of Health Research (CIHR); and Dr Samuel Weiss, one of the CIHR's senior neurologists. All agreed that Marrero needed considerable support. Strong said he could arrange additional staff and offered himself up as a consultant. The CIHR offered the province of New Brunswick C$5 million ($3.6m; £2.7m) to investigate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And the mystery disease got a name: the "New Brunswick Neurological Syndrome of Unknown Cause". In an email to Marrero in April 2021, Strong called it "one of the most unusual constellations of findings I have ever seen".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We all owe you a debt of gratitude," he wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But not everyone was on board. Dr Gerard Jansen, a neuropathologist who was attached to the CJD Surveillance System, had noticed something unusual when referrals from Marrero's office started piling up. Jansen recalled feeling "flabbergasted" at Marrero's notes, which he said featured an array of broad and unrelated clinical observations — a "diarrhea of symptoms".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jansen saw clues in the patients' files that he said pointed to already defined neurological diseases. When he examined brain tissue samples of a few cluster patients who had died, he found signs of Alzheimer's disease and Lewy body dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He was alarmed. His superior, Coulthart, appeared to believe something unexplained was happening in New Brunswick, Jansen said. Keen to get his concerns down in writing, he sent Coulthart a long and detailed email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"All available evidence and logic" pointed to a collection of different diseases, Jansen wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The patients are real, but the clustering as a mystery disease is not."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The early cases seemed to be grouped around two locations: Moncton and the Acadian Peninsula. Suspecting an environmental link, the scientists and officials considered various possible culprits, from a rare moose-borne parasite to blue-green algae blooms to Agent Orange sprayed on the province in the 1970s. Nothing bore fruit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero said he had observed an uptick in cases in late summer and early autumn — forestry spraying season — and he zeroed in on a controversial herbicide called glyphosate. Chronic exposure to glyphosate, which is used extensively by New Brunswick's forestry industry, has been linked by some studies to neuroinflammation and Parkinson's disease. (Forest NB, an industry body, told the BBC that glyphosate was used in compliance with regulations and was "not expected to pose risks" to human health or the environment.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;According to Marrero, many of his patients were showing highly elevated levels of both glyphosate and various heavy metals. Though when asked by the BBC what proportion of his 500 or so patients had concerning results, he refused to say. "I don't want to provide exact numbers of anything, but let's say it's an unusual number. Beyond 100."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;By April 2021, the focus was firmly on a possible environmental toxin. Strong, the CIHR director, said he thought a full "boots-on-the-ground" investigation was needed. The same month, a specialist clinic — the Mind Clinic — was set up in New Brunswick with Marrero at the helm to treat the cluster patients. With the $5m on offer from the CIHR, and the backing of Strong and other top federal scientists, all the conditions appeared set to get to the bottom of the mystery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But then, everything changed. In May, New Brunswick effectively suspended the collaboration with the federal scientists. The province also decided not to take up the $5m on offer from the CIHR. According to Marrero, the decision killed off any prospect of finding an answer. "Everybody received that email like a cold shower," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;None of the provincial officials involved agreed to talk to the BBC on the record. But it is clear there was concern about Marrero's methods and about the nature of his contact with Coulthart, Strong and the other federal scientists. The view of some at senior levels of the New Brunswick government was that the informal working group, seduced by the possibility of a scientific mystery, was circumventing the province.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But the decision to leave the money on the table, rather than spend it investigating, fuelled suspicions that New Brunswick wanted to avoid scrutiny of its environment. According to Kat Lanteigne, the executive director of Canadian health non-profit Bloodwatch and a tireless supporter of Marrero, the actions of the province amounted to a full-blown cover up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They pulled the plug because they just don't want anybody looking," Lanteigne said. "Full stop."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Taking control of the process, New Brunswick mounted two investigations into the original cluster of 48 — one telephone questionnaire and one study of the patients' medical records by an oversight committee of six provincial neurologists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jansen, the neuropathologist who had raised concerns, had by that point examined the autopsies of eight cluster patients and firmly believed they all had known, diagnosable illnesses. Troubled, he passed his conclusions on to the oversight committee and presented them to the Canadian Association of Neuropathologists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Not long after that, the New Brunswick government finished its investigations, concluding in February 2022 that there was no common environmental cause and no common condition among the patients. In other words, no mystery disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;A protest sign in New Brunswick. Some residents are angry about pesticide use in the province. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But the government had decided against examining any of the patients in person, an omission that outraged those who believed they were part of the cluster. The patients — now 105 in number — were attending sporadic appointments with Marrero at the Mind Clinic but seeing little progress. Jillian Lucas's symptoms were worsening at such a rate that she had begun to weigh something once unthinkable to her: medically assisted dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;At the clinic, appointments with Marrero could be strangely conspiratorial, patients said. During one appointment, Lucas's stepmother Susan recalled, Marrero put his hand up, told them to stop talking, and went to the door to listen. "He said, 'I believe we are being recorded'."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Stacie Quigley-Cormier, whose stepdaughter Gabrielle was the youngest member of the cluster, said Marrero always spoke in a hushed tone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The experience with Dr Marrero — and other patients talk about this too — is you make sure you start talking after the door is closed, and there's a quiet tone to his voice, and you make sure you're not talking in the hallways and things like that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero declined to discuss it. "Some patients actually thought that way. And I… We wondered… But I don't want to comment."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In August 2022, Marrero was sacked from the Mind Clinic. "Despite our repeated attempts to inform you of our expectations and the deficiencies in your performance, you have not demonstrated a sustained ability to meet our expectations," wrote John Dornan, then-CEO of the health network. The 105 cluster patients each received their own letter, telling them they could stay at the clinic, with all the resources it had to offer, or strike out alone with Marrero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Many were offended on behalf of their neurologist. "When they called me to ask my choice, I said, it's not a choice, it's an ultimatum," Lucas said. "And I choose him."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Jillian Lucas at home with one of the family's 15 parrots. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She wasn't alone. Of the 105 patients, 94 chose Marrero. Just 11 people decided to stay with the clinic and get a second opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Outside of the clinic, increasingly isolated, Marrero continued to diagnose the mystery disease. He was sending patients for so many tests, for such obscure toxins or conditions, that some reported being met with an increasingly quizzical eye at the testing clinic, as if to say, "What now?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Others found it difficult to get an appointment with Marrero or even speak to his assistant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I've messaged a couple of times but they're so busy, you can't even hardly get a hold of them by email," said Lucas. "He just has so many patients."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;As the cluster generated more news coverage in Canada, little attention was paid to the 11 patients who had decided to stay with the Mind Clinic, and their stories have never been told.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Kevin Strickland's partner April was referred to Marrero after she stopped her car in the middle of the road one morning and apparently forgot how to drive. April, then 60, had already been showing some dementia-like symptoms, but the driving incident scared Strickland. Marrero ran a series of tests on April and diagnosed the mystery illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"He told me it was the mystery illness and he wanted to look further into it, but he never really did much after that," Strickland said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Kevin Strickland at home with his rescue dog. His partner April was diagnosed by Marrero with the mystery illness. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The couple waited eight months to get important test results from Marrero, Strickland said, as April's condition worsened. Soon Strickland could no longer manage her care. But to get her a place in assisted living he needed a letter of support from Marrero. "I think I waited four months for that letter," Strickland recalled. "I kept phoning and asking."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Eventually he gave up and turned to the Mind Clinic, he said, and got the letter. And the Mind Clinic neurologists gave April something else she needed — a firm diagnosis. She was suffering from a form of frontotemporal dementia. In the end, Marrero "did nothing for April," Strickland said. "I guess he was more interested in proving the mystery illness than he was helping his patients," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Sandi Partridge also chose to remain with the Mind Clinic. She felt a deep sense of loyalty to Marrero, but she also saw simple common sense in getting a second opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Partridge had first seen Marrero in 2020, after suffering headaches and balance issues. He ordered a barrage of tests — according to Partridge she had two MRIs, two EEGs, a SPECT, a CAT scan and a spinal tap, as well as more than a dozen different antibody tests. "It was mostly a lot of testing with Dr Marrero," she recalled. "Every time he would see me, it would be an hour and a half, sometimes two hours, and he would retest me every single time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But every test came back negative. Partridge had also provided Marrero with a video of her having a seizure at home, which he studied. He diagnosed her with the mystery illness. "Those were the words he used," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Sandi Partridge in a park near her home. "It was mostly a lot of testing with Dr Marrero," she said. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;One thing Marrero never mentioned to Partridge was functional neurological disorder, which was her eventual diagnosis. FND is a complex condition; previously known as psychosomatic or psychogenic illness, it describes physical symptoms with a psychological root. It presents a challenge to doctors, who have to guide patients through the stigma associated with it to an understanding that they have a real condition that requires complex treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Partridge's neurologists at the Mind Clinic also reviewed the seizure video she had shown to Marrero. "As soon as Dr Abdellah saw my seizure he said, that's FND," Partridge recalled. (Abdellah declined to speak to the BBC). Partridge threw herself into researching the condition. "And I thought, that's me, that's me, that's me, that's me," she said. "I hit every single marker."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Partridge is now on a multi-faceted FND treatment programme involving neurology, neuropsychology and occupational health. And she is at peace with her diagnosis. "The stigma is difficult," she said, "but I've accepted it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Gabrielle Cormier, the youngest patient in Marrero's cluster, would also receive a diagnosis of FND, but her journey would follow a different path.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Cormier has featured heavily in the media coverage of the cluster, becoming a kind of poster child for the mystery disease. She was first referred to Marrero at just 18. A high school student, dancer and competitive figure skater, she had begun to experience fatigue-like symptoms and muscle soreness and then passed out at school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Cormier was already taking anti-anxiety medication, and the hospital emergency room doctor told her the incident was anxiety-induced. Unhappy with his assessment (he told Cormier, who is gay, that she "just needed to find a boyfriend", she said), the family looked to Marrero for answers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Gabrielle Cormier was diagnosed by Marrero at just 18. "I've done nothing with my life since I got sick," she said. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero was different — empathetic, caring. As he had with other patients, he ran Cormier through a gauntlet of tests. When nothing showed up, he diagnosed her with the mystery illness. Canada was deep in the isolation of the Covid lockdown, but Marrero reassured them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"He said, there's a dozen other people at least that are experiencing similar things to what you're experiencing, and I don't have answers for it yet," stepmother Stacie Quigley-Cormier recalled. "He told her that she wasn't alone."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There was one test Marrero couldn't secure: a PET scan, because the hard-up province was largely reserving them for cancer patients. So Cormier's parents took her to Toronto for the scan and a second opinion by a leading neurologist there, Dr Anthony Lang.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;After a multi-day evaluation at a specialist neurology centre, Lang diagnosed Cormier with FND. Her tests showed that conscious movements were weak but forced reflex or automotive movements were normal and healthy. It pointed to psychology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The Quigley-Cormiers were initially prepared to accept the FND diagnosis, they said. But they left Toronto unhappy after Lang told them to stop treating Cormier as though she had a terminal illness because it was reinforcing her condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A few weeks later, Lang called Cormier to inform her that a delayed test result had shown some reduced blood flow in her brain — something Marrero had also observed — and which can be caused by various medical or psychological issues including depression. Lang told Cormier the abnormality was slight and bore no relation to her symptoms, so she shouldn't worry about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The call didn't sit well with the Quigley-Cormiers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"There was no reason to call her personal phone when he knew she had memory problems," said her father Andre, angrily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Global News Jillian Lucas and other patients stand in front of a government building holding signs saying 'We are not a mystery, 'We stand by Doctor Marrero' and other slogans. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Global News&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Gabrielle Cormier, in her wheelchair, with other patients calling for suppport. Jillian Lucas is far left. (Global News)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The call pushed the Quigley-Cormier family away from Lang and his FND diagnosis and back towards Marrero, who the family had come to believe in deeply. Marrero had never crossed "any kind of line," Stacie said. "He's pristine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"That's why all his patients like him," Andre said. "Love him, maybe."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero continued to test Cormier repeatedly. He prescribed anti-seizure medication to prevent possible seizures, though she had not had any. He referred her for a round of intravenous immunoglobulin treatment — which she said caused severe headaches, aches, nausea, dizziness and aseptic meningitis — and prescribed a powerful intravenous immunosuppressant used for blood cancers and autoimmune illnesses. Neither improved her condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Cormier once dreamed of studying pathology. But her illness caused her to drop out of university and for years she has gone everywhere either in a wheelchair or with a cane, living, for a 24-year-old, a restricted life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I've had this idea that my life has been wasted, or that I've done nothing with my life since I got sick," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"So, yeah, it kind of feels like I've been robbed of that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Lang, the Toronto neurologist, came away from his interaction with the Quigley-Cormier family troubled. His call to Cormier was not only appropriate, he said, he was ethically bound to communicate with her directly because she was a mentally competent adult who did not ask for her parents to act for her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Over the coming months, Lang watched with concern as the purported cluster ballooned in New Brunswick. He emailed Marrero and left messages with his secretary offering help, but never heard back. In late 2023, frustrated by what he saw as cluster misinformation everywhere, Lang decided with colleagues to mount a study. The results — published in May 2025 in the Journal of the American Medical Association, JAMA — landed in New Brunswick like a hand grenade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Lang and his co-authors — including several former Mind Clinic colleagues of Marrero and the concerned neuropathologist, Gerard Jansen — found that all 25 patients in their study had suffered from previously known conditions, from functional neurological disorder to dementia to cancer. The probability of there being no new disease was close to 100%, they said. The real cause of the cluster, they concluded, was serial misdiagnosis by Marrero, compounded by credulous media reporting, the limitations of New Brunswick's public health system, institutional distrust sown by the pandemic and the actions of a small group of people "co-opting the crisis to suit their agenda".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Dr Lang was the leading author on a paper casting doubt on the cluster. (Sammy Kogan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The cases in the JAMA paper consisted of 14 live patients and 11 autopsies. Most of the live patients were people who had chosen to remain at the Mind Clinic, like Sandi Partridge. A few, including Gabrielle Cormier, were included via a consent waiver — a legal process which allows researchers to use patient data without their express consent provided certain anonymity criteria are met.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The study's conclusions incensed the most vocal patients and patient advocates, including Kat Lanteigne and Stacie Quigley-Cormier, who allege that the research was unscientific and unethical. The Quigley-Cormiers are furious that Gabrielle's data was used for the study, and their lawyers have sent letters to Lang and to the journal alleging the paper was a violation of her privacy. JAMA declined to comment on the dispute. Lang said that the research was legal, ethical and appropriately anonymised. As for the alleged violation of privacy, he pointed out that the only reason anyone knew Cormier's data was used was because her father and stepmother had told the media, along with many other details about her life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;On a bright morning this past September, Marrero was sitting in his home office in a large cottage-style house on a plot of land just outside of Moncton. A stone fountain burbled softly in his Japanese-inspired peace garden. Birds sang in his own patch of forest — untouched by herbicides or pesticides, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero is undeniably charismatic. He has a warm smile and demeanour. He speaks gently, but with authority. He remembers small details about people he barely knows and asks about their wellbeing in a manner that conveys genuine care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Settled in his office chair, he recalled with obvious pleasure that not so long ago, some of Canada's top scientists had sat with him around that very desk, ready to take on a scientific mystery. But now, Marrero seemed increasingly isolated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They are trying to present me as it," he said, dejectedly. "I was part of it, but I was not it. The only difference is, when the table was empty, I stayed."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Of Marrero's early federal collaborators — Drs Coulthart, Cashman, Strong, and Weiss — only Coulthart agreed to speak to the BBC about the cluster. He denied ever having been convinced by the idea of a unified, mystery syndrome. "As a scientist, I use the word convinced very, very sparingly," he said. "But don't let anybody kid you — if anyone says they know what's going on or isn't going on in New Brunswick, they're either lying or grossly mistaken. Because nobody has the facts."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Dr Marrero in his home office. "I was part of it, but I was not it," he said. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;An upcoming provincial report could offer some answers. Unlike the previous studies, it will examine the claims of elevated glyphosate and heavy metals in the patients. At times, the stakes seem impossibly high. "Lives hang in the balance," read a recent letter to Premier Susan Holt, signed by 72 of the patients. "It is within your power to honour them, cherish them, and care for them," the letter said. "Or you can abandon them and let them wither, fade, and ultimately die. Please join us on the right side of history."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The patient advocates, led by Bloodwatch director Kat Lanteigne, have arguably done more than anyone to keep the story of the cluster going, with an operation that includes lobbying the government, briefing the press and sending legal letters to scientists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Lanteigne has publicly attacked both Jansen and Lang over the JAMA study, branding their work inaccurate and unethical. She denied harassing Jansen, saying she had never spoken to him directly and emailed him only once. "I have a record of speaking truth to power and I have always worked with integrity and honesty," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Both Lang and Jansen are standing their ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"What we have here is a case of misdiagnosis, evolving to misinformation, and sadly resulting in suffering for patients and families," Lang said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I would even go further," Jansen said, regarding the alleged misdiagnosis of the patients. "I would say they are being abused."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Few others are willing to criticise Marrero so openly. Privately, former senior government officials and colleagues of Marrero have questioned whether he should have been investigated. The Royal College of Physicians told the BBC it could not comment on whether there had been complaints against any individual physician, and none have been made public in relation to Marrero. Any sanction process would typically begin with a complaint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And that was the issue, one former senior health official said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It has to be a patient complaint," they said. "And all his patients love him."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The last time Jillian Lucas saw Marrero was more than a year ago. He tested her again, but she is yet to see the results. During the appointment, he told her that just getting a common cold could kill her, she said. So she rarely leaves the house — a cramped and densely cluttered property that the family shares with 15 parrots. "She spends 90% of her time in her bedroom," her stepmother said. "It's a very limited life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Kat Lanteigne told the BBC that Marrero "deserves the Order of Canada for what he has done for these people." But many patients, like Lucas, are languishing. Largely untreated, they have undergone test after test in search of the mystery disease and ended up back where they began, or somewhere worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In response to criticisms in this story, Marrero said that he would not comment on patients or fellow physicians. "The focus must remain on the hundreds of suffering patients, their families and communities who need to be the heart of our attention and care," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Jillian Lucas in her back garden. "I don't want to be in a nursing home, or be a burden," she said. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jillian Lucas has now seen a second doctor, but only because she has pushed ahead with her decision to explore medical assistance in dying, which requires two physicians to sign off. Canada has among the world's most permissive laws for assisted dying, allowing people to pursue it without a terminal diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;When Lucas told Marrero her plan, he became "choked up", she said. "It eats him up, he's fighting back tears."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And yet, Marrero agreed to support her application, despite her not having a concrete diagnosis or testing positive for any known condition. (Marrero told the BBC he "took the utmost care to abide by" the laws around Maid and had "never proposed it" to a patient.) After all the years of uncertainty with the unknown neurological syndrome, the option of dying gave Lucas some sense of control. "I have a limit in my mind of how far I can go," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Sitting in his garden office, the sun streaming in, Marrero had no such limits in mind. "I keep going because I know," he said, confidently. He had been able to meet "with some of the best scientists in the country," he said. He had more than 500 cluster patients now, and every week the number was going up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:23:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE00b0FrMWhDd2xNaUZfZG10SW5WeWxkMk10UWVhb0pGQnZJcmJQazJNeDBlMDY0S3hHVTJJOGg3Qm1UbW1EakFOWkZEdkd5ZjFmdmphMU5MV2ZZUdIBX0FVX3lxTE1oWXM1LWw5WExGVkczRlM0WWNoUXhxcndjNWZ4akFxVXVIcVdvdU1DMENQUXdfWV9TS2RkUlo4LTAyb0V1cEJ6VnhLanQ0VUdTWWtIaTl1Uko2QV83emVj</guid></item><item><title>“Super-K”流感变种正在澳大利亚蔓延。以下是它“不寻常”的原因- SBS澳大利亚</title><link>https://www.sbs.com.au/news/article/what-you-need-to-know-about-the-super-k-flu-variant/tdpgmr6b2</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleBodyLayout_articleContentBody__bS_cb"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;A new strain of influenza known as 'Super-K', or the subclade-K variant, could be responsible for an unusual spring and summer boost in flu cases, epidemiologists say.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"The unusual thing here for Australia is the timing," WHO Collaborating Centre for Reference and Research on Influenza director Patrick Reading told SBS News.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"The not unusual thing is probably the symptoms," he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ArticleBodyAdContainer_adContainer__fvTT2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reading recalls the subclade-K variant emerged towards the end of Australia and New Zealand's typical flu season, circulating in September rather than the winter months.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"That was responsible for elevated influenza cases throughout the spring and actually throughout the start of our summer in December as well."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to the Global Initiative on Sharing All Influenza Data (GISAID), the total lab confirmed cases of subclade-K in Australia so far currently sits at 1,083.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A new report by the Australian Centre for Disease Control (ACDC) stated that subclade-K's rapid spread has the potential to put increased pressure on Australian health care services over the summer and into the 2026 influenza season.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Current case numbers for influenza are higher than usual for this time of year compared to previous seasons," an ACDC spokesperson said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;So far this year, over 4,100 cases of influenza have been confirmed by laboratories, with the true number of flu cases likely to be higher.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;By comparison, in the first quarter of last year, an average of around 3,300 cases were confirmed weekly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rich-text override-heading-font MuiBox-root mui-exul89"&gt;&lt;h2 data-testid="embed-heading" id=""&gt;What was the cause of the subclade-K flu variant?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Every few decades, a flu virus can undergo a much larger genetic change called antigenic shift, which can lead to a pandemic, but this is not what has happened with super-K," University of South Australia epidemiology professor Adrian Esterman said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Instead, super-K is best understood as a drifted version of the familiar H3N2 virus, with enough changes to allow it to spread more widely in populations with existing immunity."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The ACDC report noted Australian subclade-K viruses may have originated in or been imported from the US, following detections in the US in June and July last year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reading said there's no current evidence that the variant is more severe than a regular flu. What experts are seeing, however, is that it easily transmits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"It appears that it's probably going to have an ability to at least be slightly less sensitive to antibody or vaccine-mediated protection," he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Deakin University epidemiology professor Catherine Bennett told SBS News: "This new subvariant of the H3N2 is that bit more immune evasive with these latest mutations in the part of the virus that allows it to invade our cells, making us more susceptible."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bennett said the 2025 flu vaccine included H3N2, but not this specific class.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Flu vaccines wane in effectiveness, so people vaccinated back in April-May and only getting infected now won't have the same benefit," she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;However, the 2026 flu vaccine for the southern hemisphere has already been updated to include this variant, and will likely be available around April, Bennett said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Esterman said the flu vaccine remains worthwhile and provides important protection.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"It still significantly reduces the risk of severe disease."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rich-text override-heading-font MuiBox-root mui-exul89"&gt;&lt;h2 data-testid="embed-heading" id=""&gt;What does a typical flu season look like in Australia?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"When we get seasonal influenza every year in Australia, or anywhere, it's a combination of three viruses," said Reading. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are two influenza A viruses — a H3N2 and H1N1 — and one influenza B virus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to the Australian Centre for Disease Control, there were 365,261 reports of the flu in 2024. Cases spiked between May and August, and drastically dropped following the winter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;"As we move into spring, flu generally comes down in Australia, and then it's very low during summer," said Reading.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Last year there were 502,493 reports of influenza, with cases clearly continuing until the end of the year following those winter months.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to GISAID, H3N2 subclade-K is driving an estimated 90 per cent of cases in the United States.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"What we saw around September [in Australia] onwards is the H1N1s and B viruses decreased, but we saw an increase in H3N2 viruses," Reading said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rich-text override-heading-font MuiBox-root mui-exul89"&gt;&lt;h2 data-testid="embed-heading" id=""&gt;How can I avoid catching the flu?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"People who are unwell should consider testing and should avoid mixing with other people as much as possible," Bennett said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Keep homes well-ventilated, hold gatherings outdoor if possible, and wear a mask in busy public indoor spaces if susceptible to more severe respiratory infections."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;NSW Health advises getting the annual flu vaccine, as well as practising good hand hygiene — including handwashing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SBS Australia</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:13:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQLXl5ZzdBT2hYWkVncFVCanlhVEw4M25RRHYwYnlWNDZvRjlxS1B6TUxoc2NyZUFnOWwzM0lRZEotYjdCdjFFbHowRlFfOXVtazJ0LXVuenZLWUFJeDJUdDZPcGFFV1cyYjhIZWJCc24tVzBzUktPT0NYY0MtZWRCN0JOUGxtVUJCQ1UycW55VE9MUlNrVWozV2lsMTlkUQ</guid></item><item><title>60年代和70年代的7种常见做法今天是非法的（或可耻的） - VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/r-t-7-common-practices-from-the-60s-and-70s-that-would-be-illegal-or-scandalous-today/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;The 1960s and 70s are often remembered as decades of freedom, rebellion, and experimentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They were loud, expressive, and full of cultural shifts that still influence how we live today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But they were also surprisingly casual about things we now see as dangerous, unethical, or flat-out unacceptable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking back isn’t about moral superiority, it’s about noticing how quickly norms change once we understand the consequences of our choices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you zoom out, it becomes a lesson in psychology more than history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What we tolerate says less about right and wrong, and more about what we’ve collectively agreed not to question yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are seven everyday practices from that era that would never make it past today’s laws or social standards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1) Smoking everywhere&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to overstate how normal smoking once was. Cigarettes weren’t just common, they were embedded into the physical design of public spaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You could smoke on airplanes, in offices, in restaurants, and in hospital waiting rooms. Ashtrays were built into desks and armrests, and nobody thought twice about lighting up indoors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What’s striking is that the issue wasn’t just people choosing to smoke. It was everyone else being forced to participate whether they wanted to or not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/10644-secondhand-smoke-dangers" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Secondhand smoke&lt;/a&gt; wasn’t widely discussed, and the idea that it could seriously harm others hadn’t yet entered the mainstream conversation. If you didn’t like it, that was your problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/s-bt-9-things-boomers-did-in-their-30s-that-would-get-someone-fired-arrested-or-divorced-today/"&gt;smoking indoors&lt;/a&gt; in most public places is illegal, and socially it’s often frowned upon even outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The shift feels obvious now, but at the time it required a complete reframing of what personal choice actually means.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a great example of how cultural blindness works. When a behavior is everywhere, it fades into the background and stops registering as harmful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2) Corporal punishment in schools&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was a time when physical punishment in schools wasn’t controversial. It was policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Teachers openly hit students with paddles, rulers, or straps as a form of discipline. Parents often supported it, believing it built character and respect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What we now understand about child psychology tells a very different story. Fear may produce compliance, but it also produces &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/basics/anxiety" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;anxiety&lt;/a&gt;, shame, and long-term stress responses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most schools today ban &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/z-if-you-survived-these-9-parenting-styles-from-the-70s-youre-either-incredibly-resilient-or-deeply-traumatized/"&gt;corporal punishment&lt;/a&gt; outright, and where it still exists, it’s heavily criticized. The idea of striking a child in the name of education now feels deeply unsettling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What’s uncomfortable is realizing how confident adults once were that this was the right approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Authority plus tradition created a shield that protected the practice from scrutiny.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s a reminder that just because something is common doesn’t mean it’s healthy, especially when the people affected have no voice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3) Drinking and driving as a social norm&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the 60s and early 70s, drunk driving wasn’t treated as a serious crime. It was often brushed off as bad judgment or even a funny story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Movies played it for laughs, and police responses were inconsistent at best.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In some cases, officers would simply follow a driver home to make sure they got there safely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The idea that you should not drive after drinking simply hadn’t solidified yet. Alcohol and cars coexisted with little friction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, this behavior is both illegal and socially condemned. DUI laws are strict, and public awareness campaigns have made the risks impossible to ignore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What changed wasn’t just legislation. It was perception.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once society collectively agreed that drunk driving wasn’t normal or funny, behavior shifted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/k-bt-if-youve-ever-said-no-to-these-5-types-of-invites-psychology-says-youre-mentally-stronger-than-most/"&gt;Social pressure&lt;/a&gt; turned out to be just as powerful as legal consequences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4) Casual prescribing of powerful drugs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-78422" src="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly.png" alt="" srcset="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly.png 1600w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-300x158.png 300w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-1024x538.png 1024w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-768x403.png 768w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-1536x806.png 1536w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-1200x630.png 1200w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-857x450.png 857w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-900x473.png 900w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-420x221.png 420w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-840x441.png 840w" sizes="(max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pharmaceutical culture of the 60s and 70s was shockingly relaxed by today’s standards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doctors regularly prescribed amphetamines, tranquilizers, and sedatives with minimal oversight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stimulants were given to boost productivity. Sedatives were handed out to help people &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/r-lc-7-behaviors-that-seem-normal-but-are-secretly-stress-responses-according-to-psychology/"&gt;cope with stress&lt;/a&gt; or boredom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was enormous trust in medical authority, and very little emphasis on informed consent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Patients rarely questioned prescriptions, and doctors rarely explained long-term risks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, that level of casual prescribing would raise serious red flags. We now require clinical trials, disclosures, and ongoing monitoring for good reason.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From a decision-making perspective, this shows how power imbalances work. When one side holds all the knowledge, the other side is unlikely to push back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It also shows how good intentions can still lead to harm when systems lack accountability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5) Workplace behavior with no boundaries&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Office culture in the 60s and 70s operated under rules that would be unacceptable today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sexual &lt;a href="https://thinkhumanrights.ca/know-your-rights/what-is-harassment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;harassment&lt;/a&gt; laws were minimal or nonexistent, and power dynamics were largely ignored.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unwanted comments, inappropriate touching, and relationships between bosses and employees were often dismissed as normal office life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Complaints, if they were voiced at all, were rarely taken seriously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, much of that behavior would result in immediate disciplinary action or legal consequences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The shift didn’t happen overnight, but it happened once language caught up to experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once people had words for harassment and coercion, they could finally name what felt wrong. And once something is named, it becomes much harder to ignore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Psychologically, this matters because &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/s-t-8-signs-youre-intelligent-enough-to-see-problems-everywhere-but-not-emotionally-equipped-to-enjoy-anything/"&gt;naming a problem&lt;/a&gt; is often the first step toward dismantling it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6) Children roaming freely without supervision&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many people feel nostalgic about how free childhood once was. In the 60s and 70s, kids often left the house in the morning and came back at dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They played far from home, rode public transportation alone, and sometimes hitchhiked. Parents trusted that things would work out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, that level of freedom would likely trigger concern or even legal consequences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parents can now be accused of negligence for situations that were once routine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our perception of risk has shifted dramatically. We are far more aware of worst-case scenarios, and that awareness shapes how we parent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s an ongoing debate about whether we’ve &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/dna-8-quiet-behaviors-that-suggest-you-dont-trust-easily-no-matter-what-you-say/"&gt;become too cautious&lt;/a&gt;. But regardless of where you land, the contrast between eras is undeniable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It shows how fear and safety evolve alongside information, media, and cultural narratives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7) Advertising that openly manipulated or lied&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Advertising in the 60s and 70s played fast and loose with the truth. Cigarettes were marketed as healthy, and sugary foods were framed as essential to a balanced diet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gender stereotypes were blatant, and &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/nat-8-signs-someone-is-emotionally-manipulative-but-doesnt-realize-it-according-to-psychology/"&gt;emotional manipulation&lt;/a&gt; was unapologetic. Regulations were limited, and accountability was rare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, advertising laws are stricter, and consumers are more skeptical. Companies are still persuasive, but outright false claims are more likely to be challenged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What really changed was media literacy. People slowly learned how persuasion works and how easily emotions can be exploited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you understand framing and repetition, you don’t consume messages the same way. That awareness has forced brands to evolve, even if reluctantly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking back at the 60s and 70s isn’t about shaming the past. It’s about understanding how flexible our sense of normal really is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What feels obvious today once required decades of debate, research, and resistance. And what feels acceptable now may one day be questioned just as intensely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The real takeaway is simple. Staying curious and willing to reexamine our assumptions is one of the most practical skills we can develop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-1119277622"&gt;&lt;p&gt;				 &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong data-start="380" data-end="431"&gt;VegOut Magazine’s November Edition Is Out!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;In our latest Magazine “&lt;em&gt;Curiosity, Compassion &amp;amp; the Future of Living&lt;/em&gt;” you’ll get FREE access to:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;– 5 in-depth articles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;– Insights across Lifestyle, Wellness, Sustainability &amp;amp; Beauty&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;– Our Editor’s Monthly Picks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;– 4 exclusive Vegan Recipes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/magazine-november-2025/"&gt;&lt;button class="buttonStyle buttonStyleAlternate"&gt;Learn more&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="g-ytsubscribe" data-channelid="UCdGKHK52616Dpj-FpFjeNSg" data-layout="full" data-count="hidden"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 			&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:04:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxOOVp4cks0SVlpZGNXVWtpamxacm15YnVoTlhvUlM2eW9nZ2JXWXZSMlRsOV9BaGF1YnEzX2kyZzlpWkdQUHdXcVVEWkppdDc2Mm9wZ3VNM3V0bkZMUWp3Q1BCRVRDZVFjYUFQNlpNSERHNFU5SDVTWS1RVVdrMTJ5NkQyZmQ0aVlpdmt2Tl9FUTdYMUEwV2Z4RGxuX05VcWUzYVZFRl9fYWYxcGJmYUZMSEN5TXJGZWNPOWc</guid></item><item><title>血色素沉着症：成千上万的北爱尔兰人正在接受凯尔特诅咒检测- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cx2wgl01wxgo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;'I'd never heard of Celtic curse until I was diagnosed'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 gXJgDY"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 gqeTMs"&gt;Niall McCracken&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 bIfajQ"&gt;Mid Ulster reporter, BBC News NI &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Haemochromatosis UK Finbar Polin is staring intently at the camera. It is a close up of his face against a black background. He has short grey hair and blue eyes." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Haemochromatosis UK&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Finbar Polin was diagnosed with haemochromatosis in 2020&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Thousands of people in parts of Northern Ireland are being offered free testing for a disorder commonly known as the Celtic Curse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Haemochromatosis is the most common genetic disorder in Northern Ireland and is mostly found in people of Irish and Scots ancestry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The disorder means a person is more at risk of absorbing too much iron and it can start to damage other parts of their body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Symptoms can range from chronic fatigue, joint pain, memory issues, abdominal pain and skin conditions. If left untreated it can lead to serious long-term health complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Neil Irwin works for Haemochromatosis UK and was diagnosed with the condition seven years ago&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;BBC News NI previously reported on &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-northern-ireland-64813957" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;concerns that not enough people were being tested for it in Northern Ireland because of the cost&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The Department of Health's current policy is to screen for genetic haemochromatosis when a patient shows symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But a charity has said it is hoping to capture more information on areas of Northern Ireland where people may be undiagnosed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Haemochromatosis UK will offer up to 23,500 households free genetic screening in Irvinestown, Portadown, Ballymena and Magherafelt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Neil Irwin works for Haemochromatosis UK and was diagnosed with the condition seven years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He says early diagnosis is key to allow people access to effective treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt; "In recent years we have had anecdotal evidence from areas like Mid Ulster where people have been contacting us saying their area seems to have high rates of haemochromatosis," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"But there is a lack of official data, so we're looking to fill in some of those blank spots in Northern Ireland that have never screened before, to paint a more detailed picture of the prevalence of the condition."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;'I knew something was wrong'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Collette McKnight is a mother of three who lives in rural County Down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She was diagnosed with haemochromatosis in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I would have had severe fatigue and pains, but I just would have put it down to being busy with the children and things like that, "he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"But then I started to develop heart palpitations and I knew something else was wrong."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Collette McKnight was diagnosed with haemochromatosis in 2019&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She added: "When the tests came back confirming haemochromatosis, I hadn't a clue what it was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Everyday is different. Some days it's joint pain, other days it's breathing problems, but it's always dealing with the severe fatigue and that can be very difficult."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She is now treated with therapeutic blood removal, which helps lower iron levels and ease symptoms caused by the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;What is the Celtic curse?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The gene mutation that causes most cases of hereditary haemochromatosis is believed to have originated in the Celtic population of Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;DNA analysis of the genomes of a Bronze Age farmer on Rathlin Island off the coast of County Antrim showed that it was already established by that period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Earlier still, the remains of a Neolithic woman found at Ballynahatty near Belfast show that she carried a different variant &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-35179269" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;also associated with an increased risk of the disorder.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Daniel Bradley, Trinity College Dublin A yellowish skull with the bottom jaw missing. It has A64 written on the forehead. There is a brown tag which says Ballynahatty and Fragile. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Daniel Bradley, Trinity College Dublin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Excavated near Belfast in 1855, the Ballynahatty woman lay in a Neolithic tomb chamber for 5,000 years&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;As part of the latest screening campaign, Haemochromatosis UK is bringing a touring photographic exhibition to Northern Ireland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The exhibition, We are Overloaded, opens to the public at the Millennium Court in Portadown on 19 January.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It features a photographs of people living with haemochromatosis by &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-northern-ireland-68735037" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Pulitzer Prize-winning photojournalist Cathal McNaughton&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Finbar Polin, from Gilford, is featured in the exhibition and was diagnosed with haemochromatosis during the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="BBC News Three separate shots of Finbar Polin. Two are headshots - he has grey hair and looking intently at the camera. The other is a black and white photo of him sitting on a chair with a camera and light in the foreground, and a white screen behind him." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;BBC News&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Finbar Polin is from Craigavon and is featured in the exhibition&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Speaking to BBC News NI, he said: "I'd never heard of the Celtic curse until I was diagnosed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's scary initially because it affects you mentally; you don't know where you are going with it, but being part of the charity and meeting other people with it has really helped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"That's where I think the exhibition is really powerful, each picture is a person with a story."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;On the issue of screening, the Department of Health said it was guided by advice from UK National Screening Committee (UK NSC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Among its recommendations on haemochromatosis, UK NSC stated that there was "limited evidence on whether treatment is more effective in individuals without symptoms, compared with those who have symptoms".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But Haemochromatosis UK believe it is important to create an accurate picture as possible of the number of people living with the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;The We are Overloaded exhibition features the photos and stories of people living with haemochromatosis&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Previous research by the charity suggests that as many as one in 10 people are at risk in Northern Ireland of genetic haemochromatosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The charity previously ran a campaign to fund and offer thousands of households in Belfast, Carrickfergus and Londonderry with free self-test kits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A Haemochromatosis UK genetic testing kit usually costs about £130.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The latest kits being rolled out by Haemochromatosis UK were purchased with donations and funding received by the charity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Haemochromatosis UK will offer up to 23,500 households free genetic screening&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Businessman James Hagan, founder of Hagan Homes, is one of the donors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He said: "Someone very close to me was recently diagnosed with genetic haemochromatosis — despite having no symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Their experience highlights exactly why this campaign is so important. Most people affected have no warning signs, yet the potential consequences can be extremely serious if the condition goes undetected."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Haemochromatosis UK has said that in the coming weeks and months , households in the relevant postcodes will receive information about genetic haemochromatosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In the package they will be offered a free genetic test, alongside access to counselling to help them understand their results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:02:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5UVjV1QlYzd1ZuSmVBTkJjV1VtZHVCemgzSjZEb0VyTXMzUWpQdl9Pa3RmellJV2djUnlaaWtFLVFmclZRSzNlMlFCa3dvUjR1WE56S1g4OEp6d9IBX0FVX3lxTE56aGk0RVJoalZrS2xUZlBQanpDYmFOVWxIWVhkdUV2dFozQXZzZ25TTUpMcmNWZE5OWFJDa1ZqYW8xdkl4TGNXcG5aVXBVVVpVRXpHdTZicURlQUdRS2Fv</guid></item><item><title>萨米特县报告首例小学生麻疹病例- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51431382/summit-county-reports-its-first-case-of-measles-in-elementary-school-student</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;COALVILLE — Summit County confirmed its first case of measles Saturday in a South Summit School District student.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The student attended school or school activities while infectious at South Summit Elementary School, the Summit County Health Department said in a statement, adding that exposures may have occurred during school hours on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The health department is working closely with the school district to provide notification and guidance to parents, students and faculty. Health officials, meanwhile, are taking immediate action to investigate and limit further spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our staff and school district partners have taken proactive measures for months to plan and prepare for our first measles case," Summit County Health Director Dr. Phil Bondurant said. "We encourage residents and their family members who are not already vaccinated against measles to consider the MMR vaccine, which is the most effective way to protect against measles."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Summit County health officials are encouraging those who are experiencing symptoms of measles to contact their health care provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Utah Department of Health and Human Services' &lt;a href="https://files.epi.utah.gov/Utah%20measles%20dashboard.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;dashboard&lt;/a&gt; said the measles case count statewide is now at 176 as of Saturday, after the count stood at 156 &lt;a href="https://www.ksl.com/article/51426212/utah-measles-cases-rise-to-156-amid-ongoing-national-outbreak" rel="follow" target="_blank"&gt;on New Year's Day&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 23:17:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxOVjVpcWtUZHl3WGJmbmExX3o3TW1acHJNcFpCeHNqUHhDeHlGN3JZbnNuODZVYjVYVlZ4cUg0c0IxMThNeUNlLTQ4R0xXdGRKUXlFU2JjUl9acDE5MmRjQTJPYmhZcEJTaVhYTEJVek40Q2tOQmh0VXFxamZTeDNFN3BJa2o0MEt2Y0NlbWpWVDB3eExPM3RnWXpydW92cWRSaUtHSjhzSnJJZ19QZmxLQ3ZCUQ</guid></item><item><title>南峰学区的学生麻疹检测呈阳性- KUTV</title><link>https://kutv.com/news/local/student-in-south-summit-school-district-tests-positive-for-measles</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h2 class="StoryPage_headline__AP3j8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Student in South Summit School District tests positive for measles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="ByLineContainer_storyBylineContainer__0JNT7" id="js-Story-Byline-0"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="ByLine_storyByLineText__cze7l"&gt;by Jonathan May, KUTV &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="ByLineContainer_storyDatelineText__yS9e8"&gt;Sat, January 10, 2026 at 3:33 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="ByLineContainer_storyDatelineText__yS9e8"&gt;&lt;span class="ByLineContainer_updatedText__0D6FY"&gt;Updated &lt;/span&gt;Sat, January 10, 2026 at 4:02 PM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="UserWayButton_userWayButton__h8S9a ByLineContainer_userWayButton___vCFL"&gt;&lt;img alt="UserWay icon for accessibility widget" src="/resources/defaults/news_3.0/icons/accessibility/userway-transparent.svg"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KUTV</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:34:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxONmJqajZEQjdxaERadFRTME1ycldqUTlTMk4xMUpjV1B5OTloTnpUUlJRX0FBMHB4elVFU3VuNkQ3SWRNbHc4US1TdE9mR0dPTUwwVV9Bc18zbnZuUXFEaFh2eVlsekh5U0NTdUlWeC01MWtxZlRGUm1wVnpwSm1nZ2s3dWRhUzNvalpCUXpQTlYtTFM2RTV4cGJR</guid></item><item><title>根据心理学，在这8项日常任务中挣扎的人通常比95%的人更聪明- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/r-t-people-who-struggle-with-these-8-everyday-tasks-are-often-more-intelligent-than-95-of-people-according-to-psychology/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;There’s a quiet shame that comes with struggling at things everyone else seems to do without thinking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You miss deadlines, forget small details, or feel oddly out of place in situations that look simple on the surface.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve felt that shame before, especially in my twenties when I was working in luxury food and beverage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The environment demanded polish, speed, and social ease, and yet some of the sharpest minds I met were the ones quietly wrestling with basic, everyday stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Psychology backs this up in a way that feels almost comforting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intelligence doesn’t always show up as efficiency, smoothness, or consistency, and in many cases it shows up as friction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever wondered why your brain seems to trip over things others breeze through, this list might explain more than you expect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1) Making small talk&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/s-if-small-talk-makes-you-want-to-scream-you-probably-have-these-7-rare-personality-traits/"&gt;Small talk&lt;/a&gt; is one of those social skills that’s treated like a basic requirement for adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you struggle with it, people assume you’re awkward, unfriendly, or lacking confidence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But for highly intelligent people, the issue usually isn’t social fear. It’s boredom mixed with a hunger for substance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research suggests that people with higher &lt;a href="https://www.happyneuronpro.com/en/info/what-are-cognitive-abilities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;cognitive ability&lt;/a&gt; tend to seek meaning, patterns, and depth in conversation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When an interaction offers none of that, their brains disengage almost immediately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve sat through countless dinners where the conversation revolved around weather, surface-level work complaints, or recycled anecdotes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My mind would drift not because I disliked the people, but because my brain was itching for something more nourishing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For some minds, small talk feels like empty calories. It fills time but leaves no mental satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2) Sticking to rigid routines&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a popular idea that discipline looks like doing the same thing at the same time every day. Wake up early, follow a strict schedule, repeat forever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highly intelligent people often struggle with this kind of rigidity. Their minds crave novelty, variation, and flexibility more than repetition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Psychological studies have linked higher intelligence with &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2937090/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;openness&lt;/a&gt; to experience and sensitivity to stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That combination makes rigid routines feel mentally suffocating over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve tried hyper-optimized &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/d-bt-8-morning-routines-that-give-you-an-unfair-advantage-in-life/"&gt;morning routines&lt;/a&gt; more times than I care to admit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They work for a short burst, then my brain starts rebelling and asking why everything has to happen in the same order every day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t mean you lack discipline. It often means your mind is wired to adapt rather than repeat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3) Finishing simple tasks quickly&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know the task should take five minutes. Somehow, it takes thirty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highly intelligent people &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/k-t-you-can-tell-someone-was-raised-by-emotionally-distant-parents-if-they-do-these-8-things-in-relationships/"&gt;tend to overanalyze&lt;/a&gt; even the smallest decisions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their brains naturally explore multiple possibilities, outcomes, and implications before settling on action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Psychologists sometimes call this &lt;a href="https://www.goodrx.com/health-topic/mental-health/how-can-i-stop-overthinking-everything?srsltid=AfmBOoq8lTC3kABWsWxXDcSxluyiK_NG9O-viqLMtDd_RBaP3Qs0jmoR" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;overthinking&lt;/a&gt;, but that label misses the point. It’s not anxiety driving the process, it’s depth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve caught myself spending way too long choosing what to order at a restaurant, thinking through flavor combinations, portion sizes, and regret minimization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the server is just trying to move the table along.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When your brain is built for complexity, simplicity doesn’t come naturally. Even basic tasks get upgraded into mini thought experiments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4) Letting go of mistakes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-90934" src="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking-.png" alt="" srcset="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking-.png 1600w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--300x158.png 300w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--1024x538.png 1024w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--768x403.png 768w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--1536x806.png 1536w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--1200x630.png 1200w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--857x450.png 857w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--900x473.png 900w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--420x221.png 420w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--840x441.png 840w" sizes="(max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some people mess up and move on instantly. Others replay the moment in their head for days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highly intelligent people are far more likely to struggle with this. Their brains &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/z-lc-8-signs-youre-not-a-perfectionist-youre-just-terrified-of-being-seen-failing/"&gt;treat mistakes as data&lt;/a&gt; that needs to be analyzed and integrated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From a psychological standpoint, this makes sense. Intelligence is closely tied to learning, and learning depends on noticing errors and adjusting behavior.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In high-pressure kitchens, mistakes are expensive and visible. You either reflect on them deeply or repeat them and fall behind fast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The challenge is that the same mental habit that helps you grow can also trap you in self-criticism if you don’t consciously let the lesson end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5) Falling asleep easily&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your mind lights up the moment your head hits the pillow, you’re not alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highly intelligent people often struggle to fall asleep because their brains don’t naturally slow down on command.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/psychology/articles/10.3389/fpsyg.2025.1476840/full" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Studies&lt;/a&gt; have linked higher cognitive engagement with increased nighttime mental activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When external stimulation disappears, internal processing ramps up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve had nights where a single idea snowballed into a full mental outline for an article, a career plan, or a half-baked business concept.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Great for creativity, terrible for rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn’t a failure of discipline or routine. It’s a brain that’s &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/gen-if-you-think-in-these-8-complex-ways-your-mind-operates-differently-than-95-of-people/"&gt;wired to think deeply&lt;/a&gt; whenever it has space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6) Remembering mundane details&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highly intelligent people often have &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/s-t-10-childhood-details-only-people-with-exceptional-memory-still-remember/"&gt;excellent memory&lt;/a&gt; for concepts, patterns, and ideas. Strangely, they tend to struggle with basic, everyday details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Psychology suggests this comes down to &lt;a href="https://www.verywellmind.com/what-is-selective-attention-2795022" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;selective attention&lt;/a&gt;. The brain prioritizes information it deems meaningful and filters out the rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ask me about a book I read years ago and I can recall its core argument with ease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ask me where I put my keys an hour ago and I’ll need to retrace my steps like a detective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t mean your memory is bad. It means it’s optimized for meaning, not logistics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7) Staying present in boring environments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Long meetings, repetitive lectures, or conversations that go nowhere can feel physically uncomfortable for highly intelligent people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their minds disengage quickly when stimulation drops below a certain threshold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research links intelligence with a tendency toward &lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/374102703_Intentional_mind_wandering_is_objectively_linked_to_low_effort_and_tasks_with_high_predictability" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;mental wandering&lt;/a&gt; in low-engagement environments. The brain seeks complexity when none is provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve mentally planned meals, workouts, articles, and entire trips while sitting in painfully dull settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the outside, it might look like disinterest, but internally the brain is just staying busy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This trait can be a liability in structured environments. It can also be a powerful source of creativity if you learn how to channel it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;8) Finally, turning off self-criticism&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, one of the most overlooked struggles of highly intelligent people is their relationship with themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intelligence brings awareness, and awareness often brings harsh self-evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You notice gaps others miss. You see inefficiencies, flaws, and missed opportunities with uncomfortable clarity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Psychology has long noted the connection between intelligence and heightened &lt;a href="https://paradigmpersonality.com/resources/self-monitoring-psychology-101/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;self-monitoring&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The same mind that analyzes the world with precision turns inward with equal force.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve met incredibly capable people who &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/n-t-8-behaviors-of-people-who-have-lost-their-self-worth-without-realizing-it/"&gt;downplay their achievements&lt;/a&gt; while obsessing over minor missteps. Externally impressive, internally relentless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learning to soften that internal voice isn’t about lowering standards. It’s about recognizing when analysis has stopped being useful and started becoming noise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Struggling with everyday tasks doesn’t automatically mean you’re failing at life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In many cases, it means your brain is optimized for depth, complexity, and meaning in a world that rewards speed and surface-level competence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you understand this, the shame starts to dissolve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You stop trying to force yourself into systems that don’t fit and start building ones that actually support how your mind works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intelligence isn’t always visible. Sometimes it shows up quietly, in the friction between a deep mind and a shallow world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you recognized yourself in this list, you’re not broken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’re just wired differently, and that difference can become a strength once you learn how to work with it instead of against it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-4240840399"&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong data-start="380" data-end="431"&gt;If You Were a Healing Herb, Which Would You Be?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each herb holds a unique kind of magic — soothing, awakening, grounding, or clarifying.&lt;br data-start="521" data-end="524"&gt;This 9-question quiz reveals the healing plant that mirrors your energy right now and what it says about your natural rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;✨ Instant results. Deeply insightful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="g-ytsubscribe" data-channelid="UCdGKHK52616Dpj-FpFjeNSg" data-layout="full" data-count="hidden"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:04:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6AFBVV95cUxQcUJSdzFRN1JoT3cxVGNKeUNIbVFqRlRkWFVXN1lmakM2R3lsbmRMc1Fvd3ExS1htNHlFZ09weGxyQ2Fic1ROT1c3MEsxYS02YVZ0aXNBNWFWRTlmWTVQSUlCV0hUNVBvTmZIQ1k3bjMtdnNJeUEzWm1acFpHZE1WanlsQVI5bk5vS1JqZ1JnRVMxdEJtS3JiX2xjOFJyaDNrdGd4ZFdVX1ozRi0xaEgyczVVcktlZ1dRbXV6UDVZMlh3UERuYmFpT3UtSkwwbmFQay1EVi0yY0tnUmFoX2VCaWtocGg1VHUx</guid></item><item><title>俄勒冈州警告林恩县两家医院可能有麻疹暴露- OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2026/01/oregon-warns-of-possible-measles-exposure-at-two-linn-county-hospitals.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3S2377OGL5ESND5FFG2AT6R7GQ"&gt;People who visited two hospitals in Linn County during specific times this week may have been exposed to &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/06/oregon-confirms-first-measles-case-of-2025-linked-to-international-travel.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/06/oregon-confirms-first-measles-case-of-2025-linked-to-international-travel.html"&gt;measles&lt;/a&gt;, a highly &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2019/10/measles-makes-your-body-forget-how-to-fight-other-diseases.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2019/10/measles-makes-your-body-forget-how-to-fight-other-diseases.html"&gt;infectious virus&lt;/a&gt; that spreads through the air and in rare cases can be fatal, Oregon officials said Saturday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IFOELF33PZDLHIFAKSL6HNJU3Q"&gt;The two people with Oregon’s first confirmed measles cases in 2026 developed &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2019/10/measles-or-flu-know-the-symptoms.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2019/10/measles-or-flu-know-the-symptoms.html"&gt;symptoms&lt;/a&gt; — a rash, fever, cough and runny nose — on Jan. 5. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4S2PAWGN75DPJMRJKMOADR7BOE"&gt;The measles virus can linger for up to two hours after an infected person leaves an area. The Oregon Health Authority said that people who visited one of two hospitals Jan. 6 or Jan. 7 could have been exposed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7FQZDSJG6NBG5KNCHVVLE6Z4K4"&gt;People could have been exposed to measles if they were at:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="article__unordered-list"&gt;&lt;li id="CLGYDNMOXVA7TML446UUQPLU6Y"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Lebanon Community Hospital Emergency Department between 8:53 p.m. on Jan. 6 and 7 a.m. on Jan. 7&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="WITNM2ETFFD5VAR4A33NT4YCA4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Albany General Hospital Emergency Department between 4:59 a.m. and 8:15 a.m. Jan. 7&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3HQI4QB5SVB7NAQKQA6V4RZQJM"&gt;Anyone who was at either of those hospitals during those times should immediately tell their doctor they may have been exposed to the measles virus, the health authority warned. Their doctor will then be able to determine whether they are immune to the virus based on their vaccination record and other factors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:SLTSWQF3NZCUTNLS2YLKIUU4CA" data-fusion-component="SLTSWQF3NZCUTNLS2YLKIUU4CA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:SLTSWQF3NZCUTNLS2YLKIUU4CA" data-fusion-component="SLTSWQF3NZCUTNLS2YLKIUU4CA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KSPDMSID3BGUBHIHUEUE4DIGZE"&gt;Measles symptoms usually appear seven to 21 days after exposure and include fever, cough, runny nose and red eyes, followed by a rash that starts on the face and spreads to the rest of the body, the health authority said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6CNW7SEOZ5C77N5XPE5X7AV5LI"&gt;Most people infected with measles survive without complications. But the disease is nonetheless dangerous and can cause brain swelling and even death. The disease is particularly dangerous for infants and people with weakened immune symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GOUB3OJ5QRDANMRKGUXJPUUKBE"&gt;Measles &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/04/there-are-800-measles-cases-in-the-us-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-outbreaks.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/04/there-are-800-measles-cases-in-the-us-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-outbreaks.html"&gt;has been on the rise nationally&lt;/a&gt;, with the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention recording the &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/07/measles-cases-in-the-us-reach-highest-levels-in-33-years-cdc-reports.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/07/measles-cases-in-the-us-reach-highest-levels-in-33-years-cdc-reports.html"&gt;worst year for measles spread&lt;/a&gt; in more than three decades just halfway through 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ABTYCRID2VHO5IQAXS2QOPA5YM"&gt;The agency reported 2,144 confirmed cases nationwide by the end of the year, including three that were fatal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GOSPBTJE7FAKTJ6Q7EJOLFH3EQ"&gt;Oregon had &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/06/oregon-confirms-first-measles-case-of-2025-linked-to-international-travel.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/06/oregon-confirms-first-measles-case-of-2025-linked-to-international-travel.html"&gt;just one confirmed measles case&lt;/a&gt; last year, according to CDC data. But the state reported 31 confirmed infections in 2024, according to CDC data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BKDS7OP3XBBR5IJ5GVYB5GU23M"&gt;The measles vaccine is highly effective, with two doses of the measles-mumps-rubella vaccine preventing 97% of infections, according to the Oregon Health Authority. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MEJDXXK2WBCWNCJZ3WIA6W6DVY"&gt;Distrust in government and misinformation erroneously linking vaccines to autism have contributed to declining vaccination rates and a concomitant increase in infections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZEU7Y65MYNHTTDG3FGTLXW7OGA"&gt;The health authority continued to urge Oregonians to get themselves and their children vaccinated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JFQALZUMYFGSBAOMBKZE4YU5J4"&gt;“Measles is here in Oregon and rates are increasing nationally,” said Dr. Howard Chiou, OHA’s medical director for communicable diseases and immunizations. “We encourage everyone to make sure they’re protected by talking with their providers about being up to date on vaccinations.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:22:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxNM1dBdkhEUG9fZXNaTzl4Zl9wVmFQeFptTDlreFFGM2V3bVFiVTE3bVJIdllWWS1adWZLem1XenFqVG03VmtxMVota0Iyc0JJZ0JhanVPR0NUVDUwc1k3b1FGSUNFbU9VVUhELTYyV0RUcGdZblozT0V2eDNWbjFFQk1XZ25uRU8tUUJ1dWhpYzN0MFF3QS1nMHJPOUJHdlB1aU9RelVzMWdnaHFWeElxSlZjSFkxQk1S0gHMAUFVX3lxTE50NVJlVERWc0M2XzlVY211WW42VDhCbWtXd1RfMG5NU1NmN1BqMnlpN2NBWGN3X05raDlqVnE5T1FJbWVLTE13QWJ2NTB1MDZseTZjdGVveW5iSVdqeE5ULUt5R2dJRFBfeFZzbGI3ZEw2djF0ZUZ6dlBuLWtOMVBDZTNKVFpFb2xzY3BKTDFENHcxRkpCV1poamR1MGQ3T2xqWUJDSDRsSFRnWEl6NVRLSXlUaHlxN0RIbzlMQzJ1Y2N6VzBZMU56dmxkZw</guid></item><item><title>流感季节流泪穿越弗吉尼亚州北部- InsideNoVa.com</title><link>https://www.insidenova.com/news/fairfax/nasty-flu-season-tears-through-northern-virginia/article_b885e69b-eb59-424e-b1a5-b119d986e754.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;It’s that time of year again, but this time it’s particularly bad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Respiratory illnesses, especially influenza, are tearing through Northern Virginia, accounting for 22% of ER visits in the week ending Jan. 3, &lt;a href="https://www.vdh.virginia.gov/epidemiology/respiratory-diseases-in-virginia/data/"&gt;according to the Virginia Department of Health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;A particularly nasty strand of influenza A, subclade k, is driving this flu season, which peaks from December to February. The mutated strand emerged after the 2025 flu vaccine was developed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;The U.S. Centers for Disease Control &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-52.html"&gt;estimates&lt;/a&gt; there have been at least 11 million cases of flu this season nationwide. The CDC also estimates 120,000 hospitalizations and 5,000 deaths. The spread is rated at high or very high in 48 states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Dr. Meredith Porter, medical director for Inova-GoHealth Urgent Care in Northern Virginia, said there are “very high acute respiratory illness levels” across the region. The urgent care system is a joint venture between Inova and GoHealth and operates 23 centers across the region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="opscoad-nvm_instory_ad" data-unit="/22545743209/insidenova/news/fairfax/instory" data-targeting='{"pos":"nvm_instory"}'&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;The urgent care system is increasing support staff and extending virtual visit hours to midnight to meet demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;“We’re trying our best to avoid people going to the emergency room,” Porter told InsideNoVa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;There might be a light at the end of the tunnel, Porter said. Statewide, the number of respiratory-related cases at ERs dropped from the week ending Dec. 27 to the week ending Jan. 3.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;This flu season started picking up after school was out and people started traveling for the holidays, Porter said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="opscoad-nvm_instory_ad" data-unit="/22545743209/insidenova/news/fairfax/instory" data-targeting='{"pos":"nvm_instory"}'&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;“When you are around a lot of people, you may not yet know that you’re starting to get sick,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Porter said the typical flu symptoms start, and “you almost feel like you’ve been hit by a bus.” That includes body aches, fever, cough and fatigue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Unless you’re having difficulty breathing, chest pain, dehydration or changes to your lucidity, Porter recommended going to a primary care or urgent care first. Those providers can provide early testing and antiviral treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;If you’ve got the flu, rest as much as possible and stay hydrated. If you’ve got to go out into the world, Porter recommended wearing a mask and staying as far from others as possible. The first three days after the onset of symptoms are when people are the most contagious, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="opscoad-nvm_instory_ad" data-unit="/22545743209/insidenova/news/fairfax/instory" data-targeting='{"pos":"nvm_instory"}'&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;For everyone else, Porter recommended using hand sanitizer, washing your hands frequently, wipe down things like grocery store carts and keep your distance from people who look symptomatic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;“If you’re standing in that check out line,” she said, “give yourself a bit of space.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="clearfix"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>InsideNoVa.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:51:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1AFBVV95cUxOQlpGUkdDdHNaREdWTUJxLXd6MlRsZjYyMS1ySmJkMUp3WjRrSGRwV0RZYTVnRktvWWdDY0ItQ3Ntb25PdksxUmJkX3JyaHJ6cW5sY0o2endnN1pZN1E0YlJPdnFNODVzZVdRVVAyTUZxSEVHZ2Z2ZkV5YXo4Y1FrSjVpTU5CR0tvVTYwWUxyc3BHbzlsaWtWVDh4VmY5QUN2bzFiSk5OU1R4SFVvRFpOcm9GUm5objFlSmpEQ2stQzdwU3QwQldmdWdFS3hJUlpkNjdERg</guid></item><item><title>什么是低密度脂蛋白胆固醇以及如何降低它？ - GQ</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/what-is-ldl-cholesterol-and-how-do-you-lower-it-1</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chances are, your cholesterol isn’t something you think too much about. When it comes to your health, your thoughts may already be preoccupied with figuring out &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/heres-how-to-get-enough-protein-a-day-1"&gt;more ways to get protein&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/how-to-sleep-better-according-to-sleep-experts-1"&gt;how to get more sleep&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/cardio-before-or-after-weight-lifting-1"&gt;whether you should do cardio before or after lifting weights&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not to mention, according to &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamacardiology/fullarticle/2811350"&gt;a 2023 study published in &lt;em&gt;JAMA Cardiology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, more than 40% of U.S. adults with high LDL cholesterol didn’t know they had it. This means that there are a whole lot of people out there who are at &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK470561"&gt;an increased risk&lt;/a&gt; of having a heart attack, stroke, or getting heart disease, and they don’t even know it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is that your cholesterol levels are something you can control. We asked cardiologists about how to do exactly that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is LDL cholesterol?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/cholesterol-explained"&gt;Cholesterol&lt;/a&gt; is typically referenced generally and almost always negatively, but it’s actually a bit more nuanced. &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.abbott.com/corpnewsroom/utilities/our-experts/ethan-korngold.html" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.abbott.com/corpnewsroom/utilities/our-experts/ethan-korngold.html"}' href="https://www.abbott.com/corpnewsroom/utilities/our-experts/ethan-korngold.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Ethan Korngold, MD,&lt;/a&gt; an interventional cardiologist who works with the health company Abbott, explains that cholesterol, which is a waxy fat-like substance found in the body, is essential to build cells and produce vitamins and hormones. “However, too much cholesterol can cause problems because it narrows the arteries, blocking blood flow, which increases the risk of heart disease,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK470561/"&gt;Cholesterol&lt;/a&gt; is transported through the blood by lipoproteins, including two types of lipoproteins: high-density lipoproteins (HDL) and low-density lipoproteins (LDL). HDL (often referred to as “good” cholesterol) transports cholesterol to the liver, where it’s then broken down and excreted. LDL transports cholesterol to cells, and as Dr. Korngold explained, too much of it can lead to plaque buildup in the arteries. That’s why LDL cholesterol is often referred to as “bad” cholesterol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How do you know if you have high LDL cholesterol?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if you’re relatively young and generally in good health, preventing high LDL cholesterol is still important. &lt;a data-offer-url="https://lluh.org/provider/hoff-jason" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://lluh.org/provider/hoff-jason"}' href="https://lluh.org/provider/hoff-jason" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Jason Hoff, MD&lt;/a&gt;, a structural interventional cardiologist and assistant professor at Loma Linda University Health, says that cholesterol plaque buildup is something that can happen over time without you even realizing it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s not something you can feel. It can eventually lead to a heart attack or stroke, and the process often starts decades before symptoms appear, even as early as your 20s and 30s,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-offer-url="https://walkwithadoc.org/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://walkwithadoc.org/"}' href="https://walkwithadoc.org/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Walk with a Doc&lt;/a&gt; CEO and cardiologist &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.ohiohealth.com/find-a-doctor/profile/1962401083/david-a-sabgir-md" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.ohiohealth.com/find-a-doctor/profile/1962401083/david-a-sabgir-md"}' href="https://www.ohiohealth.com/find-a-doctor/profile/1962401083/david-a-sabgir-md" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-aps-asin="1962401083" data-aps-asc-tag="gqdailynl-20"&gt;Dr. David Sabgir, MD&lt;/a&gt;, says being proactive about your heart health is key to staying healthy. “Even if you feel great, cholesterol can climb quietly, especially if you have a family history of heart disease,” says Dr. Sabgir. “High LDL cholesterol builds up over time and raises the risk for heart attack and stroke. The fix is simple. If we know our numbers and stay ahead of them, we can make a huge difference in our health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since you can’t feel LDL cholesterol slowly creeping up, how do you know if yours is too high? All three cardiologists say that it requires a blood test from your doctor and it’s something Dr. Korngold recommends everyone 20 and older have regularly checked. &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/cholesterol/about-cholesterol/what-your-cholesterol-levels-mean"&gt;The American Heart Association says&lt;/a&gt; that optimal LDL cholesterol is at or below 100 mg/dL.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sabgir explains that genetics play a big role in causing high LDL cholesterol. &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2903789/"&gt;Research published in the &lt;em&gt;Journal of Lipid Research&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; estimates that 40 to 60% of high cholesterol is due to genetics. That means you could be working out regularly and hitting your nutrient goals and still have it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Something else that contributes to high LDL cholesterol that’s out of your control is aging. “As you age, your body becomes less efficient at clearing bad cholesterol from the bloodstream, which increases your risk,” Dr. Korngold says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>GQ</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:20:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTFByMFQ2dEV5dDItNWNPd191Uy16RE9raW1LYmJxcTRNUnh6WXBNVmFGZWJaemljd3JBb1pDT0ZZZ3V1Ym5Ia0Q1em1BZmFISGRjamJRR1FwMWFTNUc2eFZMU0gyNmRQNUxvRW5zTld3b1FyYWVsNVFDS2dDS01GVGs</guid></item><item><title>人类卵子提前“恢复活力” ，可以提高试管婴儿成功率--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2026/jan/09/human-eggs-rejuvenated-in-advance-that-could-boost-ivf-success-rates</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Scientists claim to have “rejuvenated” human eggs for the first time in an advance that they predict could revolutionise &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/ivf" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;IVF&lt;/a&gt; success rates for older women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The groundbreaking research suggests that an age-related defect that causes genetic errors in embryos could be reversed by supplementing eggs with a crucial protein. When eggs donated by fertility patients were given microinjections of the protein, they were almost half as likely to show the defect compared with untreated eggs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If confirmed in more extensive trials, the approach has the potential to improve egg quality, which is the primary cause of IVF failure and miscarriage in older women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Overall we can nearly halve the number of eggs with [abnormal] chromosomes. That’s a very prominent improvement,” said Prof Melina Schuh, a director at the Max Planck Institute for Multidisciplinary Sciences in Göttingen and a co-founder of Ovo Labs, which is aiming to commercialise the technique.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Most women in their early 40s do have eggs, but nearly all of the eggs have incorrect chromosome numbers,” added Schuh, whose lab has been investigating egg biology for the past two decades. “This was the motivation for wanting to address this problem.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The findings will be presented at the &lt;a href="https://www.fertilityconference.org/event/1ee53df6-56c5-4634-a9d6-30bbe6c9deec/home" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;British Fertility Conference in Edinburgh&lt;/a&gt; on Friday and have been published as a &lt;a href="https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.64898/2026.01.08.698387v1" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;preprint paper on the Biorxiv website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The decline in egg quality is the main reason IVF success rates drop steeply with female age and is why the risk of chromosome disorders such as Down’s syndrome increases with maternal age. For patients under 35, the average birthrate for each embryo transferred in IVF treatment was 35%, compared with just 5% for women aged 43-44, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.hfea.gov.uk/about-us/publications/research-and-data/fertility-treatment-2023-trends-and-figures/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;most recent UK figures&lt;/a&gt;. The average age of fertility patients starting treatment for the first time in the UK is now over 35.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Agata Zielinska, a co-founder and co-CEO of Ovo Labs, said: “Currently, when it comes to female factor infertility, the only solution that’s available to most patients is trying IVF multiple times so that, cumulatively, your likelihood of success increases. What we envision is that many more women would be able to conceive within a single IVF cycle.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The latest approach targets a vulnerability in eggs linked to a process called meiosis, in which sex cells (eggs or sperm) jettison half their genetic material so they can join together to make an embryo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In eggs, this requires 23 pairs of X-shaped chromosomes to align along a single axis in the cell. On fertilisation, the cell divides causing the chromosome pairs to be – ideally – neatly snapped down their centres to create a cell with precisely 23 single chromosomes from the mother, the rest being delivered by the sperm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;However, in older eggs the chromosome pairs tend to loosen at their midpoint, becoming slightly unstuck or detaching entirely before fertilisation. In this scenario, the X-shaped structures fail to line up properly and move around chaotically in the cell, so when the cell divides they are not snapped symmetrically. This results in an embryo with too many or too few chromosomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Schuh and colleagues previously found that a protein, Shugoshin 1, which appears to act as a glue for the chromosome pairs, declines with age. In the latest experiments in mouse and human eggs, they found that microinjections of Shugoshin 1 appeared to reverse the problem of chromosome pairs separating prematurely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Using eggs donated by patients at the Bourn Hall fertility clinic in Cambridge, they found that the number showing the defect decreased from 53% in control eggs to 29% in treated eggs. When they looked only at eggs from women over 35 years of age, a similar trend was seen (65% compared with 44%), although this result was not statistically significant, which the scientists said was probably due to them only having treated nine eggs in this age range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“What is really beautiful is that we identified a single protein that, with age, goes down, returned it to young levels and it has a big effect,” Schuh said. “We are just restoring the younger situation again with this approach.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The approach would not extend fertility beyond menopause, when the egg reserve runs out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Aside from intra-cytoplasmic sperm injection (ICSI), there are not currently any treatments involving microinjections into eggs, but the team does not anticipate safety issues and are in discussions with regulators about a clinical trial. An important question will be whether the apparent improvements in egg quality results in embryos with fewer genetic errors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Güneş Taylor, of the University of Edinburgh, who was not involved in the research, described the findings as “really promising”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This is really important work because we need approaches that work for older eggs because that’s the point at which most women appear,” she said. “If there’s a one-shot injection that substantially increases the number of eggs with properly organised chromosomes, that gives you a better starting point.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:59:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxQdTA2SEdWU3NfV2NDc21mS1lqUW5OaER4QzY3dUJnRHFjdjVxQXdsbXFpbnZEbHotQ2FpWjAtNlZ0dkxxMjJfQnFFc2dvZWZJYlMzNW9yRTdIR1k3bTBpNUJFZEp4aDAzWDMzZ1BxdUFlM1F4YWVwc2EwWENrTWhZd1ZtV2ZyMWFJUWsxcG1fUnl6NkZmU2hnYW1EeUdIOTh1MklUTklnNUctcl9fQTQ2YXcxTElLYUk</guid></item><item><title>尊敬的Annie ：肿瘤学家告诉我，我是“幸存者” ，但我不觉得自己是“幸存者” - NJ.com</title><link>https://www.nj.com/advice/2026/01/dear-annie-oncologists-tell-me-im-a-survivor-but-i-dont-feel-like-a-survivor.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KWC4BU7SJNCJLKPO75DZQV7ZMY"&gt;DEAR ANNIE: I was diagnosed with breast cancer a few months ago. I’ve been through surgery and radiation treatments. According to the oncologists, I should now consider myself a “survivor.” Since I have scars, I’m taking medication for the next 10 years that has potentially really bad side effects, and the chance of reoccurrence is a definite possibility, I don’t feel like a “survivor.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HOESMRSVMFG5ZC2LOUMOI2RTHA"&gt;I readily admit that I’m depressed. I maintain that this is a perfectly reasonable reaction to something bad that has upended and changed my whole life for the foreseeable future. I’m not suicidal, and although some mornings are hard, I get up every day, shower, brush my hair and teeth and maintain my usual schedule. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FF26BAMBO5DINFIHNXYLVOVGP4"&gt;The worst thing to me about cancer is that I can’t talk to anyone because I’ve gone from an actual person with thoughts and interests to people only wanting to know about the cancer. It’s all anyone asks about. That being the case, I tried to talk to people about how I feel, but the word “depressed” freaks people out more than “cancer.” Now I just say I’m fine or OK to make others feel comfortable, which applies to my doctors as well. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XIYAEA7KDVENPHBBP7UWUY5SJ4"&gt;I don’t need medication, and I tried online and in-person group discussions a few times, and they aren’t for me. I’ve noticed the same thing with people who lose a loved one or have something else bad happen -- they aren’t allowed to be depressed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7YJRC56AINEV7OAKKAREX3R7ZI"&gt;When did it become shameful and something that needs to be fixed when people have a true human emotion to events? Sad things should understandably make us sad -- and maybe depressed? Please note, I’m not talking about people with real diagnosed clinical depression or other mental issues. -- Sad “Survivor”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CGYCUX75JRBLBH6NP33WQV36MU"&gt;DEAR SAD “SURVIVOR”: The word “survivor” may sound triumphant, yes, but it doesn’t cancel out the fear, pain and lifelong change you’ve endured to get here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="733I5T7VYFH3ZOQ4ATJNAC2EDE"&gt;It &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; a victory to be where you are today, and there’s nothing troubling about feeling conflicted. What is troubling is feeling you have to hide it -- especially from your doctors, who need the full picture, whether it’s pretty or not. You’re allowed to say, “I’m getting through it, but it’s still hard,” and you deserve people in your corner who can hear that without panicking or minimizing it, no matter how uncomfortable it may make them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UZORQBPD3NGXNKHFJDA4DSTYZM"&gt;Healing doesn’t happen overnight. Give yourself permission to feel whatever comes and ask honestly for the support you need. A survivor isn’t someone who feels strong all the time; it’s someone who keeps going despite hardship. By that measure, you absolutely are one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RKGCFJAREZCO3HLKQM7G2ETVDY"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Send your questions for Annie Lane to &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:dearannie@creators.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;dearannie@creators.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:ROH5FJTRMZCZTHCFOLA3XBXUHI" data-fusion-component="ROH5FJTRMZCZTHCFOLA3XBXUHI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:ROH5FJTRMZCZTHCFOLA3XBXUHI" data-fusion-component="ROH5FJTRMZCZTHCFOLA3XBXUHI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NJ.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxONjk4OWRXSVZIYXE0NktQSFJ1SFRIZ2tvVnV6SnpYS29qTzVLSFd4bms1YzFHT2VTLVRKWFY4eldGOGlMam1Tb1JPVEc2LVhnYnRNSkUyTXhGdFpxVHFPTmdFajY4c2VWVHhkZnVrdjFERmtkOXhlSDhXenhXUmpqV1o4Qm9MR29EWk9IYTZyWV82bE9PMGQxV3RMNnphSU5ZWEppM05OaEItMGlPV0l0X1VXOG9Sd9IBygFBVV95cUxOMUo3OGVpLXFOcDh3M3d1SUFIVVQwdTdYblp1RVluTU9KbU5ET1k2TGx1VXMxM0pLLUFqMkpQTmlNZlFUcXNpdTV2cXZEVE5zWHYtOVVPdS0wMmpXM0JReGp1RkJyeV9FdG0xNElYZ0RfZGRNYUhLemZZbm44NGpEMTV6Y1R5cDR5UnNNQ2JWZTMzZDdxelF0TEJHNjZwNDBPejJUQjNhVFoySzBJRHg2YnFtZWxvUkJYeHU3dV85b2Z4VE5SbjlkZHdn</guid></item><item><title>弥撒女孩正在从与流感有关的罕见严重疾病中康复- Boston.com</title><link>https://www.boston.com/news/local-news/2026/01/10/mass-girl-recovering-from-rare-serious-illness-linked-to-flu/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="content-well content-well--article" role="main"&gt;
									&lt;p id="presentedby"&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;header class="m-article-header m-article-header--standard"&gt;
												&lt;span id="article-header-primary-term"&gt;
								&lt;a class="a-term a-term--primary" href="https://www.boston.com/tag/local-news/"&gt;
								Local News								&lt;/a&gt;
							&lt;/span&gt;
							
					&lt;h1 class="m-article-header__headline"&gt;Mass. girl recovering from rare, serious illness linked to flu&lt;/h1&gt;
					&lt;h2 class="m-article-header__sub-headline"&gt;Acute necrotizing encephalopathy is a rare but dangerous flu complication that can cause brain damage or even death.&lt;/h2&gt;

					&lt;figure class="a-photo m-article-header__photo "&gt;
	&lt;figcaption class="a-photo__caption"&gt;
	&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;	&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

					
				&lt;/header&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;A Massachusetts mother is sharing her family’s frightening experience with the flu after her 4-year-old daughter developed a rare but potentially deadly complication of the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caitlin Lyons of Ashland &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/boston/news/massachusetts-flu-brain-swelling/"&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; CBS News that her daughter, Althea, came to her in the middle of the night, complaining of dizziness. She was taken to Mass General Hospital, where doctors became concerned after diagnosing her with acute necrotizing encephalopathy (ANE).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though rare, ANE is linked to common viral infections such as the flu and causes rapid brain swelling that can lead to lasting brain damage or death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://www.childrenshospital.org/conditions-treatments/acute-necrotizing-encephalopathy-ane"&gt;Boston Children’s Hospital&lt;/a&gt;, symptoms of ANE can develop quickly and often begin with signs similar to the flu, including fever, congestion, cough, vomiting, or diarrhea. As the condition progresses, symptoms may become severe and life-threatening, with some patients losing consciousness, experiencing seizures, or developing serious breathing problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://answers.childrenshospital.org/ane-flu/"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; from Boston Children’s Neuroimmunology Center found that ANE has a mortality rate of about 27 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I just remember [the doctor] saying, ‘She’s very sick, I’m very concerned,’” Lyons told CBS. “And my only question was, ‘Is she going to live?’ And he said, ‘I hope so.’”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lyons said her daughter’s age may have helped her survive. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Thank God she’s the age that she is — old enough to fight the flu, which she had to get over before the swelling could come down, but young enough to have the time to heal, for her brain to heal, because there was damage done,” she told the news station.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Althea is now recovering, Lyons said, but she chose to share her family’s story to raise awareness about the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I understand they are seeing more cases of this disease, but I think overall it’s still pretty unknown,” Lyons told CBS. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her story comes as flu cases continue to surge across Massachusetts this winter. State health officials have reported 66 flu-related deaths so far this season, &lt;a href="https://www.boston.com/news/health/2026/01/06/4th-massachusetts-child-dies-of-flu/"&gt;including four children&lt;/a&gt; — two of whom were under the age of 2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Boston, confirmed flu cases increased by 126 percent between Dec. 14 and Dec. 27, &lt;a href="https://www.boston.gov/news/two-flu-related-deaths-among-children-under-two-years-old-boston"&gt;according&lt;/a&gt; to city health officials, with hospitalizations nearly tripling. Flu-related emergency room visits also rose by 135 percent during that period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Flu cases are surging in Boston, and we are seeing an uptick in serious cases involving children, including the tragic deaths of two very young children,” said Dr. Bisola Ojikutu, commissioner of public health for the City of Boston. “While the flu is usually mild, it can cause hospitalization and death. Children under the age of 2 are at higher risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ojikutu urged parents to vaccinate children ages six months and older and to seek immediate medical care if a child with flu symptoms shows signs of severe illness, including trouble breathing, decreased urination, persistently high fever, or extreme lethargy.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="o-author-single has-avatar"&gt;

	
	&lt;section class="author-info"&gt;
		&lt;div class="m-author__section"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morgan Rousseau is a freelance writer for Boston.com, where she reports on a variety of local and regional news.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="m-block m-generic-cta
	 m-generic-cta--post-content	 m-generic-cta--dark	 m-generic-cta--homepage	 m-generic-cta--email-signup		 m-generic-cta-block-style--default 
	t-amp__generic-cta"&gt;
		&lt;div class="m-generic-cta__wrap"&gt;
		
		
		&lt;div class="m-generic-cta__content"&gt;
							&lt;h3 class="m-generic-cta__title"&gt;Sign up for the Today newsletter&lt;/h3&gt;
			
							&lt;p class="m-generic-cta__subtitle"&gt;Get everything you need to know to start your day, delivered right to your inbox every morning.&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
		

			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							
			&lt;p class="content-below-article"&gt;
							&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;


			&lt;/article&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Boston.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxPVEZINlVYc2FBSGUxZ01TUDRVSzc0MXFuMTNTVnpSSF9neWU3OVZZUjJqM1ZBQ3pKckNBQTYxaUd2VHUtVV95ZHZFNlNHWlBaS0ZhU1gzbFZZaE1tLU9EYXhmLU9pWFgyS0VBSnNZSzNNVzBiaENENDI5YXJXX3pmTm5EWnZiNng5TVR0cnJZVGREMWYwUEVVZ0diNlZFY0tyRHZrSVBPZXUwNkpjek10Xw</guid></item><item><title>禽流感病毒引发科学家越来越多的担忧--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/10/health/bird-flu-viruses-health.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:20:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE55eEZ1Yy1oaU5ISjJHc3dVTC1rVTVCTVVkSzhsZmM1YUFMUXZEU1R3QjFxYVp2a2Y0bFN2engzZGNaeE9McHRNTTFyMGMwY09tbk8xUEdUU2ptaFlST1ZGQW5ITlM4bWUwWGdEMGFqUzBIUXBTR2hmX2dR</guid></item><item><title>FDA刚刚标记为对60岁以上的任何人都有危险的8种非处方药- savingadvice.com</title><link>https://www.savingadvice.com/articles/2026/01/10/10713695_8-over-the-counter-drugs-the-fda-just-flagged-as-dangerous-for-anyone-over-60.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;title&gt;You are being redirected...&lt;/title&gt;
		&lt;noscript&gt;Javascript is required. Please enable javascript before you are allowed to see this page.&lt;/noscript&gt;
		&lt;/head&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>savingadvice.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:48:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1wFBVV95cUxORUZKUEhoelEwYzFTaVBKN0R6TEJPcEhVSjMtOFI5c3pWVnFSQzJaUGFDYTdRc0pkcmFsWEY1dlI2a1UwaFd3UDVEdXZ2aFRmLUNhQlNJcGhMQzR2SVU2ZnhMd3hfS3dRTTRtcFZPWHZVM25lT2U0Nm5UQ25tQWZRVHRFNHpWV1d0Y2hWTVJuUUg2bFRlbVlwb1lSSjJFUU9QdTYzbU1GNUt0ZGZ4Q2QtS0JwSGhLVHhyLUdSb0E0V2ZibG8wUzhhb3pqbV81ZFZJOVRWTE1mRQ</guid></item><item><title>医生说，美国疫苗建议的变化让父母感到困惑，可能会伤害孩子-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/vaccines-rfk-shared-decision-making-pediatrician-70cf2dad36ca9934e033edd71025ea63</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;Dr. Molly O’Shea has noticed growing skepticism about &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/childhood-vaccine-schedule-trump-rfk-hhs-9b8df9e2767c1261aaac4e2331e77fa3"&gt;vaccines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; at both of her Michigan pediatric offices and says this week’s unprecedented and confusing changes to federal vaccine guidance will only make things worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of her offices is in a Democratic area, where more of the parents she sees are opting for alternative schedules that spread out &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/trump-childhood-vaccines-fact-check-17c0cb6f2f208f11b3474b96d1726945"&gt;shots&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The other is in a Republican area, where some parents have &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/vaccines-fluoride-kennedy-trump-science-antiscience-legislation-73af8e65f407331e8f31b2909812a004"&gt;stopped immunizing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; their children altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She and other doctors fear the new recommendations and the terminology around them will stoke vaccine hesitancy even more, pose challenges for pediatricians and parents that make it harder for kids to get shots, and ultimately lead to &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/vaccines-measles-polio-whooping-cough-rubella-af4cd1aef8f408a960601df6372f9c32"&gt;more illness and death&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The biggest change was to stop blanket recommendations for protection against six diseases and recommend those vaccines only for at-risk children or through something called “shared clinical decision-making” with a health care provider.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;The phrase, experts say, is confusing and dangerous: “It sends a message to a parent that actually there’s only a rarefied group of people who really need the vaccine,” O’Shea said. “It’s creating an environment that puts a sense of uncertainty about the value and necessity or importance of the vaccines in that category.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/trump-rfk-gold-standard-science-research-autism-6e4c6bc2534252ab1e7add0942043778"&gt;Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, who helped lead the anti-vaccine movement for years, said in announcing the changes that they better align the U.S. with peer nations “while strengthening transparency and informed consent.”&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;But doctors say they are sowing doubt — the vaccines have been extensively studied and proven to be safe and effective at shielding kids from nasty diseases — at a time when childhood vaccination rates &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/vaccination-rates-cdc-kindergarten-0d261546a130dc256735d7b1ff8c6a5f"&gt;are already falling&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/us-flu-cases-cdc-subclade-k-29cc5a68eb100585c8e0dbd2ec47b3eb"&gt;some of those infectious diseases&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are spreading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Friday, the American Academy of Pediatrics and more than 200 medical, public health and patient advocacy groups sent &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdownloads.aap.org%2FDOFA%2FChildhood%2520Vaccine%2520Schedule%2520Joint%2520Letter%2520Final.pdf&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7Clungar%40ap.org%7Ca1fb226ec30c4cdff05c08de4fc36b97%7Ce442e1abfd6b4ba3abf3b020eb50df37%7C1%7C0%7C639035898073595504%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=o8rZF2%2BTwKkMqKrfe0eboUu%2FPrvyzOuqOuUveQ9lD8o%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;a letter to Congress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; about the new childhood immunization schedule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We urge you to investigate why the schedule was changed, why credible scientific evidence was ignored, and why the committee charged with advising the HHS Secretary on immunizations did not discuss the schedule changes as a part of their public meeting process,” they wrote.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Many don’t know what ’shared decision-making’ means&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;O’Shea said she and other pediatricians discuss vaccines with parents at every visit where they are given. But that’s not necessarily “shared clinical decision-making,” which has a particular definition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On its website, the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices says: “Unlike routine, catch-up, and risk-based recommendations, shared clinical decision-making vaccinations are not recommended for everyone in a particular age group or everyone in an identifiable risk group. Rather, shared clinical decision-making recommendations are individually based and informed by a decision process between the health care provider and the patient or parent/guardian.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this context, health care providers include primary care physicians, specialists, physician assistants, nurse practitioners, registered nurses and pharmacists.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;A pair of surveys conducted last year by the Annenberg Public Policy Center at the University of Pennsylvania suggested that many people don’t fully understand the concept, which &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/covid-vaccines-cdc-kennedy-fd6ab0c7303a4a1698b319885a02ef54"&gt;came up last year&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; when the federal government changed recommendations around COVID-19 vaccinations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only about 2 in 10 U.S. adults knew that one meaning behind shared decision-making is that “taking the vaccine may not be a good idea for everyone but would benefit some.” And only about one-third realized pharmacists count as health care providers to talk with during the process, even though they frequently administer vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of this week, vaccines that protect against hepatitis A, hepatitis B, rotavirus, RSV, flu and meningococcal disease are no longer universally recommended for kids. RSV, hepatitis A, hepatitis B and meningococcal vaccines are recommended for certain high-risk populations; flu, rotavirus, hepatitis A, hepatitis B and meningococcal vaccines are recommended through shared decision-making — as is the COVID-19 vaccine, although that change was made last year.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Shortly after the federal announcement Monday, Dr. Steven Abelowitz heard from half a dozen parents. “It’s causing concern for us, but more importantly, concern for parents with kids, especially young kids, and confusion,” said Abelowitz, founder of Ocean Pediatrics in Orange County, California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though federal recommendations are not mandates — states have the authority to require vaccinations for schoolchildren — they can affect how easy it is for kids to get shots if doctors choose to follow them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under the new guidelines, O’Shea said, parents seeking shots in the shared decision-making category might no longer bring their kids in for a quick, vaccine-only appointment with staff. They’d sit down with a health care provider and discuss the vaccine. And it could be tougher to have a flu clinic, where parents drive up and kids get shots without seeing a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Staying the course as challenges mount&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, doctors say they won’t let the changes stop them from helping children get the vaccines they need. Leading medical groups are sticking with prior vaccine recommendations. Many parents are, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Megan Landry, whose 4-year-old son Zackary is one of O’Shea’s patients, is among them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s my responsibility as a parent to protect my child’s health and well-being,” she said. “Vaccines are a really effective and well-studied way to do that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She plans to keep having the same conversations she’s always had with O’Shea before getting vaccines for Zackary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Relying on evidence and trusted medical guidance really helps me to make those decisions,” she said. “And for me, it’s not just a personal choice for my own son but a way to contribute to the health of everybody.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But for other families, confidence about vaccines is waning as trust in science erodes. O’Shea lamented that parents are getting the message that they can’t trust medical experts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If I take my car to the mechanic, I don’t go do my own research ahead of time,” she said. “I go to a person I trust and I trust them to tell me what’s going on.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abelowitz, the California doctor, likened the latest federal move to pouring gasoline on a fire of mistrust that was already burning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We’re worried the fire’s out of control,” he said. “Already we’ve seen that with measles and pertussis, there are increased hospitalizations and even increasing deaths. So the way that I look at it — and my colleagues look at it — we’re basically regressing decades.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:17:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxPd2EzY0sxRXRTZjVUNmRrVFJQeVQ1RFEyVmpVNDFQWkFWVEQ5MjR4S1BXMjROdHdpRDZYSGdzSGFEdnc1bkZNSnVPOGRSeXhsZDlBV1ZaMkEzNlR0NEE1c2ExZlQ0WElOUlM2Si1oUXF1aUR2dENVclg3V2d5REZNSW0yWGttQm12dnhZM3RuQkNqTVRPSHZWcEN2ek1OWGVpUUR4TU5jcENMWnBI</guid></item><item><title>绝经后力量训练至关重要。如何充分利用您的锻炼-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/menopause-perimenopause-exercise-strength-training-b379697dd2290786739ed442d4173cd7</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;When Sarah Baldassaro turned 50, she took stock of her health and began working with a fitness coach on &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/weightlighting-train-to-failure-exercise-9f8781dac9ecdc9e75471ac546881d39"&gt;strength training&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, a type of exercise that’s crucial for &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/menopause-hormone-therapy-hot-flashes-0f3258f1762e1fb3c9a6f7205a43e66e"&gt;women in midlife&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Now I would say I’m stronger overall than I ever have been at any age,” said Baldassaro, 52, of Alexandria, Virginia. “My fitness level is much more like when I was in my early 30s.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical experts say &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/strength-training-excercise-4eb437efde74b4dc5e937c53f26ff528"&gt;strength training keeps bones and muscles healthy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; after &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/hormone-therapy-estrogen-hot-flashes-fda-5b1f29a73553c142f67b1f88b6656428"&gt;menopause&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; when estrogen loss speeds up a reduction in bone density and contributes to the gradual loss of muscle mass. This type of exercise — which involves working against resistance — also helps women maintain a healthy weight and stay on track with New Year’s resolutions about fitness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People underestimate how powerful it is,” said Dr. Christina DeAngelis, an OB-GYN at Penn State Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what should your workout look like and how do you get started?&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2&gt;Strength training with weights&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Physical therapist Hilary Granat said bone and muscle health are intertwined: When muscle pulls on bone during resistance training, it stimulates bone-building cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Resistance can come from dumbbells, free weights or machines such as rowers. One example of a strength training exercise is the chest press, which involves lying back on a bench or the ground, pressing weights up from chest level and then lowering them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s important to work “close to muscle failure,” said Granat, who owns Core Total Wellness in Washington, D.C. “You really have to push yourself.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="Infobox" data-module data-gtm-region="This article is part of AP's Be Well coverage, focusing on wellness, fitness, diet and mental health. Read more Be Well." data-align-center&gt;
    
    &lt;div class="Infobox-items RichTextBody"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article is part of AP’s Be Well coverage, focusing on wellness, fitness, diet and mental health. &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/hub/be-well"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Read more Be Well.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That means lifting weights that are heavy enough to be challenging and doing somewhere between six and 30 repetitions.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;You’ll know you’re working hard enough if you start slowing down in tempo or speed or can’t do another repetition in good form, she said. A good rule of thumb for an exercise like a bicep curl is to lift weights somewhere between 5 pounds (2.3 kilograms) and 20 pounds (9.1 kilograms), with novices starting at the lower end.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Baldassaro has worked her way up to 20 pounds (9.1 kilograms) for some exercises, incorporating techniques she learned from Granat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She said the health coach has helped her expand her workouts beyond mostly cardio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While she still does aerobic exercises, “the strength training has really been the difference maker for me,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;No weights? No problem&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Building up bones and muscles doesn’t necessarily require equipment. You can also do pushups, squats, lunges, situps, crunches or planks. Another good exercise is squatting down with your back against a wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even the simple act of getting into and out of a chair can be helpful, DeAngelis said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You have to engage your core going from sitting to standing,” she said. “That also allows you to work on your coordination and balance.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s also what Granat calls “impact training” — exercises like walking, hiking, running, jumping, skipping and climbing stairs. On the high-impact end of the spectrum is a “rebound jump,” which involves jumping up and down from a step 10 to 30 times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We’re not talking about jumping hard and fast and a lot,” she said, adding that three times a week is enough.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Don’t forget about balance&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts say middle-aged women should also perform balance exercises, which play a crucial role in preventing falls that can break or fracture bones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These include tai chi, yoga or even standing on one leg while brushing your teeth for around 30 seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of these exercises are great for younger people too, experts say, especially since bone mass peaks at 25 to 30 years old and slowly begins to lessen around age 40.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After seeing how strength training has improved her life, Baldassaro advises others: “Don’t wait. Get started.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;———-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxPNjFtSnVlRlhycUpRMVQwd1h2MWtkajFTdUZDOWRrVmhGYmZFQkN4bWVFWXBSUkM2S0ljemtIV3gtR0hqM3RSZ29ab0UzUDd5QUNSaS1hOFJqVEszNDlDZFZuUHRCR29HN2J2Xy10cFpZbHZDMzhINHRhQUhyaVdXeXM3UU9ER3dZeVVNR0NseElQelE0dWxkOEpUbWIzdmdXNXltZ0o1a29KRURlMjFr</guid></item><item><title>“超级流感”病毒使每个人都生病了。今年的疫苗有效吗？ - NJ.com</title><link>https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2026/01/a-super-flu-strain-is-making-everyone-sick-is-this-years-vaccine-effective.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="M6ISVQU5BBBOFB3QS2Y2GIEVQM"&gt;A fast-spreading new flu strain is gaining a reputation as a monstrous “super flu.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SLQAJTFE5JA7BHTUW2EV24E7QA"&gt;The mutation of influenza A(H3N2) called subclade K is driving up infections across the country, including in New Jersey, where the season’s &lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/staff/jroman/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.nj.com/staff/jroman/"&gt;first pediatric flu death&lt;/a&gt; was reported Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KXQTYAZM3JDHXGD5SGXFVWBXGY"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-53.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-53.html"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; estimates that there have been at least 180,000 hospitalizations and 7,400 deaths from flu so far this season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NG3UZUTH2FGX3HL2T6BFDAJEDI"&gt;The majority of infections have been driven by influenza A(H3N2) viruses, specifically subclade K. This strain accounts for 91.5% of the influenza A(H3N2) viruses that have undergone additional testing at the CDC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IMR7DNUWDBB63MXE3T5VH6DM4A"&gt;Here’s what makes the new strain so fierce and how this year’s vaccine will fare against the so-called “super flu.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-heading"&gt;Why does the flu seem worse this year?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="U6AYPQC3LZAQ7MX3DE7UZ55RL4"&gt;Flu viruses are constantly changing and mutating. Each year, researchers analyze data to try and predict which flu strains will be most common during the upcoming season and develop a vaccine to target those selected strains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AUNAWARDBNEANLAZGSODAZA4VU"&gt;However, occasionally there are some genetic differences between the circulating viruses and the strains targeted by the vaccine. Therein lies what makes subclade K so stubborn. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NNUZGINBFRH5TM3EJVBVJD6XZI"&gt;“This is a strain that evolved after the vaccine had been prepared earlier last year. So, the vaccine may not fully cover the influenza this year,” said Dr. Adeel Butt, an infectious disease expert at JFK University Medical Center in Edison, an affiliate of Hackensack Meridian Health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IABTEKED4ZDRJF35RFNDYGTT7Y"&gt;The selection of viruses used in this season’s flu vaccines was made in February 2025. Subclade K, however, didn’t emerge until in August 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="E6YJYWF34REAXNXSMANUJISO3E"&gt;According to the &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/emergencies/disease-outbreak-news/item/2025-DON586" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.who.int/emergencies/disease-outbreak-news/item/2025-DON586"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;, subclade K viruses have several changes from related A(H3N2) viruses, which are already associated with lower vaccine effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BLIVUWU7NFD5DDJI4IQFPKUYCQ"&gt;However, current epidemiological data doesn’t indicate an increase in disease severity, although the WHO said “this subclade marks a notable evolution in influenza A(H3N2) viruses.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-heading"&gt;Is the vaccine still effective?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3RWTYAEUJ5FMZCLLREFINTLLFQ"&gt;Even if there are some differences between the flu strains circulating right now and the strains included in the vaccine, preliminary data suggests the shot is still effective to a strong degree. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OWQGQU2MZZAOLE4HDDFINZ7WRQ"&gt;Data from the &lt;a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/pre-print-early-influenza-virus-characterisation-and-vaccine-effectiveness-in-england-in-autumn-2025" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/pre-print-early-influenza-virus-characterisation-and-vaccine-effectiveness-in-england-in-autumn-2025"&gt;UK Health Security Agency&lt;/a&gt; shows the 2025-2026 vaccine is currently 70 to 75% effective at preventing hospital attendance in children aged 2 to 17 years and 30 to 40% effective in adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UEMUHTBW4VGW3CHV6QLK46XHP4"&gt;The numbers line up with what Dr. Daniel Ruderfer is seeing at K. Hovnanian Children’s Hospital, based on the campus of Jersey Shore University Medical Center in Neptune.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KISXZXGI6FD5DEZWIHJKKVPXWI"&gt;“What we do find year in and year out is that those who get the flu vaccines really have better outcomes overall,” said Ruderfer, the hospital’s division chief of pediatric infectious diseases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3ZDR3TMKXVFFRCDAZVCSAR5QM4"&gt;“Essentially, the kids that I see in the hospital are those who are not vaccinated for the flu. And the ones who do end up in the hospital with the flu, who are vaccinated, they often have much less significant clinical courses,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FGDIJT5K5RDXTFRNAWWHFDEFTM"&gt;However, national flu vaccination coverage is on the decline for children, something that Ruderfer said he finds concerning. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RDWFJYZV5ZCTPKJF5YPKAFK4EY"&gt;During the 2024–2025 flu season, vaccination coverage was 49.2% among children 6 months through 17 years, down from 55.4% the previous season and 63.7% during the pre-pandemic 2019–20 season, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LL3PQMPM5RA4LAYYLHSVWQ7UOA"&gt;The last time flu vaccination coverage among children was this low or lower was 2011. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="I3SC4CGAVBECZDYFA6TA32ZHSU"&gt;As of Dec. 27, the most recent date for which data is available, only 42.5% of children 6 months through 17 years have received a vaccination, according to the CDC’s &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluvaxview/dashboard/children-vaccination-coverage.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.cdc.gov/fluvaxview/dashboard/children-vaccination-coverage.html"&gt;weekly flu vaccination dashboard&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-22" data-gaid="inarticle-22"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-heading"&gt;Can you still get sick?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-23" data-gaid="inarticle-23"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="U5VCYB2YGNFL7ASAUJGU7FZGFY"&gt;While vaccines may not fully protect everyone, public health experts say they’re still proven to help prevent serious illness and death. In the average flu season, vaccines have a 40-60% efficacy in reducing the incidence of severe illness, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-24" data-gaid="inarticle-24"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YXRIT7EYPNA5XKAHTVH2BG563E"&gt;“I want to be very clear, vaccination is still the best way to protect ourselves and the population against influenza and severe illness related to influenza,” said Butt, who has more than three decades of experience in infectious diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-25" data-gaid="inarticle-25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4SAQXJDJOZCPVFOPBPEXFFM7OM"&gt;There’s a common misconception that getting the flu shot will give you the flu. However, Butt said that’s not possible “because none of the vaccines recommended by the CDC contain active, live virus.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-26" data-gaid="inarticle-26"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MNFENVF4QZHPHFKINDRHL73BWI"&gt;Flu vaccines may use viral proteins, inactivated viruses, or even small portions of the virus capsule to teach the immune system how to fight off germs. But they don’t contain the active flu virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-27" data-gaid="inarticle-27"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IRUQFZS3PFCPRA65JUBU7Y3YSE"&gt;There are other reasons why you may still get sick, despite receiving a flu shot. It’s possible the symptoms may be the result of a different infection, not the flu. It’s also possible that exposure to the virus happened before the vaccine had time to kick in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-28" data-gaid="inarticle-28"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CHHMOJ344BATLCGU44L6DNLAUY"&gt;It takes about two weeks for antibodies to develop in the body following vaccination, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-29" data-gaid="inarticle-29"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MYTFMFEDGVGLFIDCFCB3NAW6GI"&gt;So, the vaccine can’t completely prevent infection, but it does reduce your chances of getting infected. Its main strength is preventing the worst-case scenario — severe illness and death. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-30" data-gaid="inarticle-30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-heading"&gt;Is there still time to get a flu shot?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-31" data-gaid="inarticle-31"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OU4F2KXB7JFOJFBOSV6XKF5M7I"&gt;Yes! The good news is that it’s not too late to try and prevent getting sick. The bad news is that’s because flu season is far from over. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-32" data-gaid="inarticle-32"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZDTUZWW44VC67FDQ6RCTQMPSUQ"&gt;While you can get sick with the flu any time of year, the CDC technically defines flu season as running from October to May. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-33" data-gaid="inarticle-33"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AMQSYSYX7FHR5GFDLRHZ4AMNGY"&gt;Currently, nearly 15 states are in the CDC’s highest possible tier of &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/usmap.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/usmap.html"&gt;flu activity&lt;/a&gt;. The elevated activity is expected to continue for several weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-34" data-gaid="inarticle-34"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YK4BB467XNC6FN3DTZ3KB6W6MQ"&gt;Flu vaccines are available for use in people aged 6 months and older. They’re offered at doctor’s offices, pharmacies, community health clinics, health departments and other community locations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-35" data-gaid="inarticle-35"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DXGD7YFL6RHB7B2QZWXJ5MYOUU"&gt;Visit the CDC website for additional help &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines-adults/recommended-vaccines/vaccine-planning.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines-adults/recommended-vaccines/vaccine-planning.html"&gt;finding vaccines in your area&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-36" data-gaid="inarticle-36"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:PTQBCLTUR5B2ZJUU3WBM5JWDDM" data-fusion-component="PTQBCLTUR5B2ZJUU3WBM5JWDDM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:PTQBCLTUR5B2ZJUU3WBM5JWDDM" data-fusion-component="PTQBCLTUR5B2ZJUU3WBM5JWDDM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-37" data-gaid="inarticle-37"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NJ.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxQNU5jbV8tRHQ3ZDhFemZUZFRjX0VGOFZOUjVVUnotX0J3Q19rRGxJNEg5RVBwQUNVd1loRmtYaGM3X3dUbFpMU0xaMFpBRnVlWUo1eEc3OVpBTU1QbUFONm9fM2dyYVVrRE11TTNwaEJ3TXBvUG9FcllRajI1RFEtVHpGZUZzaFFlMjJuckhob0FmajBpN0Rva2psb3Zib1NBNnVyR0FRRUNpZXp0Z3lVaUY0WjJxMUk</guid></item><item><title>金毛猎犬超越激动人心的惊喜生日派对在奶奶家- DogTime</title><link>https://dogtime.com/news/201838-golden-retriever-excited-surprise-birthday-party-grandma-video</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s hard not to smile when you see a dog being celebrated like a full-fledged family member. From custom cakes to heartfelt traditions, pets are often at the center of some of the happiest moments at home. That’s exactly the energy behind a video featuring a &lt;a href="https://dogtime.com/dog-breeds/golden-retriever"&gt;Golden Retriever&lt;/a&gt; whose birthday party turned into a full family event.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-golden-retriever-s-reaction-to-surprise-birthday-party-at-grandma-s-will-fill-your-heart"&gt;Golden Retriever’s reaction to surprise birthday party at grandma’s will fill your heart&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-instagram wp-block-embed-instagram"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Wally recently turned five, and his family made sure the occasion was nothing short of unforgettable. The video, shared by @wally.meets.world, begins with the Golden arriving at his grandma’s house wearing a birthday hat. As his owner films the moment, the front door opens, and Wally enthusiastically greets his grandma before dashing inside, eager to see what awaits him.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t take long for the pup to realize something special is happening. Grandma had transformed her home with balloons, banners, and candles, all arranged around a table prepared just for Wally. The spread included dog-friendly treats and a cake made especially for him, ensuring he could enjoy every part of the celebration safely.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Wally’s excitement only grows as he explores the decorations and zeroes in on the presents. True to form, he wastes no time tearing into the gift wrapping, clearly delighted with the attention. Soon after, the family gathers around the table, placing Wally front and center as they sing “Happy Birthday.” Sitting proudly in his seat, he appears fully aware that the celebration is all about him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="pb-in-article-content test-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Once the song ends, Wally dives straight into his cake as his family laughs and cheers him on. While it’s clear he’s a bit spoiled, his owner humorously sums it up in the caption by saying that “dogs are the new grandchildren.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Some pointed out how Wally seemed to understand that the party was for him, while others loved how “proud” he looked during the birthday song. Many praised grandma’s decorating skills, calling the setup thoughtful and impressive. Several viewers described the video as the “most precious thing” they had seen all day, though a few jokingly noted that Wally might feel a little sad once the excitement was over.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>DogTime</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPQ1FwME9iOEpXRnV2VDB5VDhhczVNNFhpbHdScmVPeWRkTFEtVHdJZjk4c3hDV1o1eVVVdFV0c005VnBGRVpGT2tvcS0yV3lvdC00OG5GNXl4WkJfZHk5SG00SElHSHhFSC1aaEdhVTFfMjlWdU9oc1QtYU43NXVoVHJTMXFFcTk2T0Zwb21xemRFMm55cVhHRzJ30gGfAUFVX3lxTE5JMmJmV0tsSXdoQ3o4bk1SVUdUd1Fmb0hvQVBtdldyNGRZWXJBZ1kyZVE3Ujg2RWJTd0dMOFZDbmg5WUk0QV9ORHlhemhlNnNVMU8yTGl1UDU5VUE5bHhwcUVFV294QVdLOGNpS2NEanRFZXJ1d1d0V2RIMFF3UXpTenBvbm4tdk1GRlpWV2xzREQ5bXpCSUVLNXNGaGNtZw</guid></item><item><title>营养学家为Samantha Ruth Prabhu提供了3个绝经期应对脑雾的技巧，专家事实核查- NDTV</title><link>https://www.ndtv.com/lifestyle/nutritionist-gives-samantha-ruth-prabhu-3-tips-to-tackle-brain-fog-during-perimenopause-expert-fact-checks-10564441</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="Art-exp_wr" id="ignorediv"&gt;
                                        
                                        
                                        &lt;p&gt;Samantha Ruth Prabhu has often spoken openly about wellness, healing, and listening to one's body. In a recent conversation on her YouTube channel, the actor sat down with nutritionist Rashi Chowdhary to talk about perimenopause – the transitional phase that leads up to menopause. The discussion focused on symptoms that many women struggle with but rarely talk about. These included sudden weight gain, poor sleep, anxiety, and one very common issue: brain fog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the chat, Samantha asked the nutritionist about how to deal with brain fog. Rashi Chowdhary broke down why this happens and what can be done to improve cognitive function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Is Brain Fog?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brain fog is not a medical condition. It is a term used to describe feeling mentally slow, forgetful, unfocused, or confused. Many women experience it during perimenopause due to hormonal and metabolic changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Does Brain Fog Happen?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Explaining the science in simple terms, Rashi Chowdhary said hormones play a big role. “Our brain has estrogen receptors. These estrogen receptors pick up glucose and fire it up into ATP. That is how memory builds,” she explained. During perimenopause, estrogen levels start dipping. Because of this, these receptors do not work as fast, which can slow down thinking and memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-personalisation---lifestyle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                                            
                                    &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="v-ndtv"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She also pointed out another reason. “Because we have insulin resistance, our blood glucose keeps fluctuating. Suddenly, the brain does not have a steady supply of glucose,” the nutritionist said. This uneven fuel supply makes thinking feel sluggish. According to her, all of this together leads to brain fog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nutritionist Tells Samantha How To Deal With Brain Fog&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Samantha Ruth asked how to make cognitive function “A++”, Rashi Chowdhary shared a few practical habits that can help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Start Your Day With Healthy Fats&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nutritionist suggested beginning the morning with fats instead of sugar. “Take one teaspoon of ghee, butter, or coconut oil,” she said. She advised adding fresh turmeric root with black pepper. “These work as nootropics and support brain health,” she added. She stressed using turmeric root, not the powdered version. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Add Lion's Mane Mushroom&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rashi Chowdhary said she loves lion's mane mushroom for brain support. Half a teaspoon of powdered form can be added to coffee, liquorice tea, or any morning drink. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Use Smart Supplements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They also spoke about creatine monohydrate and CoQ10. Rashi Chowdhary explained that creatine also acts as a nootropic and supports brain energy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nutritionist Gives Samantha 3 Tips To Tackle Brain Fog, Expert Fact-Checks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Ravina Patel, a gynaecologist at Mayflower Women's Hospital, Ahmedabad, spoke to NDTV, fact-checking the claims made by nutritionist Rashi Chowdhary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DTQR5w_jL73/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="14"&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Begin Your Day With Healthy Fats&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking about healthy fats, she said, "Everyone, irrespective of their age, especially women, needs to start their day with healthy fats to maintain stable blood glucose levels for the rest of the day. It can be from nuts and seeds or from fats like ghee and coconut oil."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She explained that adding turmeric and black pepper to fat makes sure your body absorbs curcumin efficiently due to the presence of piperine. If you consume it with fat, it won't cause iron deficiency or anaemia in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Stable blood sugars are what can keep brain fog at bay, and there is generalised inflammation too, so if you can't consume the aforementioned concoction, any healthy fat source works for you," the expert further noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Add Lion's Mane Mushroom To Your Diet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coming to the second point, where nutritionist Rashi Chowdhary suggested that lion's mane mushroom supports the brain, Dr Patel clarified that there are not enough human studies to prove that its consumption can improve brain fog during perimenopause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's been used for centuries in Asia for neurodegenerative diseases, but also for other chronic inflammatory conditions and digestive issues. And the evidence of a medicinal plant and food plant used in Chinese traditional medicine is anecdotal," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Most studies have been conducted in cognitively compromised subjects," the expert mentioned, suggesting that a person take any supplements containing vitamin B complex, omega-3 fatty acids, and EGCG (green tea). They all promote good health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Start Taking Smart Supplements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the last tip, in which nutritionist Rashi Chowdhary suggested taking creatine monohydrate and CoQ10, Dr Patel explained, "CoQ10 is produced by the body as well as available from food sources like nuts, seeds, vegetables, and legumes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So she's not wrong, but a healthy diet and a balanced nutrient profile would almost render all the supplements useless unless the symptoms are not manageable through diet and exercise," the doctor mentioned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Her (referring to nutritionist Rashi Chowdhary) advice is not sustainable, not affordable," concluded Dr Patel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;a class="sp_lnk2" href="https://www.ndtv.com/lifestyle/gynaecologist-tells-samantha-why-age-should-not-pressure-women-to-have-kids-9778507" rel="noindex,nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Gynaecologist Tells Samantha Why Age Should Not Pressure Women To Have Kids&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                                                        
                                                                                                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                                                        

                                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NDTV</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:25:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3wFBVV95cUxPbkpEalI5WWxrM29ETmlfRnk5cmNFTHd5X2xhbXlqcU9UQm9fX2lLSUZuRGhGQ3B5MTZyVS1hYWxQcHZGQnVWd3lTbTN2U0RoemdtM25JYWlIbnBqUmVVRi00c2RnN01XamN5UUpYaTNLZUJFV3RGSHAwRFFHMjdBMzVYVlpWU0FtdXlTUVJXb1RFVXR6Ym5yam96bmVLUnljSXNKaFhDZXhtTHJCemNUX19wMFlCc2gzX0NIdndjTFZoMUFwQVlDOTBIb01RYlNaY3M3eVFZTTRTXzRMXzdZ0gHnAUFVX3lxTE9nSjZWcDZDV28zYzMtUVh6cVZIcndxMHRuVEdMQVRFMi1wc2ZYNWlrRUhnd084T0czekRHSDhkSW40SUNvSmduOGdqWU9MTHg2UWdtbDByT2ZiREJSMUx5SVY4TjN6a3dTMHY3QVF5TzNsV3RxUmtZUkxZSjVjcENTeEYxWkZsZl9tQmdtZTlITHZvNm5nb21ZTTdBTld4S2xmSTJlMFR5bmdoNUJ4NzU3OEhRT0czUGVxTEdKMFNQdFBudGRabjZUNjdRcVRoVzFsZ2dqZi03dDlITzI0OFVRNEZNNDh2Zw</guid></item><item><title>美国国立卫生研究院已经失去了其科学完整性。所以我们离开了- statnews.com</title><link>https://www.statnews.com/2026/01/10/nih-resign-protest-four-leaders-cite-interference-censorship/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-constrained wp-block-post-content-is-layout-constrained"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are National Institutes of Health scientists and administrators with more than 50 years of collective civil service.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Or, more accurately, we &lt;em&gt;were &lt;/em&gt;NIH scientists and administrators.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of 2025, we anticipated changes with the new administration, but expected that rigorous scientific inquiry would continue to be valued. After all, the country’s health research infrastructure, considered the most prestigious in the world, had always garnered broad bipartisan support.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Over the course of the year, as we witnessed the Trump administration’s reckless policies, we tried to protect the science we had always championed. We spoke up when we could, and in June we joined hundreds of our colleagues in signing the &lt;a href="https://www.standupforscience.net/bethesda-declaration" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Bethesda Declaration&lt;/a&gt;, an open letter to the NIH director detailing how several new policies were undermining scientific integrity and the institute’s mission. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But we can no longer lend our credibility to an organization that has lost its integrity. In recent months, each of us independently reached the decision to resign in protest of the actions of an administration that treats science not as a process for building knowledge, but as a means to advance its political agenda. One of us resigned just Friday. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;We have resigned because:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;We protest the hypocrisy of an NIH leadership that claims to protect academic freedom while censoring grants and staff communication. Instead of applying our skills and knowledge to science, we have been instructed to tell scientists competing for NIH funding to remove words like “equity,” “diversity,” “minority,” and “underserved,” regardless of the scientific appropriateness of these terms or the significance of the projects. To this day, grants continue to be “realigned” with administration priorities, a clear form of ideological coercion. The damage to research and destabilizing effects on the scientific workforce will be long lasting.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;We protest an NIH leadership that &lt;a href="https://www.nih.gov/about-nih/nih-director/statements/advancing-nihs-mission-through-unified-strategy" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;claims&lt;/a&gt; to champion early-career scientists and prioritize “solutions-oriented” health disparities research while selectively terminating and censoring these awards. We witnessed unilateral withdrawals of applications and terminations of active awards to early-career scientists simply because they had applied to funding announcements designed to broaden participation in the scientific workforce. The progress or promise of this science was never considered.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Similarly, funding announcements that solicited research to address health disparities were disappeared from the public record because they were deemed “DEI.” Associated applications were withdrawn without review and awards were terminated. Some of these applications and awards were in our portfolios and we urged reconsideration of these actions, providing justifications based on the awards’ merit and even its actual alignment with publicly stated priorities. Our requests went unanswered and the grantees’ appeals were ignored. These decisions will hurt American communities and stifle scientific advancements for decades to come.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;We protest an NIH leadership that creates a culture of fear within the agency’s dedicated staff. Colleagues who question illegal and politically motivated orders have been silenced, with some &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/11/14/nih-puts-trump-critic-on-administrative-leave/"&gt;placed on leave &lt;/a&gt;or &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/16/nih-jeanne-marrazzo-sues-trump-administration-over-dismissal/"&gt;forced out&lt;/a&gt;. Each of us has been told not to push back because “people would lose their jobs.” Refrains heard in the hallways include: “What I’m being asked to do feels wrong, but I need my health insurance” and “we have to keep our heads down and avoid putting a target on our backs.” These should not be concerns articulated in a world-class scientific institution.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Upholding our oath of office — “to protect and defend the Constitution from enemies foreign and domestic” — and living up to our values requires us to leave the jobs we previously cherished.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;We are by no means the only ones leaving. Many of our colleagues have resigned, have retired earlier than planned, or are actively taking steps to leave the NIH, sometimes at great personal sacrifice. Other colleagues are wrestling with whether the costs of staying outweighs the costs of leaving.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In sharing our personal reasons for leaving, we hope to let our colleagues know they are not alone in recognizing the harms that are undermining the agency they loved.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A stable research funding infrastructure is essential to solve the country’s health challenges and to support a functional democracy where policy is based on evidence. Despite leaving the NIH, we refuse to lose hope. We remain committed to the work of advancing science and improving public health.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To researchers whose work lifts up vulnerable communities and who have devoted their work to currently “sensitive” topics — vaccines, health equity, the health of sexual and gender minorities, climate change, misinformation: We need to continue to speak up and speak out. We also need to work together to build new opportunities for this critical work until the NIH returns to its mission. &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;To our colleagues who plan to remain at the NIH and those who continue to seek funding from the NIH: The options in front of us are not good: continue in a compromised process or refuse to participate and risk professional stability.  We wish all of you well as you continue to weigh the impact of your choices on the scientific enterprise and on the communities across the nation. We know you seek to do your best to navigate the ethical and practical challenges and uphold the moral and scientific integrity. We are already moving down the slippery slope. Please decide where your red line is so you can choose to act before the line is already behind you.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Not only is our health at stake, but this attack on science is an attack on freedom of speech and thought. What we have seen at NIH is a threat to the fundamental freedoms that all of us cherish.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But we can fight back. The biggest lesson the four of us have learned over this past year is that what feels impossible and overwhelming when you’re sitting by yourself can begin to feel achievable and urgent when you are working with others that share your values. Working together, we can preserve our moral and scientific integrity. We can rebuild a robust biomedical research ecosystem free from heedless political interference. Acting boldly now will help to protect democracy and ensure better health for all.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sylvia Chou, Ph.D., MPH, resigned Friday from the position of program director at the National Cancer Institute. Paul Grothaus, Ph.D., retired on Dec. 31, 2025, earlier than planned, from the position of program officer at the National Institute of Aging. Alexa Romberg, Ph.D., resigned Dec. 8, 2025, from the position of deputy chief of the Prevention Research Branch at the National Institute on Drug Abuse. Vani Pariyadath, Ph.D., resigned June 14, 2025, from the position of chief of the Behavioral and Cognitive Neuroscience Branch at the National Institute on Drug Abuse&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQV291TE11dndSY1lITHkzNTh0cTVfWW5rSVZ1ZXBXWlMxZ3dJUW5PT3IzZllNNEx2dVZ0WUEyTDRiWXdEaTZkaDdMeUhqMTQ1ZXE3bUtwdnhGa3F5T29YS3dEcE4zczNBVkIzY21DY084VVZsdHJxQ0xJakJ1Z3hUYjY5VFZLX2xkV3c2dG5VbXMwRXpzTjlOZ2ZaWEZHUQ</guid></item><item><title>像这样坐着可以随着年龄的增长带来重大的健康益处- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/benefits-of-sitting-on-ground-goog_l_69616c0be4b08ce691f7cdea</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s well-established that spending too much time sitting (ahem, working at a desk) could have an impact on our bodies. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/walking-benefits-for-sedentary-lifestyle_l_65f05b55e4b032e17a83914d" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="Sitting all day" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69616c0be4b08ce691f7cdea" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="65f05b55e4b032e17a83914d" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;Sitting all day&lt;/a&gt; can &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/healthrisksofaninactivelifestyle.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="decrease muscle strength" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69616c0be4b08ce691f7cdea" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://medlineplus.gov/healthrisksofaninactivelifestyle.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;decrease muscle strength&lt;/a&gt; and is linked to bad health outcomes like &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/life/topic/heart-disease" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="heart disease" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69616c0be4b08ce691f7cdea" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/life/topic/heart-disease" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;But is all sitting created equal?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://r.bttn.io?btn_ref=org-677cb81987ed72f9&amp;amp;btn_url=https://www.amazon.com/Built-Move-Essential-Habits-Freely/dp/0593534808?tag=thehuffingtop-20%26ascsubtag%3D69616c0be4b08ce691f7cdea%252C-1%252C-1%252Cd%252C0%252C0%252Chp-fil-am%253D0%252C0%253A0%252C0%252C0%252C0" target="_blank" role="link" data-amazon-link="true" data-aps-asin="0593534808" data-aps-asc-tag="thehuffingtop-20" data-aps-asc-subtag="69616c0be4b08ce691f7cdea,-1,-1,d,0,0,hp-fil-am=0,0:0,0,0,0" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Some folks" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69616c0be4b08ce691f7cdea" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://r.bttn.io?btn_ref=org-677cb81987ed72f9&amp;amp;btn_url=https://www.amazon.com/Built-Move-Essential-Habits-Freely/dp/0593534808?tag=thehuffingtop-20%26ascsubtag%3D69616c0be4b08ce691f7cdea%252C-1%252C-1%252Cd%252C0%252C0%252Chp-fil-am%253D0%252C0%253A0%252C0%252C0%252C0" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Some folks&lt;/a&gt; say sitting on the ground is actually good for your health, and should be done regularly ― a concept that almost seems too good to be true.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below, experts shared with HuffPost the pros and cons of sitting on the floor — and why no one posture is ideal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sitting cross-legged on the ground can be good for mobility and flexibility.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most adults likely don’t often find themselves frequently sitting on the floor in the cross-legged position. But kids who regularly sit and play on the floor may be onto something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I really think from a health benefits or a musculoskeletal condition standpoint, that [cross-legged sitting] posture really does help us with ... hip, low back and knee range of motion,” said &lt;a href="https://www.shrs.pitt.edu/people/christopher-bise" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Christopher Bise" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69616c0be4b08ce691f7cdea" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.shrs.pitt.edu/people/christopher-bise" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;Dr. Christopher Bise&lt;/a&gt;, an assistant professor in the department of physical therapy at the University of Pittsburgh. It also helps keep our lower body flexible, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hss.edu/physicians_oconnell-jennifer.asp" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Jennifer O’Connell" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69616c0be4b08ce691f7cdea" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.hss.edu/physicians_oconnell-jennifer.asp" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;Dr. Jennifer O’Connell&lt;/a&gt;, a physiatrist at the Hospital for Special Surgery in New York, added that “one of the problems with sitting in a chair is that it’s a position where your hamstrings tend to be tight — sitting in a cross legged position may help that somewhat.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if you aren’t able to get yourself down to the floor, you can still work on your mobility and flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Remember that these positions don’t necessarily have to be on the floor. You can, on a couch, get in to the cross-legged sitting position, or you can use different sitting positions on the couch that will also increase your range of motion, as well,” Bise explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Having a good range of motion is important as you age.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maintaining your range of motion is important for many reasons — you’ll be better able to get around your house, do your errands, and play with children and grandchildren as your years increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But I think one of the things that happens when we get older is ... we become less flexible because we begin to slow down ― but we don’t have to be less flexible,” Bise said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“And when you think about the treatments you’re going to receive from a physical therapist ... one of the first things they’re going to do is assess both your joint mobility and your muscle flexibility for the muscles around your joints and see how they’re moving,” Bise continued. “And when we have bones and joints and muscles that are inflexible, that are stiffer, we’re not going to move as well or as efficiently as we could.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Going from sitting on the ground, to the chair, to walking and exercising is a great way to keep yourself mobile and flexible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plus, the ability to actually get into and out of a seated-on-the-floor posture is also important, Bise said. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/older-patients-aging-geriatricians_l_6515e29ee4b055cbc0a72975" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="Older adults" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69616c0be4b08ce691f7cdea" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="6515e29ee4b055cbc0a72975" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;Older adults&lt;/a&gt; are prone to falls, he said, but if they have the ability to rise and lower to and from the floor, they’ll be more able to prevent falls in the future or get themselves up if need be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: PeopleImages via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;PeopleImages via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Sitting on the ground can be a good way to maintain your range of motion and flexibility. &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sitting on the ground can work your core, too.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sitting on the ground engages your core muscles in a way that just doesn’t happen when you’re sitting on a chair, according to O’Connell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without back support from a chair, your core muscles automatically turn on, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“And then just the mere act of getting up from that position is beneficial for your whole body. You’re exercising your hips, your knees, your entire lower chain and your core in order to get up,” O’Connell explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But this doesn’t mean you should sit on the ground &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; the time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can try sitting on the ground for 30 minutes or so, but you should not plop down on the floor for the entire day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There’s a reason that your Apple Watch reminds you every 60 minutes to get up and start moving again ... some of it is postural, some of it is just simple motion and getting calories going, but some of it is also changing postures as well,” Bise noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;O’Connell said that she routinely tells her patients who work desk jobs to get up and move around — whether that’s walking to get a glass of water or just moving around the house.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Before you know it, an hour to two hours have gone by, you didn’t get up and move. And although you didn’t really notice that because you were focused on tasks, your back did notice that,” O’Connell explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sitting on the ground is not ideal for everyone.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One reason where floor seating may be detrimental is if you have joint issues,” O’Connell said. “As a matter of reference, I have an issue where my hips don’t open up very well, so sitting in a traditional cross-legged position on the floor for me is very challenging.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, people recovering from certain surgeries or injuries may also have trouble sitting on the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Just like with anything ... check with your doctor before you start any type of exercise regimen,” O’Connell said. “But you can consult with a physical therapist, and they can give you strategies for getting up and down off the floor.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it’s good to put your body in different postures and positions, you shouldn’t do so if it’s not safe for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The original version of this story was published on HuffPost at an earlier date.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:00:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNcjBRRHR3MVFtU0VZUmEtTkdtWlZSMjV5VHQyMVI5V1FHemJUMmdheml4NUxaVlo5aGlHUzVhSHpGUVJGZDN1TkF5N2RnQ1BjWXZhbk1GVG1MUGxjUUw1NlZiX2NoUWFpZkpLdFppbktxUHVxbDhic2N0R2M0aXFMbzVFaE5QeGJ6M0hqbDlGS1Jsb1pBSk530gGcAUFVX3lxTE93ZHFWS2FSS2hKNUtmTC1lb25qYzdQNTdJblg5dFpqanVLM3F6X0ZjWm1pdXFlbUhFRDRpcWFVaTFIem5pOW5WYlFTa0NkdjczbTRraHcwT0wxZUYzcXA2dC1VR085dXl1NW0tdFhyTndDanRHY2hOWmtLS04xVWhTdEJfUGFFWDZQSXBCdWFrMVJHMUMtSm4ydmtvVQ</guid></item><item><title>纽约市的高度传染性“超级流感” ：以下是症状- SILive.com</title><link>https://www.silive.com/news/2026/01/highly-contagious-super-flu-in-nyc-here-are-the-symptoms.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="G4JXYAD445BGJOZ7UTDQWK5L6U"&gt;STATEN ISLAND, N.Y. — A new flu strain has engulfed the United States, causing the highest flu infection rate in 25 years as New York City’s flu-related hospitalizations continue to rise at alarming rates, data shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZPHKAFCOQ5CTVAUQQ42NQJUEOY"&gt;Dubbed “super flu,” the strain, &lt;a href="https://www.silive.com/health/2026/01/staten-islands-super-flu-outbreak-hospitalizations-climb.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.silive.com/health/2026/01/staten-islands-super-flu-outbreak-hospitalizations-climb.html"&gt;called A/H3, is responsible for 95% of cases in New York, &lt;/a&gt;according to the state Department of Health’s most recent data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CHOPMZLY7VCUBIQLVIDCQFI75Y"&gt;The strain is somewhat resistant to this year’s vaccine, which was created months before the outbreak, medical experts have reported. And since vaccination rates are down in the United States, more people are vulnerable to catching and spreading the virus, according to the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XBZR3BHLCZDPNB3FLSY3Z2INNM"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.silive.com/news/2022/09/flu-season-2022-when-does-it-start-in-the-united-states.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;The flu, a very contagious respiratory illness&lt;/a&gt;, is caused by influenza viruses that infect the nose, throat, and sometimes the lungs, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TY7VVJJB7REBNOTAXCNP367D2M"&gt;Though it can be mild at times, it can also lead to severe illness, even death in children and vulnerable populations. Two pediatric deaths have so far been reported in New York City.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PUMX7MACJJB2BK2UARKH6I4DEQ"&gt;There were 130 hospitalizations on Staten Island for the week ending Dec. 27, 2025, an increase from the previous week, though the 1,297 cases reported on Staten Island for that week were a drop from the 2,429 reported the week prior, according to data. That’s still more cases than were recorded any single week in the last two flu seasons, the state Health Department said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="54QGLZ3EONC6TOMPBUL4UBPXQY"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.silive.com/news/2026/01/masks-return-to-new-york-hospitals-amid-2026-super-flu-outbreak.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.silive.com/news/2026/01/masks-return-to-new-york-hospitals-amid-2026-super-flu-outbreak.html"&gt;And hospitals in the capital region of the state are now requiring visitors to wear masks, according to recent reports.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FKZTC6TTQJE7RGMWPWFUESSTLU"&gt;The contradiction may be caused by a time delay between infection and serious illness. Hospitalization numbers this week may reflect illness reported in a previous week, doctors said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GH3RLJH5UNC2FPRN2NXSZYEP64"&gt;Also, many with mild symptoms don’t get tested at all, and may develop into serious symptoms, ultimately leading to hospital admission, local medical experts said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KC4CLOOKWRGDRGUYKYWRSH6Y64"&gt;“Children oftentimes are admitted due to dehydration and require IV fluids as part of their symptomatic care,’' Dr. Dolly Sharma, a pediatrician at Northwell Staten Island University Hospital, Ocean Breeze, told the Advance/SILive.com. ”Recent holidays may have also been a factor, as families travel outside of town ... may have still been experiencing mild symptoms but not sought medical attention or been tested."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3JQCIXF2DBGPFJALA2VYH5L5RQ"&gt;And several weeks of peak flu season lie before us, doctors said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WU3DIBY4NFEO3BJGZ2CCE6QQCQ"&gt;Influenza A activity in country usually peaks from January through March, Sharma said. Influenza B infection comes typically after Influenza A and it peaks from March through May, she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="A5T2OL5DEFDEBGJMDO5QNJ43RQ"&gt;Most admissions for viral illnesses in the first three weeks of December were children with Influenza A, said Dr. Ana Mendez, chief of Ambulatory Pediatrics at Richmond University Medical Center in West Brighton. The same is true at RUMC’s Pediatric Clinic, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Symptoms of ‘super flu’ variant&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="W5X5TNC5LZEVBO5SHFQ6L434UQ"&gt;Doctors reported that this year’s most common flu variant presents similarly to last year’s variant, causing mild to severe illness, with one exception. Many patients have described vomiting “yellow bile” as one of the standout symptoms of their flu infection, according to a report on &lt;a href="https://www.healthandme.com/health-news/unique-symptoms-of-flu-in-2026-and-how-long-infection-now-last-article-153402967" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.healthandme.com/health-news/unique-symptoms-of-flu-in-2026-and-how-long-infection-now-last-article-153402967"&gt;Healthandme.com. &lt;/a&gt;Virologists said they believe this may happen because the flu is suppressing appetite more than usual, leading people to vomit when their stomachs are empty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MAAIGZAR2NCIZBZOJJADL6COYY"&gt;Vomiting and diarrhea are more common in children than adults, the CDC reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6VO2NCZUPNEHDLYGNJ4WV2KO3I"&gt;Most common symptoms of the circulating variant include: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="article__unordered-list"&gt;&lt;li id="V4LZ2KUFMVCVJHY4SNKXMMJG5Q"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cough&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="CX3X7JKFXFH5LNMI3RTMEGFQTQ"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sore throat&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="DJJ23BQLPNB3ZLPUL44XKQZJFI"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Runny or stuffy nose&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="QNBLJJVFYBFL7LXRNLPUNJLQJU"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Muscle or body aches&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="ADISOIA5EBGI7M6G2HE3VEWEUI"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Headache&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="SJE5WNOMDRGKBATTVBYSRF7LHU"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fatigue &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JOLYBYAACZF7TAGZWI6AQZZ3GE"&gt;The flu is more dangerous for the pediatric population, as children can experience more GI symptoms, like vomiting and diarrhea, which can lead to dehydration, Sharma said, noting that some children may present with a bacterial pneumonia compounded with the flu virus, which can cause breathing difficulty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6OF3J2657JF25OEOXCZJNG4K7E"&gt;“Severe complications occur in 6% to 20% of hospitalized children, including pneumonia as well as other bacterial co-infections, ICU admission and mechanical ventilation,’' Sharma said. Neurologic complications occur in approximately 8% to 11% of hospitalized children, with influenza, mostly in kids 2 to 4 years of age, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OGUIZ74EVRHV7HK6ZVATWCOTGA"&gt;The CDC recommended flu antiviral treatment as soon as possible in people who are very sick or people at higher risk of developing serious complications because of their age or the presence of certain underlying conditions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5Z7QNINKPZHOXJNYPWRDWNGS2U"&gt;Vaccination is a critical element in prevention, Sharma said, echoing the advice of the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-22" data-gaid="inarticle-22"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:5W6T2AXKZBEIJBEWAKNAOQWHA4" data-fusion-component="5W6T2AXKZBEIJBEWAKNAOQWHA4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:5W6T2AXKZBEIJBEWAKNAOQWHA4" data-fusion-component="5W6T2AXKZBEIJBEWAKNAOQWHA4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-23" data-gaid="inarticle-23"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SILive.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQd00yTHBEZU1vVlNLNVJvUzVPOFRCc2J3NTZKOEY4VDVZcUpWMEZxVmppVGVPS0hrR2Ezd0FnY09TYVp1dW1aZ3NmUGNSd1F3bWRid3BnZk13QXZuU1RNUXpBWTN6MDJ0WTJJbDM1TndYOFJwUDJEVlpoMUl1X2FTTjRXWm5NT2RMdS1QdkJkVldyaUdxa19RSHZneGVpUdIBsgFBVV95cUxOdmYyLXJFcFAtTkNiOF94bW5vVTVVWk1RZi1kUy1GNFVhREQzWGRwZzRSVDlLakl5REx5UXpGRk9wYkZtazJrNVNyeXJ3WF9zN3NvSG02WmdBREI3N3o1TExaVjhYT08yUFNWTTB6SENFbE5IWHJwcGhxYS0zS056RWtuTlktVXY1RzlNZ3ZhRmlQd2g3TE1VZmdsZmVxTF85ZkR5R0hIX0JXSGNsdjFJazdB</guid></item><item><title>从与儿童癌症的斗争中，一个家庭的故事闪耀-皇家公报|百慕大</title><link>https://www.royalgazette.com/health/news/article/20260110/from-a-battle-with-child-cancer-a-familys-story-shines/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-restofcontent"&gt;
						&lt;p class="article_image_caption image_text" data-uuid="c5aa7a8b-075c-5ade-8e7a-57bb3749e955"&gt;Colm and Niamh Homan and their daughter, Aisling, rally behind Eoghan Homan, among this year’s St Baldrick's Ambassadors, who lost his life at age 16 to paediatric cancer (Photograph by Akil Simmons)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;A family’s bitter loss three years ago when 16-year-old &lt;a href="https://www.royalgazette.com/health/news/article/20230315/community-rallies-to-honour-teenagers-strength-bravery-maturity-and-resilience/" id="link-10c8563e85cef3dc3a41e6317a11c89e" target="_blank"&gt;Eoghan Homan&lt;/a&gt; did not survive his medical battle has been carried forward to fundraise for research and shine a light on the complexities of the paediatric cancer experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;Equally importantly, Eoghan’s parents, Colm and Niamh, and his sister, Aisling, can use their opportunity to share their story as a 2026 ambassador family for the global St Baldrick’s Foundation to bring solace to other families facing the same difficult journey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;“We’ll just keep going until there’s more awareness,” Mrs Homan said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;She spoke after her relationship with the Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre caught the attention of St Baldrick’s, a powerful worldwide charitable fundraising force for childhood cancer research with a significant presence in Bermuda.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;Paediatric cancer is rare, often leaving families in Bermuda confronting the diagnosis in a lonely position. Eoghan’s cancer, Ewing sarcoma, was far rarer still.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;Mrs Homan said: “On the island, it’s very difficult, because with paediatric cancer, children are sent away for treatment, and for children that survive — they’re a young family; children have to go back to school and their day-to-day lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;“It’s a busy time, and the island really doesn’t have a support group for paediatric cancer caregivers, parents and survivors. It’s a difficult one.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;Additionally, the drugs powerful enough to fight cancer are highly toxic, she said, complicating the recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;“There are issues with diabetes, heart problems, secondary cancers, and there isn’t a lot of awareness about that either.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;St Baldrick’s announced its&lt;a href="https://blog.stbaldricks.org/meet-the-2026-st-baldricks-ambassadors/" id="link-e87feedbc5c9376aa31e2c00d150ebc0" target="_blank"&gt; five ambassadors&lt;/a&gt; this week. Each child represents a different story in the worldwide community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;Mr Homan said: “Each year, they will pick one child who has passed away. Through the work Niamh has been doing, and the link-up Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre has with St Baldrick’s, they became aware of our story and thought it resonated with what they’re looking to promote.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;Eoghan’s story will be highlighted through the foundation and its social media on February 10.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;Beyond education and fundraising, Mr Homan said it marks “a chance to share our experience of being a family dealing with a child going through a cancer diagnosis, and helping people understand what that means”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;Eoghan was a distinguished runner, and shared the sport with his father.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article_image_caption image_text" data-uuid="c2c885b1-a720-53e9-bebd-96c027325d52"&gt;Eoghan Homan breasts the tape at the finish line of the 2020 Butterfield Front Street Mile, in which he was middle school boys’ champion (File photograph by Blaire Simmons)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;In the years since, Mr Homan has taken his marathon running to &lt;a href="https://www.royalgazette.com/running-triathlon/sport/article/20250426/colm-homan-to-run-second-marathon-in-six-days-for-cancer-research/" id="link-4e9bf9255fefe3bb2c389529ed6396c8" target="_blank"&gt;fundraising heights&lt;/a&gt; in tandem with Boston Children’s Hospital, where Eoghan fought through 14 months of gruelling treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;Mr Homan said: “We had a high level of confidence that he was getting the best care he could, and the best chance that he would have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;“Unfortunately, one in five children diagnosed with cancer will not survive it. Eoghan was one of those five.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;In the marathon next week for the Bermuda Triangle Challenge, father and daughter will run together to fundraise for the Boston Children’s Hospital research fund named in Eoghan’s memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;Mr Homan will run the full marathon, and join Aisling at the halfway mark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;He said: “We should be able to meet up and run the rest of it together — if I can keep up with her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;“It’s been really special that she’s taken to running with passion, having never run more than a mile just five months ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;“It means a lot that she is going to be running for Boston Children’s Hospital and the fund we have named after Eoghan specifically targeting research into Ewing sarcoma and neuroblastoma, which we know are two of the rarer cancers.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;He added: “That’s one of the things St Baldrick’s has done a great job with, identifying projects specifically around those lesser-known cancers, so that there is hope for people that receive one of those diagnoses, and they’re able to work through it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;Mr Homan said: “I think cancer should be almost redefined. There are so many that are totally treatable and it’s not the end of your life. Others are extremely severe.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;St Baldrick’s will proceed with its signature head-shaving fundraiser in March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;In the meantime, Eoghan’s family join the other work connected with the movement — sharing the lessons of their experience and joining the broader support network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__body"&gt;“It’s more than the fundraising,” Mrs Homan said. “It’s the awareness.”&lt;/p&gt;						
					&lt;/div&gt;
					
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Royal Gazette | Bermuda</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:58:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxONlU0MzdYeEJKQWJnSlNxVFJKVEVwQ1NJeWY0WENVOVY3ZzFtT3hnS2JjUVBGNXdyVDBQc01jMTUzZEd3eUc2cF9Ta05vbXRoTTFFek00N0hSTXFjOEgyY1lzdjZDZXhaLXVzSkZDTkpLSFNWcjBMbm0wYTc3LXlTTGJKUDdEZ1JCWGpUQlU4SnNjbHlRbnVOWWxYc25laDVxSWNfZDZ5QVJpMFdxdGF5WXBTdw</guid></item><item><title>脱离GLP-1s的人正在经历突然和可怕的饥饿-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/go-off-glp-1s-sudden-hunger</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;Glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1) receptor agonist drugs, like the popular weight-loss jabs Wegovy and Ozempic, have proven to be immensely effective. Beyond allowing patients to significantly reduce their weight, they’ve been shown to have a &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/glp-1-ozempic-benefits-map"&gt;constellation of other health benefits&lt;/a&gt;, like &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/ozempic-delays-aging-scientist-claims"&gt;lowering the risk of heart disease&lt;/a&gt; and staving off &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/semaglutide-diabetic-kidney-disease"&gt;diabetic kidney disease&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/doctors-surprised-patients-semaglutide-cured-other-conditions"&gt;Parkinson’s&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/ozempic-lowered-alzheimers-risk"&gt;Alzheimer’s&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;But the harsh reality of &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/health-medicine/glp1-weight-gain"&gt;what happens when monthly injections stop&lt;/a&gt; is raising a grim wrinkle: will patients ever be able to &lt;em&gt;stop&lt;/em&gt; taking these extremely expensive drugs, or are they signing onto a lifetime habit they won’t be able to break without suffering severe consequences?&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/392/bmj-2025-085304" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;new study&lt;/a&gt; led by researchers at the University of Oxford, which reviewed 37 existing weight loss medication studies involving over 9,000 participants, has found that patients who stopped taking GLP-1 weight-loss medications regained weight four times as fast as those who used alternative behavioral programs, like diets and physical activity.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;On average, participants returned to their original weight just 1.7 years after stopping the medication. Patients who went off the drugs &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cn98pdpyjz5o" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;told the &lt;em&gt;BBC&lt;/em&gt; last month&lt;/a&gt; that the hunger came roaring back.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“It was like something opened up in my mind and said: ‘Eat everything, go on, you deserve it because you haven’t eaten anything for so long,'” Tanya Hall, who has been on and off GLP-1 injections, told the broadcaster at the time, adding that she felt “completely horrified” by the amount of food she was consuming after just a couple of days.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Worse yet, the Oxford-led research team found that the secondary health benefits of the drugs dissipated as well. They observed that health markers, such as blood pressure and cholesterol, bounced back to original levels within an average of 1.4 years.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“This review found that cessation of [weight management medications] is followed by rapid weight regain and reversal of beneficial effects on cardiometabolic markers,” the researchers wrote. “These findings suggest caution in short-term use of these drugs without a more comprehensive approach to weight management.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The researchers suggest that the drugs alone don’t form lasting lifestyle changes that persist after you stop taking them.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“This faster regain could be because people using drugs don’t need to consciously practise changing their diet to lose weight, so when they stop taking the medication, they might not have developed the practical strategies that could help them keep it off,” said senior author and Oxford associate professor Dimitrios Koutoukidis in an &lt;a href="https://www.ox.ac.uk/news/2026-01-08-new-study-finds-stopping-weight-loss-drugs-linked-faster-regain-ending-diet" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;official statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The scientists are now calling for a more careful approach.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“These medicines are transforming obesity treatment and can achieve important weight loss,” said lead author and University of Oxford research scientist Sam West in the statement. “However, our research shows that people tend to regain weight rapidly after stopping — faster than we see with behavioral programs.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;However, that doesn’t mean GLP-1 drugs aren’t still astonishingly effective.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“This isn’t a failing of the medicines — it reflects the nature of obesity as a chronic, relapsing condition,” West added. “It sounds a cautionary note for short-term use without a more comprehensive approach to long-term weight management, and highlights the importance of primary prevention.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Others advocate for a more holistic prescription model.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Weight loss drugs can be effective tools for managing weight and type 2 diabetes risk — but this research reinforces that they are not a quick fix,” Diabetes UK research communications lead Faye Riley &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2026/jan/07/weight-loss-jabs-regain-two-years-health-study" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;told &lt;em&gt;The Guardian&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. “They need to be prescribed appropriately, with tailored wraparound support alongside them, to ensure people can fully benefit and maintain weight loss for as long as possible when they stop taking the medication.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on GLP-1s:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/health-medicine/glp1-weight-gain"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Something Grim Is Happening to People Who Go Off GLP-1s&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE1DLVBoM1NOeHg0WVhMdG9hOEl3QThORnJrTlJCWnpaQVN1TjN0X2xZcTdVWkRGV0JhQU1SUHV3d2UzUjYtZTRQWDUwak5rLWdmYzZZZ3g0X1lWaUZKa1U5WlZ3bXJDQTZuSWZHQXlvTVFxZw</guid></item></channel></rss>