<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>小RFK表示，美国应该在疫苗方面将目光投向欧洲。这可能意味着美国人会越来越少。- Politico</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2025/12/25/rfk-jr-europe-on-vaccine-schedule-00704242</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Politico</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQeUxkRDU5RmY1LWpuSHBndmxwOWRzVE50RHFpQk8zbXhyZXBBSU9YYVlkUktGSkpCeEgzeTU4TTJZT3ZzOE5fcEZaNnBJUmlZZUdxWHZnSkRlOHR3LU93ZEhmY3hrd1NhTlJScXJoNnA5U0FST0xLYXRWUEMwVnA3SmVCZ1RHMDh2clBJ</guid></item><item><title>专家揭示假日菜肴会增加您患癌症的风险-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15307625/holiday-foods-colon-cancer-bacteria.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The holidays are a time for coming together with family, tearing open presents and, of course, eating heaps of hearty, delicious food. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;However, health experts warn that some of your festive favorites may come with a side of deadly consequences&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Processed meats, fried foods and sugary desserts have all been shown to induce harmful inflammation and damage DNA in the colon - potentially leading to cancer - over extended periods of time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Expert warnings come as colorectal &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-2b763af0-dac0-11f0-8942-5515e5e6263b"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; rates have been rising steadily among adults under the age of 55 throughout the past decade, according to recent studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Advanced-stage diagnoses in this younger population are also increasing, often having spread to other organs, making the cancer harder to treat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;But, experts have said it's not just potential future health risks to worry about - some foods put you in immediate danger of ingesting deadly bacteria.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The stars of the holiday table - such ham, certain side dishes and even classic cocktails - could be breeding grounds for &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15324801/boars-head-deli-products-recalled-listeria.html"&gt;bacteria that infect millions of Americans every year&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To lower the risk of cancer and foodborne illnesses, doctors and food safety experts have told the Daily Mail which foods to approach with a little extra caution - and which to avoid entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;As families prepare for festive gatherings, health experts warn that certain foods can influence long-term colorectal cancer risk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Turkey, ham and processed meats&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Elaine Siu, a dietitian and supervisor of clinical nutrition services at City of Hope in California, told the Daily Mail that processed meats like ham, bacon and sausage are classified by the World Health Organization (WHO) as Group 1 carcinogens, meaning there is strong evidence they can cause cancer in humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She pointed&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15266129/bacon-kill-you-nitrate-processed-meat-cancers.html"&gt; to research&lt;/a&gt; showing that just 50g per day (about two slices of bacon or one hot dog) can increase colorectal cancer risk by 18 percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One of the biggest problems is that processed meats are packed with preservatives, Dr Krushangi Patel, a medical oncologist also at City of Hope, told the Daily Mail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Those common additives include sodium nitrite (used to preserve color and prevent bacterial growth), sodium erythorbate and ascorbate (antioxidants to stabilize color and flavor) and sodium phosphate (used to retain moisture and improve texture).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These meats are generally high in sodium, which can raise blood pressure and contribute to gastric cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The combination of preservatives, sodium levels and processing at high temperatures can also play a role in disrupting the gut microbiome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Raw turkey can contain salmonella Campylobacter, which can lead to bloody diarrhea, stomach cramps and vomiting (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Suneel Kamath, a gastrointestinal oncologist at the Cleveland Clinic in Ohio, said that disruption - which damages beneficial bacteria - 'makes the colon more prone to forming cancer cells.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As for food safety, turkey and ham must be prepared correctly to eliminate illness-causing bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ham, for instance, can carry salmonella, one of the leading causes of food poisoning in the US. Sickening 1.3 million Americans every year, the bacteria leads to bloody diarrhea, severe stomach cramps, vomiting and loss of appetite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While most people recover on their own or have no symptoms, the bacteria can be especially dangerous to young children and the elderly, both of whom have weakened immune systems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 420 Americans die from salmonella every year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Darin Detwiler, food safety expert at Northeastern University in Boston, told the Daily Mail that raw ham also contains Campylobacter, which sickens 1.5 million people in the US annually and causes fever, stomach cramps and diarrhea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'These bacteria thrive in undercooked meat, particularly in thick areas near the bone,' he said. 'Improper thawing, such as leaving a frozen bird on the kitchen counter, can also give bacteria a chance to multiply.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Detwiler, who is also a former advisor to the &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/fda/index.html" id="mol-743b40d0-d793-11f0-b88c-e72179d70611"&gt;FDA&lt;/a&gt; and US Department of Agriculture (USDA), warns those cooking a turkey or ham against leaving it on the counter to defrost, as it can fall into the 'danger zone' of temperatures, between 40F and 140F.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Always thaw meat in the refrigerator,' he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Sugary cocktails may raise the risk of colon cancer, experts warn. Some eggnog often uses raw eggs, which contain salmonella (stock image of eggnog)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Alcoholic and sugary drinks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many people are still unaware that alcohol can cause cancer, said Kamath, who pointed out that acetaldehyde, a toxic byproduct of alcohol metabolism, can damage DNA and trigger mutations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Holiday celebrators should also note, according to Siu, that alcohol is classified by the WHO as a Group 1 carcinogen and is a known risk factor for colorectal cancer, even at moderate levels. She noted that sugary and ultra-processed cocktails such as eggnog are common holiday indulgences that have been linked to increased colorectal cancer risk when consumed in excess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10764622/"&gt;2023 meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; of 17 studies found that drinking more sugar-sweetened beverages was associated with a 17 percent higher risk of colorectal cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So, she advised staying within the recommended limits during the festive season: no more than one drink per day for women and no more than two drinks per day for men. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Frequent holiday drinking can also disrupt sleep, irritate the digestive tract, weaken the immune system and increase inflammation, placing extra stress on the body, Dasgupta added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;While store-bought eggnog is pasteurized to kill bacteria, homemade, traditional versions are often made with raw eggs, which carry salmonella. While alcohol &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;added to the drink can help kill bacteria by causing bacterial molecules to break down, it doesn't completely eliminate the risk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Detwiler suggested sticking with the store-bought beverage, but warned drinkers against letting it sit out in a serving container for hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The USDA recommends pasteurizing or heating eggnog to at least 160F to kill off bacteria before consuming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Cranberry sauce runs the risk of being contaminated with bacteria if it comes into contact with raw meat (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Cranberry sauce and other side dishes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mashed potatoes, mac and cheese and green bean casserole are often key players in holiday dinners. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While these 'are typically safe when freshly cooked,' they tend to be left out at room temperature for long periods of time while other dishes finish cooking or so guests can grab additional servings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;That's when the problems can arise, Detwiler told the Daily Mail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Gravy is particularly risky because it provides an ideal environment for Clostridium perfringens, a bacterium that can cause gastrointestinal illness if food is not kept hot or cooled quickly,' he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Detwiler added that side dishes made with milk, butter or cream support the growth of listeria if left out. The USDA recommends leaving dishes out for no longer than two hours at a time so temperatures do not dip into the 'danger zone.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cranberry sauce is naturally acidic and high in sugar, which helps inhibit bacterial growth. The low pH in highly acidic foods interferes with bacteria's cellular processes and stops them from multiplying. Sugar reduces the amount of water available in food, which dehydrates bacteria and stops it from growing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, cranberry sauce 'isn't entirely risk free,' Detwiler said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'If it's made from scratch and prepared on surfaces contaminated by raw meat or poultry, cross-contamination becomes a concern.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Fried foods&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Patel pointed out that while fried holiday favorites, such as doughnuts, fritters and crispy appetizers, are not harmful when enjoyed occasionally, a diet consistently high in fried foods has been linked to increased risk of colorectal cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One concern is that f&lt;span&gt;rying foods at high temperatures can produce compounds like acrylamides and advanced glycation end products (AGEs), which may increase cancer risk over time. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Acrylamides can be converted in the body to substances that damage DNA, potentially causing mutations that trigger cancer. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;AGEs, on the other hand, promote oxidative stress and chronic inflammation, and activate pathways that encourage cell growth, creating an environment favorable to tumor development. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Kamath noted that these foods also fall under the umbrella of ultra-processed products (UPFs), a category increasingly tied to immune and microbiome disruption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;UPFs are foods that are highly processed and industrially formulated. Additionally, in contrast to whole foods, UPFs often contain additives, emulsifiers, preservatives, sweeteners and refined ingredients that disrupt the gut microbiome, promote chronic inflammation and contribute to tumor development in the colon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Research over the past decade has linked high consumption of UPFs to increased colorectal cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Traditionally fried holiday foods, however, can be made healthier by baking or air-frying instead of deep-frying, which reduces harmful compounds and excess fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:35:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNSUpDVU5SZnY1c3UwelI2eExZM3Vhd0Z2NEJxWnY0bW55bHNsRDJOTVJfR1JGVG5Ga0VIOHlxekdfTEwyY0hHSWs2N3FIa2lQUm5Ca0lMbmZ3dXR4UWl5ajdVcU9XTFpELTd0eENmdVJzb01ZemlFeE5mSFNCZFFpOWRTRktBUGNoZzg5bnE1cmJEVUpMc2Yw</guid></item><item><title>心理学家利用特定的心态来保持积极的态度，研究结果- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/psychologists-tap-into-a-specific-mindset-to-stay-positive-study-finds</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxNck56OU1iRzJYY2FxdEtYRWxEM3YtM01FdzU5TmVaVXpIaEdYVE1ZbUdwVXI2LW1UZXVnTVZFV0c2MWFoRVVONmFDZFVXcVhqWXB0WmpOZmRGUzhaVzNKV2J6UGtSX3M3cGpPTS1aLU1aRmxjeDNkZklPY0JtcjV5TnkzYzNjYzZqLVFyYmE2VDJYdG5Iaml6UzFSbEhqUjhk?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Psychologists Tap Into a Specific Mindset to Stay Positive, Study Finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ScienceAlert&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxPVTBRQVlPdmpwaEswVUc1WGItU0I3alg2OHZQcjFkZnctRjNpLXFXV2VxN0ZTNzM0MmRtZzhFcE5qZ1dQRDdkS09rbXJ3WWpFYU9OTnY5QXVYekgxSkxrV1lyNHk5MFVoOGp2R1E0Q3YwSVJkTjNETndnWjg3MUp5QWNNMzY3VDZkUHlKUHAxS0RpRHR6WVR6d0V0ODhDSTh5SEptd2swSEw2WWJQVC1wT9IBtgFBVV95cUxQLTV4a19DRVFodVRXbDVmdUpGVlI5SThsSXlYVHdWcnFtQVNNYzlUejZJc0NDOFQzTkU2Z2UwZUxfaGROSkhiYXpZeUJiVEhRTHdCTlZnWFlzMHJBeG9waVcwVWI3U21sWWJRVThYWVFoSS05Z25xMGhvRTJpLWZkQ1pVYjJBNXRNZzlQeTNfd180NkhQb1VGMDV5cjJJaTJUZFI0dE9QWFQ5eW0yWUFBZ01LZERQdw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;The True Art of Wellbeing: A Mindset Shift Beyond Positivity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Devdiscourse&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNeFhiWG0yT0F3MUVuUU80T3p1NTc0bXJ0TTMweldHTE80SzBlVFZuR3VvZEw4NV8xLWthWXJhNVROWTZINWhTU3RzZU5lc3FkaU9HZEZKMEszQk9EdEl1Y3pQVlM5eTRPeFBmb1RxbEFLOEZWSmgyWXlCYS1OY1IwZGVTSE1UMFl6UzFF?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Positive psychology experts don't follow their own advice. What they actually do may be the key to well-being&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Medical Xpress&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:02:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxNck56OU1iRzJYY2FxdEtYRWxEM3YtM01FdzU5TmVaVXpIaEdYVE1ZbUdwVXI2LW1UZXVnTVZFV0c2MWFoRVVONmFDZFVXcVhqWXB0WmpOZmRGUzhaVzNKV2J6UGtSX3M3cGpPTS1aLU1aRmxjeDNkZklPY0JtcjV5TnkzYzNjYzZqLVFyYmE2VDJYdG5Iaml6UzFSbEhqUjhk</guid></item><item><title>尊敬的医生： 65岁以上的人应该多久接种一次RSV疫苗？ - OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/advice/2025/12/dear-doctor-how-often-should-people-older-than-65-get-the-rsv-vaccination.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OWYZPM2A4RGIJB672SNCYX32DM"&gt;DEAR DR. ROACH: My husband and I are over 65. We got the respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) vaccinations two years ago. I’m reading mixed reports on how often we should be getting them. -- N.W.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZEJTBKFZDBFZHBBNWIYD5PV7HE"&gt;ANSWER: Along with influenza and COVID, RSV is yet another virus that causes respiratory disease in adults -- one that is especially dangerous for young children and older adults. It is recommended to be discussed for those who are over the age of 60.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3NINZBBJ6RAWPNC4B4VZJYGONY"&gt;People younger than 60 with moderate to severe immune system diseases, such as those that deal with an organ (especially lung) or a stem-cell transplant, should also consider vaccination. I recommend the vaccine to all adults over 75 and to those over 60 who have risk factors such as chronic heart or lung disease, complicated diabetes, or hemodialysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KLOLW5IA55HGTBCZH7Q65B5L6M"&gt;At the current time, booster doses of the RSV vaccine are not recommended. This may change; although there is evidence that immunity wanes after a year, repeat doses were not found to be helpful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI" data-fusion-component="CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI" data-fusion-component="CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KVF24K3KTZDAFKOSBLDSBTYRO4"&gt;DEAR DR. ROACH: When I was about 6 years old in the early ’40s, my 16-year-old brother was sent to a sanitarium for tuberculosis patients. He was there for 18 months and was a survivor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ARJQBPK52NCF3EKSXI3NJH6XSE"&gt;During this period of time, we (the family) went regularly for chest X-rays and some kind of test that involved a needle in my forearm. Why aren’t X-rays done today -- not to detect tuberculosis but to look for cancer? CT scans are expensive and sometimes involve a long wait, so why not do a simple X-ray for starters? And then if they see something, perhaps they can do a CT scan? -- N.C.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SLKL5RRCMJFI5E7NFDBF7KV73I"&gt;ANSWER: Many physicians and scientists at Johns Hopkins, Memorial Sloan-Kettering, and other first-rate institutions have sought to answer the question of whether annual chest X-rays led to a reduction in the risk of dying from lung cancer. But unfortunately, the consensus of opinion is that chest X-rays do not lead to an improvement in lung cancer mortality. There were tens of thousands of participants in these studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NBWMU2K4B5C65EQ4LGB7VJGRJU"&gt;You are also right to think that a CT scan might be more useful. Studies have shown that for a subset of people who are at a high risk, screening with a CT scan does lead to a reduction in lung cancer deaths. Specifically, lung cancer screening should be considered for people between the ages of 50-80 (Medicare will pay up to age 77) who are in generally good health; those who have smoked at least 20 “pack years” (such as a pack a day for 20 years, two packs a day for 10 years, or a half pack a day for 40 years); and those who currently smoke or have quit within the past 15 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SALM4LIHEBGN3ANNCAWUPIDQMU"&gt;The benefit from lung cancer screening is modest; it takes about 250 people to be screened annually for three years to prevent one lung cancer death. Still, this is significant, and I do discuss lung cancer screening with my eligible patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3UTZXFHD7VFW7M3GWVTCS4GIU4"&gt;Finally, the best way by far to prevent lung cancer is to quit smoking as soon as possible. If you are a smoker, your doctor has many ways to help you quit. Calling a quit line, such as 800-QUIT-NOW, will connect you with your state service. You can also text QUITNOW to 333888, and there are web-based programs such as Smokefree.gov and apps like quitSTART from the National CANCER Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JYP7VFMJNFGDBPE7SIG4MUGEHI"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Dr. Roach regrets that he is unable to answer individual letters, but will incorporate them in the column whenever possible. Readers may email questions to &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:ToYourGoodHealth@med.cornell.edu"&gt;&lt;i&gt;ToYourGoodHealth@med.cornell.edu&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; or send mail to 628 Virginia Dr., Orlando, FL 32803.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AUMP2LSRGJBWVFXGMISV4TEA2E"&gt;&lt;i&gt;(c) 2022 North America Syndicate Inc.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="U7EQ3GITRJHTXMWUUBM53ZNYZM"&gt;&lt;i&gt;All Rights Reserved&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxQNlRlWC1UeWJSbjV2VEFkMEpYOS14YS1yWGljbjEyZ0pqbVdiMTIxNFFrek1IbzAyQ0x5a2V3VTB2MXl4Um1pSVlaZ19JQWdvUHc0MWs3UmV2N00tbUFoT0FBaElUUWdOTDZYQWtQSk1oTzVtRFhVR2g2S1FEdUNkb1B5Z2xRdmpqZ2VZZnc3Mm9lcnVsU09pdmxvUDZseHZnbGo4cXk0V3BfYkR4dURnbWVNV2FIQWU1QzZ0atIB0AFBVV95cUxPbjFyR29PbXVMQ0VTeEY1ZXQ5dnZTSU1EVlJtcHNWSUhza3gtYVZtekRWRC1FdjNKQkFORDB1XzE5Q1FuY2ZNdVlreUFhaUNsekkyOE5EY1RNZ25iT2ItaE03VERpVnZTT1ZaeVlDcEY0cjZUYW1iN3hneEF6ZWFZTWw0NXlxaE9ZRi1uOUU1bFl6UVVrSTNGaTh6cXJEZmk3dWZiRndVblAwb3p5cVpZbFl1emtmWndWWFNHNGNxNmEtOVp3UG0xWHprTHhiZEg2</guid></item><item><title>血液测试可以预测谁最容易患上常见遗传性心脏病--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/dec/25/blood-test-predict-risk-inherited-heart-condition-hypertrophic-cardiomyopathy</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Scientists are developing a simple blood test to predict who is most at risk from the world’s most common inherited heart condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Millions of people worldwide have hypertrophic cardiomyopathy (HCM), a disease of the heart muscle where the wall of the heart becomes thickened. It is caused by a change in one or more genes and mostly passed on through families.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some feel fine most of the time and have few or no symptoms. But others can suffer complications, such as heart failure and abnormal heart rhythms, which can lead to a cardiac arrest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The problem is there is no cure. Doctors also &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/jan/08/outdated-guidelines-mean-doctors-failing-to-spot-heart-condition-in-women" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;do not know which patients&lt;/a&gt; with the genetic condition are most at risk from deadly complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But now a team of scientists from universities including Harvard and Oxford have found a way to forecast risk for people living with HCM.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The blood test could identify those patients most in danger of complications, enabling them to be monitored more closely or receive life-saving treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In a landmark study, the team measured the levels of a protein, N-terminal Pro-B-type natriuretic peptide (NT-Pro-BNP), in the blood of 700 HCM patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;NT-Pro-BNP is released by the heart as part of normal pumping. But high levels are a sign the heart is working too hard. Those with the highest levels had poorer blood flow, more scar tissue and changes in their heart which could lead to atrial fibrillation or heart failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A blood test measuring NT-Pro-BNP could transform the care of millions of people with the world’s most common inherited heart condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The study leader, Prof Carolyn Ho, the medical director of the cardiovascular genetics centre at Harvard medical school, said the test could help “target the right therapies to the right patients at the right time”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;She added: “Continued studies on blood biomarkers will lead to better understanding of HCM so that, in future, we can offer our patients a blood test to identify who is at high versus low risk of experiencing serious consequences of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“People with the highest risk could be targeted for potentially life-saving treatments as they stand to receive the greatest benefit, while those at lowest risk could avoid unnecessary treatment.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Lara Johnson, 34, from Southampton in the UK, is one of many who could benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="3eeff211-4533-46b2-bfc2-0e18861b2e1f" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":13,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Parasite cleanses: why are so many people obsessed with intestinal worms?","elementId":"3eeff211-4533-46b2-bfc2-0e18861b2e1f","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2025/dec/09/parasite-cleanses-people-obsessed-intestinal-worms"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Eight years ago, she began experiencing breathlessness and fatigue. After being referred by her GP for hospital tests, she was diagnosed with HCM. Several relatives on her father’s side were subsequently also diagnosed with the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“One of the hardest parts of living with HCM is the constant uncertainty, never knowing what might change next,” Johnson said. “A simple blood test, which could help identify future risks earlier, would take away so much of that anxiety.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;She added: “It could give people like me a chance to prepare and adjust our lifestyles as needed, and help us to feel more in control. That kind of clarity wouldn’t only help me, it would make a world of difference for my whole family.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Bryan Williams, the chief scientific and medical officer of the British Heart Foundation, which funded the research, said the test “could benefit patients around the world”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“After a diagnosis of HCM, patients and their families want to know what the future holds. This study shows that measuring various proteins circulating in the blood could help predict how the heart is functioning and future risk of complications from heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This new method may also provide insights in the evolution of the structure and function of the heart in people with HCM that could point to new ways of treating this condition to reduce future risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxPUlppcm1LVVd3MDZPbEtJd25TX3Y4Z2NwdDh2d3RWcTJhLTNBN3BJaHAtX3BlMUxOdDVfSkF3Vlk1TG1NcU1JVDVWRUNkU183VFJMc0M0SEJZQWJmRm5HczA3OTFzY3pmNGJxaEtqOVcxeXpRSW5QS255QUhJODhKdkNYNV9mNWxhdTZfNl9Gai0tQ1VQQVRUOG9kTlVjNDN6ckhYQnJyMjUxcncyNkp6YWpISXR3QlNkN29jRlNuelZWRzQ</guid></item><item><title>如果您正在感受这11件事，您可能会陷入生存模式- YourTango</title><link>https://www.yourtango.com/self/feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anxiety and stress are a normal, though bothersome, part of life for many people. But when a person is stuck in "survival mode," a non-stop cycle of fight or flight, it has repercussions on our mental and physical health. According to &lt;a href="https://drgiamarson.com/the-negative-impact-of-prolonged-survival-mode-what-can-you-do-to-thrive/" rel="nofollow"&gt;psychologist Dr. Gia Marson&lt;/a&gt;, "Stressful stimuli cause a physiological and psychological response called survival mode. This... involves the release of stress hormones and the activation of our stress-response systems. Our mind and body become focused on combating danger."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though survival mode is a defense mechanism meant to protect against imminent threats, modern stressors like school, work, and family can trap people in a vicious state of survival. Whether it's suffering from exhaustion or feeling unable to focus, if you're feeling these things, you're probably stuck in survival mode. So, it's crucial to identify these signs to prevent further turmoil&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;If you're feeling these 11 things, you're probably stuck in survival mode&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Everything feels urgent&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-everything-urgent.png" alt="woman looking at watch with a sense of urgency" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode everything feels urgent" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Andrii Iemelianenko | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://www.humnutrition.com/blog/how-to-get-out-of-survival-mode/" rel="nofollow"&gt;psychotherapist Kiara Luna&lt;/a&gt;, a person may be experiencing survival mode if they have an urgent sense to take care of specific tasks right away. "We often get into this state where we feel a sense of urgency over non-urgent items because we're operating from fear, anxiety, and even anger. Those emotions are sending a signal to our brain that we must act now," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This heightened state puts immense strain on our mental and emotional well-being, which can lead us to operate in survival mode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/someone-stops-doing-these-things-home-theyre-low-key-struggling"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If Someone Stops Doing These 11 Things In Their Home, They're Low-Key Struggling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. You're always tired&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-always-tired.png" alt="extremely tired woman yawning" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode always tired" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;MAYA LAB | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part of the process of preparing our bodies for survival mode includes extending more energy than usual. Our bodies do this &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/staying-healthy/understanding-the-stress-response" rel="nofollow"&gt;by raising our cortisol levels&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While this is useful for a short duration of time, prolonged use tires our body, depleting our energy sources close to zero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/subtle-signs-not-just-stressed-completely-exhausted-emotionally"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;15 Subtle Signs You're Not Just Stressed, You're Completely Exhausted Emotionally&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. You anger easily&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-anger-easily.png" alt="angry woman yelling" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode anger easily" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Krakenimages.com | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're feeling anger at the slightest things, you're probably stuck in survival mode. Maybe your partner loaded the dishwasher the "wrong" way or another car cuts you off in traffic. And it's &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/straightforward-signs-stress-no-longer-normal-no-matter-how-much-you-deny-it"&gt;not just a one-off — this happens every day&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your partner makes you roasted garlic chicken instead of plain roasted chicken? Irritated. Your children say one word to you after you get home from a long day of work? Irritated. The server gives you BBQ chicken wings instead of buffalo chicken wings? Irritated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://hbr.org/2022/01/what-to-do-when-youre-stuck-in-the-survival-zone" rel="nofollow"&gt;author Tony Schwartz&lt;/a&gt; pointed out, "The survival zone is when your energy is high, but negative. When we feel threatened or devalued, control of our nervous system shifts from the prefrontal cortex to the sympathetic nervous system and we move into fight-or-flight mode. People in this zone are anxious, impatient, irritable, fearful, and self-critical."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/subtle-signs-woman-who-has-been-through-lot-life-according-research"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Subtle Signs Of A Woman Who Has Been Through A Lot In Life, According To Research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4. Nothing feels good enough&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-nothing-feels-good-enough.png" alt="sad stressed man not feeling good enough" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode nothing feels good enough" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;DedMityay | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not being able to enjoy the activities you once loved is a gut-wrenching experience, but you can't help it. Nothing ever feels good enough. The book you just read is trash, the date your partner took you on was horrendous, and that good grade you got on your paper could have been better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're experiencing this feeling every day, you're likely in survival mode. Because even the tiniest accomplishments just aren't enough for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/small-things-you-can-do-morning-so-you-dont-want-get-back-bed-and-hide"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Small Things You Can Do In The Morning So You Don't Want To Get Back In Bed And Hide&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;5. No day feels like a good day&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-no-day-good-day.png" alt="stressed man in survival mode having a bad day" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode no day feels like a good day" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;wavebreakmedia | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you find yourself constantly feeling that no day is a good day, this could be a sign of multiple underlying mental health issues. While &lt;a href="https://drbrookeweinstein.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;occupational therapist Dr. Brooke Weinstein&lt;/a&gt; identifies this as a sign of survival mode, it's crucial to delve deeper into the root cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's important to highlight that this emotional state aligns with other mental health issues beyond survival mode, making it essential to seek professional guidance to tackle the problem more effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/phrases-people-use-to-pretend-theyre-fine-when-theyre-absolutely-not"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10 Phrases People Use To Pretend They're Fine When They're Absolutely Not&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;6. You wake up stressed&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-wake-up-stressed.png" alt="woman sitting up in bed feeling stressed" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode wake up stressed" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;yourphotopie | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://acceleratedresolutiontherapy.com/are-you-in-survival-mode/" rel="nofollow"&gt;experts from Accelerated Resolution Therapy&lt;/a&gt;, "Stress becomes chronic when a person experiences frequent stress-producing stimuli without a return to comfortable normalcy in between stressors. As a result, the body and mind cannot return to a rested state. Individuals experiencing chronic stress are hypervigilant, physically tense and 'on edge,' unable to return to a deepened, relaxed state required for recovery," they explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health/strange-signals-body-sends-when-under-too-much-stress"&gt;stress can create immense problems&lt;/a&gt; such as anxiety, depression, and sleeping disorders, as well as digestive issues, sweating, headaches, dizziness, and weight fluctuations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/reasons-people-who-are-always-tired-can-never-fall-asleep-usually-have"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People Who Are Always Tired But Can Never Fall Asleep Usually Have These 11 Reasons&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;7. You feel anxious for no reason&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-anxious-no-reason.png" alt="woman holding chest feeling anxious for no reason" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode anxious for no reason" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;PeopleImages | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have you been anxious a lot lately? For instance, your friends want to go out to a nice restaurant and you're so anxious because you don't know what to wear. Or maybe you're cooking a nice dinner for your partner but you're anxious because what happens if they don't like it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're feeling anxious and unsure of why, &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/subtle-warning-signs-someone-in-survival-mode-according-research"&gt;you're probably stuck in survival mode&lt;/a&gt;. Lately, you may be feeling on edge. You wake up anxious, get dressed anxious, and you're constantly working feeling anxious. No matter what, your heart feels as if it's going to fall out of your chest every single day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/signs-youre-more-anxious-than-average-person"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10 Signs You're More Anxious Than The Average Person, According To Psychology&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;8. You find yourself zoning out and unable to focus&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-zoning-out-unable-focus.png" alt="woman zoning out outside unable to focus" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode zoning out unable to focus" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Twinsterphoto | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether it's in a meeting or while you're in a conversation with someone, you can't seem to pay attention. Pinching yourself doesn't work and rubbing your eyes somehow makes it worse. According to &lt;a href="https://www.newswise.com/articles/the-mental-fatigue-you-feel-is-called-cognitive-dulling-and-you-are-not-alone-if-you-are-experiencing-it" rel="nofollow"&gt;licensed psychologist and assistant professor Jennifer Bahrman&lt;/a&gt;, cognitive dulling is "a form of mental fatigue that l&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/psychology-tools-stop-zoning-out-stress-dissociate"&gt;eads to difficulty concentrating&lt;/a&gt;, decreased productivity, and a decline in emotional and mental health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This can occur due to our bodies constantly living in survival mode. Cognitive dulling can cause issues with our productivity and a decline in our mental and physical health, which, in the long run, can affect both our personal and professional lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/psychology-tools-stop-zoning-out-stress-dissociate"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;According To Psychology, 5 Simple Tools Can Stop Zoning Out When Stress Makes You Dissociate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;9. You feel overwhelmed&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-overwhelmed.png" alt="overwhelmed stressed man sitting at home" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode feel overwhelmed" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;voronaman | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can be hard to focus on important tasks when you're constantly in fight or flight, and your sense of uncertainty can quickly escalate into powerful emotions. This may &lt;a href="https://www.newportinstitute.com/resources/mental-health/feeling-overwhelmed/" rel="nofollow"&gt;lead to forgetfulness, confusion, and withdrawal&lt;/a&gt;. Over time these can snowball into bigger issues such as depression and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, if you're feeling these things, you're probably stuck in survival mode. And if that isn't bad enough, being overwhelmed on a daily basis &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2732004/" rel="nofollow"&gt;can be a catalyst for dependency issues&lt;/a&gt; and many other disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/if-youve-stopped-enjoying-these-things-its-sign-youre-more-burned-out-you-think"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If You've Stopped Enjoying These 11 Things, It's A Sign You're More Burned Out Than You Think&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;10. You engage in destructive behaviors&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-destructive-behaviors.png" alt="woman engaging in destructive behaviors being unproductive" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode engage in destructive behaviors" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Stokkete | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of us have engaged in destructive behaviors at some point, whether it was throwing a pillow or breaking up an otherwise healthy relationship. However, when experiencing constant stress, our coping mechanisms tend to be a bit more extreme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overeating and dependency issues are just some of the &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/subtle-signs-someone-path-of-self-destruction"&gt;many dangerous destructive behaviors we engage in&lt;/a&gt; when under constant stress. If you're experiencing these problems, it's essential to seek out professional help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/habits-people-need-slow-down"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10 Worrisome Habits Of People Who Need To Slow Down, According To Psychology&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;11. You're easily startled&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-easily-startled.png" alt="startled woman covering her mouth" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode easily startled" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Anatoliy Karlyuk | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you the type of person who is easily startled when someone taps you on the shoulder and greets you? Do you jump out of your skin when you hear an unexpectedly loud noise? Startling easily is biologically programmed into us when we are in survival mode in order to keep us safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Startling easily in this way means your nervous system is working in overdrive, which can cause exaggerated reactions. Eventually, however, this leads to exhaustion from hypervigilance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/unhappy-people-almost-always-do-these-things-before-leaving-house"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unhappy People Almost Always Do These 11 Things Before Leaving The House&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Marielisa Reyes is a writer with a bachelor's degree in psychology who covers self-help, relationships, career, family, and astrology topics.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="midcat-most-popular"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Related Stories From YourTango:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="rc-widget-c743d1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>YourTango</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:35:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxNbGZNTHEwemdnUlJ5emlRLXhTYkk0SDBjQm4zQ2JNMHprUTNtUjE0amFIOFpuM0JRc2hOZkhqOGRiNFBSVGpQZnlvX0VOcDJFOFR3RnRlVW5IT3NJS013UkJsOTVyOWN0VXNYMGpnNWJxV1hHcmo1TlE5bjVkTEVLVXo1ZWVNUTVkMUVrX3BIOA</guid></item><item><title>用药过量危机正在好转- Salon.com</title><link>https://www.salon.com/2025/12/25/the-overdose-crisis-is-turning-around/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="article__content page-article"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Overdose deaths &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2024/11/15/cdc-overdose-set-to-dip-below-100000-for-the-first-time-since-2020/"&gt;are falling&lt;/a&gt; at a pace the United States has not seen in decades. Centers for Disease Control projections show a nearly &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/nvss/vsrr/drug-overdose-data.htm"&gt;&lt;span&gt;25% decline&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; for the twelve months ending in April 2025. But the meaning of that decline shows up long before it appears in national reports. It shows up in a son who makes it home from work, in a daughter who stays in treatment long enough to rebuild her life, in the quiet, daily act of someone returning home to the people who love them. It shows up in having another table setting at the holiday dinner.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;These moments of return do not happen by chance. They happen because public policy finally &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;aligns with evidence and because communities were able to use tools we already know save lives. Policymakers &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://chir.georgetown.edu/tackling-another-public-health-emergency-recent-state-and-federal-policies-to-increase-opioid-use-disorder-treatment-access/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;expanded access&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; to medications for opioid use disorder, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.samhsa.gov/substance-use/treatment/statutes-regulations-guidelines/buprenorphine-telemedicine-prescribing"&gt;&lt;span&gt;protected telehealth&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; for addiction treatment and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pew.org/en/research-and-analysis/issue-briefs/2025/09/state-policy-approaches-to-expand--naloxone-access"&gt;&lt;span&gt;widened community access&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; to naloxone. People are home for the holidays because life-saving systems were finally allowed to fully function.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="right_quote"&gt;
&lt;p class="insert-quote"&gt;Whether this progress continues depends on the choices we make now. As we head into 2026, the foundational policies that saved lives this year could disappear before the next holiday season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Whether this progress continues depends on the choices we make now. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;As we head into 2026, the foundational policies that saved lives this year could disappear before the next holiday season.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lifesaving tools that have driven the decline remain vulnerable. Medications for &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/topic/opioids"&gt;opioid&lt;/a&gt; use disorder — especially buprenorphine and methadone — cut the risk of death by more than half. Yet for years, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ecfr.gov/current/title-21/chapter-II/part-1306/subject-group-ECFR1eb5bb3a23fddd0/section-1306.07"&gt;&lt;span&gt;federal rules&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and insurance barriers have kept these treatments out of reach. Even now, many patients face bureaucratic paperwork hurdles, such as prior authorization requirements, which interrupt care and separate patients from necessary prescriptions. States have worked to close these gaps by &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S2949875924001401"&gt;&lt;span&gt;expanding mobile treatment programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://americanhealth.jhu.edu/news/bringing-addiction-treatment-primary-care-settings"&gt;&lt;span&gt;embedding addiction treatment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; into primary care, specifically in Texas and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pew.org/en/research-and-analysis/fact-sheets/2025/12/how-massachusetts-addresses-substance-use-disorders-in-primary-care-settings"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Massachusetts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;These changes increased the odds of survival, but the initiatives &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://nasadad.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/The-Substance-Use-Workforce-Crisis-Drivers-Challenges-and-Promising-Strategies_POST-2.pdf"&gt;&lt;span&gt;remain under-resourced&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and at-risk. In recent years, telehealth has become one of the most powerful drivers of improved access. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S2949875925001432"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Research&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; shows that patients who begin treatment virtually stay in recovery at similar or higher rates than those who start in person. While skeptics remain, the data confirm that telehealth provides quality care without increasing overdose risk. This is especially important to rural counties and households without reliable transportation, where telehealth means the difference between care instead of a crisis. But in 2026, those flexibilities &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cms.gov/files/document/telehealth-faq-updated-11-26-2025.pdf"&gt;&lt;span&gt;will vanish&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; unless Congress acts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Additional changes to insurance coverage expose how quickly people can lose access and be &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;pushed out of treatment. &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/topic/medicaid"&gt;Medicaid&lt;/a&gt; covers nearly half of non-elderly adults with opioid use disorder, paying for the critical treatment services that get people to recovery. But this backbone &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2025/03/21/cutting-medicaid-could-worsen-overdose-and-erase-recent-progress-in-treating-addiction/"&gt;is weakening&lt;/a&gt;. During the unwinding of pandemic protections, more than 23 million people have lost Medicaid coverage, which is often &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/medicaid/medicaid-enrollment-and-unwinding-tracker/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;due to paperwork errors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; rather than changes in eligibility. This number is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aha.org/news/headline/2025-07-21-cbo-projects-obbba-increase-uninsured-10-million-federal-deficit-34-trillion"&gt;&lt;span&gt;estimated to increase significantly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; following the passage of the &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/topic/big_beautiful_bill"&gt;One Big Beautiful Bill&lt;/a&gt;, which according to the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office (CBO), will &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/medicaid/allocating-cbos-estimates-of-federal-medicaid-spending-reductions-across-the-states-enacted-reconciliation-package/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;slash Medicaid and Children’s Health Insurance Program (CHIP) spending&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; by nearly $1 trillion over a decade and eliminate over 10 million people from the programs. Similarly, the CBO warns that about 1.5 million Americans will be uninsured in 2026 if Congress delays extending the ACA enhanced tax credits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Want more sharp takes on politics? &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/newsletter?utm_source=onsite&amp;amp;utm_medium=organic&amp;amp;utm_campaign=standing-room-only-edit-signup"&gt;Sign up for our free newsletter&lt;/a&gt;, Standing Room Only, written by Amanda Marcotte, now also a weekly show &lt;a href="%E2%80%9Dhttps://www.salon.com/2025/06/13/standing-room-only-amanda-marcotte-salon-youtube-podcast/%E2%80%9D"&gt;on YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Congress has the power to address these lapsing policies in 2026 and needs to act — just as it did with the bipartisan reauthorization of the SUPPORT for Patients and Communities Act, which promises to continue federal funding for core recovery programs and to address overdose. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But maintaining the status quo is not enough to resolve the fracture points where people still fall out of care. In 2026, Congress should pass legislation to ensure that Americans who are most vulnerable to fatal overdose, such as those entering and leaving jail and prison, receive evidence-based, lifesaving treatment. Congress can grow the treatment workforce by funding and expanding peer recovery support workers. These proposals follow the same evidence that drove the decline in 2025.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The drop in overdose deaths this year is real. It reflects years of work by clinicians, community &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;groups, families and bipartisan lawmakers who chose data over dogma. But a decline does not &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;equal victory. It equals a narrow window of opportunity. The difference between momentum and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;reversal now runs through the legislative decisions that will shape 2026. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Just like this holiday season, families will gather again next December. Some seats will be filled because of the policies that worked in 2025. Others will stand empty if those policies unravel in 2026. The country already knows which choices save lives. What remains unclear is whether it will keep making them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="layout_template_wrapper read_more"&gt;
&lt;div class="red_white_box"&gt;
&lt;p class="red_box"&gt;Read more&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="white_box"&gt;about this topic&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Salon.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:30:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTFByR0tuZUdWSmxBNWtTT3p6S3JyWlVUSTA0cE0wVDJ0Vk9qQ3RQcjkxVVRfTVl0QUZzZGhjcVpfNUI2NXJoX1g1NHZoV3QwNTdiYjZTdEEtSjFLNXZNYldfZThHdEM3alNTUnBETUhaeW5NRVM2em11LWprdw</guid></item><item><title>5项早晨站立锻炼， 40岁后早餐前肚子变平-吃这个不是那个</title><link>https://www.eatthis.com/morning-standing-exercises-flatten-stomach-after-40/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content single-post-content"&gt;
																			&lt;p class="tagline"&gt;No floor work needed, these 5 standing moves wake up your core before breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;
												
																			
																		
						
						
						&lt;p&gt;While turning 40 has many upsides, waking up typically means more soreness and less excitement for morning workouts compared to when you were younger. And the idea of getting down on the floor for crunches or grinding through a lengthy cardio session before breakfast can feel more draining than energizing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The good news is you don’t need intense morning workouts or hour-long cardio sessions to tighten your midsection. Instead, all you need are standing exercises to boost your body composition as you age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While no exercise can literally “spot reduce” belly fat, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/endocrinology/articles/10.3389/fendo.2025.1409474/full" target="_blank"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; show that daily movement and strength training exercises combined with light-to-moderate cardio performed consistently can improve insulin sensitivity, preserve lean muscle, and support fat loss. Additionally, morning exercise can help &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://journals.physiology.org/doi/full/10.1152/japplphysiol.00001.2019" target="_blank"&gt;combat overnight stiffness&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/physiology/articles/10.3389/fphys.2019.00762/full" target="_blank"&gt;enhance blood flow&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-025-02659-8" target="_blank"&gt;boost your metabolism&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To learn more, we chatted with &lt;b&gt;James Brady&lt;/b&gt;, a personal trainer at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.origym.co.uk/blog/author/jbrady/" target="_blank"&gt;OriGym&lt;/a&gt;, who shares his top five morning standing exercises for those 40-plus to flatten your stomach before breakfast. Read on for the exercises and detailed instructions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(And when you’re done, don’t miss these &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/chair-exercises-shrink-belly-pooch-over-50-no-planks/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Chair Exercises That Shrink Belly Pooch Better Than Planks After 50&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="bodyweight-squats" class="o-slide-title" data-num="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bodyweight Squats&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/l83R5PblSMA?si=jSGruoD8y8f6cWKJ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;span aria-hidden="true"&gt;6254a4d1642c605c54bf1cab17d50f1e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Squats are king when it comes to compound exercises. That’s because this classic move engages multiple large muscle groups at once. “Bodyweight squats activate the largest muscle groups in the body and quickly raise the heart rate,” explains Brady. “This helps increase calorie burn early in the day while building lean muscle that supports long term weight loss.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand with your feet about shoulder-width apart and your toes slightly turned outward.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage your core while keeping your chest upright and your shoulders relaxed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Push your hips back as if sitting into a chair while bending your knees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower until your thighs are roughly parallel to the floor (or as far as you can go comfortably).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive through your heels to stand back up while squeezing your glutes at the top.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform three to four sets of 10 to 12 reps. Rest for 60 to 90 seconds between sets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed karma_unit--halfpage"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="standing-knee-drives" class="o-slide-title" data-num="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Standing Knee Drives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/lGsMmiLMj3o?si=XPSDehA5UlJ0HoJI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike high-impact exercises, standing knee raises increase your heart rate gradually while reinforcing coordination and stability, both of which tend to decline without regular practice after 40.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Standing knee drives combine gentle cardio with core engagement, helping to improve balance while encouraging blood flow and energy production,” explains Brady. “This exercise supports weight loss by increasing movement efficiency and metabolic activity without feeling overwhelming in the morning.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand tall with your feet hip-width apart and your hands resting lightly at your sides or on your hips.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lift one knee toward your chest while keeping your torso upright.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage your core to control the movement rather than swinging your leg.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower your foot back to the floor with control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alternate sides while moving smoothly and rhythmically.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aim for three to four sets of 12 to 15 reps per side. Rest for 60 to 90 seconds between sets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

	&lt;h2 id="jumping-jacks" class="o-slide-title" data-num="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Jumping Jacks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/iSSAk4XCsRA?si=TdkawKsjhJ1JpDWC" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jumping jacks often get overlooked because they seem basic, but they’re undeniably one of the most efficient full-body movements you can do. “Jumping jacks are a simple but powerful exercise that elevate the heart rate and get your full body moving,” Brady says. “From a weight loss perspective, they’re great as they burn calories and improve cardiovascular fitness with minimal setup.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand with your feet together and your arms relaxed at your sides.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Step or jump your feet out wide while raising your arms overhead.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep your core engaged and your chest lifted throughout the movement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Return to the starting position with control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continue at a steady, comfortable pace rather than rushing the reps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jump for 30 to 45 seconds without stopping. Rest for 90 seconds and repeat two to three more times.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="standing-torso-twists" class="o-slide-title" data-num="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Standing Torso Twists&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/h6XyzlM8m24?si=35Xd0CrrwVfSbM9R" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Morning stiffness in the spine is common after 40, especially after hours of sleep. Fortunately, this movement can help restore mobility while lightly engaging your obliques (side abs) and deep core muscles that support posture and rotation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Standing torso twists focus on the core and obliques while promoting spinal mobility, which is particularly beneficial after sleep,” explains Brady. “Although lower impact, they support weight loss by making other physical activity feel easier throughout the day.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart and your knees slightly bent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring your arms out in front of you or place your hands across your chest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rotate your torso slowly to one side while keeping your hips facing forward.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Return to center, then rotate to the opposite side.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move in a controlled, fluid motion without forcing the range of motion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete 15 to 20 reps per side, resting for 60 to 90 seconds between sets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

	&lt;h2 id="marching-in-place-with-arm-swings" class="o-slide-title" data-num="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Marching in Place With Arm Swings&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1IC-B4A91Ds?si=WgJVmtHGQUmcbrXl" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marching in place may look simple, but it’s a powerful way to wake up the nervous system and reinforce coordination between the upper and lower body. “Marching in place with arm swings gently raises the heart rate while encouraging coordination and full body circulation,” Brady tells us. “This movement supports fat loss by helping people ease into activity and build consistency, which is one of the biggest drivers of sustainable weight loss.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand tall with your arms relaxed at your sides.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lift one knee while swinging your opposite arm forward.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower your foot and repeat on the other side.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep your movements smooth and controlled rather than rushed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain steady breathing and upright posture throughout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform this movement nonstop for three to four sets of 30 to 45 seconds. Rest for 60 to 90 seconds between sets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

																		
																	&lt;/div&gt;
										&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio"&gt;
	&lt;p class="c-article-short-bio__name"&gt;Adam Meyer, RHN&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio__bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
		Adam is a health writer, certified holistic nutritionist, and 100% plant-based athlete.					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="c-article-short-bio__more" href="https://www.eatthis.com/author/adam-meyer/"&gt;Read more about Adam &lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Eat This Not That</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:00:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxQcTlpTkhmcnR2Y2xKdi1MMHplaGI0MkxtTDNHOVRKT2dlSGhKeTZaekx6cWl2NVVoSF9NejlvSVNUOUF0RDVTdW5QZ3JqbUZMOGJWSW9BUlRRQm5paHUxb2EtRnJtbWVmRUo4OTFIVnlkWUUtbF9DQVMzYVJqVnpNMWdn</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现了一种恢复痴呆症患者脑血流的方法- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251225031247.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A potential new way to treat reduced brain blood flow and certain forms of dementia is beginning to emerge. Scientists at the University of Vermont Robert Larner, M.D. College of Medicine have uncovered new details about how blood circulation in the brain is controlled and how vascular problems might be reversed. Their preclinical research, published December 22 in &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences&lt;/em&gt;, suggests that replacing a missing phospholipid in the bloodstream could help restore normal brain blood flow and ease dementia-related symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This discovery is a huge step forward in our efforts to prevent dementia and neurovascular diseases," says principal investigator Osama Harraz, Ph.D., assistant professor of pharmacology at Larner College of Medicine. "We are uncovering the complex mechanisms of these devastating conditions, and now we can begin to think about how to translate this biology into therapies."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Rising Burden of Dementia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer's disease and related dementias affect about 50 million people worldwide, and that number continues to grow. The increasing prevalence places heavy pressure on families, caregivers, and health care systems. Ongoing research is working to untangle how proteins, inflammation, neural signaling, and malfunctioning brain cells contribute to these disorders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Work in the Harraz lab centers on how cerebral blood flow is controlled and how blood vessels communicate through molecular signals. A major focus is Piezo1, a protein found in the membranes of cells that line blood vessels. Piezo1 helps regulate brain blood flow by sensing physical forces created as blood moves through the brain's vascular network. Its name comes from the Greek word for "pressure." Earlier research showed that Piezo1 behaves differently in people who carry certain genetic variations of the Piezo1 gene.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Key Lipid That Keeps Blood Vessels in Check&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new study, titled "PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; Corrects an Endothelial Piezo1 Channelopathy," offers fresh insight into how Piezo1 influences cerebral blood flow. The findings also show that conditions such as Alzheimer's disease are linked to abnormally high Piezo1 activity in brain blood vessels. To better understand why this happens, the research team examined a phospholipid called PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;, which is found in brain cell membranes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; plays an essential role in cell signaling and ion channel regulation -- a complex process that controls when protein pores in cells open and close. The researchers discovered that PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; normally acts as a natural suppressor of Piezo1. When PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; levels fall, Piezo1 becomes overly active, disrupting normal blood flow in the brain. When the team added PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; back into the system, Piezo1 activity decreased and healthy blood circulation was restored. These results suggest that increasing PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; levels could form the basis of a new treatment strategy aimed at improving brain blood flow and supporting brain function.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next Steps Toward Future Treatments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Future studies will focus on understanding exactly how PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; interacts with Piezo1. Researchers want to determine whether PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; attaches directly to specific parts of the protein or changes the surrounding cell membrane in ways that limit channel opening. Additional work will also explore how disease-related declines in PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; remove this regulatory control, allowing Piezo1 to remain overactive and impair cerebral blood flow. Gaining clarity on these mechanisms will be critical for developing therapies based on restoring PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; or directly targeting Piezo1 to improve neurovascular health in dementia and related vascular disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 08:55:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBvaHlFUzBHanpKNDJadmM5OW9zOE9hbXdpSTZNYjltT1lVYXdlT1hya3V4ekRTdTU4VHdBTkxIUmMxQk5abDV0R3pZemVKTjdQdUZRbnZwU0Q0NlMweVZRZWlJRHFBSklBOUNJdVAyOA</guid></item><item><title>不明原因的体重增加？医生透露这可能是甲状腺活动不足的迹象|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/gained-unexplained-weight-doctor-reveals-it-may-be-a-sign-of-underactive-thyroid-101766644639293.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/gained-unexplained-weight-doctor-reveals-it-may-be-a-sign-of-underactive-thyroid-101766644639293.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/chennai-fitness-trainer-with-18-years-of-experience-shares-4-mindful-hacks-to-prevent-weight-gain-due-to-overeating-101766492474363.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Weight gain"&gt;Weight gain&lt;/a&gt; is usually associated with a sedentary lifestyle, frequent consumption of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/dermatologist-explains-why-simply-cutting-out-junk-food-does-not-cure-acne-busts-5-common-acne-myths-101759478620994.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="junk food"&gt;junk food&lt;/a&gt;, or insufficient physical activity. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;However, when the numbers on the scale continue to rise despite mindful eating habits and regular movements, then the cause may be deeper, beyond behavioural or lifestyle factors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/25/550x309/weight_gain__1766645134269_1766645134504.jpg" alt="Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/25/550x309/weight_gain__1766645134269_1766645134504.jpg" alt="Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ALSO READ: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/ahmedabad-physician-shares-the-key-foods-and-nutrients-you-should-include-in-your-diet-for-a-healthier-thyroid-101765873817961.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Ahmedabad physician shares the key foods and nutrients you should include in your diet for a healthier thyroid"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ahmedabad physician shares the key foods and nutrients you should include in your diet for a healthier thyroid&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To understand one of these unseen causes, HT Lifestyle connected with Dr Gaurav Jain, senior consultant of internal medicine at Dharamshila Narayana Superspeciality Hospital, Delhi. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;According to him, unexplained weight gain can often be linked to an imbalance in the thyroid gland, which plays a crucial role in regulating the body's metabolism.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;When the thyroid becomes underactive, a condition known as hypothyroidism, the body’s metabolic processes slow down, leading to gradual and often confusing weight gain,” he explained.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;How do you know if your weight gain is connected to a thyroid imbalance? Some subtle signs are often attributed to other causes, as they tend to overlap with common health issues. This is why paying closer attention to these symptoms is crucial so that you can distinguish and identify.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Gaurav Jain shared 5 signs:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Weight gain despite normal eating habits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Jain explained that weight gain is the first red flag with an underactive thyroid, particularly when there has been no major change in diet or lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt;Why does this happen? He explained, “A sluggish thyroid slows down the body's calorie-burning rate, leading to fat accumulation, particularly around the abdomen.” Another key indicator that he informed is that weight is very hard to lose, even if you are regularly exercising.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Persistent fatigue and low energy levels&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exhaustion is generally linked to stress or burnout. In fact, fatigue overlaps with several mental and physical issues, which is why it is often overlooked. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;However, Dr Jain pointed out that persistent, unexplained fatigue can also be an early sign of an underactive thyroid, especially when it occurs alongside gradual weight gain and low energy levels.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He described why this happens: “&lt;span&gt; Thyroid hormones are essential for energy production. When levels drop, the body feels constantly tired and sluggish. This ongoing fatigue reduces physical activity, further contributing to weight gain and a feeling of heaviness in the body.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Dry skin, hair fall and slow nail growth&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/07/24/550x309/hair__1753345225207_1753345225312.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="You experience a lot of hairfall with an underactive thyroid. (Shutterstock)" title="You experience a lot of hairfall with an underactive thyroid. (Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;You experience a lot of hairfall with an underactive thyroid. (Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Changes in the skin, hair, and nails may look like cosmetic issues that require you to change your skincare, haircare or manicure routine, but sometimes they can be associated with deeper health issues.&lt;/span&gt; Dr Jain cautioned that an underactive thyroid affects the skin's ability to retain moisture, making makin it dry, rough, and less elastic.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He named some changes, “Hair fall is common, and hair may become thin or brittle. Nails often grow more slowly and may appear weak or ridged.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Hormonal imbalance and menstrual changes in women&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Thyroid health is closely linked to reproductive health, which means it can impact hormone levels and make women more likely to experience problems associated with hormonal disruptions when the thyroid is underactive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Describing how the menstrual flow gets affected, “In women, hypothyroidism can disrupt menstrual cycles, making them irregular, heavy or painful.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Jain also elaborated that low thyroid hormone levels can disturb hormonal balance, leading to fluid retention and increased fat storage, which can result in unexplained weight gain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Neck swelling, eye symptoms and digestive slowdown&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/08/25/550x309/stomach_pain_1756092360701_1756092366710.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Unhealthy gut causes weight gain.(Shutterstock)" title="Unhealthy gut causes weight gain.(Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Unhealthy gut causes weight gain.(Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;Physical changes in the neck and eyes, along with digestive issues, can also point to thyroid dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Jain shared these 3 signs related to these areas:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;An enlarged thyroid may appear as a swelling in the neck and can sometimes cause difficulty in swallowing.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mild vision disturbances, blurred vision and puffy eyes may also be present.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Digestion slows down, leading to bloating and constipation, which can add to weight gain and discomfort.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the doctor warned about a couple of important points. Firstly, unexplained weight gain and other subtle symptoms should not always be dismissed. Secondly, with the increasing use of non-iodised salts and changing dietary patterns, early and subclinical thyroid disorders are increasingly common.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:54:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4wFBVV95cUxNUDI0ajJ4aU9yOTBrSVZERUMwc3IxZFYtR2MwQVFUMm04X1NqaDMyX0t1VjYxcW9yd2s1ZFRfOV9UQkJsa0ZIVUZGd1NkbHd2S2YzUXNPUEVsMm1BOGtuVF93eXlRXzBBUW1fOTNVZnVmUlBkTjFiTXAyMTNia2U0TkNoVnNsNnBIRVYwNUNJTk1EMnVvRkFuTkpFc2p0ZVdGYmJpTFRWOE93M21tbFRZTS1sVmJIRE1lTjdONnNhUXlsbVd0VlZzX0U4blBBSFFSNUtnMGplaDNZODNJX0pJbEpNc9IB6AFBVV95cUxOMUc1eTVjQkNLSFZyWFQ4UlpGTTByQ2ZVa0g1NzIyOTZ4cTlSbkVpbFFFdUZTRkVZd3gxTDYtaXNyc1k2NW5ibG9adHg0TEZvNkc2MVZUUHVyc3JvbW5wNHRLeWZPVEhwaEFQa1lmZGtyak5SOGdSWVdQcmFHdUJ1ZHF6M3pyRFY4VWEyb0NzOFlPd2dpcHRfckp4T2QwZEg2VmNkSm5LaHdoem1PVHAwWDZIU083VTEyR3hUaEJmLWlHUTVmYkVEZF8wbWRDeEdKek1SVVliamZNZUJTUno3UzBZem5FY0Rs</guid></item><item><title>新技术以创纪录的速度和效率消除“永久化学物质” - ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251224032401.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A research team at Rice University, working with international collaborators, has created the first environmentally friendly technology that can quickly trap and break down toxic "forever chemicals" (PFAS) in water. The results, published recently in &lt;em&gt;Advanced Materials&lt;/em&gt;, represent a meaningful advance against one of the most stubborn pollution threats worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project was led by Youngkun Chung, a postdoctoral fellow mentored by Michael S. Wong, a professor at Rice's George R. Brown School of Engineering and Computing. The effort also included Seoktae Kang, a professor at the Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST), and Keon-Ham Kim, a professor at Pukyung National University in South Korea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Are PFAS and Why Are They a Problem&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PFAS, short for per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances, are man-made chemicals that date back to the 1940s. They have been used in many everyday products, including Teflon pans, waterproof clothing, and some food packaging. PFAS became popular because they resist heat, grease, and water, but that same durability also means they break down very slowly, which is why they are often called "forever chemicals."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PFAS have now spread widely and can be found in water, soil, and air around the world. Research has linked exposure to liver damage, reproductive disorders, immune system disruption, and certain cancers. Cleanup has been difficult because once PFAS enter the environment, they are hard to remove and even harder to destroy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Current PFAS Removal Methods Fall Short&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many standard approaches rely on adsorption, meaning the chemicals stick to materials such as activated carbon or ion-exchange resins. These methods are common, but they have major limitations, including low efficiency, slow operation, limited capacity, and the buildup of additional contaminated waste that still has to be handled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Current methods for PFAS removal are too slow, inefficient and create secondary waste," said Wong, the Tina and Sunit Patel Professor in Molecular Nanotechnology and professor of chemical and biomolecular engineering, chemistry and civil and environmental engineering. "Our new approach offers a sustainable and highly effective alternative."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Breakthrough LDH Material That Works Fast&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new approach is built around a layered double hydroxide (LDH) material made from copper and aluminum. Kim first identified this type of material while he was a graduate student at KAIST in 2021. As the team explored these compounds further, Chung found that a specific version containing nitrate could adsorb PFAS with unusually high performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"To my astonishment, this LDH compound captured PFAS more than 1,000 times better than other materials," said Chung, a lead author of the study and now a fellow at Rice's WaTER (Water Technologies, Entrepreneurship and Research) Institute and Sustainability Institute. "It also worked incredibly fast, removing large amounts of PFAS within minutes, about 100 times faster than commercial carbon filters."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers say the impressive results come from the material's internal design. Its ordered copper-aluminum layers, along with small charge imbalances, create a highly favorable surface where PFAS molecules can attach quickly and strongly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tested in River Water, Tap Water, and Wastewater&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To see how well the system could perform outside the lab, the team tested the LDH material in river water, tap water, and wastewater. Across all three, it remained highly effective. It also performed well in both static tests and continuous-flow setups, pointing to possible use in municipal water treatment systems and industrial cleanup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Closing the Loop With PFAS Destruction and Reuse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Capturing PFAS is only half the battle since the chemicals still need to be destroyed safely. Working with Rice professors Pedro Alvarez and James Tour, Chung developed a process to thermally decompose PFAS after they are captured on the LDH material. When the PFAS-loaded material was heated with calcium carbonate, the researchers removed more than half of the trapped PFAS without releasing toxic by-products. The same step also regenerated the LDH, making it possible to use the material again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early testing showed the material could go through at least six complete cycles of capture, destruction, and renewal. That makes it the first known eco-friendly, sustainable system for PFAS removal that combines rapid cleanup with repeated reuse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;International Collaboration and Research Support&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We are excited by the potential of this one-of-a-kind LDH-based technology to transform how PFAS-contaminated water sources are treated in the near future," Wong said. "It's the result of an extraordinary international collaboration and the creativity of young researchers."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A list of all the researchers involved in this study and their institutional affiliations can be found here. This research was supported by the Basic Science Research Program through the National Research Foundation of Korea funded by the Ministry of Education (2021R1A6A3A14044449, RS-2023-00242795), grants from the National Convergence Research of Scientific Challenges and the Sejong Science Fellowship through the National Research Foundation of Korea and funding from the Ministry of Science (NRF-2022M3C1C8094245) and ICT (RS-2024-00395438). This work was also funded by Saudi Aramco-KAIST CO2 Management, Nanosystems Engineering Research Center for Nanotechnology-Enabled Water Treatment (NEWT), the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers' Engineering Research and Development Center grant (W912HZ-21-2-0050), Rice Sustainability Institute and Rice WaTER Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:46:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE1KN0pYLW5VMEM2T2I2R2phaU9RVEZLZEVPa210YXAtNnJQZWxTcUZGUGZRYXRtRTBBUElXWFZ2VUxfLXozVkowZHhOQzBTYjhWWDlPN0JVa1JDZG9COVpaNy1CT1hDUFE3bEp6a1pLOA</guid></item><item><title>科学家表示，进化的运作方式与我们想象的不同- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251224032359.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;For decades, many evolutionary biologists have believed that most genetic changes shaping genes and proteins are neutral. Under this view, mutations are usually neither helpful nor harmful, allowing them to spread quietly without being strongly favored or rejected by natural selection.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new study from the University of Michigan challenges that long-standing assumption and suggests evolution may work very differently than once thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rethinking the Neutral Theory of Evolution&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As species evolve, random genetic mutations arise. Some of these mutations become fixed, meaning they spread until every individual in a population carries the change. The Neutral Theory of Molecular Evolution argues that most mutations that reach this stage are neutral. Harmful mutations are quickly eliminated, while helpful ones are assumed to be extremely rare, explains evolutionary biologist Jianzhi Zhang.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zhang and his colleagues set out to test whether this idea holds up when examined more closely. Their results pointed to a major problem. The researchers found that beneficial mutations occur far more often than the Neutral Theory allows. At the same time, they observed that the overall rate at which mutations become fixed in populations is much lower than would be expected if so many helpful mutations were taking hold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Beneficial Mutations Often Do Not Last&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To explain this contradiction, the team proposed a new explanation rooted in environmental change. A mutation that provides an advantage in one setting may become harmful once conditions shift. Because environments change frequently, many beneficial mutations never spread widely enough to become fixed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study, which was supported by the U.S. National Institutes of Health, was published in &lt;em&gt;Nature Ecology and Evolution&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We're saying that the outcome was neutral, but the process was not neutral," said Zhang, a professor of ecology and evolutionary biology at U-M. "Our model suggests that natural populations are not truly adapted to their environments because environments change very quickly, and populations are always chasing the environment."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zhang calls this framework Adaptive Tracking with Antagonistic Pleiotropy. The idea helps explain why organisms are rarely perfectly matched to their surroundings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What This Means for Humans and Other Species&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zhang believes the findings have wide-ranging implications, including for humans. Modern environments differ dramatically from those our ancestors experienced, which may help explain why certain genetic traits no longer serve us as well as they once did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I think this has broad implications. For example, humans. Our environment has changed so much, and our genes may not be the best for today's environment because we went through a lot of other different environments. Some mutations may be beneficial in our old environments, but are mismatched to today," Zhang said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He added that how well a population is adapted depends on how recently its environment has changed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"At any time when you observe a natural population, depending on when the last time the environment had a big change, the population may be very poorly adapted or it may be relatively well adapted. But we're probably never going to see any population that is fully adapted to its environment, because a full adaptation would take longer than almost any natural environment can remain constant."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Scientists Studied Beneficial Mutations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Neutral Theory of Molecular Evolution was introduced in the 1960s, when advances in protein and gene sequencing allowed scientists to study evolution at the molecular level rather than focusing only on physical traits like shape and structure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To measure how often beneficial mutations occur, Zhang and his team analyzed large deep mutational scanning datasets generated by their own lab and others. In these experiments, researchers deliberately created many different mutations within a single gene or section of the genome in organisms such as yeast and E. coli.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They then tracked these organisms over many generations and compared their growth to the wild type, or the most common form found in nature. By measuring growth differences, the researchers could estimate whether a mutation helped or harmed the organism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results showed that more than 1% of mutations were beneficial. This rate is far higher than what the Neutral Theory predicts. If all those helpful mutations became fixed, nearly all genetic changes would be beneficial and evolution would proceed much faster than what scientists actually observe. That realization led the team to question the assumption that environments stay constant over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Testing Evolution in Changing Environments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To explore the effects of environmental shifts, the researchers studied two groups of yeast. One group evolved in a stable environment for 800 generations (each generation lasted 3 hours). The second group evolved for the same number of generations but in a changing environment made up of 10 different types of media, or growth solutions. Each medium was used for 80 generations before switching to the next.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The yeast exposed to changing conditions showed far fewer beneficial mutations becoming established than those in the stable environment. Even when advantageous mutations appeared, they rarely lasted long enough to spread before conditions changed again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This is where the inconsistency comes from. While we observe a lot of beneficial mutations in a given environment, those beneficial mutations do not have a chance to be fixed because as their frequency increases to a certain level, the environment changes," Zhang said. "Those beneficial mutations in the old environment might become deleterious in the new environment."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limits and Next Steps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zhang cautioned that the study focused on yeast and E. coli, single-celled organisms where the effects of mutations are easier to measure. Data from multicellular organisms will be needed to determine whether the same patterns apply to more complex life, including humans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research team is now planning follow-up studies to better understand why it takes so long for organisms to fully adapt even when environmental conditions remain stable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other authors of the study include former U-M graduate students Siliang Song and Xukang Shen and former U-M postdoctoral researcher Piaopiao Chen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:02:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE45R2ZSUFR3elNuZlJ2V1JPdWt0NW82R2xVTFlFVGxqYkhuanFSU19JT1BuZk1UZV9XTFBTcVZ0Tjl1dGpqSWkxa19tWUdySGpmS0o1MVhPQ2xQaFNKY1BrVEhTamkwS1FYbmZBajZtZw</guid></item><item><title>他身边的“守护天使” ： 20岁的斯特林高地男子如何努力从中风中恢复过来-底特律新闻</title><link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/local/macomb-county/2025/12/24/sterling-heights-resident-20-continues-his-recovery-from-a-stroke/87604563007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_dt"&gt;Dec. 24, 2025&lt;span class="gnt_ar_ut"&gt;Updated Dec. 25, 2025, 9:25 a.m. ET&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;When he gathers with family at his grandparents' house for Christmas dinner this year, Edward Constantineau of Sterling Heights will be surrounded by the people who pushed him to fight to recover from the hardest thing he's ever faced in his young life, a hurdle he's still working to overcome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Constantineau was just 19, working out at his local gym in March of this year, when he suffered the unimaginable for a teenager: a stroke. He underwent immediate surgery on a bleed in his brain and later went through six weeks of inpatient rehab at a facility in Detroit, learning how to move again, talk and regain fine motor skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Detroit News</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:06:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4gFBVV95cUxPV0xBYzA5dEFOYjhCM2RYbUduaElVWkNPeGdBd2lraEttb1pGY2dRdlEweU51VVMxQVpTdnpRXzBpNTNkRmFUUWRVeDhpNkhfMHhPdWRuX2ZGUVdubmJrYUZEZmdjWVR6WUpTcGVYVUFUeDVEeWlncU5EcFlqTEVjNWc3b0ZKb3N3a050QzN4bUZEdTNQQXd5V21aOWtnSUpIMGNEN3k3a2VrSUpDZlpfempldk9VaTN3Y2RSQkhjT2NFTlctZFJxeEdtYi1Md0dHMFhIR3d5WFVlblFfMWhPOEJB</guid></item><item><title>医生回答：如何治疗流感和无用的药物- Ynetnews</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/health_science/article/bjplqrfmwg</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-contents="true"&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="3rd6n-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="3rd6n-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="3rd6n-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;This year’s flu season began early, with five children dying from complications of the disease and hospitalizations on the rise. Family doctors are warning that influenza is not a mild winter illness, outlining its symptoms, identifying who is truly at risk and explaining how it should, and should not, be treated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="6etn1-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6etn1-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6etn1-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“Influenza is a viral disease characterized by complications of the respiratory system,” says Dr. Zehava Alon, a family medicine specialist with Clalit Health Services’ Central District. She describes it as a severe illness that typically lasts about a week and is marked by very high fever and serious respiratory symptoms, including cough, pneumonia, sinus infections, shortness of breath and bouts of bronchitis, along with body aches and profound weakness. Unlike common cold viruses, which usually cause mild symptoms and resolve within days, influenza can worsen significantly. “Patients die from the complications, when the underlying cause is influenza,” she says, noting the deaths of five children this year and severe outcomes among older adults.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="63c9c-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="cudbb-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="cudbb-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="cudbb-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Dr. Adam Reiter, a family medicine specialist with Maccabi Healthcare Services, echoed her remarks. “Generally speaking, influenza is a viral disease of the respiratory tract. In most cases it begins and remains in the upper respiratory tract, meaning the nose and throat, but it can, God forbid, worsen and spread to the lower respiratory tract — the lungs. That is why it has the potential, like any viral illness and perhaps more so than other viruses, to cause significant respiratory disease with lung involvement.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="ai7j8-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta wrapped"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleWrappedImageComponenta"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleWrappedImageData.rkx003ERYQbg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/12/21/H1gRB7qHm11l/H1gRB7qHm11l_142_528_697_930_0_medium.jpg" alt='ד"ר זהבה אלון, רופאת משפחה, כללית' title="Dr. Zehava Alon " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="caption" contenteditable="false"&gt;Dr. Zehava Alon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="5i9be-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5i9be-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5i9be-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;One of the most common misconceptions about influenza and other winter illnesses is whether they are caused by a virus or a bacterium — a distinction that is critical for treatment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="4md5g-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4md5g-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4md5g-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“Not everyone understands the difference between a virus and a bacterium,” says Dr. Reiter. “Both can make us sick, but the key difference is practical: what medicine can do.” Bacterial infections can be treated with antibiotics, he explains, while viral illnesses cannot. “There are no drugs that kill viruses, so treatment for viral diseases is supportive and aimed at relieving symptoms. That is why people with fever or worsening symptoms should be examined, so we can determine whether the illness is viral or bacterial.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="fff2j-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta wrapped"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleWrappedImageComponenta"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleWrappedImageData.SJgvtB0KXWx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/12/21/BkAr7crmWg/BkAr7crmWg_511_94_619_826_0_medium.jpg" alt='ד"ר אדם רייטר, רופא משפחה, מכבי' title="Dr. Adam Reiter (Photo: Ofer Hajayov) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="caption" contenteditable="false"&gt;Dr. Adam Reiter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span disabled class="credit" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Ofer Hajayov&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2svm5-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2svm5-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2svm5-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The confusion often leads patients to expect antibiotics even when they have influenza. “Influenza does not respond to antibiotics. It is a viral disease,” says Dr. Alon. “Antibiotics are sometimes given only for complications, such as pneumonia — not to treat the flu itself, but to treat a secondary infection that develops when the immune system is weakened.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="1ejg5-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="ed4i-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="ed4i-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="ed4i-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Influenza does not affect everyone the same way. While many recover within days, others can deteriorate quickly and develop serious complications, including pneumonia, severe respiratory failure requiring ventilation and even death.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="6s07i-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6s07i-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6s07i-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“When someone has a viral illness, the immune system is already weakened, which allows bacterial infections to develop on top of it,” says Dr. Reiter. “If there is no improvement, it is important to seek medical evaluation.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="b8g74-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="b8g74-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="b8g74-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;These warnings are especially relevant for high-risk groups — people whose immune systems may struggle to fight a viral infection. They include the very old and the very young, people with underlying medical conditions and those taking medications that suppress the immune system, for whom vaccination is particularly important. Dr. Alon adds that nearly everyone carries some level of risk, particularly people in close, ongoing contact with children, such as teachers and preschool staff.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2lqqo-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="9gg97-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9gg97-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9gg97-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Treatment for influenza is not the same for everyone and depends largely on the severity of symptoms, a person’s overall health and whether the illness is mild and self-limiting or requires medical evaluation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="9q6n7-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9q6n7-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9q6n7-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“It very much depends on the individual, their medical background, whether they are in a high-risk group, and how the illness presents,” says Dr. Reiter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="c0ke3-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="c0ke3-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="c0ke3-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“There is a big difference between a bit of coughing and a sore throat and a significant illness with high fever and breathing difficulty. The individual situation determines whether testing is needed. If symptoms are mild and within a day, two or three there is improvement, there is no need to seek medical care. But if the illness is severe, with high fever and significant symptoms, a medical evaluation is necessary. We have to rule out worsening, a secondary bacterial infection or lung involvement from influenza.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="1pelu-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1pelu-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1pelu-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;In recent years, home test kits sold at pharmacies have also become available, allowing for rapid diagnosis of influenza and in some cases combined testing for influenza and COVID-19. These kits can help in cases of mild symptoms and guide initial management at home.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="5a4t1-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5a4t1-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5a4t1-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“In general, we always recommend looking first at the child’s overall condition,” says Dr. Efrat Wechsler, head of primary care and a pediatrician at Meuhedet Health Services. “The first step is to bring the fever down. When the fever drops, the child usually recovers somewhat — plays, eats and drinks. If there is no shortness of breath, you can wait through the first 48 hours and see how things develop.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="5ndfr-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2cnij-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2cnij-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2cnij-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;If the fever lasts more than two days, especially if it is very high, as is typical of the current wave, or if other concerning signs appear, including decreased alertness, reduced eating or drinking, breathing difficulties, a troubling cough or unusual rashes — the child should be examined, she says. “These can be signs of a secondary infection or another condition that requires treatment. Of course, this is not treatment of the illness itself, but of possible complications. Some complications are rare but can be very dangerous, such as inflammation of the heart muscle.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2our4-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2our4-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2our4-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Dr. Alon adds that with any illness, preventing further spread is essential. “It’s important not to go to work for two days while sick and then collapse, after having already infected everyone. People who are ill should stay home, wear a mask, drink plenty of fluids, eat appropriately and rest. Grandma used to say chicken soup — but above all, hydration, light food and rest are key.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="63l74-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="63l74-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="63l74-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Fever reducers can be used, she adds. “There is also a medication given in severe cases, called Tamiflu, but it is prescribed only in serious cases and only in hospitals.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="6kank-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6kank-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6kank-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Dr. Reiter stresses the importance of basic hygiene. “Wash hands, cough into your elbow and keep distance from people in high-risk groups, such as infants, older adults and those with weakened immune systems.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="fjnm0-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="fjnm0-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="fjnm0-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Alongside treating the illness itself, one of the main ways to reduce infection and complications is prevention — foremost through the influenza vaccine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2rui1-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2rui1-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2rui1-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“There are two types of flu vaccines,” says Dr. Reiter. “There is a live attenuated vaccine given as a nasal spray, and the familiar injected vaccine, which is inactivated. The live vaccine may cause very mild illness, but not significant disease, while the inactivated vaccine should not cause illness at all. Both are very similar in terms of effectiveness and the protection they provide.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="5vdo6-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="76jvc-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="76jvc-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="76jvc-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The vaccine, he says, is safe and recommended for all residents of Israel starting at 6 months of age and should be taken once a year ahead of the winter flu season. “This is especially important for people in high-risk groups. For them, vaccination can truly mean the difference between severe illness and hospitalization and a mild illness that passes easily.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2iv-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2iv-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2iv-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“This year alone, more than 800,000 people have already been vaccinated through Clalit, and that is not enough,” adds Dr. Alon. “At most, the inactivated vaccine can cause muscle aches for a day. Beyond that, there are no side effects. It does not cause the flu or complications. People remember the COVID-19 vaccines, which were developed quickly due to an emergency, but this is not the same. This is a vaccine that has existed for decades — safe and without side effects. Personally, I have been getting vaccinated for more than 25 years. As soon as vaccines are available, I am first in line.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="9n92e-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9n92e-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9n92e-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;She notes that the vaccine is available as a nasal spray for children and as an injection for the rest of the population, with a formulation for older adults and nursing home residents that contains additional virus strains.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:37:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE1tcmptQldLWWp5Q0R5V0hzREZZWWFYc0RUM0N5Nm5DU29fTmVxcy1YLUtyOFRDQXJTY3NDSWh5REZSUl9WdE55WENwUkx1VUg2QzFRakE2VGJ0TVVGTERLcU1UdHZRMjZaREE</guid></item><item><title>骨科专家分享5种食物，以预防维生素D缺乏症，并在阳光不足的冬季保持骨骼健康|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/orthopaedic-experts-share-5-foods-to-prevent-vitamin-d-deficiency-and-maintain-bone-health-during-sun-deprived-winters-101766582027818.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/orthopaedic-experts-share-5-foods-to-prevent-vitamin-d-deficiency-and-maintain-bone-health-during-sun-deprived-winters-101766582027818.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reduced sunlight exposure during winters quietly pushes a large section of the population toward &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/can-vitamin-d-levels-affect-colon-cancer-risk-florida-gastroenterologist-explains-the-link-between-the-two-101765888189094.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="vitamin D"&gt;vitamin D &lt;/a&gt;deficiency. While the issue is often underestimated, its consequences are far-reaching - ranging from bone pain and muscle weakness to &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/5-ortho-experts-share-the-top-5-joint-issues-people-faced-in-2025-back-pain-knee-osteoarthritis-and-tech-neck-101765884132221.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="joint"&gt;joint &lt;/a&gt;stiffness and increased fracture risk. Medical experts warn that during winter months, diet becomes a critical tool to maintain adequate Vitamin D levels.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/24/550x309/vitd_1766582537962_1766582550017.png" alt="Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)" title="Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/24/550x309/vitd_1766582537962_1766582550017.png" alt="Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)" title="Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fitness-trainer-warns-women-are-at-greater-risk-of-muscle-loss-in-winter-shares-4-tips-to-prevent-101766327891932.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Fitness trainer reveals women are at greater risk of muscle loss in winter; shares 4 tips to prevent"&gt;Fitness trainer reveals women are at greater risk of muscle loss in winter; shares 4 tips to prevent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;HT Lifestyle reached out to two orthopaedic experts - Dr Abhishek Vaish, Orthopaedic, Joint Replacement and Sports Injury Specialist at Apollo Hospital, and Dr Akhilesh Rathi, Director of Robotics, Joint Replacement and Orthopaedics at Sri Balaji Action Medical Institute and founder of Rathi Orthopedic and Spine Clinic - to discuss wintertime vitamin D deficiency and the most effective ways to optimise levels through diet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Vitamin D and winters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As daylight hours and sun exposure decline during winter, vitamin D levels in many people tend to drop as well. Dr Vaish highlights, “We routinely see patients complaining of unexplained &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/mumbai-orthopaedic-surgeon-explains-why-knee-pain-worsens-in-winter-shares-causes-symptoms-and-easy-tips-to-manage-it-101765811662475.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="knee pain"&gt;knee pain&lt;/a&gt;, backache, and muscle fatigue during winter. In many cases, the underlying cause turns out to be Vitamin D deficiency aggravated by lack of sun exposure.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He explains that vitamin D is essential for calcium absorption and bone mineralisation. When sunlight-driven synthesis drops, nutritional sources play a compensatory role - and a thoughtful winter diet can significantly help prevent deficiency.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fatty fishes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to Dr Vaish, salmon, mackerel, sardines and tuna are among the richest natural sources of vitamin D. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;He recommends including them regularly in your diet - at least two to three times a week - as this can help support bone density and muscle strength.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He notes, “Vitamin D from fatty fish is highly bioavailable and supports joint health, particularly in individuals with early arthritis or age-related bone loss.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Egg yolks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Rathi emphasises that egg yolks are often the most overlooked source, but they provide a steady amount of vitamin D, along with essential fats. For non-vegetarians, eggs are an easy addition to winter meals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He explains, “Egg yolks are nutritionally dense and help improve vitamin D intake without major dietary changes. When consumed sensibly, they benefit immunity and musculoskeletal health.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/24/original/photo-1699892726871-22e77ee1b75b_1766582217747.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Egg yolks are a great source of vitamin D.(Unsplash)" title="Egg yolks are a great source of vitamin D.(Unsplash)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Egg yolks are a great source of vitamin D.(Unsplash)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fortified foods&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fortified milk, yoghurt, cereals, and plant-based milk alternatives have emerged as practical vitamin D sources, especially for vegetarians. These foods are widely recommended during winter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Rathi notes, “Fortified foods are extremely useful for people who spend most of their day indoors - office workers, students, and elderly individuals - who get minimal sun exposure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;UV-exposed and sun-dried mushrooms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to Dr Rathi, certain mushrooms naturally produce vitamin D when exposed to ultraviolet light, making them another great source. Sun-dried mushrooms can be incorporated into curries, soups, and stir-fries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He explains, “This is one of the few plant-based natural Vitamin D options and works well for those avoiding animal products.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cod liver oil and select dairy products&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Vaish highlights that cod liver oil remains one of the most concentrated dietary sources of vitamin D. Cheese and butter contribute smaller amounts but can support daily intake when eaten as part of a balanced diet. He cautions, “While food helps maintain levels, individuals with deficiency may still require medical supplementation after proper testing.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In a season when sunlight is limited, informed dietary planning and expert advice remain the most effective tools to safeguard long-term health. Both doctors stress that persistent bone pain, muscle cramps, fatigue, or frequent infections during winter should not be ignored. Dr Vaish concludes, “Timely screening, dietary correction, and guided supplementation can prevent long-term bone and joint complications.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Adding to this, Dr Rathi emphasises a preventive approach, stating, “Vitamin D deficiency is not just a bone issue - it impacts immunity, energy levels, and overall well-being.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Winter should be seen as a time to proactively support the body through nutrition, testing when required, and medical guidance rather than waiting for symptoms to appear.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:31:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgJBVV95cUxOaHU3OFFESTVFZloyaTJSX1BGeHh2Mk9uQU1QSEl5QWhab2lIWktpNHkySkVmTXozVDNNTWJFZkxSak9yQ3RQMTZxbHhOOEUtaGJOdjRTbllqcHhyNnZjU0xsYk5TemRBNnQ2aW9CbEpKODNoWWN2czRyNmtnNTgxTjM2aGJqdzN6ckd2X20wRHhrcEltYzlmZF9GajV1MVdHVWFrUmxONHJmaDJoNmc4M2VjQlZIQWNxbnpDRDVwblFNbWdGN0M0MHBOZU40elZvYXBWajRMc2dfQ29mMV90dGNhVWd5NlNqb0R6Y2p5aE9UMlR0bng2RE9LMk1heEZubk5KY2xlVDRrdUswN000ZmhKYmxIQdIBmwJBVV95cUxNTkFVNWoyNEFIeU5scG5uajRRdlJVZWFiR29JNXJhQ3BGRjJnNFQ5NUlqVFJuemlyRjNWOFg0aHZWa0tPZkxhZU4tQTBxalFZWWZQMUFBT2t4QlV0d3dIMmNqRVBmMmNxUTFkdzFlQjBuSnA0Um5Kc1VGMDBPRE00c0VpTE1UUGp4Nl85UVpKa2tUTU15cl9aSVdaemx1U3JHaUdha0hrWk5LR3FNV2pRSlhqTzVxY1ptcU1WVmM2ME11dURCcTR2NFVvTE03WDlnYm1xb2dKcEdWaTQ5SjJQdmVMRVNwVnE3c04xTkJKblJBRFhCaG9SOTdrRWY2Y1pxVm1kYnlDeGoxcldheDFZTmtxQUh3QUFWalhV</guid></item><item><title>Mark Damon -频道3000</title><link>https://www.channel3000.com/obituaries/mark-damon/article_9c04abc2-5bc3-4bd5-a09e-ce8f100abfdb.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;Mark James Damon, age 61, passed away on Tuesday, December 9, 2025, at his home in Madison, Wisconsin. Mark was born on November 26, 1964, grew up in Stoughton, and attended LaFollette High School in Madison, graduating in 1984. Mark was a dedicated State of Wisconsin employee for over 35 years, delivering mail and pharmaceutical supplies throughout Central Wisconsin Center with courtesy, humor, and a movie-star smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Living with cerebral palsy that affected his arms and legs, Mark mastered the operation of a series of motorized wheelchairs outfitted with chin and foot controls for ignition, gear-shifting, and steering, and he pushed these vehicles to their limits. He had a strong bent for mechanics, an eagle eye for detail, and an unflagging enthusiasm for creative problem-solving. Generations of occupational, vocational, and social work professionals owe a debt of gratitude to Mark for being willing to experiment with new devices and systems such as a foot-controlled computer mouse and door openers; mouth-held tools for use with keyboards and dial pads; and voice-activated appliances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark was also a skilled instructor, patiently training countless aides and attendants on the intricacies of his assistive technology, as well as food preparation, household maintenance, and daily care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_top" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark was always up for adventure, exploring new trails and seeing where they might lead. Some favorite spots included Camp Wawbeek in Wisconsin Dells, his sister Bev’s house in Tacoma, Washington, and the annual Mad City Model Railroad Show.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark will be sorely missed: his kindness, intelligence, courage, humor, and friendship brought light and joy to the lives of many, many people. He was preceded in death by his loving foster parents, Ruth and Harry Kirby, and his dear friend Audrey. He leaves behind many foster brothers, sisters, nephews, and nieces; long-time friend and roommate Kevin Danz; and scores of other friends and colleagues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many thanks are owed to the staff at Lakeview Supported Living Services, Community Work Services, FA, Inc., My Choice Wisconsin, UW Health, Unity Point Health – Meriter Hospital, and St. Croix Hospice for the care and support they provided to Mark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A memorial gathering for Mark will be held at Ryan Funeral Home, 2418 N. Sherman Drive, Madison, Wisconsin on Friday, January 9, from 4 to 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In lieu of flowers, donations in Mark’s memory may be made to one of Mark’s favorite organizations, Easterseals Wisconsin, to support Camp Wawbeek and Respite Camp, using their Online Giving Form | Easterseals Wisconsin or by mailing contributions to Easterseals Wisconsin at 1468 N. High Point Rd., Ste. 202, Middleton, WI 53562. To view his obituary and leave a memory, please visit: &lt;a href="https://www.ryanfuneralservice.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;www.ryanfuneralservice.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;​COPYRIGHT 2025 BY CHANNEL 3000. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. THIS MATERIAL MAY NOT BE PUBLISHED, BROADCAST, REWRITTEN OR REDISTRIBUTED.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Channel 3000</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOZEdCREZxY2RsVk03VVZ1b25ydGM4NklaOFUtREJDQy1oYlpIakdGSkw1T2NmSVNSWTE5YlZOQm9JNTh4MnFyVnRfYzROWDk0OXJaQ3JkNXBNS1B6RjZtSkFndmNCc2ljMXdLVGlwc3N3Qk9NMk5YWHNENnRDRmJ4MlRKTlFMcG9GSUQyRXBaSFFKdzRWQTNpaGpfWWdSendl</guid></item></channel></rss>