<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>根据专家的说法，如果你不吃早餐，你的身体会发生什么。- Stewartville Star | Here’s what happens to your body if you skip breakfast, according to an expert. - Stewartville Star</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiugFBVV95cUxPQzE2TVdwa3B2NUY5VjlXZmpJa2V0cnM2dXVOUk9NQTBOTS1LTlVYZlJlOVRPakJYZ3lqNmtqM0xmWGJjeXFMWmN2Ul9hX090X1FzYmNSano5aGt2Uy1Jb0N3eHotSmdEai1ZTGM1Sk1aU1llMDB4ZlQxQmlRN0tza0dYSDVDZXhoSHBWWHdLcEZuUl82aDVtNVBuSTRYQmsxSTlnRWhlazFSenV1Nnk3RFZBdzNaRXZmOGc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content" itemprop="text"&gt;
			&lt;details class="toc"&gt;&lt;summary&gt;&lt;span class="show"&gt;Show table of content &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="hide"&gt;Hide table of content &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Breaking the overnight fast with a morning meal has long been considered a nutritional cornerstone. Yet, millions regularly skip breakfast, either through habit or deliberate intermittent fasting practices. A nutrition expert has recently revealed surprising effects this common habit has on your body, challenging conventional wisdom about the “most important meal of the day.”



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="toc-title-1"&gt;The surprising metabolic impact of skipping breakfast&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;When you finish your evening meal around 8 PM, your body begins a natural fasting period. By midnight, your blood sugar typically returns to normal levels. By 6 AM, after approximately ten hours without food, your digestive system has essentially reset itself. If you then continue to delay your first meal, your metabolism enters an interesting state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="think-display-in-text" id="think-2761774683"&gt;

&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-7994036760405448" data-ad-slot="7418520743" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The twelve-hour mark is when your body transitions to fat-burning mode,” explains dietitian Wintertok7, who has studied breakfast habits extensively. “Around 10 AM, this fat-burning process accelerates significantly, especially if you’ve incorporated morning exercise into your routine.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="related-article simple" href="https://thinkstewartville.com/2025/04/25/heres-the-actual-distance-you-should-walk-every-day-to-get-back-in-shape/"&gt;
                        &lt;span class="label dynamic"&gt;Well being&lt;/span&gt;
                        &lt;span class="title"&gt;Here’s the actual distance you should walk every day to get back in shape.&lt;/span&gt;
                        &lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" class="icon icon-chevron-right" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 384 512" fill="currentColor"&gt;&lt;path d="M342.6 233.4c12.5 12.5 12.5 32.8 0 45.3l-192 192c-12.5 12.5-32.8 12.5-45.3 0s-12.5-32.8 0-45.3L274.7 256 105.4 86.6c-12.5-12.5-12.5-32.8 0-45.3s32.8-12.5 45.3 0l192 192z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This metabolic shift represents the core benefit many intermittent fasting enthusiasts seek. By extending the overnight fast until midday, your body maintains this fat-burning state for longer periods. Breaking your fast around noon with a protein-rich meal that includes healthy fats and fiber helps maintain stable blood glucose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="think-display-adsense-2" id="think-1422578327"&gt;

&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-7994036760405448" data-ad-slot="7418520743" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Research suggests that this approach may help avoid insulin spikes that typically follow carbohydrate-heavy breakfast options. For those working toward &lt;a href="https://thinkstewartville.com/2025/02/01/doctor-reveals-five-hidden-effects-of-stopping-alcohol-for-30-days-has-on-the-brain/"&gt;specific health goals&lt;/a&gt;, this metabolic advantage could complement other healthy habits like reducing alcohol consumption.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="toc-title-2"&gt;Energy regulation and cognitive function without morning meals&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Morning fasting creates distinct energy patterns throughout the day. Without the immediate glucose influx from breakfast, your body maintains more stable energy levels by drawing from fat stores. This can prevent the mid-morning energy crashes many experience after consuming sugar-laden breakfast options.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, cognitive function responses vary significantly between individuals. Some report enhanced mental clarity during extended morning fasts, while others experience concentration difficulties, irritability, or decreased productivity. These variations often relate to metabolic flexibility—how efficiently your body switches between glucose and fat for fuel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="related-article simple" href="https://thinkstewartville.com/2025/04/15/heres-what-to-do-if-you-wake-up-in-the-middle-of-the-night-and-cant-get-back-to-sleep-according-to-this-expert/"&gt;
                        &lt;span class="label dynamic"&gt;Well being&lt;/span&gt;
                        &lt;span class="title"&gt;Here’s what to do if you wake up in the middle of the night and can’t get back to sleep, according to this expert&lt;/span&gt;
                        &lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" class="icon icon-chevron-right" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 384 512" fill="currentColor"&gt;&lt;path d="M342.6 233.4c12.5 12.5 12.5 32.8 0 45.3l-192 192c-12.5 12.5-32.8 12.5-45.3 0s-12.5-32.8 0-45.3L274.7 256 105.4 86.6c-12.5-12.5-12.5-32.8 0-45.3s32.8-12.5 45.3 0l192 192z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nutrition expert Nicci Roscoe notes, “While intermittent fasting works beautifully for some, others genuinely need that morning metabolic kickstart to function optimally.” Individual factors like sleep quality, stress levels, and activity demands all influence your morning nutritional needs.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those seeking to improve their mental resilience, breakfast timing may be worth examining. The relationship between nutritional habits and psychological fortitude is complex, as demonstrated in studies of &lt;a href="https://thinkstewartville.com/2024/11/30/people-who-recover-quickly-failure-tend-display-these-8-traits/"&gt;traits associated with resilience&lt;/a&gt;. Your breakfast choices—or decision to skip—may influence how effectively you handle daily challenges.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="toc-title-3"&gt;Who should reconsider the breakfast-skipping trend&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Despite potential benefits for some, breakfast remains crucial for specific populations. Growing children and adolescents typically require regular morning nutrition to support development and academic performance. Athletes with high energy demands often benefit from early fueling to optimize training quality and recovery.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Individuals with blood sugar regulation issues, including diabetes or hypoglycemia, should approach breakfast skipping cautiously. Similarly, those taking certain medications requiring food or experiencing certain digestive conditions may need consistent morning meals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="related-article simple" href="https://thinkstewartville.com/2025/04/05/after-knee-surgery-a-17yo-teenager-forgets-his-native-language/"&gt;
                        &lt;span class="label dynamic"&gt;Well being&lt;/span&gt;
                        &lt;span class="title"&gt;After knee surgery, a 17yo teenager forgets his native language.&lt;/span&gt;
                        &lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" class="icon icon-chevron-right" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 384 512" fill="currentColor"&gt;&lt;path d="M342.6 233.4c12.5 12.5 12.5 32.8 0 45.3l-192 192c-12.5 12.5-32.8 12.5-45.3 0s-12.5-32.8 0-45.3L274.7 256 105.4 86.6c-12.5-12.5-12.5-32.8 0-45.3s32.8-12.5 45.3 0l192 192z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For those juggling busy schedules, combining breakfast skipping with &lt;a href="https://thinkstewartville.com/2025/03/05/is-walking-1-mile-per-day-enough-to-reap-health-benefits-experts-weigh-in/"&gt;simple exercise habits like daily walking&lt;/a&gt; may provide manageable health improvements. However, breakfast timing should complement rather than complicate your overall wellness approach.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People struggling with disordered eating patterns should be particularly mindful about meal timing strategies. What begins as intermittent fasting can sometimes reinforce problematic relationships with food. Working with nutrition professionals helps ensure fasting practices support rather than undermine health goals.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="toc-title-4"&gt;Finding your optimal breakfast strategy&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Rather than viewing breakfast habits through a rigid lens, nutrition experts increasingly recommend personalized approaches based on individual responses. Self-experimentation with different meal timing patterns—while tracking energy, hunger, mood, and performance metrics—can reveal your optimal strategy.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you decide breakfast benefits you, prioritize protein-rich options while minimizing sugar and caffeine. This approach provides sustained energy without dramatic blood sugar fluctuations. For those who thrive without breakfast, ensuring adequate nutrition during eating windows becomes especially important.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="related-article simple" href="https://thinkstewartville.com/2025/04/04/how-long-should-you-walk-per-day-for-effective-weight-loss-a-fitness-coach-explains/"&gt;
                        &lt;span class="label dynamic"&gt;Well being&lt;/span&gt;
                        &lt;span class="title"&gt;How long should you walk per day for effective weight loss? A fitness coach explains.&lt;/span&gt;
                        &lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" class="icon icon-chevron-right" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 384 512" fill="currentColor"&gt;&lt;path d="M342.6 233.4c12.5 12.5 12.5 32.8 0 45.3l-192 192c-12.5 12.5-32.8 12.5-45.3 0s-12.5-32.8 0-45.3L274.7 256 105.4 86.6c-12.5-12.5-12.5-32.8 0-45.3s32.8-12.5 45.3 0l192 192z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Developing self-awareness around hunger signals represents a crucial skill regardless of your breakfast preference. Learning to distinguish between habitual eating, emotional hunger, and true physiological need helps create sustainable nutrition patterns that &lt;a href="https://thinkstewartville.com/2024/12/20/if-you-want-boost-your-confidence-say-goodbye-these-8-self-doubting-behaviors/"&gt;boost confidence in your health decisions&lt;/a&gt;.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember that nutritional needs evolve with life circumstances. During particularly demanding periods, you might benefit from adjusting your breakfast approach. Remaining flexible rather than dogmatic allows for adaptation to changing requirements.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps most importantly, protect your dietary choices from unnecessary social pressure. Whether you’re a breakfast enthusiast or prefer extended morning fasts, learning &lt;a href="https://thinkstewartville.com/2024/12/15/8-ways-protect-your-peace-when-dealing-toxic-people/"&gt;techniques to protect your peace&lt;/a&gt; when others challenge your well-considered habits helps maintain consistent nutrition practices.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The breakfast debate highlights a broader nutritional truth: individualization matters more than universal rules. By understanding your unique metabolic responses, lifestyle demands, and personal preferences, you can develop morning nutrition habits that truly serve your health goals—whether that includes breakfast or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="related-article simple" href="https://thinkstewartville.com/2025/04/03/this-little-known-leafy-vegetable-is-actually-the-secret-to-youth-among-the-japanese-and-koreans/"&gt;
                        &lt;span class="label dynamic"&gt;Well being&lt;/span&gt;
                        &lt;span class="title"&gt;This little-known leafy vegetable is actually the secret to youth among the Japanese and Koreans.&lt;/span&gt;
                        &lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" class="icon icon-chevron-right" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 384 512" fill="currentColor"&gt;&lt;path d="M342.6 233.4c12.5 12.5 12.5 32.8 0 45.3l-192 192c-12.5 12.5-32.8 12.5-45.3 0s-12.5-32.8 0-45.3L274.7 256 105.4 86.6c-12.5-12.5-12.5-32.8 0-45.3s32.8-12.5 45.3 0l192 192z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;
		&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Stewartville Star</author><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 13:33:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxPQzE2TVdwa3B2NUY5VjlXZmpJa2V0cnM2dXVOUk9NQTBOTS1LTlVYZlJlOVRPakJYZ3lqNmtqM0xmWGJjeXFMWmN2Ul9hX090X1FzYmNSano5aGt2Uy1Jb0N3eHotSmdEai1ZTGM1Sk1aU1llMDB4ZlQxQmlRN0tza0dYSDVDZXhoSHBWWHdLcEZuUl82aDVtNVBuSTRYQmsxSTlnRWhlazFSenV1Nnk3RFZBdzNaRXZmOGc</guid></item><item><title>专家最担心的4种营养素短缺- HuffPost | The 4 Shortfall Nutrients Experts Worry Most About - HuffPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiswFBVV95cUxPZmV4Q0pFUndwOVlicktYeEdRQ0FuXzE2b2ozc1k4M19pSUY5R1FKOEFISG84XzdLNGZxOFlKRk1ZcjBqRXd2Z3Q3OXdXVVhwUWkyRWhFUmE2UzZoQTI0ZmgxTFFhYlJ2TGJSWU1UWEdiOVdGc1FkeG1zNlhyYVZuTl9rN3B4aWRXSmRXQWhDQktfMV9GMWpGZ1NaUThvLXdFZjV5WXBTLVR5NGxqbENSX2xMZ9IBuAFBVV95cUxPQ0NiYzNXTlh5LVB5dTJWSUxqY3pDNi00WGpmODVEc1c3S3hmVFJMVmtOTVV1YzFzVXh2eHp1ZUFZYXVSeDRvSWFkVkhRaktveXRSeFB5M0RGZnVvdzhkZ3JQVThZQ0xXbmc4TEY3R2dGbVMzcWVsVlZ5T3lBaHRjaDNma0pBZmZnY3RXRTJURU9OM3FLdGFLa1lBRHRWb0hZZ2daZlVlWjVtWEFBRXZrTmF6Uk9ROE1l?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you’re eating the way most people in America do these days, you’re probably falling short of the vital nutrients you need. Fewer than &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ers.usda.gov/amber-waves/2024/september/satisfying-fruit-and-vegetable-recommendations-possible-for-under-3-a-day-data-analysis-shows" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="10% of us" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="http://www.ers.usda.gov/amber-waves/2024/september/satisfying-fruit-and-vegetable-recommendations-possible-for-under-3-a-day-data-analysis-shows" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;10% of us&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; meet the daily recommended intake for vegetables (2 to 3 cups a day), and only &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ers.usda.gov/amber-waves/2024/september/satisfying-fruit-and-vegetable-recommendations-possible-for-under-3-a-day-data-analysis-shows" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="20% of us" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="http://www.ers.usda.gov/amber-waves/2024/september/satisfying-fruit-and-vegetable-recommendations-possible-for-under-3-a-day-data-analysis-shows" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;20% of us&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; eat enough fruit (1 1/2 to 2 cups daily). The situation is even worse with what the U.S. Department of Agriculture and Department of Health and Human Services call &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="shortfall nutrients" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;shortfall nutrients&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, which are important but underconsumed nutrients.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The current shortfall list includes vitamins A, D, E and C, along with folate, calcium, magnesium, fiber and potassium. For adolescent and premenopausal females, iron is also a shortfall nutrient. Of these, four have been classified as “nutrients of public health concern” because their underconsumption has been linked in scientific literature to adverse health outcomes. Those vital four are fiber, calcium, vitamin D and potassium. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It’s a downward trend that concerns nutrition experts. Registered dietitian nutritionist &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/sharonpalmerrd" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Sharon Palmer" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.instagram.com/sharonpalmerrd" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sharon Palmer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; said: “Unfortunately, our diets are not as nutrient-rich as we wish they could be, for reasons that include access and affordability of healthful foods and reliance on overly processed foods over minimally processed foods. People aren’t cooking as much as they used to, and they’re snacking more instead of sitting down to meals. That adds up to more refined foods, and fewer nutrients, on the plate.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The situation, for Palmer, has less to do with the sludge we’re currently consuming than with all the important things we &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;aren’t&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt; eating: “We’re missing out on nutritious foods that are so rich in these nutrients, such as fruits, vegetables, whole grains and beans.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We asked nutrition experts to tell us more about these “public health concern” nutrients — to find out why they’re so important and how to eat enough of them. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Health Concern No. 1: Fiber&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Nearly every nutritionist interviewed for this story led off with a plea for us to eat &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/signs-not-enough-fiber-digestions_l_66ba37afe4b0eabd2393b96d" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="more fiber" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="66ba37afe4b0eabd2393b96d" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;more fiber&lt;/a&gt;, right now. They are really serious about this, explaining that it’s important for many more reasons than just avoiding constipation. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Registered dietitian &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.theprebioticdietitian.com/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Kara Landau" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="http://www.theprebioticdietitian.com/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kara Landau&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; said: “Dietary fiber is essential not only for a healthy digestive tract, but it also plays an important role in our metabolic health, such as protection from heart disease and improving blood glucose regulation.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Eating more fiber comes with other benefits, too, said registered dietician nutritionist &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/chelseyamernutrition" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Chelsey Amer" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.instagram.com/chelseyamernutrition" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Chelsey Amer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;: “When you focus [on] boosting fiber intake, you’ll also consume more of other shortfall nutrients, like vitamins A, D, E and C, which are found in fruits and vegetables, or the magnesium and iron found in beans.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Most of us are falling woefully short of fiber goals, said registered dietician &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://godutchmen.com/staff-directory/morgan-walker/469" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Morgan Walker" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://godutchmen.com/staff-directory/morgan-walker/469" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Morgan Walker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, an adjunct professor at Lebanon Valley College: “The recommended daily intake of fiber is 25 grams for women and 38 grams for men, but most Americans consume fewer than 15 grams per day,” she said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;And fiber under-consumption can’t just be solved with a morning bowl of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ku42Iszh9KM" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Colon Blow" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ku42Iszh9KM" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Colon Blow&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, Landau said: “You need to look for diversity, so rather than just selecting one high-fiber bran-based cereal, it’s more beneficial to include different high-fiber choices all day long.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;The recommended daily calcium intake is 1,000 milligrams for most adults.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Health Concern No. 2: Calcium&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We all grew up hearing that calcium would help build strong bones, but now that we’re done growing, many of us feel that we don’t need it anymore. But this under-appreciated nutrient is of lifelong importance, Landau said. “It’s important for ongoing bone and heart health,” she said, adding a reminder that vitamins D and K2 enhance its absorption.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Registered dietician nutritionist &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nutritionnowcounseling.com/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Lauren Manaker" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.nutritionnowcounseling.com/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lauren Manaker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; highlighted the benefits of keeping up with calcium, D and K2: “Together, they reduce the risk of osteoporosis and fractures later in life.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/nutrition-and-healthy-eating/in-depth/calcium-supplements/art-20047097" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="recommended daily calcium intake" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/nutrition-and-healthy-eating/in-depth/calcium-supplements/art-20047097" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;recommended daily calcium intake&lt;/a&gt; is 1,000 milligrams for most adults, increasing to 1,200 milligrams for women over 50 and men over 70. While dairy is a great source of calcium, there are plenty of other options, the experts said. “It’s becoming more well-accepted that there are other great sources such as broccoli, leafy greens, chia and basil seeds,” Landau said. “A great example of a calcium-rich snack would be Greek yogurt topped with chia seeds and fruit.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Health Concern No. 3: Vitamin D&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The role of vitamin D is continuing to be studied, and it seems as if new benefits emerge all the time. “It’s well-known for its role in bone health, but emerging research has also highlighted its broader role in overall health,” Walker said, noting that it’s been shown to boost immune function and has been linked to a lower risk of chronic diseases such as heart disease, diabetes and certain cancers. “There’s also research showing an influence on mental health, with vitamin D deficiencies associated with conditions like depression,” she added. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminD-HealthProfessional/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="recommended daily intake of vitamin D" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminD-HealthProfessional/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;&lt;span&gt;recommended daily intake of vitamin D&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; is 600 international units, or IU, for adults under 70 and 800 IU for adults over 70. Walker noted that many experts believe that higher amounts may be necessary for optimal health. Approximately &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/15050-vitamin-d-vitamin-d-deficiency#:~:text=Vitamin%20D%20deficiency%20is%20a%20common%20global%20issue.,States%20have%20vitamin%20D%20deficiency." role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="35% of adults" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/15050-vitamin-d-vitamin-d-deficiency#:~:text=Vitamin%20D%20deficiency%20is%20a%20common%20global%20issue.,States%20have%20vitamin%20D%20deficiency." data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="12"&gt;&lt;span&gt;35% of adults&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in the United States have a vitamin D deficiency, research shows. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It’s an increasingly common situation, said registered dietician &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/realnutrition/?api=Top%2Bpartners%F0%9F%8E%88We%2Btailor%2Bour%2Bsolutions%2Bto%2Byour%2Bneeds%2Bas%2Ban%2Binvestor.%2B.wbao&amp;amp;hl=af" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Amy Shapiro" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.instagram.com/realnutrition/?api=Top%2Bpartners%F0%9F%8E%88We%2Btailor%2Bour%2Bsolutions%2Bto%2Byour%2Bneeds%2Bas%2Ban%2Binvestor.%2B.wbao&amp;amp;hl=af" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="13"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amy Shapiro&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, lead nutritionist at ButcherBox. “Almost everyone is deficient in vitamin D, which can be hard to get from food,” she said. “Lean into sustainably sourced salmon, grass-fed beef, crate-free pork and mushrooms, and you’ll get a good dose. By setting up your plate to be 1/4 lean protein, 1/2 vegetables and 1/4 complex carbohydrates, you can improve your odds of meeting nutrient needs.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Anna Blazhuk via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Anna Blazhuk via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;A medium banana contains 422 milligrams of potassium.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Health Concern No. 4: Potassium&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you can’t remember the last time you ate a banana or a potato (chips and fries don’t count), you might be one of the millions who are falling short of the amount of potassium you need. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Most people eat &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK587683" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="less than 2,600 milligrams of potassium" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK587683" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="14"&gt;&lt;span&gt;less than 2,600 milligrams of potassium&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; per day, which is significantly lower than the recommended 4,700 milligrams,” said registered dietician nutritionist &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.instagram.com/plantpoweredkidneys" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Jen Hernandez" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="http://www.instagram.com/plantpoweredkidneys" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="15"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Jen Hernandez&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. One of the reasons it’s important to get enough of this nutrient, she said, is because potassium plays an important role in regulating blood pressure. “But the foods richest in potassium — fruits, vegetables, nuts, seeds and legumes — aren’t eaten enough as part of the standard American diet,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;One reason for this imbalance, said registered dietician nutritionist &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/corymygrant/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Cory Mygrant" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.linkedin.com/in/corymygrant/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="16"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cory Mygrant&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, is the high sodium content in our diets. “Many people consume too much sodium, often due to processed foods, and so they aren’t getting enough potassium to balance it out. Potassium is a crucial nutrient that works alongside sodium to help maintain the right balance of fluids and electrolytes in your body. This imbalance can lead to high blood pressure, which is a major contributor to cardiovascular disease.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Two top sources of potassium, potatoes and bananas, have been “demonized” in some circles, Hernandez said, but they’re great sources of a vital nutrient: “A medium baked potato has 164 calories and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/170030/nutrients" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="952 milligrams of potassium" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/170030/nutrients" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="17"&gt;&lt;span&gt;952 milligrams of potassium&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, and a medium banana has just 105 calories, but &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/173944/nutrients" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="422 milligrams of potassium" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/173944/nutrients" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="18"&gt;&lt;span&gt;422 milligrams of potassium&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whole Foods, Not Pills, Will Make A Difference&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;All this talk of shortfalls might leave you wondering if it’s at all possible to keep yourself well nourished these days. But if you’re reaching for a bottle of multivitamins right to supplement the gaps, you may want to slow your roll, experts said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Registered dietician nutritionist &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mpmnutrition.com/about" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Marissa Karp" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.mpmnutrition.com/about" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="19"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Marissa Karp&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; had this advice: “While supplements can help us bridge the gap and serve as an insurance policy, they aren’t a replacement for eating nourishing foods. If you aren’t already eating well, moving your body, drinking water and managing your stress, don’t waste money on supplements. Taking supplements and then eating processed foods is not the same as eating a whole foods diet and using supplements to help ensure you’re getting enough.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="support-huffpost-entry" class="cli support-huffpost-mid-article primary-cli cli cli-text cli-support-huffpost hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__content-wrapper"&gt;&lt;h4 class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;We Don't Work For Billionaires. We Work For You.&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message-container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message support-huffpost__message--control"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Big money interests are running the government — and influencing the news you read. While other outlets are retreating behind paywalls and bending the knee to political pressure, HuffPost is proud to be unbought and unfiltered. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="Will you help us keep it that way?" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="21"&gt;Will you help us keep it that way?&lt;/a&gt; You can even access our stories ad-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;You've supported HuffPost before, and we'll be honest — we could use your help again. We won't back down from our mission of providing free, fair news during this critical moment. But we can't do it without you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the first time, &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="21"&gt;we're offering an ad-free experience&lt;/a&gt; to qualifying contributors who support our fearless journalism. We hope you'll join us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;You've supported HuffPost before, and we'll be honest — we could use your help again. We won't back down from our mission of providing free, fair news during this critical moment. But we can't do it without you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the first time, &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="21"&gt;we're offering an ad-free experience&lt;/a&gt; to qualifying contributors who support our fearless journalism. We hope you'll join us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a class="js-entry-link cli-support-huffpost__support-button accent-button" href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" data-vars-item-name-overwritable="support-huffpost" data-vars-item-name="Support HuffPost" data-vars-item-type="button" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="20"&gt;Support HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="support-huffpost-login"&gt;Already contributed? &lt;a class="js-entry-link" href="https://login.huffpost.com/login?dest=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.huffpost.com%2Fentry%2Fthe-4-shortfall-nutrients-experts-worry-most-about-goog_l_680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c%3Fhp_auth_done%3D1" data-vars-item-name="Log in to hide these messages" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/login" data-vars-target-content-type="utility" data-vars-type="web_internal_link"&gt;Log in to hide these messages.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="support-huffpost-entry-variant" class="cli support-huffpost-mid-article primary-cli cli cli-text cli-support-huffpost cli-support-huffpost--variant hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__content-wrapper"&gt;&lt;h4 class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;We Work For You.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Not Billionaires.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message-container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message support-huffpost__message--control"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Big money interests are running the government — and influencing the news you read. While other outlets are retreating behind paywalls and bending the knee to political pressure, HuffPost is proud to be unbought and unfiltered. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="Will you help us keep it that way?" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="21"&gt;Will you help us keep it that way?&lt;/a&gt; You can even access our stories ad-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__sub-headline"&gt;Protect Free Journalism&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a class="js-entry-link cli-support-huffpost__support-button accent-button" href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" data-vars-item-name-overwritable="support-huffpost" data-vars-item-name="Support HuffPost" data-vars-item-type="button" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="20"&gt;Support HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="support-huffpost-login"&gt;Already contributed? &lt;a class="js-entry-link" href="https://login.huffpost.com/login?dest=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.huffpost.com%2Fentry%2Fthe-4-shortfall-nutrients-experts-worry-most-about-goog_l_680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c%3Fhp_auth_done%3D1" data-vars-item-name="Log in to hide these messages" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680a68f8e4b0d1cc4a5a853c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/login" data-vars-target-content-type="utility" data-vars-type="web_internal_link"&gt;Log in to hide these messages.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;She offered this example of the joy of whole foods: “When you eat an avocado, it’s not just about the potassium or dietary fiber, but the synergy of the nutrients working together. It’s how the fat and fiber in the avocado slow down your gastric emptying and help keep you fuller longer. It’s also about how satisfying it tastes.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Staying well-nourished is much simpler than you might think, Walker said. “We don’t need extreme diets or supplements to fill these nutrient gaps, but simple, intentional dietary shifts that can make a significant impact. By increasing whole foods like fruits, vegetables, whole grains, legumes, nuts, seeds, dairy and lean proteins, you can improve your intake of these critical shortfall nutrients, leading to better long-term health and disease prevention.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 11:00:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxPZmV4Q0pFUndwOVlicktYeEdRQ0FuXzE2b2ozc1k4M19pSUY5R1FKOEFISG84XzdLNGZxOFlKRk1ZcjBqRXd2Z3Q3OXdXVVhwUWkyRWhFUmE2UzZoQTI0ZmgxTFFhYlJ2TGJSWU1UWEdiOVdGc1FkeG1zNlhyYVZuTl9rN3B4aWRXSmRXQWhDQktfMV9GMWpGZ1NaUThvLXdFZjV5WXBTLVR5NGxqbENSX2xMZ9IBuAFBVV95cUxPQ0NiYzNXTlh5LVB5dTJWSUxqY3pDNi00WGpmODVEc1c3S3hmVFJMVmtOTVV1YzFzVXh2eHp1ZUFZYXVSeDRvSWFkVkhRaktveXRSeFB5M0RGZnVvdzhkZ3JQVThZQ0xXbmc4TEY3R2dGbVMzcWVsVlZ5T3lBaHRjaDNma0pBZmZnY3RXRTJURU9OM3FLdGFLa1lBRHRWb0hZZ2daZlVlWjVtWEFBRXZrTmF6Uk9ROE1l</guid></item><item><title>我开车去上大学，由于数百万人鲜为人知的状况，突然失明了10年-每日邮报 | I was driving to college and suddenly went BLIND for 10 years due to little-known condition millions have - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxNM0p4d1VlN0VTVTAxUVNHZlRkdjVrcHo3OFRPVGVUbVF0dElSX0RINlo1OWh0OXF4czBFTXpCdE9GTlR6Z3ItaVlwdEpVRllSZFhod1NxLUNKbHRiRW00VlNabWVaemNQeHlfZ0E5TWZKVl8zdjBSX1BnVi1jMUJSQUJYTUY5aUU3bUVFamkzOTZqTnU4MnfSAZsBQVVfeXFMT0tDdFgwTng0UjYtRXg4dlREbDA1aWQ3UkhsS2hVTmtsMVdHLTZRa2hfRi1CWjJFVFRHQmRPRnIzN29GeWhSM3ItZDZXcXlmaHB4NkcyMnNaQ2lwcXRJajN1aTZWek9JRHdZaDhkRFVwSEJiYXZZb2NSa2ZNdmJGWm8zdHdKNWoxVElESEltU2QxcDVvRDJkejRTWG8?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sierra Domb was driving to college when suddenly her vision completely blacked out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She managed to swerve off the road and park despite physically shaking with fear. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A few minutes later her &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14622833/experts-reveal-eye-mucus-bacteria-sleep-wake-up.html"&gt;eyesight gradually returned &lt;/a&gt;— but it has never been the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;That moment, back in 2015, marked the beginning of her battle with an extremely rare neurological condition known as visual snow syndrome. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The condition is often described by people as seeing flickering, tiny dots or 'snow' &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14555215/PROF-ROB-GALLOWAY-children-BLINDNESS-screens-myopia-treatment.html"&gt;across their entire field of vision.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Shockingly, doctors say about 2 to 3 percent of people have it to varying degrees but it's challenging to get a precise number of officially diagnosed cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For most sufferers it's something they live with but, because of the lack of scientific research, it can be very difficult to get a diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A decade on from her initial blackout, Domb, now 30, says it has left her feeling like she's 'seeing through a TV with a very bad reception'. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She likens it to a snow globe that's been shaken up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Sierra Domb was driving to college when suddenly her vision completely blacked out. That moment, back in 2015, marked the beginning of her battle with an extremely rare neurological condition known as visual snow syndrome&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She also has to contend with double vision, extreme sensitivity to light, ringing in her ears, and constant headaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her symptoms became so debilitating that she could no longer drive and had to take an extended leave of absence from college. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Because visual snow syndrome is so rare and difficult to diagnose, it took years before Domb finally understood what was happening to her body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now, she's leading the charge to raise awareness for the condition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'For years, I struggled to find answers, only to be misdiagnosed and constantly dismissed by medical professionals who claimed my symptoms "didn't exist" or told me I was "too young" to have serious health problems,' Domb told the Daily Mail.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Soon, even familiar faces and beautiful landscapes transformed into disorienting, nightmarish experiences.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Cleveland Clinic notes that visual snow syndrome is a relatively new diagnosis — the term was only coined in 2013 — and researchers still don't fully understand what causes it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some scientists believe it may be the result of overactivity in the parts of the brain responsible for processing images. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In some cases, experts have found the syndrome in people who also suffer from anxiety or migraines — conditions often preceded by 'auras,' or sensory disturbances that can include ringing in the ears, flashing lights, or even speech and language problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Auras associated with anxiety are often linked to heightened sensitivity and hyperstimulation, which can trigger visual or sensory distortions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While Domb was desperately hunting for a diagnosis, she was prescribed medications that actually made her symptoms worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The doctors who took me seriously warned that I was likely going blind, but they couldn't confirm when or if it would happen, as my medical tests on my eyes consistently came back "normal",' she recalled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This is because visual snow syndrome is a neurological condition so standard eye tests will not work.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There is no cure for visual snow syndrome but, along with medication, treatment options include therapy to help reduce stress and specialized lenses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The popular notion that my twenties would be the best years of my life quickly turned into a nightmarish medical odyssey I wouldn't wish on anyone,' Domb said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Because visual snow syndrome is so rare and difficult to diagnose, it took years before Domb finally understood what was happening to her body&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;After realizing she was suffering from visual snow syndrome, Domb founded the Visual Snow Initiative to raise awareness and support others who were 'suffering in silence.' She now travels the world talking about the condition and helping others &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It was devastating to feel invisible and alone in my struggle.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Despite everything, Domb threw herself into research and eventually discovered that others were suffering from the same mysterious symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said realizing she wasn't alone was 'both comforting and heartbreaking.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Many shared their pain and frustration, and some, feeling desperate and without the resources or support they needed, even suggested suicide as a way out,' she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After realizing she was suffering from visual snow syndrome, Domb founded the Visual Snow Initiative to raise awareness and support others who were 'suffering in silence.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Since she launched the organization in 2018 — three years after her symptoms first appeared — it has heard from patients in 93 countries and amassed more than 60,000 followers across social media platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Touching on some of the groundbreaking discoveries she's helped support, Domb says, 'Some individuals are born with symptoms, while others, like me, experience onset of the condition at any point in life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Clinical cases show that people as young as 8 years old have developed visual snow syndrome, though onset most commonly occurs during the teenage or young adult years.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Thanks to her efforts, the condition has now been recognized by the World Health Organization and included in its annual International Classification of Diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In addition to raising awareness, Domb's organization is helping to fund research into treatment and management options for the little-known condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The health advocate and entrepreneur concludes, 'I wasn't and am not a doctor – just a patient who had been disregarded, but I refused to let that silence me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'My mission was never about proving others wrong, but about giving a voice to those who were overlooked, so no one would have to endure the medical odyssey that I did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Recognition from the WHO is historic and lives forever. I am deeply grateful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'But this is just the beginning. With continued support, I hope Visual Snow Initiative can continue pushing for further advancements in research, treatments, and patient care.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 05:58:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNM0p4d1VlN0VTVTAxUVNHZlRkdjVrcHo3OFRPVGVUbVF0dElSX0RINlo1OWh0OXF4czBFTXpCdE9GTlR6Z3ItaVlwdEpVRllSZFhod1NxLUNKbHRiRW00VlNabWVaemNQeHlfZ0E5TWZKVl8zdjBSX1BnVi1jMUJSQUJYTUY5aUU3bUVFamkzOTZqTnU4MnfSAZsBQVVfeXFMT0tDdFgwTng0UjYtRXg4dlREbDA1aWQ3UkhsS2hVTmtsMVdHLTZRa2hfRi1CWjJFVFRHQmRPRnIzN29GeWhSM3ItZDZXcXlmaHB4NkcyMnNaQ2lwcXRJajN1aTZWek9JRHdZaDhkRFVwSEJiYXZZb2NSa2ZNdmJGWm8zdHdKNWoxVElESEltU2QxcDVvRDJkejRTWG8</guid></item><item><title>哈佛医生解释了您的身体需要必需营养素的5个微妙迹象-印度时报 | Harvard doctor explains 5 subtle signs your body is crying out for essential nutrients - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi-gFBVV95cUxOV2NMZXFpb04xRlhUMVh5ZlZFaXJpZVozSW8zcDRtX21Oc0lrUlYzNW05b3d6d2dxQVBrcVV1UU5UNDBabV80dE9UcV93MEFYY1MzT2pPeDMzOU1qMl83eDA2TUlTM19zektyNkpIQ2pjUmVaT25ELTJUZ25id0hldV9WbTFrTGJlOFQ3QkZ6U3RRQ1AzM2lzWjhuNTBKVGlSS3l3N2RDcjZHRHdPTmduQ2FhTmF2MWJGc0N0UVZxVmpqSU0wd2I0Uk54M0R6bzMzaEdjU01JVTBWMFRKVjR4WUtSNEVlRHBwTXBVbThPdkxpNHFoblVpTk9n0gH_AUFVX3lxTE9mR2h2ZmdLcUVXeURQNU1jZGdiaF9aUGZYX1JUQjJPbGtEdE1JUnI3bF9KdTc0SGRCUGJBcHhmSUpSS3BmcmRJX3lGakpUTmlOU3NJRGR6Rm9xRXk1Q0Y0NUFDSmltVEJtcTNnZ3UtNUtGRGZTQnFUVjlnaWRpTkNyYTNaMDlvZm0zdHQ1MlVTUzY1T09UVzVuaXZkN0JkaGFRY3Q0Y1Zqa1RVTUZJTlN5VUJZbE1VcHJRSnJBTmdDVGF6VXU2MVRJQWFpdk9TWGRnRnZQS2luZ0VvTjNyRy16R3AzOFpYX2ZZTmJlaVp5aHV4THBOc29BbUJZQU9IRQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ever looked in the mirror or felt something weird in your body and thought, “Hmm, that’s odd”? Well, sometimes, your body sends little clues that it’s running low on key nutrients. Our body signals us in various ways about the deficiencies of key nutrients which are essential for several bodily functions. We often overlook the signals until it is too late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, Dr Saurabh Sethi posted on Instagram about the signs that indicate your body needs more nutrients. "Is your body trying to tell you something? In this video, Dr. Sethi breaks down key signs that may indicate you’re not getting enough essential nutrients. From unexpected fatigue to skin issues, discover how these common symptoms could be your body’s way of craving more vitamins and minerals," he has captioned a video giving details of the signs of nutrient deficiency. The five signs, which seem subtle, are brittle nails, twitching in the eyelids, joint clicking, premature graying of hair,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s start with brittle nails. If your nails are constantly cracking, peeling, or breaking, it’s not just because you washed your hands too much. Brittle nails are one of the earliest signs that your body might be running low on certain key nutrients. Iron is usually the first suspect here. Low iron levels mean your body can’t get enough oxygen to your nail cells, making them weak and flimsy. Biotin, a B-vitamin that often gets a lot of love in beauty supplements, is another major player. Without enough biotin, your nails lose their strength and flexibility. Zinc is also critical because it helps in cell repair and growth. Without sufficient zinc, your nails basically don’t stand a chance at being strong and healthy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-type="in_view" class="  "&gt;&lt;div class="EEW3_ timeline_pollWrapper_as " data-scrollga="scroll#poll_view"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="hLnAH"&gt;Poll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="KEEGr"&gt;Have you noticed any changes in your hair color at an early age?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, about that annoying twitching in your eyelid that comes and goes without warning—it’s almost always harmless but super irritating, right? Well, believe it or not, that little muscle spasm could be your body begging for more magnesium. Magnesium plays a huge role in keeping your muscles relaxed and your nerves calm. When your levels dip too low, your nerves can start firing off tiny spasms, especially in delicate muscles like your eyelids. Potassium is another nutrient involved in muscle function, and a deficiency here can add to the twitching drama. Dehydration also worsens things because when your body is low on fluids, your electrolyte balance gets thrown off, making muscle spasms more likely. If you're living on coffee and forgetting water or skimping on magnesium-rich foods like greens and nuts, don't be surprised when your eyelid starts twitching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moving on to joint clicking, you know, that sudden pop or crack you hear when you stand up, stretch, or even just move your neck? While a bit of joint noise can be normal, a sudden increase could signal your body is short on a few joint-supporting nutrients. Vitamin D is a big one here. Without enough vitamin D, your bones and joints can lose their strength and cushioning, leading to all sorts of noises and even discomfort. Calcium also plays a starring role in keeping joints smooth and bones strong. A shortage means your bones aren't as sturdy as they should be, and your joints may protest more loudly. Let’s not forget about collagen—nature’s glue that holds your joints, ligaments, and tendons together. As you age or if your diet is low in collagen-boosting nutrients like vitamin C, your joints can become a bit "creaky." So, if your joints have started sounding like an old rocking chair, it might be time to rethink your nutrient intake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And then, there's the heartbreak of spotting gray hairs in your twenties or thirties. Sure, genetics have a lot to do with when you go gray, but if your hair seems to be losing pigment earlier than expected, it could be a sign of a few hidden deficiencies. Vitamin B12 is often the main suspect. It’s essential for healthy blood and nerve cells, and when you don't have enough B12, your hair follicles can suffer, losing the melanin that gives your hair its color. Another player is copper, a mineral that actually helps produce melanin itself. Without enough copper, the pigmentation process stalls, and gray hairs can start creeping in early. Iron deficiency can also mess with the oxygen supply to your hair roots, weakening your strands and robbing them of their vibrant color. So, if you’re finding silver strands in your early 20s, it’s definitely worth checking your B12, copper, and iron levels before blaming it all on "bad genes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re noticing random bruises popping up like little mysteries on your arms and legs, your body might be dropping a big hint. Easy bruising often points to low levels of vitamin C, which your body needs to keep blood vessels strong and healthy. Without enough vitamin C, even a slight bump can cause tiny blood vessels to break. Vitamin K is another important one because it helps your blood clot properly—without it, bruises linger and spread. Sometimes, low iron levels can also make your skin more fragile. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your body doesn’t just wake up one morning and decide to act weird. It sends little messages when things aren’t quite right—through your nails, eyes, joints, and hair. Drink your water, get some sunlight, and maybe toss in a supplement if your doctor says it’s okay. It’s amazing how quickly your body can bounce back when you give it the fuel it’s quietly asking for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-gFBVV95cUxOV2NMZXFpb04xRlhUMVh5ZlZFaXJpZVozSW8zcDRtX21Oc0lrUlYzNW05b3d6d2dxQVBrcVV1UU5UNDBabV80dE9UcV93MEFYY1MzT2pPeDMzOU1qMl83eDA2TUlTM19zektyNkpIQ2pjUmVaT25ELTJUZ25id0hldV9WbTFrTGJlOFQ3QkZ6U3RRQ1AzM2lzWjhuNTBKVGlSS3l3N2RDcjZHRHdPTmduQ2FhTmF2MWJGc0N0UVZxVmpqSU0wd2I0Uk54M0R6bzMzaEdjU01JVTBWMFRKVjR4WUtSNEVlRHBwTXBVbThPdkxpNHFoblVpTk9n0gH_AUFVX3lxTE9mR2h2ZmdLcUVXeURQNU1jZGdiaF9aUGZYX1JUQjJPbGtEdE1JUnI3bF9KdTc0SGRCUGJBcHhmSUpSS3BmcmRJX3lGakpUTmlOU3NJRGR6Rm9xRXk1Q0Y0NUFDSmltVEJtcTNnZ3UtNUtGRGZTQnFUVjlnaWRpTkNyYTNaMDlvZm0zdHQ1MlVTUzY1T09UVzVuaXZkN0JkaGFRY3Q0Y1Zqa1RVTUZJTlN5VUJZbE1VcHJRSnJBTmdDVGF6VXU2MVRJQWFpdk9TWGRnRnZQS2luZ0VvTjNyRy16R3AzOFpYX2ZZTmJlaVp5aHV4THBOc29BbUJZQU9IRQ</guid></item><item><title>抗衰老突破：天然补充剂逆转生物年龄并改善健康- SciTechDaily | Anti-Aging Breakthrough: Natural Supplement Rewinds Biological Age and Improves Health - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxOS0hINEpSUWp4SHVhVkgzT09VWldTYURxNS1iWEZlZ2xKSjRtaUJFOUFxNXNoS3ROcnRDYjlMbHM1QkRHOU9DRDU5NWlrTl94VEk1NTdfM3Z1dnZOenJ2cEN3a0hZMlRpajBEdnd2WGFHeGZCeE1NNGM2aFBTUTNkNG5MdDJxeWQ2NmNxQmtMbzliRlV1STdnUEg0VG0tenFyel81WnJMU09fbmJUeU01Ug?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:12:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxOS0hINEpSUWp4SHVhVkgzT09VWldTYURxNS1iWEZlZ2xKSjRtaUJFOUFxNXNoS3ROcnRDYjlMbHM1QkRHOU9DRDU5NWlrTl94VEk1NTdfM3Z1dnZOenJ2cEN3a0hZMlRpajBEdnd2WGFHeGZCeE1NNGM2aFBTUTNkNG5MdDJxeWQ2NmNxQmtMbzliRlV1STdnUEg0VG0tenFyel81WnJMU09fbmJUeU01Ug</guid></item><item><title>家人说， Lake Grove婴儿在拙劣的包皮环切术后为自己的生命而战-新闻12 | Lake Grove infant fighting for his life following botched circumcision, family says - News 12</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisgFBVV95cUxOVllPY3JvbktjbHRDN0R4cmFFWFFBeEEtLVJDLVJHeHBCQjRET3BPa2g3V18xYm5LSzRPN0pFYmN1WmE2SDNOS1ZYWEFCOUh1cUxVeW5UMjE3NXQ4UTdQSk5qcGhqZW1XWnY1TXhEcXVISi1yRG03S3FJam53MjNwdERhS3NtZ0FkN3JXS29vbTdHLUg2dXNlQmQzTDlnN2pqRjNOV3ladE9rWUoyS1BnbDFn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div alignitems="normal" justifycontent="normal" direction="column" gap="1rem,1.25rem" flexwrap="nowrap" class="sc-fsYfdN hQgjIe sc-e6358465-0 dxMubp"&gt;&lt;p class="block"&gt;A newborn baby from Lake Grove is fighting for his life after a circumcision that went wrong, according to the infant's family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="block"&gt;Cole Groth nearly bled to death last week in the cardiac neonatal intensive care unit at Columbia Hospital.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="block"&gt;It happened a few hours after the procedure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="block"&gt;Cole's father, Tim Groth, told News 12 his son was born with a heart defect and says the hospital didn't warn them of the possible impact of the surgery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="block"&gt;"People need to be educated about the risks and the benefits and the complications of procedures, and not all of a sudden be the victim of a tragedy and have no idea that was possible because I think people would make different decisions," Groth said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="block"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/support-cole-jordan-groths-fight-for-life?attribution_id=sl:8893fa98-bcae-404c-8d1d-509cf97f018f&amp;amp;lang=en_US&amp;amp;utm_campaign=fp_sharesheet&amp;amp;utm_content=amp13_c-amp15_c&amp;amp;utm_medium=customer&amp;amp;utm_source=copy_link"&gt;GoFundMe page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; has been set up for donations to help Cole in his recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>News 12</author><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:21:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxOVllPY3JvbktjbHRDN0R4cmFFWFFBeEEtLVJDLVJHeHBCQjRET3BPa2g3V18xYm5LSzRPN0pFYmN1WmE2SDNOS1ZYWEFCOUh1cUxVeW5UMjE3NXQ4UTdQSk5qcGhqZW1XWnY1TXhEcXVISi1yRG03S3FJam53MjNwdERhS3NtZ0FkN3JXS29vbTdHLUg2dXNlQmQzTDlnN2pqRjNOV3ladE9rWUoyS1BnbDFn</guid></item><item><title>这种古老的草药对健康有益，但要小心风险- ScienceAlert | This Ancient Herb Is Trending For Health Benefits, But Beware The Risks - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxOcE41RkxWekxTMTNEeDM1QmZkS1ZKWEVGMWJKNHBadWwyZlhDLURxYWdocmt4ZUdpMEhrNTQ3OFZIb05DSWNhUzF2eWNzb05UY2lzY2tvUFZuRHVmaldTT1ZkazFQd2JMTXgzcXZNR0E4eFNTUlhVS3Jqc0ZSU2ZmRUxpQXU5R01GWFhpeVNQT2htYUZpQ0ZGVElUbFJ6bHJH?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Depending on who you follow on social media, you may have come across talk of a little-known herb called ashwagandha over the past year. Celebrities including Meghan Markle, Gwyneth Paltrow and Jennifer Aniston are &lt;a href="https://uk.style.yahoo.com/anxiety-aid-meghan-markle-jennifer-063000616.html"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; to use ashwagandha for its calming effects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://apa.uk.com/herb-of-the-month/ashwagandha"&gt;Ashwagandha&lt;/a&gt; has been trending on social media with &lt;a href="https://opalbond.co.uk/blog/ashwagandha-trends-and-consumer-benefits#:%7E:text=Social%20Media%20Influence,new%20health%20and%20wellness%20trends"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt; showing #ashwagandha had more than 670 million views on TikTok in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientifically known as &lt;em&gt;Withania somnifera&lt;/em&gt;, ashwagandha is a common herb used for thousands of years in Ayurvedic medicine – an ancient Indian system of healing based on the belief that health and wellness depend on a balance between the body, mind and spirit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ayurveda emphasises a holistic approach to health using natural treatments, such as herbal remedies, dietary changes, physical therapy, meditation and yoga.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But beyond the social media buzz, what does science say about this herb's benefits?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ashwagandha root has been used in traditional medicine as an &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33103257/"&gt;adaptogen&lt;/a&gt;. This means it could help people become more resilient to various types of stress, whether biological, physical, or chemical.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The strongest &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2210803321000142"&gt;evidence&lt;/a&gt; available for ashwagandha is as a stress and anxiety reliever. A &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2210803321000142"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; looking at several small studies showed that ashwagandha can significantly reduce levels of perceived stress and anxiety in people. This may be partly due to its regulating effect on stress hormones such as cortisol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;p class="aspect-w-16 aspect-h-9 youtube-iframe relative"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Govl2FUGTUw?wmode=transparent&amp;amp;start=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ashwagandha is also known for its ability to improve sleep quality. The "somnifera" part of its scientific name, meaning "sleep-inducing" hints at its effects. Some &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Ashwagandha-HealthProfessional/#en2"&gt;trials&lt;/a&gt; show it can help people fall asleep faster and enjoy deeper, more restful sleep, thus boosting energy levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This may be beneficial for people suffering from insomnia. But there is no evidence showing whether it is better than taking sleeping tablets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Possible benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, this herb has been associated with other benefits. The Sanskrit word "ashwagandha" means "the smell of a horse," symbolising its ability to give the strength and stamina of a horse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Athletes and fitness enthusiasts may benefit from ashwagandha's ability to enhance physical performance. Some &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2210803321000142"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; indicates that ashwagandha can improve strength, muscle mass and oxygen use during exercise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For men, ashwagandha has been shown in some &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30466985/"&gt;small studies&lt;/a&gt; to boost testosterone levels and improve fertility by increasing sperm count and motility. This may be linked to dehydroepiandrosterone (&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK526128/"&gt;DHEA&lt;/a&gt;) – a sex hormone that your body naturally produces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DHEA is used to make other hormones such as testosterone. This means men with prostate  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="159248" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; sensitive to testosterone should avoid using this herb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_159253" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-159253" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/04/ashwagandha-2-642x428.jpg" alt="Ashwagandha: This Ancient Herb Is Trending For Its Potential Health Benefits – But Also Comes With Risks" class="wp-image-159253 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/04/ashwagandha-2-642x428.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/04/ashwagandha-2-622x415.jpg 622w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/04/ashwagandha-2-768x512.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/04/ashwagandha-2-600x400.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/04/ashwagandha-2.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-159253" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;(eskymaks/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ashwagandha has been linked to improved cognitive function, such as better memory and focus. &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31742775/"&gt;Small studies&lt;/a&gt;, involving older people who have some cognitive impairment, suggest that ashwagandha may help to reduce &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5551541/"&gt;oxidative stress&lt;/a&gt; – harmful molecules called free radicals that can damage cells in the body – and inflammation, which can negatively effect memory and thinking processes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are also ongoing &lt;a href="https://www.isrctn.com/editorial/retrieveFile/1d0c866d-98bd-4fd2-937d-a21ca36c4d7a/42176"&gt;clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; investigating whether ashwagandha may be effective in treating long COVID symptoms such as fatigue and cognitive dysfunction – having trouble with mental tasks such as thinking, remembering and making decisions – but there's no robust evidence yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ashwagandha is rich in phytochemicals, including withanolides. &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/agricultural-and-biological-sciences/withanolide"&gt;Withanolides are steroidal lactones&lt;/a&gt; – they are structurally similar to steroids, with a lactone ring in their chemical structure – that are thought to help cells absorb glucose from the bloodstream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This can lower blood sugar in both healthy people and those with  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="159248" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, although larger &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31975514/"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; need to be done. In &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7696210/"&gt;animal studies&lt;/a&gt;, withanolides show anti-inflammatory activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Side effects&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While ashwagandha may offer potential health benefits, it also has numerous &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Ashwagandha-HealthProfessional/"&gt;risks and side effects&lt;/a&gt;. The long-term safety of ashwagandha is not well-documented. Most studies have focused on short-term use, typically up to three months – but the benefits may take some weeks or months to appear. The most common side effects are mild stomach upsets and nausea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;p class="aspect-w-16 aspect-h-9 youtube-iframe relative"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/rGVGMQno3QM?wmode=transparent&amp;amp;start=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its use is not advised in people with some pre-existing health conditions such as liver disease. Although rare, there have been &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Ashwagandha-HealthProfessional/#en8"&gt;reports&lt;/a&gt; of liver problems, including severe liver failure, associated with ashwagandha use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ashwagandha may &lt;a href="https://www.rheumatologyadvisor.com/features/herbal-supplement-use-in-autoimmune-disease/"&gt;stimulate&lt;/a&gt; the immune system, potentially causing flare ups for people with autoimmune conditions such as multiple sclerosis and rheumatoid arthritis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's also possible that ashwagandha may interact with some medications, such as immunosuppressants, sedatives and thyroid hormone medications. &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25624699/"&gt;Research suggests&lt;/a&gt; that ashwagandha may influence thyroid function, particularly by increasing thyroid hormone levels. It may also interact with thyroid medications, such as levothyroxine, possibly leading to overmedication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pregnant and breastfeeding women are advised to avoid ashwagandha, especially at higher doses. The herb may be linked to miscarriages and, although there's conflicting &lt;a href="https://herbal-ahp.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/Press-Release-Ashwagandha-Abortifacient-Assessment_06-24-2024.pdf"&gt;evidence&lt;/a&gt;, it's best to be cautious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ashwagandha holds promise, then, as a stress reliever, sleep aid and even an energy booster. With growing interest and a large body of anecdotal evidence, it's no surprise that it's become a favourite among wellness enthusiasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, scientific research is still developing and more extensive  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="159248" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; are needed to confirm the benefits, side effects and determine the safest, most effective doses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're considering incorporating ashwagandha into your routine, especially for long-term use, do consult a healthcare professional first, especially if you have pre-existing health conditions or are taking other medications.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/253979/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/dipa-kamdar-1485027"&gt;Dipa Kamdar&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Lecturer in Pharmacy Practice, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/kingston-university-949"&gt;Kingston University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/ashwagandha-this-ancient-herb-is-trending-for-its-potential-health-benefits-but-also-comes-with-risks-253979"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:01:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOcE41RkxWekxTMTNEeDM1QmZkS1ZKWEVGMWJKNHBadWwyZlhDLURxYWdocmt4ZUdpMEhrNTQ3OFZIb05DSWNhUzF2eWNzb05UY2lzY2tvUFZuRHVmaldTT1ZkazFQd2JMTXgzcXZNR0E4eFNTUlhVS3Jqc0ZSU2ZmRUxpQXU5R01GWFhpeVNQT2htYUZpQ0ZGVElUbFJ6bHJH</guid></item><item><title>医生确切地解释了为什么随着年龄的增长，您的皮肤看起来“可丽” ，以及您可以做些什么- BuzzFeed | Doctors Explain Exactly Why Your Skin May Look "Crepey" As You Age, And What You Can Do About It - BuzzFeed</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiZkFVX3lxTE1aajEtT003eWVuVnVaYlBTRUlRNzAxNEtmemtHV1U5V2UyejRaZWJ3el9LU2VYcjJmRkVPdWFPenpwSnZVMFQxdER5dTBROXVpMk0zelBoeDd6RFZiZnN4MUY0d3VhQQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz__description
  "&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;As Marmon hinted, crepey skin primarily results from sun exposure. “A frequent misunderstanding is that crepey skin develops solely from aging, but lifestyle factors like sun exposure and smoking are significant contributors,” she said. “While everyone is susceptible to crepey skin, people with lighter skin tones, who are more prone to sun damage, are particularly at risk.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sun exposure causes the &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/best-products-for-sagging-skin_l_614b5430e4b0175a1839f2cc" target="_blank"&gt;skin to lose volume&lt;/a&gt; due to dehydration. “It doesn’t store water the same because the integrity of the skin is damaged,” board-certified dermatologist Dr. Shani Francis told HuffPost. That leads to degradation of &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/topic/collagen" target="_blank"&gt;collagen&lt;/a&gt; and elastin, the proteins that hold water and therefore help the skin keep its structure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any ultraviolet exposure, even from tanning beds, can lead to the formation of crepey skin. “It’s really not the sun itself — it’s ultraviolet radiation,” Francis explained. “Any type of ultraviolet radiation exposure is going to damage and degrade the collagen and the elastin tissues.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genetics play a factor, too. “If you look at your parents, if they have crepey skin, you know you need to start the process of preventing a little bit earlier,” Francis said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Marmon, many women begin to notice crepey skin around the time they hit &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/topic/menopause" target="_blank"&gt;menopause&lt;/a&gt; because the drop in estrogen during that time speeds up the decrease in collagen and elastin, resulting in a thinning of the skin with a loss of moisture and fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It starts around middle age and gets worse as we age,” Francis reiterated. “The elastic fibers, they start off very strong. Twenty-something-, 30-something-year-olds, their skin snaps right back. Once you get to 40, it doesn’t quite work that way.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Board-certified dermatologist &lt;a href="https://www.sherberandrad.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Noëlle S. Sherber&lt;/a&gt; told HuffPost that crepey skin from UV damage usually shows up around the eyes, the chest and the backs of the hands. Some people also see it above the knees and on the inner arms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:16:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZkFVX3lxTE1aajEtT003eWVuVnVaYlBTRUlRNzAxNEtmemtHV1U5V2UyejRaZWJ3el9LU2VYcjJmRkVPdWFPenpwSnZVMFQxdER5dTBROXVpMk0zelBoeDd6RFZiZnN4MUY0d3VhQQ</guid></item><item><title>医生确切地解释了为什么随着年龄的增长，您的皮肤看起来会“皱纹” ，以及您可以做些什么-雅虎 | Doctors Explain Exactly Why Your Skin May Look "Crepey" As You Age, And What You Can Do About It - Yahoo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgFBVV95cUxPWC1wdmMwU0FtY21fb2tKZllROUVHeWlnQXNuZWF0ZDN4bTBDaHFudG9lMllEQ3g5aXZRTXJSNHpjT1pMbjlpX1hZY2N5akFhM2Rvano1a0p4QWdTUmhxUDZHbUxnN3FWWkFMaVEwYi1UV2lyOC1OTzNLakxMdERPRjZKa2xkQQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Crepes may be delectable, but &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/best-products-for-crepey-skin_l_60ef1593e4b00ef8761828c2" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:crepey skin;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;crepey skin&lt;/a&gt;? Not so much. The term describes skin that, like crepe paper, appears thin and crinkled and typically lacks the elasticity, thickness, and firmness of youthful skin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Alexandr Zhenzhirov / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Crepey skin is primarily an &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/angelicaamartinez/soul-aesthetic-personality-quiz" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:aesthetic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;aesthetic&lt;/a&gt; concern but it can also be indicative of potential health issues,” board-certified dermatologist Dr. Shoshana Marmon told HuffPost. “Since it usually develops as a result of substantial sun damage, individuals with crepey skin may be at increased risk for the development of skin cancer. Additionally, since crepey skin is thinner and less elastic, it may be more susceptible to bruising and tearing, which could lead to infection if not properly cared for.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Plenty of creams and lotions claim to alleviate the appearance of crepey skin, and anyone who wants to take care of it quickly can seek doctor-administered treatments. We spoke with experts who weighed in on what works best and whether there’s anything you can do to prevent crepey skin from forming in the first place.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Why and when crepey skin forms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Peter Finch / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As Marmon hinted, crepey skin primarily results from sun exposure. “A frequent misunderstanding is that crepey skin develops solely from aging, but lifestyle factors like sun exposure and smoking are significant contributors,” she said. “While everyone is susceptible to crepey skin, people with lighter skin tones, who are more prone to sun damage, are particularly at risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Sun exposure causes the &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/best-products-for-sagging-skin_l_614b5430e4b0175a1839f2cc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:skin to lose volume;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;skin to lose volume&lt;/a&gt; due to dehydration. “It doesn’t store water the same because the integrity of the skin is damaged,” board-certified dermatologist Dr. Shani Francis told HuffPost. That leads to degradation of &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/topic/collagen" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:collagen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;collagen&lt;/a&gt; and elastin, the proteins that hold water and therefore help the skin keep its structure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Any ultraviolet exposure, even from tanning beds, can lead to the formation of crepey skin. “It’s really not the sun itself — it’s ultraviolet radiation,” Francis explained. “Any type of ultraviolet radiation exposure is going to damage and degrade the collagen and the elastin tissues.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Genetics play a factor, too. “If you look at your parents, if they have crepey skin, you know you need to start the process of preventing a little bit earlier,” Francis said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According to Marmon, many women begin to notice crepey skin around the time they hit &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/topic/menopause" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:menopause;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;menopause&lt;/a&gt; because the drop in estrogen during that time speeds up the decrease in collagen and elastin, resulting in a thinning of the skin with a loss of moisture and fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“It starts around middle age and gets worse as we age,” Francis reiterated. “The elastic fibers, they start off very strong. Twenty-something-, 30-something-year-olds, their skin snaps right back. Once you get to 40, it doesn’t quite work that way.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Board-certified dermatologist &lt;a href="https://www.sherberandrad.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Noëlle S. Sherber;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Noëlle S. Sherber&lt;/a&gt; told HuffPost that crepey skin from UV damage usually shows up around the eyes, the chest and the backs of the hands. Some people also see it above the knees and on the inner arms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;span&gt;What you can do to prevent crepey skin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Nancybelle Gonzaga Villarroya / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Wearing &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/topic/sunscreen" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sunscreen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;sunscreen&lt;/a&gt; may seem like the obvious way to ward off crepey skin, but Francis said another method may be more effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“You can’t see light through your clothes — that’s better,” she said, “Sunglasses, a hat, those things are always better than &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/best-sunscreens-amazon_l_6440071be4b0d8403885b584" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sunscreen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;sunscreen&lt;/a&gt; because they’re on and in place. Sunscreen doesn’t last. It’s not permanent. Sun protection instead of sunscreen is much more comprehensive. I always tell people, think of sunscreen as your last line of defense.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;For the areas that clothing and accessories can’t cover, apply sunscreen. &lt;a href="https://www.aad.org/public/everyday-care/sun-protection/shade-clothing-sunscreen/is-sunscreen-safe" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The American Academy of Dermatology;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;The American Academy of Dermatology&lt;/a&gt; recommends a water-resistant one that offers broad-spectrum protection with SPF 30 or higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Some over-the-counter options to try for crepey skin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Anna Frank / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Marmon wants to temper expectations of seeing results from over-the-counter treatments claiming to eliminate the appearance of crepey skin. “While creams, moisturizers, lotions and especially sunscreen are helpful in maintaining skin health, eliminating all &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/anti-aging-skin-care-body_l_62aa46fee4b0cf43c8520b45" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:signs of aging;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;signs of aging&lt;/a&gt; is pretty much impossible,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;However, with regular use, topical products with ingredients such as retinoids, alpha hydroxy acids, peptides, growth factors, hyaluronic acid and antioxidants can help to stimulate collagen production, therefore improving skin quality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“These products generally take several months before you see their potential benefit,” Sherber warned, adding that a high price tag doesn’t equate to a higher likelihood for results. “A misconception is that only high-end skin care products can combat crepey skin, when in fact, consistent use is far more important than the price tag.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;You want to make sure the moisturizer you pick also contains water to rehydrate the skin. “Water is the number one hydrator,” Francis said. “A big mistake people make is coating skin with oil when they’re already dehydrated because all that’s going to do is improve the barrier.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Francis particularly loves &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/what-is-niacinimide_l_60d9d297e4b0b9db24990abe" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:products with niacinamide;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;products with niacinamide&lt;/a&gt;, a form of vitamin B3, as a way to help alleviate the appearance of crepey skin. It can also be taken as a supplement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Sherber offered an easy way to test whether a moisturizer is thick enough to properly hydrate: “When you open the jar and flip it upside down, if it doesn’t drip, then it should be a good barrier support product.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Doctor-administered treatments to address crepey skin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Klaus Vedfelt / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;On May 15, the Food and Drug Administration approved the first skin booster, Skinvive by Juvederm, to improve skin smoothness in adults over 21. The booster is an injectable hyaluronic acid with a serum texture that has been used for years overseas, where they refer to it as Volite. “Unlike fillers, which volumize, skin boosters replenish skin’s deep hydration and can give fantastic results for skin quality improvement, especially in thin-skinned areas that are prone to crepey texture,” Sherber explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Other injectables, like Radiesse and Sculptra, stimulate the body to synthesize collagen. Options such as radio frequency skin tightening and fractional non-ablative lasers stimulate the body’s natural healing process, leading to the production of new collagen and elastin that promotes thicker and more elastic skin. “Both can significantly improve skin quality,” Sherber said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;For certain anatomical areas, such as around the eyes, she suggested neuromodulators like Botox for reducing crinkling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Still, “while we can somewhat improve the appearance of crepey skin, the aging process is ongoing and inevitable,” Marmon said. “It is important to have realistic expectations in terms of what to expect from anti-aging products regardless of what they claim to do. Aging is a natural part of life and much better than the alternative.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;i&gt;This article originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/crepey-skin_l_648227d3e4b025003edc406e" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:HuffPost.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;HuffPost.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:16:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxPWC1wdmMwU0FtY21fb2tKZllROUVHeWlnQXNuZWF0ZDN4bTBDaHFudG9lMllEQ3g5aXZRTXJSNHpjT1pMbjlpX1hZY2N5akFhM2Rvano1a0p4QWdTUmhxUDZHbUxnN3FWWkFMaVEwYi1UV2lyOC1OTzNLakxMdERPRjZKa2xkQQ</guid></item><item><title>小RFK的愿望成真：每个人都得了麻疹-《每日野兽》 | RFK Jr.’s Wish Is Coming True: Everybody’s Getting Measles - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxOeTlRUjloZVpoVTZWZnF0ZC1YUkJwaHRhUkUzNU9MeXBnMUpuZlJRUzJ0M2MzZ1pZcm9xZjdVVEVVbHlHdTR5Z293UnhYNDhTQ3djTXU1NFRqTU0yck02a184eVhhWF9TdGFXRE5lRThncC1OamJGcDlvMFdLbzdGWUNNV1NuNGtBUFcxR1BR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/keyword/robert-f-kennedy-jr/" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.thedailybeast.com/keyword/robert-f-kennedy-jr/"&gt;RFK Jr.&lt;/a&gt;’s vision for America is rapidly becoming reality, with the number of measles cases skyrocketing across the country, bringing the number of confirmed cases to a total of 884.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt; published by the CDC on Friday, there have been 884 cases of measles reported across 29 states, including Alaska, California, Hawaii, Illinois, New York and Texas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Just last month, the Health and Human Services Secretary appeared to argue in an interview with Sean Hannity that natural immunity was the best defense against the highly infectious disease. In other words, Kennedy believes that it would be great if everyone got measles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“It used to be, when I [was] a kid, that everybody got measles,” he told the Fox News host. “And the measles gave you lifetime protection against measles infection.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;He continued, “The vaccine doesn’t do that. The vaccine is effective for some people for life, but for many people it wanes.” He went on to argue against the MMR vaccine, telling Hannity that the government shouldn’t force people to get the vaccine, because “There are adverse events from the vaccine. It does cause deaths every year. It causes all the illnesses that measles itself cause, like encephalitis and blindness, etc., so people ought to be able to make that choice for themselves.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;In 2025 alone, measles cases have been reported in Alaska, Arkansas, California, Colorado, Florida, Georgia, Hawaii, Illinois, Indiana, Kansas, Kentucky, Louisiana, Maryland, Michigan, Minnesota, Missouri, Montana, New Jersey, New Mexico, New York, Ohio, Oklahoma, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island, Tennessee, Texas, Vermont, Virginia and Washington.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;At least six of those states—Indiana, Kansas, Michigan, New Mexico, Ohio and Texas—have reported outbreaks, meaning three or more related cases. Texas, the epicenter of the outbreak, has seen 646 cases since late January.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;There have been three confirmed deaths, two of whom were children: 8-year-old Daisy Hildebrand and 6-year-old Kayley Fehr. Those mark the first deaths from measles in the U.S. in more than a decade. The majority of cases have occurred in individuals under the age of 20.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Stanford University researchers have &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/04/24/measles-cases-deaths-vaccine-rates-rfk-jr/" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/04/24/measles-cases-deaths-vaccine-rates-rfk-jr/"&gt;predicted&lt;/a&gt; that if vaccination rates remain steady, measles could become entrenched, resulting in hundreds of thousands of cases “where deaths are commonplace and hospitalizations are happening all the time,” according to Nathan Lo, a Stanford University physician and author of the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Only two percent of the 884 people infected in 2025 have received the recommended dose of the MMR vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Daily Beast</author><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOeTlRUjloZVpoVTZWZnF0ZC1YUkJwaHRhUkUzNU9MeXBnMUpuZlJRUzJ0M2MzZ1pZcm9xZjdVVEVVbHlHdTR5Z293UnhYNDhTQ3djTXU1NFRqTU0yck02a184eVhhWF9TdGFXRE5lRThncC1OamJGcDlvMFdLbzdGWUNNV1NuNGtBUFcxR1BR</guid></item><item><title>美国最有可能患上最致命癌症的国家……您的排名在哪里？ --《每日邮报》 | States most at risk of America's deadliest cancer... where does YOURS rank? - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxOSHFSZkU0eTh1dUQxLVY0U1l3a3g1OU5FYjUxSjBRM1psaUZoSGpRNDg2MVQxTjY2UlZYMTRxUC1HbDNOMWVCc1RRNjBJWEszYTIySDMzaGE3X1o5RXNNemYzenUxeDZqczFjenJCQU81VnFQQUtrR1VnNXJqbnhrNGxPczdnSHhMVnQxbWhjTU9kOHNxa3hNeEJnS3LSAaIBQVVfeXFMT3laRFVRV0FfQ19mcWREbkxSTVNreDZZaTh1aThOdDh0LVAxN2tMdktUUDl2cDlMMUtlTWRJSzlfbGktWVktNHhSOFlsYjZUVktZVGJsNE5fQlZocF9zZmNOV3BLQzVQQUF6TG94cmFiWmNUcldPaWRDVFU0R054WFpaMW9PUWhIM0xkUUdKSjM3MXFxbUt3cWtIem5DLUo2Ykl3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;People living in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/iowa/index.html" id="mol-baa475d0-2200-11f0-a330-01676fa8611e"&gt;Iowa&lt;/a&gt; may be at the greatest risk of lung &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-baa0cc50-2200-11f0-a330-01676fa8611e"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; in the next decade, a new study suggests.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers at the University of &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/california/index.html" id="mol-baa400a0-2200-11f0-a330-01676fa8611e"&gt;California&lt;/a&gt; San Diego surveyed 1.7million Americans in all 50 states to track rates of cigarette use from 1992 through 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They also used that data to predict which states would have the most smokers in 2035.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers found since the early 2000s, smoking rates have decreased by more than 60 percent nationwide, from 23 percent to 9.4 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Statewide, Utah recorded the lowest rate of smokers in 2022 with 4.4 percent. Maine, however, had the highest smoking rate in the country at 16.4 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And by 2035, even as nationwide smoking rates dip to just five percent on average, experts estimate Iowa's rate - which is about 16 percent - will remain unchanged, making it the highest in the country. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Smoking and tobacco use is the number one cause of lung cancer, responsible for 80 to 90 percent of cases. The disease is &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-13490375/lung-cancer-rising-young-americans.html"&gt;America's deadliest and third-most common cancer&lt;/a&gt;, with 226,000 cases per year and 130,000 deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And while smoking is on the decline, lung cancer rates will take significantly longer to drop in areas with heavy smoking rates, researchers warned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Researchers at the University of California San Diego have revealed which states may be at the greatest risk of developing lung cancer (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above map shows smoking rates per state in 2022. Darker colors are associated with higher smoking rates&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They also cautioned an increase in vaping among young people may further stall progress.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Matthew Stone, first study author and assistant professor at the UC San Diego Herbert Wertheim School of Public Health, said: 'The rapid decline in smoking among young adults is clear evidence that the smoking epidemic will come to an end in our lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Indeed, we project that the national smoking prevalence will be under five percent by 2035. However, the much slower decline in smokers over the age of 50, particularly in previously high smoking states, will mean that the high rates of lung cancer, heart disease and chronic obstructive pulmonary disease that are caused by lifelong smoking will take longer to decrease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers analyzed US Census Bureau data on smoking and tobacco use from 1992 to 2022, which included responses from 1.7million Americans in 54,000 households.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The vast majority (78 percent) were white, and the largest age group (30 percent) was 35 to 49-year-olds.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Respondents were asked 18 times whether they had smoked at least 100 cigarettes in their lifetime. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Those who responded 'yes' were asked if they currently smoked every day, some days or none at all. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers used the survey data to calculate a smoking rate for each state from 1992 to 2022 and a projected rate for 2035. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;From 1992 to 2001, the national smoking rate was 23 percent. During that time, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/utah/index.html" id="mol-8d868150-21f2-11f0-a330-01676fa8611e"&gt;Utah&lt;/a&gt; had the lowest rate of 15 percent while &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/kentucky/index.html" id="mol-8d84fab0-21f2-11f0-a330-01676fa8611e" class=""&gt;Kentucky&lt;/a&gt; had the highest at 31 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, by 2022, smoking dropped significantly down to nine percent nationwide. Utah again had the fewest smokers that year with a rate of just 4.4 percent, while &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/maine/index.html" id="mol-61d4b740-21f5-11f0-a330-01676fa8611e" class=""&gt;Maine&lt;/a&gt; had the highest at 16.4.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above map shows smoking prevalence by state in 1992. Darker colors are associated with higher smoking rates&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Among states with the highest smoking rates, following behind were Iowa and West Virginia both at 16 percent, Oklahoma at 15 percent and South Dakota at 14 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;States with low rates following Utah were California (5.6 percent), Colorado (six percent), Connecticut (6.5 percent) and Arizona (6.7 percent).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Based on the current trends, the researchers predicted Hawaii would have the lowest smoking rate in 2035, with a projected rate of 1.4 percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Following close behind in the predictions were Colorado at 1.5 percent, Utah at 2.5 percent, California at 3.3 percent and New Jersey at 3.5 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nationally, the researchers estimated the smoking rate will dip below five percent in 2035, nearly half that of 2022. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, in 2035, Iowa is expected to have the highest smoking rate at 16 percent, followed by Oklahoma (15 percent), Wyoming and West Virginia (14 percent) and Maine (12.7 percent). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The findings are in line with rates of lung cancer, which are highest in Midwestern and some New England states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The national average is 54 cases per 100,000 people.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above map shows projected smoking rates for 2035. Researchers believe the US will drop to an average smoking rate of five percent in a decade from now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Maine, which had the highest smoking rate in 2022, had the fourth-highest rate of lung cancer in 2021, at 63 cases per 100,000 people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Kentucky (79.3 cases per 100,000 people), West Virginia (74 per 100,000) and Mississippi (65.6 per 100,000) were all in the top three states for worst lung cancer rates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Iowa has a rate of 61 cases per 100,000 residents. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Utah, which had the fewest smokers, had a lung cancer rate of 24.4 cases per 100,000 people in 2021.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the team found all 50 states experienced 'significant' declines in smoking, they warned the rise of vaping may stall this progress. The use of e-cigarettes among high schoolers has surged from 1.5 percent in 2011 to 27 percent in 2019. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;John Pierce, corresponding author and distinguished professor at UC San Diego, said: 'While the ongoing decline in cigarette smoking is a major public health success story, recent evidence suggests that the tobacco industry has successfully recruited a new generation of teenagers into e-cigarette use and nicotine addiction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Further research is needed to assess the long-term impact of this shift.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:29:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxOSHFSZkU0eTh1dUQxLVY0U1l3a3g1OU5FYjUxSjBRM1psaUZoSGpRNDg2MVQxTjY2UlZYMTRxUC1HbDNOMWVCc1RRNjBJWEszYTIySDMzaGE3X1o5RXNNemYzenUxeDZqczFjenJCQU81VnFQQUtrR1VnNXJqbnhrNGxPczdnSHhMVnQxbWhjTU9kOHNxa3hNeEJnS3LSAaIBQVVfeXFMT3laRFVRV0FfQ19mcWREbkxSTVNreDZZaTh1aThOdDh0LVAxN2tMdktUUDl2cDlMMUtlTWRJSzlfbGktWVktNHhSOFlsYjZUVktZVGJsNE5fQlZocF9zZmNOV3BLQzVQQUF6TG94cmFiWmNUcldPaWRDVFU0R054WFpaMW9PUWhIM0xkUUdKSjM3MXFxbUt3cWtIem5DLUo2Ykl3</guid></item><item><title>确定逻辑思维的关键中心-神经科学新闻 | Critical Hub for Logical Thinking Identified - Neuroscience News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifEFVX3lxTFBjR19QWGxlQUZkRVQydlE5X0xfZW9UdG9wN1pSSHNsNlZXSDFBWEpLazZmMUtIdmRrLWxIYzM2aWVqWWlGbDN1bGRJQkx0UDdEV0JTRE5yUGx6WXdKWGxvTG8zMlhxVENhN1lId1JIaEc4d21qdDhHYnFhel8?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;Researchers have identified that the right frontal lobe plays a critical role in logical thinking and problem-solving. Using lesion-deficit mapping in 247 patients with brain injuries, they found that damage to this area leads to significantly more reasoning errors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two new cognitive tests developed for the study accurately detected reasoning impairments that traditional assessments might miss. These findings could improve clinical diagnosis and treatment for patients with right frontal brain damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Right Frontal Lobe:&lt;/strong&gt; Damage here impaired reasoning abilities by around 15%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Reasoning Tests:&lt;/strong&gt; Verbal and nonverbal tasks successfully identified cognitive deficits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clinical Potential:&lt;/strong&gt; The tests could enhance NHS screening for brain injury-related reasoning problems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;UCL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A team of researchers at UCL and UCLH have identified the key brain regions that are essential for logical thinking and problem solving.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings, published in &lt;em&gt;Brain, &lt;/em&gt;help to increase our understanding of how the human brain supports our ability to comprehend, draw conclusions, and deal with new and novel problems – otherwise known as reasoning skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-109204"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows a brain." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/critical-thinking-brain-neuroscience-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;The results showed that people with damage to the right frontal lobe had a much harder time on both tests compared to those with damage in other areas. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;To determine which brain areas are necessary for a certain ability, researchers study patients with brain lesions (an area of damage in the brain) caused by stroke or brain tumours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This approach, known as ‘lesion-deficit mapping’, is the most powerful method for localising function in the human brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studying brain injuries can be difficult and time-consuming because researchers need a large number of patients with specific brain damage. This kind of damage can affect how a person thinks, feels, or moves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, very few research centres have access to enough patients to conduct these studies effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, previous studies have mainly relied on functional imaging (fMRI) techniques in healthy individuals. However, these results can sometimes be misleading as they provide correlational rather than causal evidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study, led by researchers at the UCL Queen Square Institute of Neurology and Department of Neuropsychology at the National Hospital for Neurology and Neurosurgery, UCLH, used lesion-deficit mapping to investigate 247 patients with unilateral focal brain lesions in either the left or right frontal (front) or posterior (back) regions of the brain. An additional 81 healthy individuals served as controls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To assess reasoning skills in these patients, the researchers developed two new tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These included a verbal deductive reasoning task (a type of puzzle where participants are asked to find relationships between words to solve problems), which included questions such as: &lt;em&gt;“If Sarah is smarter than Diana and Sarah is smarter than Heather, is Diane smarter than Heather?”.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And a nonverbal analogical reasoning task (a type of puzzle where participants are asked to use pictures, shapes or numbers to figure out logical patterns and solve problems), with questions like: &lt;em&gt;“Which set of numbers is 1,2,3 most similar to – 5,6,7 or 6,5,7?”.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results showed that people with damage to the right frontal lobe had a much harder time on both tests compared to those with damage in other areas. They made about 15% more mistakes than the other patients and healthy individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lead author, Dr Joseph Mole (UCL Queen Square Institute of Neurology and Department of Neuropsychology, UCLH) said: “Our study explores how the front right part of the brain helps people think and solve new problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It also shows that our two new tests can help detect reasoning problems in individuals with brain damage, improving diagnosis and treatment.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senior author, Professor Lisa Cipolotti (UCL Queen Square Institute of Neurology and Department of Neuropsychology, UCLH) added: “By combining a detailed cognitive investigation in a large sample of brain damaged patients with advanced lesion mapping techniques – developed by Professor Parashkev Nachev and his team at the UCL Queen Square Institute of Neurology – we have deepened our understanding of the complex and, so far, poorly understood, neural structures underlying human reasoning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our findings show a close connection between the right frontal brain network involved in reasoning and the right frontal brain network essential for fluid intelligence (our ability to solve problems without prior experience).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This suggests that a common area of the brain plays a critical role in both reasoning and fluid intelligence.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers believe that these findings have significant clinical implications, as the two new tests can help identify cognitive impairments that would otherwise go undetected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With further validation and implementation, the team aim to make their new reasoning tests widely available in the NHS, addressing an unmet need for tools specifically designed for assessing right frontal lobe dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding: &lt;/strong&gt;The study was funded by Wellcome and the National Institute for Health and Care Research University College London Hospitals Biomedical Research Centre (NIHR UCLH BRC) funding scheme. The researchers also received funding from The National Brain Appeal and the Guarantors of Brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this logic and neuroscience research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Poppy Tombs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;UCL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Poppy Tombs – UCL&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/brain/awaf062" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;A right frontal network for analogical and deductive reasoning&lt;/a&gt;” by Lisa Cipolotti et al. &lt;em&gt;Brain&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A right frontal network for analogical and deductive reasoning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two of the most well-studied types of reasoning are analogical reasoning (AR) and deductive reasoning (DR). Yet, our understanding of the relationship between reasoning abilities and their neuroanatomical basis remains surprisingly limited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We aimed to conduct fine-grained anatomical mapping of performance on tests of AR, DR and fluid intelligence (Gf), in a large sample of patients with unilateral focal frontal or posterior lesions and healthy controls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We assessed 247 prospectively recruited patients using two new tests: the Analogical Reasoning Test (ART) and the Deductive Reasoning Test (DRT); and the best-established measure of Gf: Raven’s Advanced Progressive Matrices (RAPM).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Non-parametric Bayesian stochastic block modelling was used to reveal the community structure of lesion deficit networks, disentangling functional from confounding pathological distributed effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ART and DRT performance was significantly impaired in patients with frontal lesions [ART: &lt;em&gt;F&lt;/em&gt;(2,238) = 18.93; &lt;em&gt;P&lt;/em&gt; &amp;lt; 0.001; Frontal group worse than Posterior group and healthy controls, both &lt;em&gt;P&lt;/em&gt; &amp;lt; 0.001; DRT: &lt;em&gt;F&lt;/em&gt;(2,387) = 18.491; &lt;em&gt;P&lt;/em&gt; &amp;lt; 0.001; Frontal group worse than healthy controls, &lt;em&gt;P&lt;/em&gt; &amp;lt; 0.01]. Right frontal effects were evident on both tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thus, on the ART, right frontal patients were more impaired than left (&lt;em&gt;P&lt;/em&gt; &amp;lt; 0.05). On the DRT, right frontal patients were more impaired than left frontal patients on questions with indeterminate solutions (&lt;em&gt;P&lt;/em&gt; &amp;lt; 0.05) but not on questions with determinate ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Non-parametric Bayesian stochastic block modelling implicated a right frontal network in ART and DRT performance. Strikingly, we found that this network was also implicated in performance on RAPM.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our study represents the most robust investigation of AR and DR in the focally injured brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our findings imply that a right frontal network is critical. The ART and DRT appear to be promising new clinical tests, capable of evaluating reasoning abilities and identifying right frontal lobe dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 21:48:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTFBjR19QWGxlQUZkRVQydlE5X0xfZW9UdG9wN1pSSHNsNlZXSDFBWEpLazZmMUtIdmRrLWxIYzM2aWVqWWlGbDN1bGRJQkx0UDdEV0JTRE5yUGx6WXdKWGxvTG8zMlhxVENhN1lId1JIaEc4d21qdDhHYnFhel8</guid></item><item><title>脐带DNA可能预测未来的代谢健康风险-神经科学新闻 | Umbilical Cord DNA May Predict Future Metabolic Health Risks - Neuroscience News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihAFBVV95cUxOTDUtSE9WbGJHYW1TeWVrWVdPOURSQl9vRmRoV3FkeURIN3c5VUc3WW9SR1RQQ3ZuQjhwVDlUd2NiSG9rSzJNVENHT3pRMG5CU2c4OVgxYjl3VUhNQmtvbzdEN1ZGcnlRYUM3ampxUEg3WjZkbWlWX29vOG5ic0h6RGROWEQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;DNA changes in umbilical cord blood may help predict which children are at higher risk for future health issues like diabetes, liver disease, and stroke. Researchers analyzed chemical tags on DNA, known as methylation patterns, and linked specific alterations to markers of metabolic dysfunction later in childhood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notably, changes in genes like TNS3, GNAS, and CSMD1 were tied to liver fat accumulation, high blood pressure, and abnormal waist-to-hip ratios. The study suggests that environmental factors during pregnancy may influence these early epigenetic signals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Early Risk Markers:&lt;/strong&gt; Changes in DNA methylation at birth were linked to metabolic issues years later.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gene Connections:&lt;/strong&gt; Alterations in genes like TNS3 and GNAS were tied to liver fat and blood pressure problems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preventive Potential:&lt;/strong&gt; Early detection could lead to proactive interventions before disease develops.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Digestive Disease Week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The umbilical cord may become a crystal ball of sorts, helping doctors predict the future of children at risk for long-term health problems, including diabetes, stroke, and liver disease. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DNA changes found in cord blood could offer early clues about which infants are at higher risk — opening the door to earlier and potentially life-saving interventions, according to research to be presented at Digestive Disease Week (DDW) 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-109200"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment.jpg" alt="This shows a heart and DNA." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/umbilical-cord-DNA-neurodevelopment-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;When these switches occur in critical parts of the DNA, called imprint control regions, their effects can persist through fetal development and into later life. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We’re seeing kids develop metabolic problems earlier and earlier, which puts them at higher risk for serious complications as adults,” said lead author Ashley Jowell, MD, a resident physician in internal medicine at Duke University Health System.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If we can identify that risk at birth, we may be able to prevent it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers used a new genetic tool to analyze umbilical cord blood from 38 children enrolled in the Newborn Epigenetics Study, a long-term birth cohort study based in North Carolina. They looked for changes in chemical tags — called methyl groups — on the infants’ DNA that switch genes on or off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When these switches occur in critical parts of the DNA, called imprint control regions, their effects can persist through fetal development and into later life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team compared the DNA changes to health data collected when the children were 7 to 12 years old — including body mass index, liver fat, an indication of liver inflammation or damage known as alanine transaminase (ALT), triglyceride levels, blood pressure, and waist-to-hip ratio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They identified multiple regions of altered DNA associated with metabolic dysfunction later in childhood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changes in a gene called &lt;em&gt;TNS3&lt;/em&gt; were linked to liver fat, ALT, and waist-to-hip ratio, while alterations in others, including &lt;em&gt;GNAS&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;CSMD1&lt;/em&gt;, were connected to blood pressure, waist-to-hip ratio, and ALT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These epigenetic signals are laid down during embryonic development, potentially influenced by environmental factors such as nutrition or maternal health during pregnancy,” said co-author Cynthia Moylan, MD, associate professor of medicine, division of gastroenterology, at Duke University Health System.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If validated in larger studies, this could open the door to new screening tools and early interventions for at-risk children.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the sample size was small, the researchers say the findings are promising and warrant further investigation. A larger National Health Institute-funded follow-up study is underway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current findings do not suggest a direct cause-and-effect relationship between the genetic changes and disease but highlight a potential biological pathway for further research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Just because you’re born with these markers doesn’t mean disease is inevitable,” Dr. Jowell said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But knowing your risk earlier in life could help families and clinicians take proactive steps to support a child’s long-term health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this genetics and neurodevelopment research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#6b050e1c18190404062b0c0a181f19044504190c" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Rachel Shubert&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://gastro.org" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Digestive Disease Week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Rachel Shubert – Digestive Disease Week&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;The findings will be presented at the Digestive Disease Week 2025 conference.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 21:22:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxOTDUtSE9WbGJHYW1TeWVrWVdPOURSQl9vRmRoV3FkeURIN3c5VUc3WW9SR1RQQ3ZuQjhwVDlUd2NiSG9rSzJNVENHT3pRMG5CU2c4OVgxYjl3VUhNQmtvbzdEN1ZGcnlRYUM3ampxUEg3WjZkbWlWX29vOG5ic0h6RGROWEQ</guid></item><item><title>男子因涉嫌给妻子艾滋病而被指控谋杀，同时知道他是艾滋病毒阳性- WKRC | Man charged with murder after allegedly giving wife AIDS while knowing he was HIV-positive - WKRC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi9AJBVV95cUxPY3hFQTh0Sk13ek5xbVVIeXU1MzNjVENXX2hXQ3FIOWt5WnNNVERvaE9tbGNabHBNVGhRTkpnVXY4ekExek1OZ1l0dVFPQ0hPSHhLN0VLX3FGZnpGLU15M1NkQUpqSEJ5SEVjYW1kNlJYT3hfZjdXNXk0a2otWkJVZVdRQWc2U1dNaGV4ZjFVTzlQWFJzSU1DeHgzbE5jWWNkbldjUnl5cWxKT3ZMbWRsWlZJN1hNakRUUmUtZFZuRGFMQlhaOHJ0Q0VEcWlsYmR0X2VmQ25HMnBmZExwYVBFZTdCRE9wLVJRSm00eHpiM3FQRWw4ZU5UR3ZmNkwybkhPQW92M0tiOVRHS09pMl9IUkN3SWpKbGpCWG1Od0lnM3JhMk1sNm03NFFMdVFwbHpQdVRYWFRXZmxlck1feU9mR3hVQTZjZ3NZX0F0ZGpfSzdKa1hDZVhDWnVabFU2OU5LZEtVTk1qcUZ1ZkFac2czUTU5REY?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText-module_storyText__FWhP"&gt;&lt;p&gt;ROCKDALE COUNTY, Ga. (WKRC) - A man was charged with murder after his wife allegedly died from AIDS that she contracted from him after he never told her he was HIV-positive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to reports from the victim's family given to local outlet &lt;em&gt;WAGA&lt;/em&gt;, when Denise Broadie passed away from AIDS in 2022, her family immediately became suspicious that her husband, Cleveland Broadie, knew that he was HIV-positive when he married her in 2014 and intentionally neglected to inform her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The family knew that Denise had been sick in the past, including two bouts of cancer in 2017 and 2019, both of which she beat. However, even after beating cancer a second time, she was still extremely ill and remained in the hospital. While there, tests reportedly found that she had AIDS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Denise was diagnosed with AIDS on March 31, 2022 and passed away from the disease on April 2, 2022, according to an arrest warrant obtained by &lt;em&gt;Law&amp;amp;Crime&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Denise's family claimed that their mother could have been treated for the disease had they known about it earlier, which may have prevented her death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There is malice in what [Cleveland] did," said Denise's daughter Karen Young. "At any time, he could have told her and given her the right to make that decision to stay with him. Not that she would have."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cleveland was arrested after multiple other women came forward claiming that he had also infected them with AIDS, leading to three charges of reckless conduct filed in 2023. According to prosecutors, Cleveland knew he was HIV-positive since 2006 and did not tell any sexual partners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the reckless conduct charges, a grand jury indicted Cleveland with malice murder and felony murder for Denise's death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WKRC</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 19:09:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9AJBVV95cUxPY3hFQTh0Sk13ek5xbVVIeXU1MzNjVENXX2hXQ3FIOWt5WnNNVERvaE9tbGNabHBNVGhRTkpnVXY4ekExek1OZ1l0dVFPQ0hPSHhLN0VLX3FGZnpGLU15M1NkQUpqSEJ5SEVjYW1kNlJYT3hfZjdXNXk0a2otWkJVZVdRQWc2U1dNaGV4ZjFVTzlQWFJzSU1DeHgzbE5jWWNkbldjUnl5cWxKT3ZMbWRsWlZJN1hNakRUUmUtZFZuRGFMQlhaOHJ0Q0VEcWlsYmR0X2VmQ25HMnBmZExwYVBFZTdCRE9wLVJRSm00eHpiM3FQRWw4ZU5UR3ZmNkwybkhPQW92M0tiOVRHS09pMl9IUkN3SWpKbGpCWG1Od0lnM3JhMk1sNm03NFFMdVFwbHpQdVRYWFRXZmxlck1feU9mR3hVQTZjZ3NZX0F0ZGpfSzdKa1hDZVhDWnVabFU2OU5LZEtVTk1qcUZ1ZkFac2czUTU5REY</guid></item><item><title>男子因涉嫌给妻子艾滋病而被指控谋杀，同时知道他是艾滋病毒阳性- WSYX | Man charged with murder after allegedly giving wife AIDS while knowing he was HIV-positive - WSYX</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi_gJBVV95cUxORkd3d25Ja0FISldOSVo5UVI1TU9BQTh6a2QtT2Q3LXdiY0lVSW9QNHZwZWRaMk11SHUzR3F3MDkwLTN1TEFfT0dRdHp4VzJNYXY5eFdjU2RPU2E3VjlmYTBWcWdtN1FqcTdpMzFCOF95X2YzY0VlajdJM3F1MzJiYU1MN3ZGSkRyOHNBeWlLdVR3emZ0SGlfTm1MUjJTVVpEQTYtcG5JbnZfY0VhMF93a3hMd1psV2VOVHFxNFJwMm53d3VZOUNYNFRqRmNZd0F6Z01NTWdKeGNSWk5XOHYtcHNEaWlHS0VGQWluNUJRLTl5dHgySE56eWt0bWt0VjBQWUc3OWd3ZWQ2d2ZPR2NZOVlaNnFMVXJfWXFDVm5fRzYzdmtSb0tVdEI3M3RCYkJjZERuWGpZODZVVlB2X2s5bHdYbFZyR1AydzdSV1BpbzBNZHlKOWxvRDE4TGNPTmd5Rld1bnFUVzB6VmN1MU55eEVGR1Q4MnN1ZDlTRmNR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText-module_storyText__FWhP"&gt;&lt;p&gt;ROCKDALE COUNTY, Ga. (WKRC) - A man was charged with murder after his wife allegedly died from AIDS that she contracted from him after he never told her he was HIV-positive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to reports from the victim's family given to local outlet &lt;em&gt;WAGA&lt;/em&gt;, when Denise Broadie passed away from AIDS in 2022, her family immediately became suspicious that her husband, Cleveland Broadie, knew that he was HIV-positive when he married her in 2014 and intentionally neglected to inform her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The family knew that Denise had been sick in the past, including two bouts of cancer in 2017 and 2019, both of which she beat. However, even after beating cancer a second time, she was still extremely ill and remained in the hospital. While there, tests reportedly found that she had AIDS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Denise was diagnosed with AIDS on March 31, 2022 and passed away from the disease on April 2, 2022, according to an arrest warrant obtained by &lt;em&gt;Law&amp;amp;Crime&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Denise's family claimed that their mother could have been treated for the disease had they known about it earlier, which may have prevented her death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There is malice in what [Cleveland] did," said Denise's daughter Karen Young. "At any time, he could have told her and given her the right to make that decision to stay with him. Not that she would have."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cleveland was arrested after multiple other women came forward claiming that he had also infected them with AIDS, leading to three charges of reckless conduct filed in 2023. According to prosecutors, Cleveland knew he was HIV-positive since 2006 and did not tell any sexual partners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the reckless conduct charges, a grand jury indicted Cleveland with malice murder and felony murder for Denise's death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WSYX</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 19:09:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_gJBVV95cUxORkd3d25Ja0FISldOSVo5UVI1TU9BQTh6a2QtT2Q3LXdiY0lVSW9QNHZwZWRaMk11SHUzR3F3MDkwLTN1TEFfT0dRdHp4VzJNYXY5eFdjU2RPU2E3VjlmYTBWcWdtN1FqcTdpMzFCOF95X2YzY0VlajdJM3F1MzJiYU1MN3ZGSkRyOHNBeWlLdVR3emZ0SGlfTm1MUjJTVVpEQTYtcG5JbnZfY0VhMF93a3hMd1psV2VOVHFxNFJwMm53d3VZOUNYNFRqRmNZd0F6Z01NTWdKeGNSWk5XOHYtcHNEaWlHS0VGQWluNUJRLTl5dHgySE56eWt0bWt0VjBQWUc3OWd3ZWQ2d2ZPR2NZOVlaNnFMVXJfWXFDVm5fRzYzdmtSb0tVdEI3M3RCYkJjZERuWGpZODZVVlB2X2s5bHdYbFZyR1AydzdSV1BpbzBNZHlKOWxvRDE4TGNPTmd5Rld1bnFUVzB6VmN1MU55eEVGR1Q4MnN1ZDlTRmNR</guid></item><item><title>快速燃烧腹部脂肪：这些令人惊讶的食物可以触发身体的脂肪融化能力，科学家说-印度时报 | Burn belly fat fast: These surprising foods could trigger body's fat-melting power, says scientist - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAJBVV95cUxNYWtBY05DRmd0a2cwRG4xNWlramVUbENMaG9IOVdGQ2k2QkRvSDVSWlgwNDlLYURiTXNGaXlxQnJSd05qZDNLOFRtSTVqOTB3Rk5HZGtNNVU5ODN1MEl0Y1dqem1vamw5VkVZcWltSkpmZ2NkRTREbEQyYnNHNzRMejJiR1hOeXpjSEhPRzdSTks0S2hPakI0YVZDc25ZMWMwS0FmRnVrN2QwRXFtdTllTTM4R19iZGsycFZhOWxNZEN5QWFWdk82d0NGLVdkdG02dlFHX3dZOUkyTldkUlZTRmRjZnI4UDNiV3lGWDU1NEFVUXVYX3hJcEh5RlVBcXBad1RQRm5DRHJNSG9KR1RHMlFiV1BNWFIyd0dIR3p6YWLSAaYCQVVfeXFMTXppd25pdW54QkhYUmliekUyVkptZHdaZlVhT3FYU25Pa0RESTV1S3IwY1NEUi1IMFdjdG4tQU9OS2lJaloyYVp2VzBkaEZZclZSeHpQLTJkMmhCUEZNamtzbWtsb244bHYxMlZBaWxLZ0FPY3FsX3RPNWJwOF9VMTJFallDUk5CWmx1SzlTLUhfU0FTSUJKU0hZX3puNlB5Y2kzUVJ3UFllamlTejdFamFFa1pIUmtLY2NienQzOVdvZ0JyZGM4bTFYcUE1TUVXLXFpUWZkUUNNckY0TGM4NmJfSEpBZ2xKcVByZ0p5aGVlVlI5Q19YSVp4bDZ2M084UU0xdTgwVVdkMUV0RS1wMG9LcEVfLUFlM1ZyUjlCdHh3OUhORVNR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fat loss isn't easy to achieve and one of the most stubborn and harmful types is belly fat. Hidden deep inside, wrapped around the internal organs, it can fuel chronic inflammation and is linked to a range of serious health issues, including heart disease, type 2 diabetes, cancers, and dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is there's a secret ally inside your body that can be activated to help destroy this dangerous fat. Dr William Li, the bestselling author of book Eat to Beat Your Diet talks about the many side effects of visceral fat, more popularly known as belly fat, and suggests a mechanism that can kill this fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Li says the best way to burn this 'wiggly jiggly' (visceral) fat is by activating brown fat - a type of fat that burns calories to generate heat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The expert says there is a small percentage of brown fat in the body found around our necks, under our breastbone, a little bit on shoulder blades and scattered in the belly a bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brown fat, also known as brown adipose tissue (BAT) helps regulate body temperature, especially in cold conditions. It burns calories to generate heat, unlike white fat which primarily stores energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Li suggests five foods that can help burn white fat by activating brown fat:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Apples&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These wonderful fruits have chlorogenic acid inside their flesh, which turns on the brown fat and starts to burn down your white fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apples have around 86% water and can be quite filling. They are fibre-rich and a low-calorie fruit. Enjoying the fruit can help manage blood sugar levels, heart health, and brain function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Broccoli or Kale&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These low-calorie and nutrient-dense veggies are a storehouse of phytochemicals called sulforaphane, which helps to activate brown fat cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides, broccoli and kale are full of antioxidants, and can help boost immunity and reduce inflammation in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Bok Choy&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bok Choy or Chinese cabbage can be turned into a delicious preparation in just a few minutes. Cooking them in olive oil can help you get hydroxytyrosol and oleocanthal, both of which can activate brown fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to studies, hydroxytyrosol can increase fatty acid oxidation, potentially boosting the body's ability to burn fat. It may help cut down inflammation and improve insulin sensitivity, which can aid in weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You cut off the bottoms, you wash the leaves, take a wok or a skillet, a little extra virgin olive oil, a little garlic, [and] sauté that up," advises the expert.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By tapping into the body's natural fat-fighting systems, you can shrink belly fat and reclaim your health. Dr. Li's insights certainly offer a science-backed roadmap to a leaner, stronger you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 18:23:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAJBVV95cUxNYWtBY05DRmd0a2cwRG4xNWlramVUbENMaG9IOVdGQ2k2QkRvSDVSWlgwNDlLYURiTXNGaXlxQnJSd05qZDNLOFRtSTVqOTB3Rk5HZGtNNVU5ODN1MEl0Y1dqem1vamw5VkVZcWltSkpmZ2NkRTREbEQyYnNHNzRMejJiR1hOeXpjSEhPRzdSTks0S2hPakI0YVZDc25ZMWMwS0FmRnVrN2QwRXFtdTllTTM4R19iZGsycFZhOWxNZEN5QWFWdk82d0NGLVdkdG02dlFHX3dZOUkyTldkUlZTRmRjZnI4UDNiV3lGWDU1NEFVUXVYX3hJcEh5RlVBcXBad1RQRm5DRHJNSG9KR1RHMlFiV1BNWFIyd0dIR3p6YWLSAaYCQVVfeXFMTXppd25pdW54QkhYUmliekUyVkptZHdaZlVhT3FYU25Pa0RESTV1S3IwY1NEUi1IMFdjdG4tQU9OS2lJaloyYVp2VzBkaEZZclZSeHpQLTJkMmhCUEZNamtzbWtsb244bHYxMlZBaWxLZ0FPY3FsX3RPNWJwOF9VMTJFallDUk5CWmx1SzlTLUhfU0FTSUJKU0hZX3puNlB5Y2kzUVJ3UFllamlTejdFamFFa1pIUmtLY2NienQzOVdvZ0JyZGM4bTFYcUE1TUVXLXFpUWZkUUNNckY0TGM4NmJfSEpBZ2xKcVByZ0p5aGVlVlI5Q19YSVp4bDZ2M084UU0xdTgwVVdkMUV0RS1wMG9LcEVfLUFlM1ZyUjlCdHh3OUhORVNR</guid></item><item><title>独家|研究发现， Z世代女性滥用兴奋剂，狂饮超过任何其他群体-纽约邮报 | Exclusive | Gen Z women abuse stimulants, binge-drink more than any other group, studies find - New York Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxNay1uR1k3TnBWMktDLWxPTTl6bnNFLW0xWnYzOFBsZEtxdnh0SVZnOVhCXzRtU3d6M1YxOWRvNU9ObFBIVmd3Yk9kV25xMkxHQlZMc2t5NnlWMDl5Sk0tRFlvMUZpVVdSRVh5QlpQcGVFZUZ6SDMxVTlfeHc0QTFOVmo4M2tySVZ5LXZRZ2xSaHdnNFRPVWROTWk2QlQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom "&gt;
							


&lt;p&gt;Gen Z women are abusing stimulants and binge drinking more than their male counterparts — and any other age group, new studies have found.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nearly 37% of women ages 18 to 25 reported excessively popping uppers such as Adderall and Ritalin in the past year, more than double that reported by women older than them, according to a study published last month in &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2833100?utm_campaign=articlePDF&amp;amp;utm_medium=articlePDFlink&amp;amp;utm_source=articlePDF&amp;amp;utm_content=jama.2025.4667" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;JAMA Psychiatry. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Only 25% of women ages 26 to 34 reported improper use, according to the study. Women 35 to 64, who researchers said have seen largest rise in stimulant prescriptions, are abusing them the least — 13.7%. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Nearly 37% of women aged 18 to 25 years reported misuse of prescription stimulants. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Alex DiStasi – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Men were not far behind women in abuse of the drugs, which have become so increasingly popular since 2020 that there have been national shortages. Among men ages 18 to 25 who are prescribed the medication, 36.1% reported misuse compared to 36.3% of men aged 26 to 35 and 22% of men ages 35 to 64.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="connatix-outstream-video"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of the 83,762 men and women ages 18 to 64 included in the study, only a quarter of them reported misusing the drugs, including taking them without being prescribed or taking higher or more frequent doses than ordered.&lt;/p&gt;


	



&lt;p&gt;While older women often pop the pills to manage daily life with families, many younger women suffer “feelings of inadequacy” for not meeting social, physical, career and relationship standards, &lt;a href="/Users/dbardolf/Downloads/21-36.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;experts say.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Amphetamines, which stimulate the dopamine reward system the most, were abused three times more. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;standret – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“There’s pressure to have the perfect grades, perfect body, be super popular on social media, and appear to have it all figured out,” Stacey Ross, a mental health specialist at AddictionResource.net, told The Post. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Some feel like they need to be ‘on’ constantly, and that the misuse of stimulants seems like a quick solution to stay there,” Ross said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study’s authors said the findings highlight a need for prevention and intervention.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;They looked at the two types of drugs most commonly used to treat ADHD and help with concentration and alertness: amphetamines, which include Adderall and Vyvanse, and methylphenidates like Ritalin and Concerta. Amphetamines, which stimulate the dopamine reward system more than methylphenidates, were found to be abused three times higher.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Women were historically misdiagnosed and underdiagnosed with ADHD but the gender gap has been closing, especially since the pandemic, according to experts.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Young women also reported binge drinking more than any other group, another study found. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Witoon – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The alarming findings follow reports that young women are also out-drinking men for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A study published last week in JAMA of 267,843 men and women 18 and older found that 31.6% of women ages 18 to 25 reported binge drinking — consuming four or more drinks on one occasion — more than any other group.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;The study compared men’s and women’s habits over two time periods, 2017 to 2019 and 2021 to 2023. It found that men’s binge-drinking levels plummeted nearly 8 percentage points, from 37.7% to 29.9%. But women didn’t see such a drop, falling only 4.8 percent from the prior years.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Societal pressures drive some women to seek pharmacological support, experts say. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;ÃÂÃÂ»ÃÂµÃÂºÃÂÃÂµÃÂ¹ ÃâÃÂ¾ÃÂ½ÃÂµÃÂ½ÃÂºÃÂ¾ – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p class="comments-inline-cta" data-comment-count data-prompt="What do you think?"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Experts say heavy alcohol use has become &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/acer.14690" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;more acceptable for women&lt;/a&gt; and that they are increasingly targeted through marketing and social media campaigns, especially those with higher socio-economic status.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“For females, there continues to be pressure to be ‘fun,’ ‘cool,’ or ‘relaxed,’ and too often, that means drinking,” Ross said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The disturbing findings come amid an increase in alcohol-related liver disease and mortality among young- and middle-aged women than men.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wpcom-liveblog-container"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;

												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 17:54:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxNay1uR1k3TnBWMktDLWxPTTl6bnNFLW0xWnYzOFBsZEtxdnh0SVZnOVhCXzRtU3d6M1YxOWRvNU9ObFBIVmd3Yk9kV25xMkxHQlZMc2t5NnlWMDl5Sk0tRFlvMUZpVVdSRVh5QlpQcGVFZUZ6SDMxVTlfeHc0QTFOVmo4M2tySVZ5LXZRZ2xSaHdnNFRPVWROTWk2QlQ</guid></item><item><title>大流行潜力：科学家发现美国致命新兴疾病的3个热点- SciTechDaily | Pandemic Potential: Scientists Discover 3 Hotspots of Deadly Emerging Disease in the US - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisgFBVV95cUxPYm5jZUJLSE1SckRqVUYtM1lhVU5Wc1RSZGxSbVBFLWtqNnRSWVJsMDBIQ3d5ai1DZUJ1dHpUSTA5Z1VoX0NYX2ZLOG9sVFEwcWs5b3ZLM0NObHhMdVhWbFpjXy1iQU5ua1JsX3hzTnJpbmhoU1BQSV96WUZRNnEybVdkZmt1cE96WjRTS3NGMGJTNVdGUTVfOERNSmNyUDZlZkRvaV85TkZkSHRrM1h4Y1JR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 17:49:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxPYm5jZUJLSE1SckRqVUYtM1lhVU5Wc1RSZGxSbVBFLWtqNnRSWVJsMDBIQ3d5ai1DZUJ1dHpUSTA5Z1VoX0NYX2ZLOG9sVFEwcWs5b3ZLM0NObHhMdVhWbFpjXy1iQU5ua1JsX3hzTnJpbmhoU1BQSV96WUZRNnEybVdkZmt1cE96WjRTS3NGMGJTNVdGUTVfOERNSmNyUDZlZkRvaV85TkZkSHRrM1h4Y1JR</guid></item><item><title>美国麻疹病例达到近900例，德克萨斯州超过600例- HuffPost | Measles Cases In U.S. Hit Nearly 900, With More Than 600 Cases In Texas - HuffPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijAFBVV95cUxPa00wWHNCQXFVbFQ0bFluTGhPUkx5Y05nYTdLVmhOdzlDdVA5S2NBdkxsMWdnSFNDV25KSzZpdXotdXhjNnh1NGVxOVFINE5lTWM2SjlvRTJMMUFPNDEyR3N3eWdGQ2tnM1dmN0lVbWxDT1dyN0ZPUHhfeUc3T0NTdk9veEpybGIxemtmVtIBkgFBVV95cUxQNWlLSkNqQlhEdDV4Smd1TXhXeDNzem02RFhWQlJJRVRqandTekNxSmVmWDI2Nm5xNHpTaFRmWDhCeWtVUVVZNjVYMERDWFE1YWlTV21HWWFBQTMtc3diVEVSMmx0WFJNVVlWc0JwUHZPLVJmQ0prMXVuVkNxTU5HZ0dOMk9iXzBoUW9OZGR5MG9DQQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A deadly and fast-spreading measles outbreak that started in western Texas in January has spread across the United States, with nearly 900 cases now reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are currently &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="884 confirmed cases" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680d0467e4b04560cabe9300" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;884 confirmed cases&lt;/a&gt; of measles across the U.S., according to Friday data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. The majority of those cases come from Texas, &lt;a href="https://www.dshs.texas.gov/news-alerts/measles-outbreak-2025" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="where 646 cases " data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680d0467e4b04560cabe9300" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.dshs.texas.gov/news-alerts/measles-outbreak-2025" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;where 646 cases &lt;/a&gt;have been confirmed in the state since late January. Of all U.S. cases, 94 people have been hospitalized. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cases have now been confirmed in 29 states. Six states ― Kansas, Michigan, New Mexico, Ohio and Texas ― have reported outbreaks, meaning there are three or more related cases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Texas has seen a rise of 22 cases since Tuesday, according to the Texas Department of State Health Services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Covenant Children's Hospital is pictured from outside the emergency entrance on Wednesday, Feb. 26, 2025, in Lubbock, Texas, after the first U.S. death from measles since 2015.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three deaths have been reported since the outbreak began, two of which were school-aged children in Texas &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/ap-us-measles-outbreak-death-texas_n_67f29c32e4b0abfc4625ad56" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="who had not been vaccinated." data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680d0467e4b04560cabe9300" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="67f29c32e4b0abfc4625ad56" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;who had not been vaccinated.&lt;/a&gt; Data from the CDC shows that 97% of cases in the U.S. came from people who are unvaccinated or whose vaccination status is unknown. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Measles is an airborne, extremely infectious, and potentially severe rash illness,” the CDC’s website says. “&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/history.html" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Before the measles vaccine" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680d0467e4b04560cabe9300" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/history.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Before the measles vaccine&lt;/a&gt; was introduced, an estimated 48,000 people were hospitalized and 400–500 people died in the United States each year.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has spread misleading claims about vaccinations, and &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/rfk-jr-dismisses-measles-outbreak_n_67bf5519e4b053f9e3997f53" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="initially downplayed" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680d0467e4b04560cabe9300" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="67bf5519e4b053f9e3997f53" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;initially downplayed&lt;/a&gt; the current spread of measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s not unusual,” he said in February when asked about the measles death of a 6-year-old Texas boy. “We have measles outbreaks every year.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facing criticism, Kennedy promoted the measles vaccine after &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/06/health/measles-death-texas.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="attending the funeral of an 8-year-old Texas girl " data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="680d0467e4b04560cabe9300" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/06/health/measles-death-texas.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;attending the funeral of an 8-year-old Texas girl &lt;/a&gt;who died from measles at the start of April.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“My intention was to come down here quietly to console the families and to be with the community in their moment of grief,” Kennedy said in a message posted on X.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The most effective way to prevent the spread of measles is the MMR vaccine,” he added, referring to the measles, mumps and rubella vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public health officials have warned that cases will continue to rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Due to the highly contagious nature of this disease, additional cases are likely to occur in the outbreak area and the surrounding communities,” the Texas Department of State Health Services said in its latest update.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 17:00:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxPa00wWHNCQXFVbFQ0bFluTGhPUkx5Y05nYTdLVmhOdzlDdVA5S2NBdkxsMWdnSFNDV25KSzZpdXotdXhjNnh1NGVxOVFINE5lTWM2SjlvRTJMMUFPNDEyR3N3eWdGQ2tnM1dmN0lVbWxDT1dyN0ZPUHhfeUc3T0NTdk9veEpybGIxemtmVtIBkgFBVV95cUxQNWlLSkNqQlhEdDV4Smd1TXhXeDNzem02RFhWQlJJRVRqandTekNxSmVmWDI2Nm5xNHpTaFRmWDhCeWtVUVVZNjVYMERDWFE1YWlTV21HWWFBQTMtc3diVEVSMmx0WFJNVVlWc0JwUHZPLVJmQ0prMXVuVkNxTU5HZ0dOMk9iXzBoUW9OZGR5MG9DQQ</guid></item><item><title>Pilly Labs胶原蛋白软糖正在审核中：最佳胶原蛋白- GlobeNewswire | Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies Under Review: Best Collagen - GlobeNewswire</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimgJBVV95cUxPMURUS2hDNk1fa2psRmFQa1FXVURTQ21KZEo4dVl6QWJqTUNoN0lzVUg5MG9zb0JraDdHZ3h2eVNNRUdyeEhNcE1CUXY1Vm1IVGdqbnVFaTFFemYzM0w3QWk2MGlEZjJyZWpCZV9OUFJNUjV0ZkNLeDRaRHlVeW11bi1xWjlIRVg5RGZtQUN4TWFxM1NHY1E3Z1RDcVoxbkR1WGs1Yi16ZFhhRlRNY0dlTUIzVFJoWVNNbGVvbHNrTmtTM0g5YkRWMXM2eWh5Zng4RzFUTWpJNzhiQjhReS1SOTRiVHJMX203bkplVWdvbTdqbDZBUmc0WGVMdkgwWVA5Z0lTV0dadEc5VDhGSDNXMTc1Y2p6dTROQ2c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-body-container article-body " id="main-body-container" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chicago, April  26, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- &lt;img alt="Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies Under Review: Best Collagen Supplement for Better Skin, Joints and Hair Health on the Market" data-mce-src="https://smallfarmtoday.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Pilly-Labs-Collagen-Gummies.jpg" src="https://smallfarmtoday.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Pilly-Labs-Collagen-Gummies.jpg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;In This Article, You'll Discover:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Why Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies are considered a &lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=dw6msEoDuP3VWT3VD68f7X2VMTJdJ5-sH9rrHNGcHIt6iKK8vOuEZeSho6p4Hh7yMjd3qEePVjtXt3hOnj135GnJEyT0wtSWGeQRh-4g5t4C5SPEBLHnUREVfWJ6GV-7o5-VxRAhBrr4ruCLSm1wUw==" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;top-rated collagen supplement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for improving skin, joints, and hair health naturally over the long term.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The science behind collagen peptides and why they are essential for achieving a youthful glow, enhanced joint flexibility, and stronger hair and nails.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How do Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies compare to other best collagen supplements, and why are they the superior choice for functional beauty and inside-out wellness?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;What ingredients like Vitamin C, Biotin, and Zinc do to support faster skin hydration, hair growth acceleration, and joint comfort?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to successfully incorporate Pilly Collagen Gummies into your daily wellness routine for 3, 6, or 12 months to instill new healthy habits that support glow-up naturally.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Real user testimonials and clinical research support the effectiveness of these collagen gummies for skincare health, joint mobility, and hair strength.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Transparent details about pricing, discounts, satisfaction guarantees, and why now is the best time to start a natural collagen booster habit for long-term beauty and wellness.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;TL;DR Summary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies delivers a premium blend of hydrolyzed collagen peptides, Vitamin C, Biotin, and Zinc designed to enhance skin, joints, and hair health naturally. Recognized among the best collagen supplements for 2025, these gummies help promote a youthful glow, improve joint flexibility, strengthen hair and nails, and support inside-out wellness without the hassle of powders or pills.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;With a focus on clean beauty, bioavailable collagen, and sustainable wellness practices, Pilly Labs offers a delicious and convenient way to build a long-term collagen supplementation habit. Whether you're aiming for improved skincare health, arthritis support, or a complete glow-up, Pilly Collagen Gummies are formulated to help you achieve noticeable, lasting results.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This article will explore in depth why Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies rank among the best collagen gummies and how you can integrate this functional beauty supplement into your daily self-care routine for transformative, natural health benefits over 90 days, 6 months, or even 12 months.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Introduction&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;If you've been searching for a natural way to enhance your skin, strengthen your joints, and revitalize your hair, you're not alone. Collagen supplements have surged in popularity as more people realize how crucial collagen is for maintaining long-term health and beauty from within. Among the many options available today, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=Ix1BE7tFunhof8McScQq5tqKdipnhNJ7kybvIQ4cXTWsuqacprO1kd12szmgw0otGQvWbQdJ4MjkTt0mVquU5U74W8pCrOZnMuM-wWbk6p0TnWbJvBuxPBGAOmeCAg2O" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title="Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies"&gt;Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; stand out as one of the best collagen supplements on the market for those committed to achieving real, lasting results.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This comprehensive guide will walk you through everything you need to know about Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies — from understanding the science behind collagen peptides to uncovering the specific benefits that users are experiencing after three, six, and even twelve months of consistent use. Whether your goal is to achieve a youthful glow naturally, support joint flexibility, or restore vibrant hair health, this article is designed to provide you with all the facts, strategies, and insights needed to make an informed decision.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;By the end, you'll know precisely why Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies are consistently ranked among the best collagen gummies available today and how you can incorporate this simple, effective supplement into your daily routine to build strong, sustainable wellness habits for the future.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What Are Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies are a premium daily supplement designed to help you restore and maintain healthy collagen levels throughout your body. Formulated with hydrolyzed collagen peptides, these gummies provide an easy, delicious, and highly bioavailable way to support your skin, joints, hair, and nails without the need for powders or capsules.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Each serving delivers a clinically informed blend of collagen peptides enhanced with Vitamin C, Biotin, Zinc, and Vitamin E—ingredients specifically chosen for their ability to boost collagen synthesis, support skin hydration, promote joint flexibility, and naturally strengthen hair strands. Made with non-GMO, gluten-free, and antibiotic-free ingredients, Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies reflect a strong commitment to clean beauty and sustainable wellness that resonates with today's health-conscious consumers.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Unlike many traditional collagen supplements that require mixing or swallowing large pills, Pilly Labs offers a more enjoyable solution. These fruit-flavored gummies not only taste great but are also easy to incorporate into your daily routine, making it simple to stay consistent with your wellness goals. This convenience and delicious taste make Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies a more appealing choice for those looking to improve their health and beauty from within.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Designed for long-term results, Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies are ideal for those who want to glow up naturally, strengthen their mobility, and embrace a holistic approach to beauty and health from within. Whether you're starting a 90-day collagen challenge or looking for a full-year transformation, these gummies provide the foundation for building strong, sustainable habits and a brighter future.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=bJlDPO5oIehHNVNRzMbZyraYXS95EqQ_a7tXeSqm7eyQdmlF1vhdBAMuo9FnFyuSbZV_hTjkv7r5kBR-8akDRjrhn8YrmfqZeKO4dfZuKkMI5Biyk23P5BXMvUpu67DenP_aDkYA8YC5lgw2WnCIDZ8um5F5_6Cg5aJEIfLeGxAAzkYbd9ZZelWYL1ayAQaTMvw6alkZ5--b8U9WYvsU9eEwu8YX9Z6yymOdbG5md3Q-i6zlYoICnp-UkJAUPU9oDGOZpolm0m_M7RPMW6es2p5asxHOb3wMvb9KEBko1Opp3WTCbfl38US0FvvyHGplLUlRHoZa_ftFYijtDEtzoRR4AQuyqY8ln61x20I3t6A=" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feel confident knowing you’re nourishing your body from the inside out. Start your wellness journey today—order Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies and see the difference for your skin, hair, and joints.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why Collagen Is Essential for Long-Term Skin, Joint, and Hair Health&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Collagen is the most abundant protein in the human body, acting as a primary structural component for skin, bones, joints, tendons, and connective tissues. Often referred to as the "building block of beauty and mobility," collagen provides the strength, elasticity, and resilience needed to maintain youthful skin, flexible joints, and strong, vibrant hair.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;However, starting as early as our mid-20s, natural collagen production begins to decline by approximately 1% each year. By the time we reach our 40s and 50s, the visible and physical effects of collagen loss become more apparent — including fine lines, sagging skin, brittle hair, joint stiffness, and overall decreased mobility. Environmental stressors such as sun exposure, pollution, poor diet, and stress further accelerate this depletion, making proactive collagen replenishment an essential part of any long-term wellness strategy.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Supplementing daily with a high-quality collagen product like Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies provides a natural and effective way to restore these vital structural proteins. Unlike short-term topical solutions, collagen supplementation works from the inside out, fueling the body's ability to rebuild and regenerate critical tissues. This inside-out wellness approach not only supports a youthful appearance but also promotes better joint flexibility, stronger bones, and healthier hair over time.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Choosing a hydrolyzed collagen supplement — where the collagen is broken down into smaller, more bioavailable peptides — ensures better absorption and effectiveness. Combined with key cofactors like Vitamin C, Biotin, and Zinc, collagen peptides can significantly accelerate the body's natural collagen synthesis, amplifying results for those committed to a sustainable beauty and health routine.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Incorporating a natural collagen booster into your daily self-care regimen is no longer just about aesthetics; it is now a core pillar of the functional beauty movement. A consistent intake of collagen can help maintain skin hydration, enhance joint resilience, and provide the foundation for long-term vitality and a healthier aging process.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Whether your goal is a youthful glow, stronger hair, or greater mobility, understanding the role of collagen — and taking proactive steps to support it — is one of the smartest investments you can make in your long-term health and appearance.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Real Benefits of Taking Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies Daily&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Consistency is the key to seeing real, transformative results from any collagen supplement. Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies are designed to support a wide range of beauty and wellness goals when taken daily over time. Whether you're focused on restoring youthful skin, strengthening your hair, or improving joint comfort, this supplement delivers noticeable improvements by working from within.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Here's what consistent use of Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies can help you achieve:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;For Skin: Restore Youthful Elasticity and Hydration&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Collagen is essential for maintaining firm, smooth, and hydrated skin. As natural collagen production decreases with age, skin begins to show visible signs of aging, such as fine lines, wrinkles, and dryness.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Daily supplementation with Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies helps to rebuild collagen fibers beneath the surface, improving skin elasticity, reducing the appearance of fine lines, and boosting overall hydration. The inclusion of Vitamin C and Vitamin E further amplifies the skin's natural glow by supporting collagen stability and protecting against environmental damage.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;For individuals committed to a natural glow-up journey, these collagen gummies offer a reliable foundation for achieving long-term skin health and resilience.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;For Hair and Nails: Strengthen and Revitalize from Within&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Hair thinning, brittleness, and slow growth are common signs of weakened collagen and keratin structures. Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies, enhanced with Biotin and Zinc, work synergistically to support stronger, thicker hair and resilient nails.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Biotin promotes the production of keratin, the key structural protein in hair and nails, while collagen peptides provide the amino acids necessary to nourish follicles and support healthy growth cycles. With regular use, many users report increased hair thickness, stronger nail integrity, and a reduction in breakage.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This targeted support makes Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies one of the best collagen supplements for women and men looking to enhance their natural beauty from within.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;For Joints and Bones: Improve Flexibility and Comfort&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Joint discomfort and reduced mobility often accompany collagen loss over time. Collagen is critical for maintaining the integrity of cartilage, the cushioning tissue that protects joints. When collagen levels decline, joints can become stiff, less flexible, and more prone to wear and tear.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;By replenishing collagen stores with bioavailable peptides, Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies support joint lubrication, flexibility, and comfort. The addition of Vitamin C and Zinc further enhances connective tissue strength, helping to protect against joint degradation and supporting an active lifestyle well into the future.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;For those seeking natural arthritis support or preventative joint care, daily collagen supplementation offers a vital strategy for maintaining mobility and quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;For Overall Health and Longevity&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Beyond aesthetic benefits, collagen peptides contribute to overall wellness by supporting muscle mass, promoting gut health, strengthening bones, and even improving cardiovascular function. As part of a holistic wellness stack, Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies aligns with the growing trend of inside-out wellness, where beauty and health are treated as interconnected goals.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Making collagen supplementation part of your daily routine isn't about more than addressing current concerns—it's about investing in your long-term vitality, resilience, and confidence.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=7Bsp0RyUwajdzP_MY2Q51WipLII9Raj4Ow-BZqb_YQLUAiqwdH0Np05c2V8ZIqdfA-bYSGvfhGHcpzT0Rt3q4N0de-eFaRguVzGuRkzdfQz4LWGdIqGzBc87ssRjqjSDfbSAkWz-V7bDxG5QlGoEpS6zIcr1PYOZ1AsLr_rucGFmLhmgbOL101vi8-p7Iuxcf2xz5uP6MQChAxFHBgBsxv_KwslEQB3quxhedeCC2O0TSIwMkGM8ZMzcsJ46TCPyXHfFwXSRXEembCx7jX60Fl0qIbwOZ7l5NmKCu5wweucXK7W6BeuT4rFdsM-9-lz55S-W5SFaV73BDaD8rgwzbg==" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discover why so many are choosing Pilly Labs for their daily self-care. Ready for real results? Buy Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies now and support your beauty and mobility from within.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies Are Different from Other Collagen Products&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;In a growing market flooded with collagen powders, capsules, and gummies, it's necessary to understand what sets Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies apart from the rest. Not all collagen supplements deliver the same results, and the difference often lies in the quality of ingredients, the formulation strategy, and the overall commitment to clean, effective wellness.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Here's why Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies stand out as one of the best collagen supplements available today:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Marine-Based Collagen for Higher Purity&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Pilly Labs sources its collagen from marine collagen peptides, which are widely regarded as one of the purest and most bioavailable forms of collagen. Marine collagen has a smaller particle size compared to bovine or porcine collagen, making it easier for the body to absorb and utilize efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This enhanced absorption means users are more likely to see faster and more noticeable improvements in skin elasticity, joint flexibility, and hair strength — a critical advantage for anyone serious about natural beauty and inside-out wellness.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Enhanced Absorption with Targeted Nutrients&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Collagen alone isn't enough. For the body to synthesize and stabilize new collagen fibers effectively, it needs key cofactors like Vitamin C, Biotin, and Zinc. Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies are formulated with these essential nutrients to maximize the impact of every serving.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;By supporting the complete collagen production cycle, Pilly Labs ensures users aren't just consuming collagen — they are optimizing the conditions necessary for long-term results.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Clean Beauty Commitment&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Today's consumers demand more than just effectiveness; they want clean, sustainable, and ethically sourced products. Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies are non-GMO, gluten-free, antibiotic-free, and made without artificial flavors or colors. Natural fruit extracts like purple carrot juice are used for flavor and color, supporting the clean beauty and sustainable wellness movements.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This transparency and dedication to ingredient quality help build long-term trust with consumers who prioritize health-conscious, responsible living.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Delicious, Convenient, and Easy to Use&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Unlike traditional collagen powders that require mixing or unappealing capsules that are difficult to swallow, Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies offer a simple and enjoyable experience. The delicious fruit-flavored gummies are easy to incorporate into any daily routine, making consistency — the most critical factor in seeing tangible results — far more achievable.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This combination of effectiveness, convenience, and taste removes the most significant barriers to success with collagen supplementation, helping users stay committed to their 90-day, 6-month, or 12-month glow-up journeys.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why This Matters&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;When it comes to investing in your long-term skin, joint, and hair health, quality matters. Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies delivers a comprehensive solution that not only meets but exceeds the standards of modern wellness, making them an ideal choice for anyone ready to embrace a functional beauty approach and sustainable self-care practices.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Choosing a collagen supplement isn't just about immediate results — it's about building habits that nourish and support your body for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to Use Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies for Best Results&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Taking collagen consistently is the key to unlocking its full range of benefits for skin, joints, hair, and overall health. Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies are specifically formulated to make daily collagen supplementation simple, enjoyable, and sustainable for the long term.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Here's how to use them effectively to maximize your results:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Suggested Daily Dosage&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;For optimal outcomes, it is recommended to take &lt;strong&gt;two Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies per day&lt;/strong&gt;. This daily serving delivers a potent dose of hydrolyzed collagen peptides, along with Vitamin C, Biotin, Zinc, and Vitamin E, ensuring that your body has the building blocks it needs to support collagen synthesis and maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;The gummies can be taken at any time of day, with or without food. Many users find it convenient to incorporate them into their morning routine or as a midday wellness boost.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Building a Long-Term Habit for Maximum Benefits&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;While some improvements in skin hydration and hair strength may be noticeable within a few weeks, the most profound transformations typically occur over a longer timeframe. Collagen works cumulatively within the body, and actual regenerative changes often take consistent effort over months.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;For best results, consider following one of these wellness timelines:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;90-Day Collagen Challenge:&lt;/strong&gt; Establish a new beauty and wellness routine. Noticeable improvements in skin texture, joint comfort, and hair vitality often begin appearing around the three-month mark.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6-Month Renewal Plan:&lt;/strong&gt; Deeper structural support. With six months of continuous collagen supplementation, users typically report firmer skin, stronger nails, fuller hair, and improved joint flexibility.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;12-Month Lifestyle Transformation:&lt;/strong&gt; Long-term inside-out wellness. A whole year of consistent collagen intake can support substantial changes in overall appearance, mobility, and natural resilience, aligning with longevity and healthy aging goals.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;By committing to a 3-, 6-, or 12-month collagen habit, you're investing in a future where natural vitality and youthful radiance are not just temporary—they become a sustainable part of your life.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tips for Boosting Collagen Results Naturally&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;To further enhance the benefits of Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies, consider pairing them with additional wellness practices that support collagen production and preservation:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stay well-hydrated to maintain skin elasticity and support cellular function.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prioritize a balanced diet rich in antioxidants and healthy fats.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Incorporate strength training exercises to support joint and bone health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimize sun exposure and use SPF to protect existing collagen fibers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage stress through mindfulness practices, as high cortisol levels can degrade collagen.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;By combining Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies with a comprehensive wellness lifestyle, you create an environment where your body can truly thrive — both inside and out.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=gZZFpjM0vvDZWE7BUpc8kl8QXS-ddku6nDObqMORL095PbQ6XEpGL13nYudNFXh1z7aC7K35RuGwHT0ARQm3HVROqWlAUyoe3F7pj330lPB4dO8L3-JNACoxu62v1d_sGCxEoNi8qan_Aa1dAl9ZwojlmptMfWZ6rIylzZo11lZWrCRe8yQW2G0ErNfWbHL6f-FQUKWunghsv-r3x-aJ8tEgWiSxJDboBfS6WnDg0JQhxjPnrpjOiMvqyii9G38NWe_rJxm7d9ig9WF1VlS4kAhfZx-GOrZ8cn_BGwnv3GiEsrJDZgMpAZWQ-R6fde4U" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consistency is simple when your supplement tastes this good. Don’t wait to glow up—shop Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies and make healthy habits easy and enjoyable.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Customer Testimonials and Success Stories&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Nothing is more powerful than hearing directly from people who have experienced fundamental transformations. Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies have quickly earned a loyal following from customers who have committed to consistent use and reaped the full benefits of inside-out wellness.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Here's what real users are saying about their glow-up journeys with Pilly Labs:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skin Transformation Stories&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Many users report noticeable improvements in skin texture, hydration, and elasticity within the first 90 days of consistent use. Fine lines appear softer, skin feels firmer, and an overall youthful glow returns.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"After three months of taking Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies, my skin feels hydrated all day, and my laugh lines have noticeably faded. People keep asking me what I'm doing differently." — Sarah, 42&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"I've tried creams and serums for years, but nothing gave me results like this. My skin genuinely looks healthier from the inside out." — Jasmine, 36&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hair and Nail Revitalization&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Strengthening hair and nails from within is another area where Pilly Labs users see outstanding improvements. Regular supplementation provides the building blocks needed for stronger, shinier hair and more resilient nails.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"My hair was thinning badly before. Six months into my collagen routine, my hair is thicker, shinier, and even my hairstylist noticed." — Michelle, 49&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"I used to have brittle nails that would never grow. Now they're strong and healthy — I don't even need fake nails anymore." — Amanda, 33&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Joint and Mobility Improvements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;For those concerned about joint health, daily collagen intake has made a visible difference in flexibility, comfort, and ease of movement.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"I'm in my early 50s and started noticing knee stiffness. After four months on Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies, my knees feel better than they have in years. I'm hiking again without pain." — Robert, 53&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Yoga was getting difficult due to joint discomfort. Collagen supplementation gave me my flexibility back." — Emily, 47&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Long-Term Wellness Success&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Customers who commit to the 6-month or 12-month collagen renewal plans report feeling more confident, energized, and empowered to maintain a healthy, vibrant lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Taking Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies became part of my self-care routine. After a full year, my skin, joints, hair — everything feels stronger. It's a small habit that made a massive difference." — Monica, 58&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why Testimonials Matter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Hearing the real-world experiences of others helps reinforce the tangible benefits of consistent collagen supplementation. These testimonials not only highlight the visible transformations users are achieving but also inspire new customers to believe that lasting change is possible with a natural collagen booster.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;When you combine a potent formula with consistent use and healthy lifestyle habits, the results speak for themselves — and Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies continue to prove it with every success story.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Science Behind Collagen Supplementation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;While personal success stories are inspiring, scientific research provides the foundation that validates collagen supplementation as a legitimate strategy for promoting long-term skin, joint, and hair health. Understanding the science behind collagen peptides helps explain why consistent daily intake is such a powerful tool for those committed to inside-out wellness.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Collagen and Skin Health&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Multiple clinical studies have demonstrated that supplementing with hydrolyzed collagen peptides can significantly improve skin hydration, elasticity, and texture. A landmark study published in &lt;em&gt;Skin Pharmacology and Physiology&lt;/em&gt; found that participants who consumed collagen peptides daily for eight weeks experienced a measurable reduction in wrinkle depth and an improvement in skin elasticity compared to a placebo group.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;The mechanism is straightforward: collagen peptides stimulate fibroblast cells in the skin to produce more collagen and elastin fibers, leading to smoother, firmer skin from within. When combined with Vitamin C — a critical cofactor in collagen production — the results are amplified, supporting a natural, sustainable glow-up.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Collagen and Joint Flexibility&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Research published in the &lt;em&gt;Current Medical Research and Opinion Journal&lt;/em&gt; shows that collagen supplementation can also significantly reduce joint discomfort and improve flexibility, especially in individuals experiencing age-related joint degeneration or those engaging in strenuous physical activity.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Hydrolyzed collagen has been shown to accumulate in cartilage tissue and stimulate the production of type II collagen, the primary structural protein in joints. This improves cushioning, reduces friction, and promotes greater comfort during movement — aligning perfectly with the goal of maintaining active lifestyles well into later years.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Collagen and Hair Growth&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;While research on collagen and hair is emerging, early studies and clinical observations suggest that collagen's role in supporting the dermal layers of the scalp is critical for maintaining strong, healthy hair follicles. In combination with Biotin and Zinc, collagen supplementation creates an optimal environment for hair strength, resilience, and growth.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Users consistently report improvements in hair thickness, shininess, and reduced breakage after several months of consistent collagen intake, which aligns with the natural life cycle of hair growth phases.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why This Matters&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Scientific evidence supports what many users experience firsthand: collagen supplementation, when properly formulated and taken consistently, has measurable benefits for skin appearance, joint health, and hair vitality.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies are crafted to meet the exact conditions shown in clinical studies to be effective—providing hydrolyzed collagen peptides, Vitamin C, Biotin, Zinc, and Vitamin E in an easy-to-use daily format. By aligning real-world use with scientific best practices, Pilly Labs empowers users to achieve meaningful, lasting results through natural collagen-boosting strategies.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=H0MzqT7cQljAASZBuwxz0POuW7JpcDoo8eCwFaC5eGzOHid3wGKb6aKkIEQ_EJde7my9P4osMf-djsG07bdKoYemyclmyFr8SSC0SekQtsek2LeTC8ZFAuMlZ8O1czOyjZffHrxs5lC9oKiHYgojFmXP_HrkUVlGtvd6lHBA6_ruzQeHfRv0XosQxA_jlqPtjsdS-qMYv5iKeN9p0g-Lw9J5iGVulEsRxXya9jC3biYFhn_2C5q_F_RlV98AW3yMFK-c3VjkClVUEy0Y-lxFi4u073FHFpUfSHwdNuvpL0pUnU1FrirC9KVlhEldvTCuYZpkCeyKshhTq46Q-qivjw==" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See visible improvements as you stick to your new collagen routine. Invest in long-term beauty and joint comfort. Order Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies and start your transformation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pricing, Savings, and Bundle Options&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies are not just an investment in better skin, stronger joints, and healthier hair — they are an investment in your long-term wellness and vitality. Recognizing that lasting results come from consistency, Pilly Labs offers several pricing and bundle options designed to make building a daily collagen habit easy and affordable.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Here's how you can get started:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Single Bottle — Starter Plan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price:&lt;/strong&gt; $24.99&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contents:&lt;/strong&gt; 60 gummies (30-day supply)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ideal for individuals who want to begin their collagen journey and experience the benefits of daily supplementation firsthand.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Double Pack — 60-Day Commitment&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price:&lt;/strong&gt; Save 19% with two bottles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Perfect for those ready to build momentum with a two-month glow-up challenge, providing the foundation for visible skin, hair, and joint improvements.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Triple Pack — Best Value (90 Days)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price:&lt;/strong&gt; Save 33% with three bottles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recommended for those serious about achieving fundamental transformation. The 90-day commitment aligns with the natural collagen synthesis timeline, maximizing your chances of seeing measurable, lasting results in skin elasticity, joint flexibility, and hair strength.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies Best Collagen Supplement for Better Skin, Joints and Hair Health Prices" data-mce-src="https://smallfarmtoday.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Pilly-Labs-Collagen-Gummies-Pricing.jpg" src="https://smallfarmtoday.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Pilly-Labs-Collagen-Gummies-Pricing.jpg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free Shipping&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Orders over $99 qualify for &lt;strong&gt;free shipping within the United States&lt;/strong&gt;, making it even easier to stock up and commit to your wellness goals without additional costs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why Bundling Makes Sense&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Collagen restoration is not an overnight process. Clinical studies and real-world results show that actual improvements often emerge after three to six months of consistent use. Committing to a 90-day, 6-month, or even 12-month collagen regimen ensures that you're giving your body the time and nutrients it needs to rebuild from the inside out.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Choosing a multi-bottle bundle not only saves money but also supports your commitment to a complete glow-up transformation — from enhanced skin hydration and reduced wrinkles to stronger joints and more resilient hair.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;By starting today and selecting the bundle that fits your goals, you're taking the first step toward a healthier, more vibrant future.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Risk-Free Purchase: Satisfaction Guarantee&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Choosing the right collagen supplement is an important decision, and Pilly Labs stands firmly behind the quality and effectiveness of its Collagen Gummies. To ensure every customer feels confident in their purchase, Pilly Labs offers a comprehensive satisfaction guarantee.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;100% Satisfaction Guarantee&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;If, for any reason, you are not completely satisfied with your Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies, you can request a refund within 30 days of your purchase. This risk-free policy gives you the freedom to try the product, experience the benefits firsthand, and decide if it's the right addition to your wellness routine — without any financial worry.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Pilly Labs is committed to transparency, quality, and customer trust. From sourcing clean, bioavailable collagen peptides to maintaining rigorous manufacturing standards, every step of the process is designed with your satisfaction and long-term success in mind.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Easy Returns and Customer Support&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contact Pilly Labs customer service to initiate a return.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Returns are processed promptly to ensure a hassle-free experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Full details on the return process are available on the official Pilly Labs website.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;When you invest in Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies, you're not just purchasing a supplement—you're partnering with a brand dedicated to helping you achieve your skincare, joint health, and hair vitality goals through safe, natural, and practical solutions.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why This Matters&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Offering a satisfaction guarantee removes the final barrier to action. It assures customers that they are making a wise, low-risk investment in their wellness journey — backed by a brand that genuinely cares about delivering real results.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Confidence in both the product and the purchase process is essential for making a long-term commitment, and Pilly Labs provides that assurance with every bottle.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=fCyiwtxKrVDpCEjf0LiBXf489nnGm7PRAuMQSBORdAKWe48Mise_pddNwHP6eEb94Y_HdtdOB673PA9InAiBtAT85j9t7EaYsO5kdntfYcr05aqQ-bD1JJGtXDeqtsS_59ZKSJCCKx1kv0WQoBvY74lwkVItK9igpSzvDqddm7M1xJ32UlzAQDuENwW_If_7fTYgEhZs-hnhhe3v5tTRdomdru98Zeij0tslhadV9UQkprifkokTagkM0hN6bxHtHm4s_msp5XfQadIC0Me9sAP_8f4lOPjHh5OPvrjEUxGoqPzmsCMqZWKVRooaNFH9YYKoKAsnhOaksX8xiT_jia5PidCN9fHxR7TiMAx633c=" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A small daily habit can lead to big changes in your overall wellness. Take the first step toward stronger hair, flexible joints, and radiant skin—purchase Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies now.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pilly Labs: Company Mission and Values&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;At Pilly Labs, the mission is simple yet powerful: to empower individuals to live healthier, more vibrant lives through natural, science-backed wellness solutions. Every product — including the bestselling Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies — is designed with a deep commitment to quality, transparency, and sustainable health practices.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Commitment to Clean Beauty and Wellness&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Pilly Labs believes that what you put into your body matters. That's why all collagen gummies are crafted using non-GMO ingredients, without gluten, antibiotics, or artificial additives. Natural fruit extracts like purple carrot juice are used for flavor and color, aligning with the principles of clean beauty and holistic wellness.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This dedication to clean, responsible ingredients ensures that customers can trust every gummy they take — knowing it supports both personal health and the broader sustainability movement.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Science-Backed Formulations&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Every Pilly Labs product is formulated with a deep respect for clinical research and human biology. By combining hydrolyzed collagen peptides with key cofactors like Vitamin C, Biotin, Zinc, and Vitamin E, Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies deliver real, measurable benefits rooted in scientific evidence.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;The goal is not just temporary improvements but true inside-out transformations that support beauty, mobility, and vitality over the long term.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Customer-Centered Philosophy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Pilly Labs is dedicated to providing a seamless, supportive experience for every customer. From the easy-to-use website and fast shipping options to the 100% satisfaction guarantee, every detail is designed to make it simple for individuals to start — and succeed — in their wellness journeys.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Whether you're beginning a 90-day glow-up challenge or committing to a full year of collagen support, Pilly Labs is with you every step of the way.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ethical Standards and Transparency&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Pilly Labs is committed to transparency in sourcing, manufacturing, and marketing practices. Products are made in facilities that adhere to strict quality control standards, and customers are always provided with complete ingredient lists and usage guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This ethical approach fosters lasting trust and aligns with the growing demand for brands that prioritize integrity and accountability in every aspect of their business.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why This Matters&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;In a crowded market filled with overhyped products and questionable claims, Pilly Labs distinguishes itself by staying true to its mission: delivering clean, effective, and scientifically sound wellness solutions.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Choosing Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies means selecting a partner in your beauty and wellness journey. This brand shares your commitment to living better, aging gracefully, and supporting vibrant health from within.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Final Verdict: Why Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies Are a Must-Have for 2025&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;In a wellness landscape crowded with quick fixes and superficial solutions, Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies offer something rare and valuable: a clean, science-backed, and sustainable way to restore, nourish, and elevate your beauty and health from within.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;By delivering a synergistic blend of hydrolyzed collagen peptides, Vitamin C, Biotin, Zinc, and Vitamin E, Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies addresses the core structural needs of your skin, joints, and hair. They work with your body's natural processes — not against them — supporting inside-out transformations that grow stronger over time.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Whether your goal is to glow up naturally, restore youthful skin elasticity, strengthen thinning hair, or maintain joint flexibility and comfort well into later years, Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies provide a simple, delicious, and highly effective daily habit that fits seamlessly into any lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;With a commitment to clean beauty principles, ethical sourcing, clinical integrity, and customer satisfaction, Pilly Labs has earned its place as one of the best collagen supplement brands for 2025 — and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Suppose you're serious about building healthier habits, investing in your long-term vitality, and embracing a holistic approach to beauty and aging. In that case, Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies offers an ideal solution that aligns with your goals, values, and lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Choosing Pilly Labs is more than just picking a collagen supplement — it's choosing to prioritize yourself, your health, and your future.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Take the First Step Toward a Stronger, Healthier You&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Your journey to radiant skin, resilient joints, and stronger, healthier hair starts with one simple, powerful habit — daily collagen support. Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies make it easier than ever to invest in yourself naturally, safely, and effectively.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;With clinically backed hydrolyzed collagen peptides, essential nutrients, and a clean beauty commitment you can trust, Pilly Labs offers the best collagen supplement for skin care health, joint flexibility, and hair vitality available today.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Don't wait to experience the transformative power of inside-out wellness.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Choose your bundle, commit to your 90-day, 6-month, or 12-month glow-up plan, and start seeing the real benefits of consistent, high-quality collagen supplementation.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Shop Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies now and begin your glow-up journey today.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=pVAebl0UnyR8Utynw1Yn3HgIhRoHQ1ajs6Rz0PP7z01QIvSivC-olljyx7Y8TgQxciUcju4WrAZB8MeDRYWdmM3mvfCFoptZOlEiKPdMLgu5zFPnXsegMMPGXmJCXwNi_4siUXxnr3copUVs8KYiAriL7z5H5VkM3-6w50ShRVQ=" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visit Pilly Labs' Official Website to Order&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What are Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies is a premium daily collagen supplement designed to support healthier skin, stronger joints, and revitalized hair. Formulated with hydrolyzed collagen peptides, Vitamin C, Biotin, Zinc, and Vitamin E, these gummies make it easy to maintain consistent collagen intake for long-term inside-out wellness.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How do Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies compare to other collagen supplements?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies are considered one of the best collagen supplements on the market because they combine marine-based hydrolyzed collagen peptides with essential nutrients that enhance absorption and effectiveness. They also align with clean beauty standards by being non-GMO, gluten-free, and free of artificial additives.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Are Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies good for skincare health?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Yes, Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies are specifically formulated to improve skin care health by boosting collagen production from within. Regular use helps restore skin elasticity, minimize fine lines, and promote a youthful glow naturally over time.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Can Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies help with joint health and arthritis support?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Absolutely. Collagen is essential for maintaining healthy cartilage and connective tissues. Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies provide bioavailable collagen peptides that support joint lubrication, flexibility, and comfort, making them a strong choice for individuals looking for natural arthritis support and long-term joint health solutions.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How long does it take to see results from Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;While some users report initial improvements within 4 to 6 weeks, most experience more significant transformations in skin hydration, hair strength, and joint flexibility after 90 days of consistent daily use. For optimal results, a 6-month or 12-month collagen commitment is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Are Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies the best collagen supplement for women?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies are widely regarded as one of the best collagen supplements for women seeking to improve skin health, hair vitality, and joint strength naturally. With ingredients like Vitamin C, Biotin, and marine collagen peptides, they address the core beauty and wellness needs that many women prioritize.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What makes Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies a good choice for hair growth?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;The combination of hydrolyzed collagen peptides, Biotin, and Zinc in Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies supports stronger hair follicles, reduces breakage, and promotes healthier, thicker hair growth over time. This inside-out approach provides long-term support for natural hair revitalization.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Do Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies support natural aging and longevity?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Yes. By replenishing collagen levels that naturally decline with age, Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies help support skin elasticity, joint mobility, bone strength, and hair resilience — all crucial components of healthy aging and longevity.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Are there bundle options for Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies to save money?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Yes. Pilly Labs offers bundle pricing for two- and three-bottle packs, allowing customers to save up to 33% while committing to a longer-term collagen supplementation plan. Orders over $99 also qualify for free shipping within the United States.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Is there a satisfaction guarantee with Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Pilly Labs offers a 100% satisfaction guarantee. If you are not fully satisfied with your purchase, you can request a refund within 30 days. This risk-free policy ensures that you can try Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies confidently and experience the benefits firsthand.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=B4zuWA4S4YuYmHcry8nLQOsVdwbAxZ1vGuaBypHG0NYcrBsPMN428EHCjKGMhT4RP9xwVkfslWPZ4NwmMjgdzwJnW-GEJ23rpbWz8kB9xPY4cO2TfBgGWfjBP3flbR7ItM76IhuR7NY2qjLhDgFxXhCsRWjPR2pTuJOuFmUoC44guZU9N_QkLAoNVdxDF_ZGrQ6RFoJXTi-TeLPLLZeM9NAEI7kqo6Q87eXFlm4dpSupZ5zVmUZ2GiDWsagYaDbTnn9Kbk_LeoH-9PQ-AVPjCjsiLMZivfgUwngcSdpFbRTM8zDGOjxdY5rouk5JD7vTjKvcIt69eL1sXfhARK11-nBnzfkWpOkWZMMq1vXrw4Y=" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" title=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join the growing community of people enjoying healthier skin, hair, and joints. See why Pilly Labs Collagen Gummies are a top-rated supplement—buy now for a better you, inside and out.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Disclaimer and Disclosure&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This content is for informational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Individuals should always consult with a qualified healthcare professional before starting any dietary supplement regimen, especially if they have underlying health conditions, are pregnant, nursing, or currently taking medication. The information provided in this article is based on available research, product details from the manufacturer, and user testimonials at the time of writing.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;While every effort has been made to ensure the accuracy and reliability of the information presented, no guarantee is made regarding the completeness, correctness, or suitability of the content. In the event of typographical errors, inaccuracies, or incomplete information, neither the publisher, authors, contributors, nor syndication partners assume any responsibility or liability for any loss or damages resulting from the use of this content.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This article may contain affiliate links. If a reader clicks on these links and makes a purchase, the publisher or content distributor may receive a commission at no additional cost to the reader. These commissions help support the ongoing creation of free informational content and do not influence the objectivity or editorial integrity of the article.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;The publisher, authors, contributors, and any third-party syndication partners disclaim all warranties, expressed or implied, and assume no liability for any individual's interpretation or use of the information presented. All readers are responsible for their own decisions regarding their health, wellness, and purchasing activities.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;By reading this article, the reader acknowledges and agrees to these terms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;pre&gt;&lt;/pre&gt; &lt;img alt="" src="https://ml.globenewswire.com/media/ZWJhODFjNDYtN2VlNC00NjE0LWEyNmQtZjI2MmM3ZTMzNDhkLTEzMDU5NTgtMjAyNS0wNC0yNi1lbg==/tiny/Pilly-Labs.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade"&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;







        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>GlobeNewswire</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 16:43:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgJBVV95cUxPMURUS2hDNk1fa2psRmFQa1FXVURTQ21KZEo4dVl6QWJqTUNoN0lzVUg5MG9zb0JraDdHZ3h2eVNNRUdyeEhNcE1CUXY1Vm1IVGdqbnVFaTFFemYzM0w3QWk2MGlEZjJyZWpCZV9OUFJNUjV0ZkNLeDRaRHlVeW11bi1xWjlIRVg5RGZtQUN4TWFxM1NHY1E3Z1RDcVoxbkR1WGs1Yi16ZFhhRlRNY0dlTUIzVFJoWVNNbGVvbHNrTmtTM0g5YkRWMXM2eWh5Zng4RzFUTWpJNzhiQjhReS1SOTRiVHJMX203bkplVWdvbTdqbDZBUmc0WGVMdkgwWVA5Z0lTV0dadEc5VDhGSDNXMTc1Y2p6dTROQ2c</guid></item><item><title>9项缓解膝盖疼痛的温和锻炼-印度时报 | 9 gentle exercises for sore knees - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizAFBVV95cUxPbkpGQk5INUNORU4wTjJua1R5YnhzV1ZjOGhEVlFIQkFXT0pkQTV5YnBGYkRWS3VFTERnczFGOTd6Ylplb0txbjJpcEktdXRDLVJmZlhKQkVHM1NlVkRuZU9OV1JfMlVZTHJWa1pYcmhORTBXbzJrYnVjWW5NUVFyaWU4VnQ4VHJ5N1p1bE9xbHN4azczS2NzX2N5UGpPT3g2V2ozZ2xYaEg2My16eGlIQlNPYU9IRGpwaWpyNFBUNDgzSlkwMjI1M2tBOULSAcwBQVVfeXFMT25KRkJOSDVDTkVOME4ybmtUeWJ4c1dWYzhoRFZRSEJBV09KZEE1eWJwRmJEVkt1RUxEZ3MxRjk3emJaZW9LcW4yaXBJLXV0Qy1SZmZYSkJFRzNTZVZEbmVPTldSXzJVWUxyVmtaWHJoTkUwV28ya2J1Y1luTVFRcmllOFZ0OFRyeTdadWxPcWxzeGs3M0tjc19jeVBqT094NldqM2dsWGhINjMtenhpSEJTT2FPSERqcGlqcjRQVDQ4M0pZMDIyNTNrQTlC?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;amp-story-grid-layer class="recircular" id="rcontent" template="vertical"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt;&lt;p class="mid-heading"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;You may also like&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc3 pa"&gt;​Superfoods that rival walnuts in brain ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc5 pa"&gt;10 herbs that can help normalise fatty l...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizAFBVV95cUxPbkpGQk5INUNORU4wTjJua1R5YnhzV1ZjOGhEVlFIQkFXT0pkQTV5YnBGYkRWS3VFTERnczFGOTd6Ylplb0txbjJpcEktdXRDLVJmZlhKQkVHM1NlVkRuZU9OV1JfMlVZTHJWa1pYcmhORTBXbzJrYnVjWW5NUVFyaWU4VnQ4VHJ5N1p1bE9xbHN4azczS2NzX2N5UGpPT3g2V2ozZ2xYaEg2My16eGlIQlNPYU9IRGpwaWpyNFBUNDgzSlkwMjI1M2tBOULSAcwBQVVfeXFMT25KRkJOSDVDTkVOME4ybmtUeWJ4c1dWYzhoRFZRSEJBV09KZEE1eWJwRmJEVkt1RUxEZ3MxRjk3emJaZW9LcW4yaXBJLXV0Qy1SZmZYSkJFRzNTZVZEbmVPTldSXzJVWUxyVmtaWHJoTkUwV28ya2J1Y1luTVFRcmllOFZ0OFRyeTdadWxPcWxzeGs3M0tjc19jeVBqT094NldqM2dsWGhINjMtenhpSEJTT2FPSERqcGlqcjRQVDQ4M0pZMDIyNTNrQTlC</guid></item><item><title>为什么美国的口罩禁令可能为公共卫生树立危险的先例-福布斯 | Why Mask Bans In America Could Set A Dangerous Precedent For Public Health - Forbes</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPYTloaGpoZG11WmtsSWNVcER2dlBEa0ZELThhNFZUZDlMejV4WWtaVlZqTm8zM1AyU3FWbmxNdVdwZ0JxUHpQLWJoZXBmWG5lRWprUXJRUC1SelFUOVJxVUxtdVdRU3VBcm90M1RkTHFYdmZyZmJwVE5oZGNPcmM1SnprY25HeWhubnk5TjNaZEVuclNwM0Y0enc4TWs0Y2VhenpsRVlTZUs2TkI5NWRRZjlwajZoS2FfMU54dG5ocXgtdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="fs-article fs-responsive-text current-article article-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-0" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;fbs-accordion classname="expandable" current="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="color-body light-text" role="button"&gt;A picture taken on May 19, 2020 in Toulouse southern France shows a protective surgical face mask as &lt;span class="plus" data-ga-track="caption expand"&gt;... More&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="expanded-caption"&gt; France eases lockdown measures taken to curb the spread of the COVID-19 pandemic caused by the novel coronavirus. (Photo by Lionel BONAVENTURE / AFP) (Photo by LIONEL BONAVENTURE/AFP via Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/fbs-accordion&gt;&lt;small&gt;AFP via Getty Images&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the last several years, masks have been recognized as a crucial tool in safeguarding public health, particularly during the COVID-19 pandemic. Now, with the chaos of public rioting across universities and public spaces, many jurisdictions are considering wearing a mask as a criminal offense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="halfway_hardwall_1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="article_paragraph_2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an example, democratic governor &lt;a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2025/04/05/new-yorks-push-to-restrict-masks-is-dividing-democrats-00274350" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.politico.com/news/2025/04/05/new-yorks-push-to-restrict-masks-is-dividing-democrats-00274350" aria-label="Kathy Hochul"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.politico.com/news/2025/04/05/new-yorks-push-to-restrict-masks-is-dividing-democrats-00274350"&gt;Kathy Hochul&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is pushing legislation to effectively make masking a criminal violation for those that threaten violence. The legislation would make exceptions for those with health safety concerns, work requirements and inclement weather, to name a few. &lt;a href="https://cbsaustin.com/news/local/story/texas-senators-consider-bills-effectively-banning-masks-in-protests" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://cbsaustin.com/news/local/story/texas-senators-consider-bills-effectively-banning-masks-in-protests" aria-label="Texas senators"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://cbsaustin.com/news/local/story/texas-senators-consider-bills-effectively-banning-masks-in-protests"&gt;Texas senators&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are also introducing bills that would ban masks and criminalize those who use them to harass, intimidate and threaten others. Many other jurisdictions have already banned masks for similar reasons including North Carolina and Nassau County in New York.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="halfway_hardwall_2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While security considerations are important, banning masks could have detrimental consequences for public health. Masks are a proven means to reduce the transmission of respiratory illnesses as well as their acquisition. They do so by trapping airborne particles like viral particles that get expelled when people talk, cough or sneeze. This is precisely why masking was recommended and in some cases mandated during the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="halfway_hardwall_3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="vestpocket nsO6K"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, masks also help people from inhaling toxic chemicals and substances from air pollution, which is an important concern during wildfires and areas with high soot pollution. Particle pollution from wildfires emit &lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/omerawan/2025/01/11/how-wildfires-can-affect-human-health/" data-ga-track="InternalLink:https://www.forbes.com/sites/omerawan/2025/01/11/how-wildfires-can-affect-human-health/" target="_self" aria-label="small particles"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="InternalLink:https://www.forbes.com/sites/omerawan/2025/01/11/how-wildfires-can-affect-human-health/"&gt;small particles&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and irritants that can get deposited in the lungs and predispose to chronic medical conditions such as asthma and chronic obstructive lung disease. Masks can provide a much needed barrier and deterrent for many of these small particles that are harmful to health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="halfway_hardwall_4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The medical research overwhelmingly supports the use of masks to mitigate the spread of infections diseases. A plethora of &lt;a href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.2014564118" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.2014564118" aria-label="research"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.2014564118"&gt;research&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; shows that facemasks reduce transmission of infected respiratory particles in both laboratory and clinical contexts. The &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/masks.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/masks.html" aria-label="CDC"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/masks.html"&gt;CDC&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; also states, “When worn by a person with infection, masks reduce the spread of the virus to others. Masks also protect wearers from breathing in infectious particles from people around them.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="fbs-ad--nativeinbody-d-wrapper fbs-ad--progressive"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although legislation of mask bans makes exceptions for those with health conditions, these exceptions are difficult to enforce and implement practically. &lt;a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2025/04/05/new-yorks-push-to-restrict-masks-is-dividing-democrats-00274350" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.politico.com/news/2025/04/05/new-yorks-push-to-restrict-masks-is-dividing-democrats-00274350" aria-label="Law enforcement"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.politico.com/news/2025/04/05/new-yorks-push-to-restrict-masks-is-dividing-democrats-00274350"&gt;Law enforcement&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; officials are only allowed by law to ask about religion or health if an action pertains specifically to the crime in question. This can be difficult to enforce, and creates an uncomfortable environment for the many immunocompromised patients that require masks to protect their health. Asking these individuals about masking and to potentially take it off is an invasion of their health and privacy that should be protected by HIPAA laws. Remember, those who are immunocompromised are much more common than you may think and include cancer patients who are on chemotherapy, those who take steroids, organ transplant recipients as well as those with chronic medical conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, if mask bans are successfully implemented, those that need to mask may be forced into social isolation. Many may fear being incarcerated and could be reluctant to leave their homes. Businesses could deny service to those wearing masks, which would include immunocompromised people and patients with disabilities. Mask bans create unnecessary bias and discrimination against our most vulnerable populations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="article_paragraph_7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although politicians that seek to ban masks may have good intentions in attempting to reduce crime, public health policy must prioritize the well-being of the entire population while considering broader societal concerns. Banning masks ignores the essential role they play in mitigating the spread of deadly infectious diseases. At a time where science and health have been largely politicized, America needs leaders that will fight for the well-being of all its citizens.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Julie Lam, founder of Mask Together America and mask advocate, says, “Now I am forced to be on medication that’s making me immune compromised, more susceptible to hospitalization from infection, my immunologist warned me. I am out there protesting, wearing a mask, not to make a spectacle but to send a message that we need to rise up and say no to our government defunding public health.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="newsletter_signup_article"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Forbes</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 16:06:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPYTloaGpoZG11WmtsSWNVcER2dlBEa0ZELThhNFZUZDlMejV4WWtaVlZqTm8zM1AyU3FWbmxNdVdwZ0JxUHpQLWJoZXBmWG5lRWprUXJRUC1SelFUOVJxVUxtdVdRU3VBcm90M1RkTHFYdmZyZmJwVE5oZGNPcmM1SnprY25HeWhubnk5TjNaZEVuclNwM0Y0enc4TWs0Y2VhenpsRVlTZUs2TkI5NWRRZjlwajZoS2FfMU54dG5ocXgtdw</guid></item><item><title>大脑对潜在危害的反应比对潜在缓解的反应更强烈- Earth.com | The brain reacts more strongly to potential harm than to potential relief - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxQTTcwZXRaZGFwdWVNYjI3TGxEMENYejVzSGpUc1RoelB4SU1nS3pxejNvTnRFd1RNLWpHNy1nQVJUY2V6NFJkM1pHbEotOFVKRnFjcS1vRzl3dHBScXE4aktJSkI4dUROd1loZEtTUVhXN2RQREFWdmtwYUFoemNNSW1aa1pRdEQ4cTZyRGx4Ym1zd1R3UnlHNVpXdXhpVlEzZXQw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of us can recall times when a twinge of discomfort made us uneasy far more than a soothing moment put us at ease. Our brain reacts and certainly seems to put extra weight on signals that say something bad might be coming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research, conducted by &lt;a href="https://www.iasp-pain.org/person/ulrike-bingel-md-phd/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Dr. Ulrike Bingel&lt;/a&gt; at the University Hospital Essen, tackled a puzzle that has long kept experts on their toes. They wanted to know why negative suggestions bring on stronger responses than positive ones when it comes to &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/tapping-into-the-pain-relief-potential-of-cannabis-without-the-high/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;pain&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-power-of-suggestion-placebo-and-nocebo"&gt;Power of suggestion: Placebo and nocebo&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Placebo describes a helpful effect triggered by positive expectations of relief. Nocebo is its darker twin, sparking an increase in symptoms just from negative thoughts about a treatment or situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An earlier &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/21862825/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;investigation&lt;/a&gt; showed nocebo responses happen even when a person only hears warnings about possible side effects. Scientists point out that this is linked to &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/lsd-can-treat-crippling-anxiety-with-a-single-dose/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;anxiety&lt;/a&gt; and attention, which can spike with a single negative comment from a trusted source.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-relief-fades-faster-than-fear"&gt;Why relief fades faster than fear&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Positive experiences, like a drop in pain, often feel less memorable than unpleasant ones. Studies suggest that our minds don’t replay comfort with the same intensity or frequency as they do discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/spiders-heights-or-public-speaking-each-fear-has-a-unique-place-in-the-brain/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Fear&lt;/a&gt; and discomfort seem to leave a deeper mark. That’s likely because the brain treats them as warnings to remember and avoid in the future – making comfort easier to forget and fear harder to shake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-negative-cues-stick-more"&gt;Why negative cues stick more&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some experts explain that our minds are wired to keep us safe. That may explain why nocebo cues are remembered so strongly, even when we have only experienced them once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Significant placebo and nocebo effects were detected on day 1 and day 8, but nocebo effects were stronger on both test days,” reported Bingel. This tendency ties into an evolutionary idea often called the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1053810014001962" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;‘better safe than sorry’&lt;/a&gt; strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-brain-s-bias-toward-bad-news"&gt;The brain’s bias toward bad news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research in neuroscience shows that the brain tends to light up more, reacting more to threats than to rewards. This reaction happens quickly, sometimes even before we fully realize what we’re reacting to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This could explain why even a subtle negative expectation – like the possibility that something might hurt – grabs our attention and sticks with us. It’s not just emotional; it’s wired into how our nervous system responds to the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-role-does-personal-experience-play"&gt;What role does personal experience play&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When individuals feel pain is eased, that personal experience can shape what they expect next time. But if a past situation suggested pain might get worse, that memory can loom large.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scholars note that repeated experiences of pain reduction can slowly build trust in a treatment. Yet if negative signals stand out more, they may overshadow positive ones, which makes neutral or even reassuring messages seem less convincing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-practitioner-connection-and-beliefs"&gt;Practitioner connection and beliefs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a care provider seems highly competent, that might unintentionally boost nocebo responses when they mention potential downsides. Patients may trust them so much that any warning sounds like a sure threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain traits, like &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/2090830/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;somatosensory amplification&lt;/a&gt; (tendency to notice and worry about physical sensations), also appear to tamp down the strength of a placebo effect. During short lab tests, participants with that tendency seemed less likely to feel relief from positive suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-possible-ways-to-address-nocebo-effects"&gt;Possible ways to address nocebo effects&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Communication strategies that reduce needless worries may ease nocebo effects. Simple changes to phrasing can shift focus away from worst-case scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Addressing everyday &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/stress-eats-away-our-brains-cognitive-defenses/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;stress&lt;/a&gt; might help, too. Since anxious thoughts feed negative expectations, steps to calm the mind can prevent nocebo responses before they snowball.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nocebo effects don’t just cause discomfort in the moment – they may also change the way people act in the future. If someone links a harmless activity or medication with pain or side effects, they might start avoiding it altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over time, this avoidance can build into broader patterns like skipping doctor visits, refusing useful treatments, or becoming wary of all health interventions. These patterns might quietly reduce quality of life and increase the risk of unmanaged conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-the-brain-reacts-looking-ahead"&gt;How the brain reacts: Looking ahead&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many clinical teams plan to keep looking at how negative expectations gain momentum. By pinpointing personal and &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/study-reveals-the-neural-basis-of-social-support-in-primates/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;social cues&lt;/a&gt; that drive nocebo effects, they hope to improve care and reduce treatment dropouts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A deeper awareness of these findings could shape how doctors talk about treatments. Small adjustments to conversation style or tone might go a long way in protecting patients from nocebo-driven problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://elifesciences.org/reviewed-preprints/105753" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;eLife&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 16:06:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQTTcwZXRaZGFwdWVNYjI3TGxEMENYejVzSGpUc1RoelB4SU1nS3pxejNvTnRFd1RNLWpHNy1nQVJUY2V6NFJkM1pHbEotOFVKRnFjcS1vRzl3dHBScXE4aktJSkI4dUROd1loZEtTUVhXN2RQREFWdmtwYUFoemNNSW1aa1pRdEQ4cTZyRGx4Ym1zd1R3UnlHNVpXdXhpVlEzZXQw</guid></item><item><title>这1件简单的事情可以将您的痴呆风险降低20 ％ - AOL.com | This 1 Simple Thing Can Cut Your Risk of Dementia by 20% - AOL.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiakFVX3lxTFBXUEV4eEo1WklIdlBwMnROcC14cnZjTTJIRXB6Q1pZQ2J3MHNZS1pQRlBMVmZ1MFd6MmszYldWbUViS004UlRxM01wdndSN2hlclZqQ2ZfUDE4WTlOSUxEYkc4THZvajdPX3c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;This Vaccine Could Cut Your Dementia Risk&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;Stígur Már Karlsson /Heimsmyndir - Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Hearst Magazines and Yahoo may earn commission or revenue on some items through these links."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.nih.gov/news-events/nih-research-matters/risk-future-burden-dementia-united-states" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:National Institutes of Health (NIH);elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;National Institutes of Health (NIH)&lt;/a&gt; estimates 42% of Americans over the age of 55 will develop dementia, a term for brain diseases associated with memory loss, behavioral changes and decreased cognitive function. But new research into a common vaccine could offer some hope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a new study in &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fs41586-025-08800-x%23Sec11&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.prevention.com%2Fhealth%2Fhealth-conditions%2Fa64576923%2Fshingles-vaccine-dementia-risk%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Nature;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the vaccine for &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a39785194/covid-shingles-risk/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:shingles;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;shingles&lt;/a&gt; could significantly reduce the risk of &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/fitness/a64182704/exercise-lowers-dementia-risk-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dementia;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt;. These findings, the researchers say, support an emerging scientific theory that viruses which affect the nervous system, like shingles, can increase the chances of having dementia — therefore, being inoculated against the virus could have the opposite effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“For the first time, we now have evidence that likely shows a cause-and-effect relationship between shingles vaccination and dementia prevention,”&lt;/strong&gt; says &lt;a href="https://profiles.stanford.edu/pascal-geldsetzer" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Pascal Geldsetzer M.D., Ph.D., M.P.H;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Pascal Geldsetzer M.D., Ph.D., M.P.H&lt;/a&gt;., assistant professor of medicine at Stanford University and the study’s senior author. “We find these protective effects to be large in size, substantially larger than those of existing pharmacological tools for dementia.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're looking for a way to maintain a healthy brain, keep reading to learn more about both the shingles vaccine and the surprising findings of the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is shingles?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shingles (herpes zoster) occurs when the varicella-zoster virus (VZV) — the one that causes chickenpox — reactivates in the body.&lt;/strong&gt; If you had chickenpox, the virus remains dormant in your nerve cells and can rear its head during adulthood. &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/genetics/condition/shingles/#frequency" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:According to the NIH;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;According to the NIH&lt;/a&gt;, shingles affects between 20 to 30% of people during their lives, and is most prevalent in people ages 50 and older. This can be chalked up to our immune systems weakening with age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who have shingles most commonly experience a painful, itchy or tingly rash on one side of the face or body. The rash comes in the form of blisters that will scab over within 7 to 10 days. With shingles, you may also have fever, headaches, chills or an upset stomach, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/shingles/signs-symptoms/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; (CDC). Treatments include antiviral medications, OTC or prescription pain relievers, and self-care home remedies such as applying wet compresses, calamine lotion and taking warm oatmeal baths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you've had chickenpox, the only way to safeguard yourself from shingles is to receive the Shingrix vaccine, which the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/shingles/vaccines/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:CDC;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt; recommends for adults 50 and over, and anyone 19 and over who are immunocompromised as a result of disease or therapy. Shingrix comes in two doses, with the second one given two to six months after the first shot. The CDC reports the vaccine is more than 90% effective at preventing shingles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now you know why getting the vaccine is key for shingles prevention, and thanks to this study, we know have some viable evidence it can also help ward off cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What the study found&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Geldsetzer and his colleagues rooted their study in the interest of wanting a more up-close look between the shingles vaccine and its relation to the onset of dementia. It’s not that prior studies on the topic didn’t exist, but those studies compared people who chose to get the vaccine compared to those who didn't, and these groups usually differ in lifestyle factors such as diet and exercise, which are difficult to measure. This can bias the analyses and in general, the evidence isn't solid enough to make recommendations on, he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What sets the Stanford study apart is the researchers’ different approach, choosing to focus on, and compare the likelihood of dementia in people who received the shingles vaccine because they were born on, or just a few days later than September 2, 1933, which made them eligible versus those who were born just a few days earlier, and so therefore, weren't eligible for the shingles vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers based their findings on data from a Welsh shingles vaccine rollout that started on September 1, 2013. Because Wales needed to ration the vaccine’s limited supply, they used that cutoff date to decide who could get the vaccine and who couldn't. After analyzing the health records of the more than 280,000 Welsh adults who didn’t have dementia at the start of the vaccination program, a striking difference emerged between the two groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“To our amazement, we found that &lt;strong&gt;receiving the shingles vaccine reduced the chance of being diagnosed with dementia in the subsequent seven years by roughly 20%,”&lt;/strong&gt; says Dr. Geldsetzer. “If this is truly a causal effect, then getting the shingles vaccine would be much more effective in delaying or preventing dementia than any existing pharmacological tools.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another interesting discovery? The vaccine's protective effect was greater in women than in men. “This could potentially be due to sex differences in the immune response or in the way in which dementia develops,” Dr. Geldsetzer says. “Women on average have higher antibody responses to vaccination, for example. We also know that both shingles and dementia are more common in women than in men.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Welsh findings, the Stanford team has looked at health records from shingles vaccine rollouts from other countries, including England, Australia, New Zealand and Canada. In dataset after dataset, the researchers continued to notice the vaccine was a strong protective signal for dementia, showing the link wasn’t a fluke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why this study matters &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“This research is newsworthy because the shingles vaccine can now be looked at as a possible intervention in helping us to prevent or push dementia to later time,”&lt;/strong&gt; says &lt;a href="https://doctors.hackensackmeridianhealth.org/provider/manisha-santosh-parulekar/1319173" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Manisha Parulekar, M.D;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Manisha Parulekar, M.D&lt;/a&gt;., a geriatrician and director of the division of geriatrics and co-director of the Center for Memory Loss and Brain Health at Hackensack University Medical Center in Hackensack, NJ. “We don’t have a lot of current [intervention] options out there, and the 20% reduction in dementia risk is the best we’ve seen so far.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Parulekar says she understands the importance of the study in relation to how the shingles virus can have a negative effect on the brain. “The reactivation of the chickenpox virus can trigger significant inflammation in the nervous system, potentially damaging neurons in the brain and contributing to cognitive decline,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers still don't know &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt; the shingles vaccine protects against dementia. It could help by stimulating your immune system, specifically reducing reactivation of the chickenpox virus, or by some other mechanism, notes Dr. Geldsetzer, who is currently trying to raise funds from private and philanthropic foundations to conduct further research. “We want to be able to do a clinical trial to definitively test if a shingles vaccination prevents or delays dementia, so if there’s anyone out there who might be interested in funding such a trial, I’d love to hear from them,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The bottom line&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you’re 50 or older, and you haven’t yet gotten your shingles vaccine, get it, and be sure to follow through with both doses for the maximum benefits, recommends Dr. Parulekar.&lt;/strong&gt; “Not only can the vaccine protect you from the painful symptoms of shingles, but now there’s one more reason, and that’s to possibly lower the risk of dementia,” she adds. “Why take a chance when we have a very effective tool available? Age is a risk factor for both, so you always want to be in preventative mode.” In other words, your shingles vaccine is a win-win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 15:47:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTFBXUEV4eEo1WklIdlBwMnROcC14cnZjTTJIRXB6Q1pZQ2J3MHNZS1pQRlBMVmZ1MFd6MmszYldWbUViS004UlRxM01wdndSN2hlclZqQ2ZfUDE4WTlOSUxEYkc4THZvajdPX3c</guid></item><item><title>遗传医学可以让人们留下罕见的突变。但也有新的希望-美联社新闻 | Genetic medicine can leave people with rare mutations behind. But there’s new hope - AP News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipwFBVV95cUxPcXRuYW95cG05SXdkd0ZpcWsyNnVFR04xSVZTTzZvWUhpMldfRnJMMGptdHNaa05ib0tRYzI3SUZrTGFkLUE3NXEwSERJS3BPcEFzYXpJWUlHTEl0QWFjZ3BLS1RCa1pEZUxUVVFURDhsbUFGUVNjS0o3WVV5MGdwWDNURXNtdW5rZ2VmVHBtdHVGa1ZHZ1p0TjZrNUJWVjlHTk01c3d4dw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 14:59:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxPcXRuYW95cG05SXdkd0ZpcWsyNnVFR04xSVZTTzZvWUhpMldfRnJMMGptdHNaa05ib0tRYzI3SUZrTGFkLUE3NXEwSERJS3BPcEFzYXpJWUlHTEl0QWFjZ3BLS1RCa1pEZUxUVVFURDhsbUFGUVNjS0o3WVV5MGdwWDNURXNtdW5rZ2VmVHBtdHVGa1ZHZ1p0TjZrNUJWVjlHTk01c3d4dw</guid></item><item><title>美国有近900例麻疹病例， 10个州正在爆发麻疹疫情。以下是须知事项。-《芝加哥论坛报》 | The US has nearly 900 measles cases, and 10 states have active outbreaks. Here’s what to know. - Chicago Tribune</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizgFBVV95cUxNaTFKSTRHZWVSVHFxaWhEOW02enZVdWFLMGRXbFUzb0hIMDl0Sy1BQ3lDdDBMclpIMEY5cWJLeFJRenROVDdUS1VHeGFaVl9YRzNXZlVvOXZEUWIyQzFramJZOVJMejhUbzFLUmFaU190Q2hwWTNBc3VvMV9tNGthMjQzNWQ4d2RnQUstUXVEYmczbTRBT3ZCVUxvWF9HdjNNSUJDTnp0NWc1eUtpT0NZajB1U3hIelY5X3BfczRUeEJNRUo4dEZFcW9iREpOQQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-copy"&gt;&lt;p class="wp-remixd-voice-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With one-fifth of states seeing active measles outbreaks, the U.S. is nearing 900 cases, according to figures posted Friday by the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The CDC’s confirmed measles cases count is 884, triple the amount seen in all of 2024. The vast majority — 646 — are in Texas, where an outbreak in the western part of the state that’s approaching the three-month mark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two unvaccinated elementary school-aged children died from measles-related illnesses in the epicenter in West Texas, and an adult in New Mexico who was not vaccinated died of a measles-related illness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other states with active outbreaks — defined as three or more cases — include Indiana, Kansas, Michigan, Montana, New Mexico, Oklahoma, Ohio, Pennsylvania and Tennessee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="s2nPlayer k-wQoDAMss" data-type="float" data-s2n-api="dfm_stn_player_script_id_wQoDAMss"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;North America has two other ongoing outbreaks. One in Ontario, Canada, has resulted in 1,020 cases from mid-October through Wednesday. And as of Friday, the Mexican state of Chihuahua state had 605 measles cases, according to data from the state health ministry. The World Health Organization has said cases in Mexico are linked to the Texas outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Measles is caused by a highly contagious virus that’s airborne and spreads easily when an infected person breathes, sneezes or coughs. It is preventable through vaccines, and has been considered eliminated from the U.S. since 2000.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the virus takes hold in other U.S. communities with low vaccination rates, health experts fear the virus that the spread could stretch on for a year. Here’s what else you need to know about measles in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;How many measles cases are there in Illinois?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;State health officials &lt;a href="https://www.chicagotribune.com/2025/04/23/public-health-officials-reports-first-measles-case-of-the-year-in-illinois/"&gt;confirmed&lt;/a&gt; the first measles case of the year Wednesday in an unvaccinated adult in downstate Marion.&lt;/p&gt;				
&lt;p&gt;The health department &lt;a href="https://www.chicagotribune.com/2025/04/24/marion-first-measles-case/?lctg=F48DE5774439B4CC34FC74D9F7&amp;amp;utm_email=F48DE5774439B4CC34FC74D9F7&amp;amp;active=yesP&amp;amp;utm_source=listrak&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_term=https%3a%2f%2fwww.chicagotribune.com%2f2025%2f04%2f24%2fmarion-first-measles-case%2f&amp;amp;utm_campaign=trib-chicago_tribune-daywatch-nl&amp;amp;utm_content=curated"&gt;provided&lt;/a&gt; the additional details about the location of the unidentified individual and the person’s vaccination status in a health advisory sent to local health departments and health care providers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The advisory also listed eight locations where people might have been exposed to the individual with measles from April 7 to April 15: three laundromats, a Walmart, a Kroger, a gym and a restaurant, all in Marion, and the clinic where the person sought care, which was not identified in the advisory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;State public health officials recently unveiled an &lt;a href="https://www.chicagotribune.com/2025/04/09/illinois-measles-vaccination-rates/"&gt;online dashboard tool&lt;/a&gt; that allows users to look up measles vaccination rates and data about the risk of outbreaks at individual schools across the state.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="PnMBecwMtO"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.chicagotribune.com/2025/04/09/illinois-measles-vaccination-rates/"&gt;Illinois unveils online tool showing measles vaccination rates by school&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year, &lt;a href="https://www.chicagotribune.com/2024/03/07/city-detects-first-case-of-measles-in-chicago-in-5-years/"&gt;Chicago saw its first measles case since 2019&lt;/a&gt;, which resulted in 67 cases, according to health officials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;How many measles cases are there in Texas and New Mexico?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Texas state health officials said Friday there were 22 new cases of measles since Tuesday, bringing the total to 646 across 26 counties — most of them in West Texas. Hospitalizations were steady Friday at 64 throughout the outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;State health officials estimated about 1% of cases — fewer than 10 — are actively infectious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sixty-one percent of Texas’ cases are in Gaines County, population 22,892, where the virus started spreading in a close-knit, undervaccinated Mennonite community. The county has had 393 cases since late January — just over 1.5% of the county’s residents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The April 3 death in Texas was an 8-year-old child, according to Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Health officials in Texas said the child did not have underlying health conditions and died of “what the child’s doctor described as measles pulmonary failure.” A unvaccinated child with no underlying conditions died of measles in Texas in late February — Kennedy said age 6.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New Mexico announced one new case Friday, bringing the state’s total to 66. Seven people have been hospitalized since the outbreak started. Most of the state’s cases are in Lea County. Three are in Eddy County and Chaves and Doña Ana counties have one each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;State health officials say the cases are linked to Texas’ outbreak based on genetic testing. New Mexico reported a measles-related death in an adult on March 6.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;How many cases are there in Indiana?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Indiana confirmed two more cases Monday in an outbreak that has sickened eight in Allen County in the northeast part of the state — five are unvaccinated minors and three are adults whose vaccination status is unknown. The cases have no known link to other outbreaks, the Allen County Department of Health said Monday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;How many cases are there in Kansas?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kansas was steady this week with 37 cases in eight counties in the southwest part of the state. Finney, Ford, Grant, Gray and Morton counties have fewer than five cases each. Haskell County has the most with eight cases, Stevens County has seven, Kiowa County has six.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The state’s first reported case, identified in Stevens County on March 13, is linked to the Texas outbreak based on genetic testing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;How many cases are there in Michigan?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Montcalm County, near Grand Rapids in western Michigan, has four linked measles cases. State health officials say the cases are tied to Canada’s large outbreak in Ontario. The state has nine confirmed measles cases as of Friday, but the remaining four are not part of the Montcalm County outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;How many cases are there in Montana?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Montana state health officials announced five cases Thursday in unvaccinated children and adults who had traveled out of state, and confirmed it was an outbreak on Monday. All five are isolating at home in Gallatin County in the southwest part of the state.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They are Montana’s first measles cases in 35 years. Health officials didn’t say whether the cases are linked to other outbreaks in North America.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;How many cases are there in Ohio?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Ohio Department of Health confirmed 32 measles cases in the state Thursday, and one hospitalization. The state count includes only Ohio residents. There are 16 cases in Ashtabula County near Cleveland, 14 in Knox County and one each in Allen and Holmes counties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Health officials in Knox County, in east-central Ohio, said there are a total of 20 people with measles, but seven of them do not live in the state.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;How many cases are there in Oklahoma?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oklahoma was steady Friday with 13 cases: 10 confirmed and three probable. The first two probable cases were “associated” with the West Texas and New Mexico outbreaks, the state health department said. The state health department is not releasing which counties have cases, but Cleveland, Custer and Oklahoma counties have had public exposures in the past couple of months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;How many cases are there in Pennsylvania?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are eight measles cases in Erie County in far northwest Pennsylvania, officials said Friday. The county declared an outbreak in mid-April. The state said Friday it has 13 cases overall in 2025, including international travel-related cases in Montgomery County and one in Philadelphia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;How many cases are there in Tennessee?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tennessee has six measles cases as of Thursday. Health department spokesman Bill Christian said all cases are the middle part of the state, and that “at least three of these cases are linked to each other” but declined to specify further. The state also did not say whether the cases were linked to other outbreaks or when Tennessee’s outbreak started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The state health department announced the state’s first measles case March 21, three more on April 1 and the last two on April 17, but none of the news releases declared an outbreak. Tennessee is on a list of outbreak states in a Thursday CDC report.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Where else is measles showing up in the U.S.?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There have been 884 cases in 2025 as of Friday, according to the CDC. Measles cases also have been reported in Alaska, Arkansas, California, Colorado, Florida, Georgia, Hawaii, Illinois, Kentucky, Louisiana, Maryland, Minnesota, New Jersey, New York, Rhode Island, Vermont, Virginia and Washington.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cases and outbreaks in the U.S. are frequently traced to someone who caught the disease abroad. In 2019, the U.S. saw 1,274 cases and almost lost its status of having eliminated measles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;What do you need to know about the MMR vaccine?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best way to avoid measles is to get the measles, mumps and rubella vaccine. The first shot is recommended for children between 12 and 15 months old and the second between 4 and 6 years old.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting another MMR shot is harmless if there are concerns about waning immunity, the CDC says. People who have documentation of receiving a live measles vaccine in the 1960s don’t need to be revaccinated, but people who were immunized before 1968 with an ineffective measles vaccine made from “killed” virus should be revaccinated with at least one dose, the agency said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who have documentation that they had measles are immune and those born before 1957 generally don’t need the shots because most children back then had measles and now have “presumptive immunity.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In communities with high vaccination rates — above 95% — diseases like measles have a harder time spreading through communities. This is called “herd immunity.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But childhood vaccination rates have declined nationwide since the pandemic and more parents are claiming religious or personal conscience waivers to exempt their kids from required shots. The U.S. saw a rise in measles cases in 2024, including an outbreak in Chicago that sickened more than 60.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;What are the symptoms of measles?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Measles first infects the respiratory tract, then spreads throughout the body, causing a high fever, runny nose, cough, red, watery eyes and a rash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rash generally appears three to five days after the first symptoms, beginning as flat red spots on the face and then spreading downward to the neck, trunk, arms, legs and feet. When the rash appears, the fever may spike over 104 degrees Fahrenheit, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most kids will recover from measles, but infection can lead to dangerous complications such as pneumonia, blindness, brain swelling and death.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;How can you treat measles?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s no specific treatment for measles, so doctors generally try to alleviate symptoms, prevent complications and keep patients comfortable.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p class="time mng-originally-published"&gt;Originally Published: &lt;time datetime="2025-04-26 08:48:18"&gt;April 26, 2025 at 8:48 AM CDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Chicago Tribune</author><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 14:52:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizgFBVV95cUxNaTFKSTRHZWVSVHFxaWhEOW02enZVdWFLMGRXbFUzb0hIMDl0Sy1BQ3lDdDBMclpIMEY5cWJLeFJRenROVDdUS1VHeGFaVl9YRzNXZlVvOXZEUWIyQzFramJZOVJMejhUbzFLUmFaU190Q2hwWTNBc3VvMV9tNGthMjQzNWQ4d2RnQUstUXVEYmczbTRBT3ZCVUxvWF9HdjNNSUJDTnp0NWc1eUtpT0NZajB1U3hIelY5X3BfczRUeEJNRUo4dEZFcW9iREpOQQ</guid></item></channel></rss>