<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>微小的芯片搭乘免疫细胞到达炎症部位- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/science/2025/11/tiny-chips-hitch-a-ride-on-immune-cells-to-sites-of-inflammation/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
                      
                      
          
&lt;p&gt;Standard brain implants use electrodes that penetrate the gray matter to stimulate and record the activity of neurons. These typically need to be put in place via a surgical procedure. To go around that need, a team of researchers led by Deblina Sarkar, an electrical engineer and MIT assistant professor, developed microscopic electronic devices hybridized with living cells. Those cells can be injected into the circulatory system with a standard syringe and will travel the bloodstream before implanting themselves in target brain areas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“In the first two years of working on this technology at MIT, we’ve got 35 grant proposals rejected in a row,” Sarkar says. “Comments we got from the reviewers were that our idea was very impactful, but it was impossible.” She acknowledges that the proposal sounded like something you can find in science fiction novels. But after more than six years of research, she and her colleagues have pulled it off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Nanobot problems&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2022, when Sarkar and her colleagues gathered initial data and got some promising results with their cell-electronics hybrids, the team proposed the project for the National Institutes of Health Director’s New Innovator Award. For the first time, after 35 rejections, it made it through peer review. “We got the highest impact score ever,” Sarkar says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason for that score was that her technology solved three extremely difficult problems. The first, obviously, was making functional electronic devices smaller than cells that can circulate in our blood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Previous explorations, which had not seen a lot of success, relied on putting magnetic particles inside the bloodstream and then guiding them with magnetic fields,” Sarkar explains. “But there is a difference between electronics and particles.” Electronics made using CMOS technology (which we use for making computer processors) can generate electrical power from incoming light in the same way as photovoltaics, as well as perform computations necessary for more intelligent applications like sensing. Particles, on the other hand, can only be used to stimulate cells to an extent.&lt;/p&gt;

          
                      &lt;p class="ars-interlude-container in-content-interlude mx-auto max-w-xl"&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 21:11:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxNOXNaTTBac1ZYWVFTT0k4bkxZcE5NQ00yWWdxV3Nvb3lka0VNalpMVnhXMVRqYlFLSDkzWFhEOWwzMl9qbk1ZeVdDYUJNck1lSC1jcTJ5OUdJTGNLazBRZUlFYk8xdG5OYWN0MUtjeUI0T0o2OEhXYUFBVFBMWGNYcmZhdGw1QkgxZGVjY2htTmIyY3lkLUR6QXJ3QXZ4amxIU19tMFYwaDE</guid></item><item><title>这种突变的流感毒株引发了对大规模爆发的担忧- Axios</title><link>https://www.axios.com/2025/11/13/h3n2-new-flu-strain-symptoms-virus</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:42:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE9GZkFEZ05kdGo2N2tjd3Q5WUZIY25DTUpXdFZOUTJoZmY2LTd1V1VjZlJGeG11c2pWdFZ3bENBMkVyVEZITExVamtPdkU1NG1FaFBFaTFEcGg1dWlPV3lKYU9Helpna3ZGdkxaTVVoS2dHZ2N1YkE</guid></item><item><title>长期新冠肺炎患者血液中有这种怪异的东西- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/people-with-long-covid-have-this-freaky-looking-thing-in-their-blood-2000685488</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl prose-science dark:prose-science"&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Scientists may have uncovered an important aspect of long covid. Recent research appears to show that the blood of these patients often contains unusual clusters of microscopic material.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Researchers at Stellenbosch University in South Africa examined the blood of people with and without long covid. Those with the chronic condition had a greater amount of microclots combined with web-like structures called neutrophil extracellular traps (NETs), the study found. The findings could help doctors better identify long covid cases and might even help explain some of the symptoms these patients experience, the researchers say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Our findings present a significant advancement in the understanding of the interactions between NETs and microclots in long covid,” the researchers wrote in their paper, &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/jmv.70613"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; last month in The Journal of Medical Virology.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Microclots and NETs&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Long covid is a &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/the-challenges-of-unravelling-long-covid-1846644037"&gt;complex condition&lt;/a&gt; and is likely to be caused by a mix of factors, including viral persistence or an ongoing dysfunctional immune response to the earlier covid infection. But some research has suggested that the symptoms of long covid, such as lasting fatigue or brain fog, can be linked to chronic inflammation and blood clotting issues, at least for some cases.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The team’s past work and others have found that people with long covid are more likely to have tiny fiber-like particles in their blood, dubbed &lt;a href="https://www.unmc.edu/healthsecurity/transmission/2023/05/16/long-covid-scientists-try-to-unravel-blood-clot-mystery/"&gt;microclots&lt;/a&gt;, than the average person, for instance. Other studies have &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10565006/"&gt;found&lt;/a&gt; that long covid patients also have higher amounts of NETs, sticky structures produced by immune cells called neutrophils that help trap germs. Though NETs are important to combatting infections, their excess presence may &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41392-024-01933-x"&gt;contribute&lt;/a&gt; to harmful inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this latest research, the Stellenbosch team wanted to better understand how the NETs and microclots seen in long covid patients might interact with one another, if at all. They compared the blood of 50 people diagnosed with long covid to healthy controls.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;They found that people with long covid had higher levels of biomarkers linked to both NETs and microclots than the controls. Long covid patients seemed to have larger microclots on average as well. And perhaps most importantly, those with long covid also appeared to have more microclots that were structurally connected to NETs.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;According to the researchers, NETs might play an important role in keeping microclots safe from eradication by the body, which could then explain why people’s long covid symptoms continue to linger.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“We suggest that higher NETs formation might promote the stabilization of microclots in the circulation, potentially leading to deleterious effects which contribute causally to the LC syndrome,” they wrote. If so, finding a safe and effective way to clear microclots and NETs could potentially alleviate symptoms as well, they add.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;More research needed&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Intriguing as these findings are, they’re certainly not the end of the road.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;While research has found that people with long covid are more likely to have microclots, for instance, it’s &lt;a href="https://www.cochrane.org/evidence/CD015775_what-evidence-microclots-cause-post-covid-19-syndrome-and-removal-using-plasmapheresis-justified"&gt;not clear yet&lt;/a&gt; if and to what extent these structures are responsible for causing people’s illness. And given the complicated nature of the condition, it’s certainly possible only some people’s long covid will end up conclusively linked to these particles.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The researchers say their work could still help doctors devise tests that can easily identify long covid cases—something that isn’t possible today. In this current study, they developed an algorithm that appeared to accurately distinguish between long covid patients and controls, based on their distinctive biomarkers.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Though covid-19 is no longer the pandemic threat it once was, the infectious disease is not gone. And there are still millions of people worldwide &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/how-common-is-long-covid-1849130767"&gt;believed to be afflicted&lt;/a&gt; by long covid. The more we understand about its mechanisms, the greater the chance we can develop effective treatments for these individuals.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 18:45:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxNd21iUlNQdkFUQ084d3lUZi1xZU1TRi1EblMxMnNDbUFxaW5OQzRQS3dDaE1ZYnlWSnZ1VU4zVWYwWTBUUEtBcU5HLU1KN3BDRXJaTDZ2c19xLW9VZkxSVGNkbmV4SlJNTmFvSWhQQnBqLWlyQ3RCVTB3R1RpdmJfUHpseE9xVE9ieTNIQXlPOFNwV0pKV3lMLTNIb29Wazhk</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，超加工食品可能有助于解释50岁以下人群肠癌上升的原因-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/nov/13/ultra-processed-foods-may-help-explain-rising-bowel-cancer-in-under-50s-study-suggests</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Women under 50 who have a diet high in ultra-processed foods (UPFs) stand a greater risk of having abnormal growths in their bowel that can lead to cancer, research suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Ultra-processed foods are typically defined as industrially produced products that are often ready-to-eat, contain little in the way of whole foods, fibre and vitamins, and are typically high in saturated fat, sugar, salt and food additives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2024/mar/06/ultra-processed-food-healthy-diets-pr" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the concept is not without controversy&lt;/a&gt;, not least around whether all UPFs are unhealthy, studies have suggested such foods are &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2024/feb/28/ultra-processed-food-32-harmful-effects-health-review" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;associated with a host of health problems&lt;/a&gt;, from higher risk of heart disease to early death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Now researchers say women who have a greater intake of UPFs have a greater risk of the early onset of a common type of bowel polyp known as conventional adenomas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Andrew Chan, the lead author of the study based at Massachusetts General hospital in the US, said the study was prompted by an effort to understand &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2024/dec/11/bowel-cancer-rising-under-50s-worldwide-research" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;what was driving rising rates of bowel cancer in younger people&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“The vast majority of these polyps do not become bowel cancer. But at the same time, we know the vast majority of bowel cancers we see in young people arise from these precursor lesions,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaoncology/fullarticle/10.1001/jamaoncol.2025.4777?guestAccessKey=f519cbac-0500-444e-a957-91e4ae77c2e7&amp;amp;utm_source=For_The_Media&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=ftm_links&amp;amp;utm_content=tfl&amp;amp;utm_term=111325" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Writing in the journal Jama Oncology&lt;/a&gt;, Chan and colleagues report how they studied data collected as part of the US-based Nurses’ Health Study II (NHS II), which began in 1989 and involved female nurses born between 1947 and 1964.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;From 1991, participants were asked to complete a food questionnaire every four years in which they reported how often they had eaten various items over the previous 12 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The team studied data from 29,105 participants who had completed the questionnaires, undergone a colonoscopy at some point after 1991, and did not have a prior history of polyps, inflammatory bowel disease or any type of cancer other than non-melanoma skin cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;These participants were followed until June 2015, by which time all had reached the age of 50. By then, 1,189 cases of early-onset conventional adenomas and 1,598 cases of another type of polyp, known as a serrated lesion, had been recorded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The team divided participants into five equal sized groups based on their UPF consumption, finding that compared with the group that ate the least UPF – on average 3.3 servings a day – the group that ate the most – on average 9.9 servings a day – had a 45% greater risk of having early onset conventional adenomas once factors such as BMI, smoking and physical activity were taken into account.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;However, there was no associated risk of developing serrated lesions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The study has limitations including that it is based on participants’ recall of food, may be complicated by difficulties in classifying foods as UPFs, did not look at the development of bowel cancer itself, and cannot prove UPFs cause the development of polyps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;However, Chen said there were several plausible mechanisms that could explain the results, noting UPFs had been associated with metabolic disorders linked to obesity and type 2 diabetes that were associated with an increased risk of bowel cancer. He also said UPFs could promote a general state of chronic inflammation, or might impact gut microbes and the gut lining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Chan said while it was likely the results would also hold for men, more research was needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It doesn’t suggest that if you eat UPFs, that you are inevitably going to develop cancer. That’s certainly not our message,” he said. “But it’s a piece of the puzzle in terms of what might be driving underlying cancer rates.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Fiona Osgun, the head of health information at &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/cancer" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Cancer&lt;/a&gt; Research UK, said that while the study did not directly measure cancer risk, it offered a useful insight into how diet might influence early changes in the bowel that sometimes led to cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Osgun added that policy-level changes were needed to make healthier diets more accessible for everyone. “Our overall diet matters more for cancer risk than any single food type,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 18:13:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizwFBVV95cUxPTERKYWVtVDBuRU5yXzhzVXlicHBJMDBqV0RXRVBxMzFCTE5lazFQRDV5SzlCblYxMnREM3l0ckNTQ3hqQk4xV1FYNl9HLXFJal9pSnhWVnctS2laN0VDN0xJSE5IRlgwMU96cThPSmE4eDNpZEJ0V1VIUUotc2pEV2ZPeG5URDluX0NmR2J2cjFVZkdUMTBWUy1ZU18tLUFueWtvcjJYc3NsblZDenpZSnYxRVNuLU5yRlNLRW1VcjUtVldrSGQtWmtmMEFrOXM</guid></item><item><title>与低水平关键营养素相关的焦虑症- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/anxiety-disorders-linked-to-lower-levels-of-key-nutrient/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A sweeping analysis of brain chemistry has identified a potential biological signature for anxiety disorders, revealing that people with these conditions have consistently lower levels of the essential nutrient choline in their brains. The study, published in the Nature journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41380-025-03206-7" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Molecular Psychiatry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, synthesizes decades of research and suggests that this chemical difference could open new avenues for understanding and potentially treating these common and debilitating illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anxiety disorders, which include conditions like generalized anxiety disorder, panic disorder, and social phobias, represent the most common category of mental illness in the United States. “Anxiety disorders are the most common mental illness in the United States, affecting about 30% of adults,” said Richard Maddock, the study’s senior author and a research professor in the Department of Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences at the University of California, Davis. “They can be debilitating for people, and many people do not receive adequate treatment.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These conditions are understood to involve complex interactions between different brain regions. Areas like the amygdala, which acts as a threat detector, and the prefrontal cortex, which helps manage planning and emotional responses, can become dysregulated. This can cause the brain to perceive manageable, everyday stressors as overwhelming threats, leading to persistent worry and nervousness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new research comes from Maddock and his colleague Jason Smucny, an assistant professor at UC Davis. Maddock, a psychiatrist who has spent decades treating patients and researching anxiety, had previously observed low levels of choline in his own studies of people with panic disorder. This prompted him and Smucny to investigate whether this was a consistent pattern seen across the scientific literature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To find an answer, the researchers conducted a meta-analysis, a type of study that systematically combines and analyzes the results of many previous independent studies. This method allows scientists to detect broad patterns that might not be apparent in smaller, individual experiments. They gathered data from 25 separate studies, creating a large dataset that included 370 people diagnosed with an anxiety disorder and 342 people without.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The studies they analyzed all used a specialized, non-invasive imaging technique called proton magnetic resonance spectroscopy. This method uses the same type of machine as a standard magnetic resonance imaging scan, which creates pictures of the body’s internal structures. Instead of producing an image, however, this technique provides a chemical profile of a specific brain region, allowing researchers to measure the concentration of different molecules, known as neurometabolites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The analysis revealed a distinct and consistent chemical difference. Across the various anxiety disorders, individuals with these conditions had lower levels of choline-containing compounds in their brains. The reduction was most pronounced in the brain’s cortex, the outer layer responsible for higher-order functions like thinking, decision-making, and emotional regulation. The finding was especially consistent in the prefrontal cortex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On average, the level of choline was about 8% lower in those with anxiety disorders. While this number might seem small, even minor changes in the brain’s chemical environment can have significant effects on its function. “An 8% lower amount doesn’t sound like that much, but in the brain it’s significant,” Maddock said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that this chemical pattern was “transdiagnostic,” meaning it appeared to be a common feature across different types of anxiety disorders rather than being unique to one specific condition. The team also examined whether other factors, such as patient medication, age, or the technical specifications of the brain scans, could explain the results. The link between anxiety and lower choline held firm, suggesting it is a robust biological marker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The finding became even more defined when the researchers assessed the quality of the measurements in the original studies. In the subset of studies that used the most precise measurement techniques, the reduction in choline was even more apparent. This strengthens the confidence that the observed difference is a real phenomenon and not an artifact of inconsistent data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also looked at other neurometabolites, including N-acetylaspartate, a molecule often used as an indicator of the health and integrity of neurons. After removing a few outlier studies from the analysis, the researchers found a small but significant reduction in this molecule as well, suggesting a possible widespread effect on neuronal function in anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choline is an essential nutrient that plays a fundamental part in building cell membranes and producing neurotransmitters involved in memory, mood, and muscle control. While the body can produce a small amount on its own, the majority must be obtained through food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers propose that the chronic state of high alert, or “fight-or-flight” response, common in anxiety disorders may increase the brain’s metabolic activity. This heightened state could place a greater demand on choline resources to maintain neural circuits, gradually leading to lower overall levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is important to recognize that this study identifies a strong correlation, not a direct cause-and-effect relationship. It is not yet clear whether lower choline levels contribute to the development of anxiety, or if the biological processes of anxiety itself cause choline levels to drop. Further work is needed to untangle this relationship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these open questions, the finding points toward potential new strategies for patient care. “This is the first meta-analysis to show a chemical pattern in the brain in anxiety disorders,” said Smucny. “It suggests nutritional approaches — like appropriate choline supplementation — may help restore brain chemistry and improve outcomes for patients.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future studies will need to test this idea directly. “We don’t know yet if increasing choline in the diet will help reduce anxiety. More research will be needed,” Maddock said. He cautions that people experiencing anxiety should not begin taking high-dose choline supplements on their own, as the effects are not yet understood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, the research highlights the connection between diet and mental well-being. A healthy diet is a cornerstone of overall health, and ensuring adequate nutrient intake may be particularly relevant for brain function. Choline is found in a variety of foods, including eggs, beef, chicken, soybeans, and fish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Someone with an anxiety disorder might want to look at their diet and see whether they are getting the recommended daily amount of choline,” Maddock noted, adding that many people in the U.S. do not consume enough. “Some forms of omega-3 fatty acids, like those found in salmon, may be especially good sources for supplying choline to the brain.” This discovery of a consistent chemical signature offers a new window into the biology of anxiety and reinforces the idea that what we eat has a profound connection to how we feel and think.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41380-025-03206-7" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Transdiagnostic reduction in cortical choline-containing compounds in anxiety disorders: a 1H-magnetic resonance spectroscopy meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Richard J. Maddock and Jason Smucny.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 17:03:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQdzIwRnN1Q1pFYmNHakd0bEpIdGNIMzhVMFMxZjdKM1cydi1yTU9KY29fMWlwbXdzX0hHZF9sRHkwLXlabU1uU0t2dGRWOV9GdHl3THNKeUFpbjZMQkNLT2Q4bHZtdjRnQWF1Wl9INzFYbXY4U2FtNk5tX19GZEsxSXExSDkwckta</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现移植患者猪肾排斥反应背后的免疫反应- abcnews.go.com</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/scientists-discover-immune-reaction-pig-kidney-rejection-transplant/story?id=127446033</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;Transplanting gene-edited pig kidneys into humans has been hailed as a pioneering procedure and a way to help ease the shortage of organs available for those on transplant waiting lists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Scientists, however, have been struggling to understand why these animal organs have been rejected not long after surgery. Now, they may have an answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In the first of two studies published Thursday in the journal Nature, researchers at NYU Langone Health have discovered immune reactions that may explain why these organs get rejected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The team looked at the transplantation of a genetically engineered pig kidney into a patient who was brain dead but had a beating heart and was on a ventilator in the ICU. The family had donated the patient's body to science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;For more than two months after the surgery, the NYU Langone team performed biopsies and collected samples of blood, tissue and bodily fluid from the patient in a way that's "impossible" to do in primates or living patients, according to Dr. Robert Montgomery, lead author of the study and director of the NYU Langone Transplant Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Stock photo of doctors performing a surgery.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Alvaro Gonzalez/STOCK PHOTO/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"We could really get a very dense set of data points from doing biopsies, taking blood samples, body fluid samples and create an atlas of what that immune response looks like," he told ABC News. "And that's what's really unique about the study. I think that this is probably the most deeply studied human in history."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The team learned that pig organs were being rejected due to an immune system reaction from specific antibodies -- which recognize and attach themselves to foreign substances so they can be removed from the body -- and from T cells, which are white blood cells that help the body fight off germs and other unfamiliar invaders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;After rejection, the team used an FDA-approved drug combination to successfully reverse it, with no signs of permanent damage or reduced kidney function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"It's a huge step forward," Montgomery said. "I think it makes transplantation just that much more of a successful endeavor. As we move forward, I do believe that we will be in a position in the next few years where gene-edited pig organs will be an alternative to human organs."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In a second study published in Nature, Montgomery and his team looked at the body's immune response to the pig organ in greater detail. By measuring levels of biomarkers in the blood, they were able to spot an attack up to five days before it would be visible in bodily tissue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Montgomery said this can help transplant teams anticipate a potential rejection sooner and diagnose it quickly so it can be subsequently treated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;More than 101,000 Americans are in need of a kidney transplant but only 17,000 receive a transplant every year, according to the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.kidney.org/be-organ-donor" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;National Kidney Foundation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Additionally, 12 people die every day while waiting for a kidney. The average wait time on the transplant list can be as long as 10 years. Montgomery said finding a way for more people waiting on the list to receive a kidney with gene-edited pig organs, while lowering the risk of rejection, is crucial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"That's a great shortcoming of our health care system that we have to ration something that we know works so well," Montgomery said. "I think we really do need an alternative source of organs to really change this game."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The procedure, while considered by many to be a medical breakthrough, is still controversial, with some critics expressing ethical concerns about altering animal organs and potential health risks for patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;Some patients who have undergone the procedure have had the genetically modified pig kidneys removed after organ rejection or unrelated infection. At least two patients have died after transplantation, although doctors say these patients were terminal and were experiencing end-stage kidney disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>abcnews.go.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:07:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxNdFdOVWQ1dUEyd09lNUphczlYWC03YnJQVnY2V1F2X0lLd3BRMjJEVFhxYk5Mbml6OGYwdW9CeVRDaTdCMlVQWGFTZWV3cGpndDEtb1lKYTBiVzZENDhkNS1fWkxwMnJfNGxuaFhYTE8tdVhyQ1ZOLVM4VWtDMXBqZEpMeUhaMTk5Q3JSbXZyQ0JaSXlOSDJzYmUzUy1zaURLZTNrMVBmTEVSX0dzTkFCdE9VS3h0YlHSAbwBQVVfeXFMTVhnWVlDNjI4YXVnenB0a2N3WjRTTm12dGxmSEhUdnN6NDVxTjYxTGlERmxKWi1vU25CTTdNTVNKUnM2WXZQUUxYSlZRMnZVMHp6UE9YTkFENG1kd3RielVIdzZ4NDNyOE11b3Z0elV1NWoydXRPZkxZSmFYdmw2Rm9pSk93NlhEdTdiM2RqX3JuRTh5d3RFVVVsbTZ2bC0tS2FmRFlBSVpaOFYwTnBWOEo5TzFlZXUzbmRudEk</guid></item><item><title>与50岁以下女性结直肠癌风险相关的超加工食品-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/13/well/eat/ultraprocessed-foods-colorectal-cancer-risk.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:03:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQR3ljLWJwN3RyMUNfX2dCY3FPYXl0Z0R3dFo2YXlCMkMxcVZtelVWbmJ3eDJOQkc2M3J6NTlJNGdPZWVVQmFpbXVQbjFHNGZmTGw4Q3pQRWI2SWx2QjFIOGJoQWxPRFNibDNndGdEODdMTnVfNWRuUkhLQnpnMnJtME1mNUFfNnNqRUZBSEZKT3ZONmVsb3RJ</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，超加工食品与癌前息肉风险增加有关- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/ultra-processed-foods-linked-increased-risk-precancerous-polyps-study-rcna243574</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-773049" class="body-graf"&gt;Eating more ultra-processed foods is tied to an increased risk of precancerous colorectal growths in women under 50, according to a study published Thursday in &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaoncology/fullarticle/2841354" target="_blank"&gt;JAMA Oncology&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-16832d" class="body-graf"&gt;These growths, called adenomas or polyps, can later turn into cancer and are a good indicator of a person’s cancer risk, experts say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9a060b" class="body-graf"&gt;Rates of colorectal cancer in people under 50 have risen sharply in recent decades. The findings could offer new insights into what’s driving this increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-36e5c2" class="body-graf"&gt;“One approach we’ve been taking is trying to understand what has changed in our environment that could be driving this. What are some trends that mirror this acceleration in cancer rates?” said study leader Dr. Andrew Chan, a gastroenterologist and the chief of the clinical and translational epidemiology unit at Massachusetts General Brigham in Boston.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-845e9f" class="body-graf"&gt;Ultra-processed foods now &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/ultra-processed-foods-make-majority-kids-diet-cdc-report-finds-rcna223481" target="_blank"&gt;make up the bulk&lt;/a&gt; of the average American’s diet, especially among kids. The foods, which tend to be high in calories, have been linked to &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/mental-health/ultraprocessed-foods-linked-depression-study-finds-rcna106811" target="_blank"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/eating-food-additives-together-may-increase-diabetes-risk-study-sugges-rcna200163" target="_blank"&gt;Type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/highly-processed-food-linked-early-death-study-rcna55455" target="_blank"&gt;early death&lt;/a&gt;. Some experts have also suspected eating these foods could be driving the increase in colorectal cancer rates among young people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0e8cef" class="body-graf"&gt;To test this hypothesis, Chan and his team used data from more than 29,000 women who participated in the Nurses’ Health Study II, an ongoing study of female registered nurses established in 1989. The women, who were between 24 and 42 when they enrolled in the study, were followed for 24 years, from 1991 through 2015. Every four years, everyone filled out a questionnaire about their diets, and everyone had at least one colonoscopy before 50.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5dd606" class="body-graf"&gt;The researchers looked at whether the women were diagnosed with precancerous polyps: either adenomas, which are more likely to turn into cancer, or serrated lesions. While only about 5% of adenomas are cancerous, about 75% of colorectal cancers start as adenomas, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/15370-colon-polyps" target="_blank"&gt;according to the Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. Serrated lesions are still considered precancerous but are linked to fewer cases of colorectal cancer, Chan said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7e0b99" class="body-graf"&gt;The study found a connection between eating more ultra-processed foods and developing an adenoma before 50. It didn’t see any links between the foods and serrated lesions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4c85a4" class="body-graf"&gt;Because the majority of colon cancers arise from adenomas, the study showing  a link between eating more ultra-processed foods and an increased risk of developing adenomas specifically gave Chan and his team more confidence that these foods could increase colorectal cancer risk, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1fd075" class="body-graf"&gt;“The strength was that we looked at two major types of polyps — it’s the adenoma type that seems to underlie cancer, and we saw the link between that,” he said. “&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b604a5" class="body-graf"&gt;About 1,200 women in the study developed adenomas. Compared to those who ate the fewest ultra-processed foods, those who ate the most — accounting for one-third of their daily calories — were about 1.5 times more likely to develop adenomas. Specific foods also appeared to increase risk. Diets higher in sugar and artificial sweeteners were most linked to higher rates of adenomas, followed by diets high in sauces, spreads and condiments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f02b73" class="body-graf"&gt;Although the study included only women, the majority of whom were white, &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/evidence-links-highly-processed-food-cancer-death-rcna45713" target="_blank"&gt;other studies&lt;/a&gt; have also found a link between men eating more ultra-processed foods and developing cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-477138" class="body-graf"&gt;“We don’t have any reason to believe there would be a difference in men compared to women,” Chan said, adding that additional research should include men to be sure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-458f5f" class="body-graf"&gt;Most colorectal polyps do not turn into cancer, but nearly all colorectal cancer does start as a polyp, said Dr. Folasade May, a gastroenterologist and an associate professor of medicine at the David Geffen School of Medicine at UCLA, who wasn’t involved with the research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-50622b" class="body-graf"&gt;This is why doctors remove any polyps they find during a colonoscopy, and why people who have polyps are considered to be at higher risk for developing colorectal cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3c7b04" class="body-graf"&gt;“They are looking at the first step, who is more likely to get these polyps that can turn into cancer,” May said of the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bc08bb" class="body-graf"&gt;The problem is that routine screening for colorectal cancer does not happen until age 45, said Dr. Christopher Lieu, the co-director of gastrointestinal medical oncology at the University of Colorado Anschutz School of Medicine in Aurora.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-24e303" class="body-graf"&gt;“The concern is that whenever you have a polyp in a young person, that polyp is allowed to grow unnoticed, and because you are not screening those young patients,” Lieu said. This makes it even more important to identify the modifiable lifestyle factors that are driving increased rates of colorectal cancer in young people, added Lieu, who wasn’t involved with the new research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-33c0a1" class="body-graf"&gt;Although scientists have yet to determine a clear cause, the rise in rates is unlikely to be driven by genetics, May said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3dcf61" class="body-graf"&gt;“This has happened very fast, so it is likely unfortunately something we have done to ourselves as humans, in the way we live our lives,” she said. “It’s jarring, hearing stories every week about people in their 20s, 30s, 40s getting cancers that, when I was in medical school, we were taught happen in people in their 80s.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-40e10b" class="body-graf"&gt;Ultra-processed foods cause inflammation in the gut — which includes the colon — that impairs the gut’s ability to repair itself when damaged and keep tumors at bay. &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/anti-inflammatory-diet-may-help-colon-cancer-patients-live-longer-stud-rcna209539" target="_blank"&gt;High levels of inflammation&lt;/a&gt; are also linked to cancer in general, May said. Another hypothesis is that people who eat more ultra-processed foods are more likely to have obesity and Type 2 diabetes, both which are linked to a &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/cancer/risk-factors/obesity.html" target="_blank"&gt;higher risk&lt;/a&gt; for colorectal cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9a6bbe" class="body-graf"&gt;“More likely, it’s the direct toxic effects of these ultra-processed foods,” May said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c1effe" class="body-graf"&gt;Chan, the study author, said ultra-processed foods are known to &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/colon-cancer-young-people-dna-damage-gut-toxin-antibiotics-rcna202572" target="_blank"&gt;alter the gut microbiome&lt;/a&gt;, which, in theory, could make cells in the gut more likely to turn cancerous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-96dcf8" class="body-graf"&gt;The next step in the research is determining whether any of these hypotheses appear to have a causal effect on who develops colorectal cancer at a young age. It’s likely part of the puzzle, Chan said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e19e06" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“One thing that has been clear is that the U.S. intake of ultra-processed food has really risen in the past few decades in a way that mirrors the staggering increase in colorectal cancer cases,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:00:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxPZ2YxYW5ncG9GUEREbzVTNTcyMXdiMXFXTnMzd3MtamdJTlVPc19pZU5HbTJfREluV2dpclZJSWJCVWxPdm1ZNzRrWU94ejROZlpVRzBKX2pHWWdFTzdMSGFXVl9vSG9aVDlZTFVwRlBpTG9lVVVYem5fMk9HZDVIQVZzdkt0SHFHM2JZRE5BRkxzRVVZUURjTFJuN0RYZVFsWER6VWUtRnBwcXVmSVJBQUlqNTRTZ09kY3fSAVZBVV95cUxNSmJ3U2xHamhtRHZqRzB1ei1UUnpHX3dQdWxjQXNUN0lkS0FuWHNwS0tEVm1aWkozaWxsc19iMkdXQnZvTGlDc3Rra3Yya1VIZFM4NDF6QQ</guid></item><item><title>妈妈分享了她在乳腺癌诊断前几个月出现的“疯狂和令人兴奋”的症状- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/mom-shares-crazy-mind-blowing-213032138.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kelly Mann/Instagram&lt;/p&gt; Kelly Mann&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kelly Mann started experiencing recurring pink eye infections in April 2023&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In July 2023, she was diagnosed with breast cancer, and later learned that her eye symptoms were actually episcleritis, a condition triggered by the disease&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mom of three is now using her platform to raise awareness and share her breast cancer journey&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A woman is recalling the “mind-blowing” symptom she experienced months before she was diagnosed with breast cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than two years ago, &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/kellymann/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Kelly Mann;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Kelly Mann&lt;/a&gt;, a university professor from Abilene, Texas, started suffering from “the worst pink eye of my life,” she told &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/breast-cancer/breast-cancer-symptom-pink-eye-episcleritis-rcna243059" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:TODAY;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;TODAY&lt;/a&gt;. Antibiotic eye drops wouldn’t relieve the redness in her eyes, but after a week, the issue resolved itself. Her symptoms were gone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the pink eye returned, beginning a cycle that occurred six times between April and June 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Then one night while watching TV, I went to itch my arm and &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/breast-cancer/pictures-of-breast-cancer-lumps-signs-rcna53603" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:felt a lump;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;felt a lump&lt;/a&gt;," she recalled. "My husband was asleep, so I kind of panicked and went back and forth, like, 'Is this what I’m really feeling, or am I making this up in my head?'"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kelly Mann/Instagram&lt;/p&gt; Kelly Mann&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mann immediately made a doctor’s appointment the next morning. After a mammogram and biopsy, she received life-changing news.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In late July 2023, Mann was diagnosed with stage 2 breast cancer, just a week before her 36th birthday. Mann was devastated by the discovery, especially because she had a breast exam just in April.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was, obviously, devastated," she told the outlet. "My tumor grew from being completely undetectable to 2 and a half centimeters in about six to eight weeks.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Within a few weeks, Mann started chemotherapy treatment, which led to a “crazy” realization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"After my first chemo, I had the same pink eye situation pop up again," she said. "I was so frustrated, and it was one of the worst versions of it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-puzzler-8620185" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kelly Mann/Instagram&lt;/p&gt; Kelly Mann&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;After speaking to an ophthalmologist, Mann learned that what she thought was pink eye was actually episcleritis — swelling, irritation and redness of the tissue that covers the white part of the eye, according to the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/24974-episcleritis" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cleveland Clinic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. While there is no known cause, it can be associated with an underlying inflammatory or rheumatologic condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Your eye, being an organ, will respond in unique ways to things happening in your body," Mann explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Episcleritis was my &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/breast-cancer/breast-cancer-symptoms-doctor-monitors-in-herself-rcna234706" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:first real, tangible symptom;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;first real, tangible symptom&lt;/a&gt; that I had," she said. "I thought it was fascinating and also crazy and mind-blowing that your body really does know what’s going on far before any normal diagnostics could make sense of it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mann, now 38, was given steroid eye drops to help manage her symptoms moving forward. She underwent 12 rounds of chemotherapy, a bilateral mastectomy and breast reconstruction surgery. The mom of three then continued a number of breast cancer therapies through October 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kelly Mann/Instagram&lt;/p&gt; Kelly Mann&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mann admitted that her treatment journey has been difficult and she still sporadically deals with episcleritis, but because of her children — "three little souls watching me and worried about me" — she wouldn’t allow herself to give up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now a cancer survivor, Mann is using her social media platform to share her journey and raise awareness for episcleritis and early detection. She admitted that building a community online has helped her connect with so many young patients like herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sometimes I’m the first person they told, or it’s their caregivers that are reaching out to me," she told TODAY. "I just decided that, because I couldn’t find that resource for me, I wanted to be that resource for other women."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/woman-shares-mind-blowing-breast-cancer-symptom-11848201" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE9seDZjOFNMOTd3X0JPYkxzMmhwWmtRLXJ6Uk9QU1FiRUlDaHBMVHUzdkQxcGVrZ2RZTGprX1RsdzZVRE5nNlVsRTZFX2tlbURBZXdWaTRQcU5YaFJ6a0NudlNoLUg0S1pJTzMzVDJ5LTB0WWRjSGtvNFoza3lJZw</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，禽流感肆虐了世界上最大的象海豹种群-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/13/science/bird-flu-h5n1-elephant-seals.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:00:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxPYUZ0QklUUlRFeGRsTkRtRmlNUWJSam9xZ3ctcVg2Mi1HajFNczA5UV9Ec0JpY2QtUHEzZ3lkR0N2SjRoT1ZHbkd2Tk9la3E0YlZaeVZ2VE9hUUJneUJwRHRyX3FVT3QwZXNuRi0zYmliaGtkaUNObmVaZDIwYmQxTl9R</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现一种自然、非成瘾的止痛方法，可替代阿片类药物- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/scientists-discover-a-natural-non-addictive-way-to-block-pain-that-could-replace-opioids/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:43:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxOSk5KSE8tTHhleUdXbE84aWhDYmlpXzNwem9fX1Y0eEJDdzRUYnVpNG1HWUkzdTZ1SnhDRmI0TWwtVm9IcUk4d2ZDSnNLVVM3TExQMmpqOVFJT0hQTlRZRUxJQ19jZlNHZkFyOGxkTEdDcEIxMzNSenFTY1RYOElYWDRRdm94eWdyczZMTUhST0dnblNtRHVqYUU1eWxUbEtYOGFES1A3NDRWaDhiYzZ5aGlrYjk</guid></item><item><title>科学家说，走路可以大大降低心血管疾病的风险- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/scientists-walking-much-cuts-cardiovascular-133000531.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;New research looks into the importance of walking “bouts” in addition to step count when it comes to heart health. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;People who take less than 5,000 steps per day or walk in bouts of five minutes or less are more likely to have heart disease, according to the findings.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cardiologists explain walking habits for a healthy heart below.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;And so, the great step count debate continues. Over recent years, researchers have examined the possible health impacts of &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/fitness/a69124464/4000-steps-extend-life-lower-cardiovascular-disease-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:4,000 daily steps;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;4,000 daily steps&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a65565929/7000-steps-a-day-better-health-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:7,000 steps;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;7,000 steps&lt;/a&gt;, short &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/fitness/a69108375/exercise-snacks-longevity-heart-health-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:“exercise snacks,”;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;“exercise snacks,”&lt;/a&gt; and other amounts of movement to answer the overarching question of: How much exercise, exactly, does it take to stay healthy? The &lt;a href="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/ANNALS-25-01547" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:latest study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;latest study&lt;/a&gt; under that umbrella examines people who took less than 8,000 daily steps, &lt;em&gt;how &lt;/em&gt;they took them (in short or long bursts?), and what that cadence meant for cardiovascular health. Ultimately, researchers found that walking in longer bouts significantly cut cardiovascular disease and all-cause mortality risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meet the Experts: &lt;a href="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/christopher-j-berg" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Christopher Berg, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Christopher Berg, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, board-certified cardiologist at MemorialCare Heart and Vascular Institute at Orange Coast Medical Center; and &lt;a href="https://manhattancardiology.com/team/mary-greene-md/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mary Greene, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Mary Greene, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a cardiologist with Manhattan Cardiology in New York City and LabFinder contributor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below, cardiologists explain the conclusions and attempt to settle the step saga—as it pertains to heart health, at least.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What did the study find?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers looked at accelerometer (step counter) data from 33, 560 people in the United Kingdom who took 8,000 or fewer daily steps and were initially free of cardiovascular disease or cancer. They were categorized into sedentary participants (who had fewer than 5,000 daily steps) and low-active participants (who had 5,000 to 7,999 daily steps).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over an average of 7.9 years, researchers tracked participants’ health and learned that people who took most of their daily steps in longer bouts (between 10 and 15 minutes at a time) had lower all-cause death rates and lower risk of developing cardiovascular disease compared to those who took their steps in shorter durations. Those conclusions were “much more prominent in the sedentary group,” says &lt;a href="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/christopher-j-berg" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Christopher Berg, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Christopher Berg, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, board-certified cardiologist at MemorialCare Heart and Vascular Institute at Orange Coast Medical Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As with most studies, this one has its limitations. The findings are observational and also contain implicit bias, as people who tend to take longer walks may also make healthier choices, notes &lt;a href="https://manhattancardiology.com/team/mary-greene-md/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mary Greene, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Mary Greene, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a cardiologist with Manhattan Cardiology in New York City and LabFinder contributor. However, the findings do suggest that sustained activity over 10 or more minutes “may be necessary to stimulate the cardiovascular and metabolic benefits of activity that doesn’t occur in five minutes or less,” explains Dr. Greene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most importantly: “This research further emphasizes the danger of sedentary behavior,” says Dr. Berg. “It also suggests that the spacing of activity, even in those who are very sedentary, is related to the degree of cardiovascular risk.” &lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why longer walks work&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Longer or more continuous walking raises your heart rate and cardiac output in a more sustained way, which trains the heart and improves cardiovascular fitness more so than small bursts of activity,” explains Dr. Greene. “This sustained activity also improved insulin sensitivity and lipid metabolism in study participants, which can reduce cardiovascular risk factors like diabetes and atherosclerotic [artery] disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What advice is right?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may be thinking, what about “exercise snacks,” or past research that says even short, small bursts of activity are helpful? Well, those aren’t necessarily wrong. “Both ‘exercise snacks’ and sustained activity are good for health. Something is always better than nothing,” says Dr. Greene. “Sustained activity is better, adding ‘snacks’ to a regimen of sustained activity is best!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The important message to take away from these findings is that taking less than 4,000 daily steps is “detrimental,” Dr. Greene notes. And, if you can get in at least around 7,000, that appears to be the well-studied, average on-ramp to cardiovascular benefits, she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reality is, the longer bouts of activity that this research suggests won’t “happen by accident” and will likely take some planning, Dr. Berg notes. “This may mean scheduling 10 minutes to walk with a co-worker during lunch or incorporating a walk as part of a daily routine,” he adds. You can even intentionally take the longer route to get somewhere, or park further out in a parking lot. “Write it down in your calendar and hold yourself to it,” Dr. Berg continues. “Couple it to something enjoyable to make it more attractive—walk to your favorite coffee shop or call your best friend.” And if you miss a day, don’t let it set you back and squeeze in some steps where you can. “Anything is better than nothing,” Dr. Berg concludes.&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“&lt;/em&gt;If you are sedentary, start slow with a general increase in activity,” like taking the stairs, recommends Dr. Greene. “Start to aim for at least 7,000 steps per day. As you build up endurance, then start sustained walking sessions with a pace that is comfortably uncomfortable.” In other words, do your best to get your heart rate up, and work your way up to 10 minutes of that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you can, add some resistance training and/or body weight exercises as well, which can also provide other health benefits,” says Dr. Greene. “As with anything, consistency is key! It’s more important to be consistent with moving your body than it is to be perfect.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:37:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxQaVlDR0prVWl0ZWJkc0VGTzlYMVR0RVg3NnFzTXNZWF8tSE1JLXRNNTlvRnpfdTRjVzItQ0NNaWVic3lsbUJQRXF3bkZaZHJkZ1NlMFlhVnh0VHJtVzF3T1FXTm9LZ1I4NGxvaGx1UVd1QWZlZEtNbm9VNTdFY3J2M1BOV05EU2RIQWxuVWJ6bVU</guid></item><item><title>几十年后，科学家终于发现了泰诺的秘密机制- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/after-decades-scientists-have-finally-discovered-tylenols-secret-mechanism/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:08:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxPa2lKb090VUpEeGdjZWtNWHE3WVBxNUNMZFlhdGpBZkhkWkItQVRiQmZPQVVpSk5FQWxqZU1XVEk2STBfenlTbjUwd1RkREE2TkNsRmpTdkRSRVo5d21mZi16bjZJQzJPOVdnWGhfQll3eEMtU3lNLUtDNGFLb1g3UnVKRTMzaGdPQnItcEtUVTBnVTdaaVE1TE9IbzVROU1XTVE</guid></item><item><title>如果这7种爱好为您带来快乐，那么您可能比房间里的大多数人更聪明- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/things-to-do/a-if-these-7-hobbies-bring-you-joy-youre-probably-smarter-than-most-people-in-the-room/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;Ever notice how certain hobbies get labeled as "nerdy" or "weird," while others are considered totally normal?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've been thinking about this lately because I keep running into people who apologize for their interests, like they're confessing to some embarrassing secret.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I know it's boring, but I really love bird watching."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Don't judge me, but I spend my weekends doing puzzles."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the thing: those supposedly boring hobbies? They're often the ones that indicate a higher level of intelligence and cognitive ability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if you find deep satisfaction in any of these seven activities, there's a good chance you're operating at a higher cognitive level than most people around you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1. Reading fiction for pleasure&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most people will tell you they "should" read more, but genuinely loving fiction is different from feeling obligated to finish that bestseller everyone's talking about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're someone who gets lost in novels, who thinks about characters like they're real people, who stays up too late because you need to know what happens next, you're exercising some serious cognitive muscles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.newschool.edu/pressroom/pressreleases/2013/CastanoKidd.htm"&gt;Research from The New School&lt;/a&gt; found that reading literary fiction improves theory of mind, which is the ability to understand that others have beliefs, desires, and perspectives different from your own. This isn't just about empathy in some fuzzy, feel-good way. It's about sophisticated mental modeling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you read fiction, you're constantly making predictions, tracking multiple characters' motivations, holding complex plot threads in your working memory, and interpreting ambiguous social situations. Your brain is doing intense work that looks like relaxation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've mentioned this before, but I keep a stack of novels next to my bed, and I've noticed something interesting: the weeks when I'm reading fiction consistently are the weeks when I'm better at navigating tricky conversations and understanding subtext in my own life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fiction readers are essentially running social simulations in their heads. That's not escapism, that's training.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2. Playing a musical instrument&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learning to play an instrument is one of the most cognitively demanding activities humans can engage in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think about what's actually happening when someone plays music: they're reading symbolic notation, translating it into motor commands, coordinating both hands independently, listening to the sound they're producing, comparing it to an internal model of how it should sound, and adjusting in real time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and if they're playing with others, they're also tracking what everyone else is doing and adjusting to stay synchronized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2024.12.11.627938v1.full"&gt;Studies using brain imaging&lt;/a&gt; have shown that musicians have enhanced connectivity between brain regions, particularly between areas responsible for motor control and auditory processing. The corpus callosum, which connects the brain's two hemispheres, is often larger in musicians.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But here's what I find most interesting: it's not just about the technical skills. Music requires you to think both analytically and creatively at the same time. You're following rules while also interpreting and expressing emotion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That dual processing, that ability to be both precise and expressive simultaneously, translates to enhanced problem-solving in completely unrelated domains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you genuinely enjoy practicing scales or working through a difficult passage, your brain is thriving on complexity that most people find frustrating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3. Engaging in strategy games&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether it's chess, Go, complex board games, or strategic video games, if you love games that require planning several moves ahead, you're constantly exercising executive function.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These games aren't just about following rules. They require you to hold multiple possible future scenarios in your head simultaneously, evaluate them against each other, and make decisions based on incomplete information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What makes strategy games particularly interesting from a cognitive perspective is that they require you to model your opponent's thinking. You're not just planning your own strategy, you're thinking about what they think you're thinking, which requires sophisticated recursive reasoning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I used to think of gaming as a waste of time until I started paying attention to what was actually happening in my head during a complicated game. The mental workout is real.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you find joy in the challenge of outthinking an opponent or solving a strategic puzzle, you're someone who thrives on cognitive complexity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4. Cooking elaborate meals from scratch&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cooking might seem like a basic survival skill, but if you genuinely enjoy the process of creating complex dishes, you're engaging in a sophisticated form of problem-solving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think about what goes into making a complicated recipe: you need to understand how different ingredients interact chemically, manage multiple timelines simultaneously, adjust for variables like humidity and altitude, taste and adjust seasoning based on sensory feedback, and adapt when something doesn't go according to plan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8071848/#:~:text=Although%20not%20widely%20held%20within,fundamental%20to%20reaching%20psychosocial%20competence."&gt;Research has shown&lt;/a&gt; that cooking activates multiple brain regions simultaneously. You're using procedural memory, sensory processing, fine motor control, planning, and creativity all at once.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there's something deeper happening too. When you cook, you're essentially running a complex project with multiple dependencies, deadlines, and quality standards. The cognitive skills involved are remarkably similar to those required in project management or software development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started paying attention to this when I was developing recipes for my work. The mental process of figuring out how to veganize a traditional dish requires understanding the functional role each ingredient plays, then finding plant-based alternatives that fulfill those same functions. It's applied chemistry and creative problem-solving combined.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're someone who finds meditation in chopping vegetables or satisfaction in perfecting a technique, you're drawn to the kind of hands-on problem-solving that requires both precision and adaptability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5. Learning new languages&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you find genuine enjoyment in learning languages, not just because you need to for work or travel, but because you love the process itself, you're demonstrating cognitive flexibility that most people lack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Language learning requires you to rewire fundamental patterns in your brain. You're not just memorizing vocabulary. You're learning to think in structures that might organize reality completely differently from your native language.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3583091/#:~:text=Today%2C%20more%20of%20the%20world's,one%20language%20while%20using%20another."&gt;Studies have consistently shown&lt;/a&gt; that bilingual and multilingual individuals have enhanced executive function, better attention control, and improved ability to switch between tasks. The constant practice of inhibiting one language while using another strengthens cognitive control mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But what fascinates me most is the metalinguistic awareness that develops. When you learn how another language works, you start noticing patterns in your own language that were previously invisible. You become aware of language as a system rather than just a transparent medium for thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This kind of pattern recognition and systematic thinking transfers to other domains. People who enjoy language learning tend to be better at recognizing structural similarities across different fields and applying knowledge from one context to another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6. Pursuing photography as a creative practice&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Photography might look like just pointing a camera and clicking, but if you're someone who genuinely loves the craft, you know it's about training yourself to see differently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good photographers develop what's called "photographic eye," which is the ability to recognize visual patterns, anticipate moments, understand how three-dimensional reality will translate to a two-dimensional image, and make split-second compositional decisions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This requires simultaneously processing technical information (light, exposure, focus) while also thinking creatively about framing, storytelling, and emotional impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I spend a lot of time walking around with my camera, and I've noticed that photography has changed how I perceive everything, even when I'm not shooting. I notice light quality, I unconsciously frame scenes, I'm more attuned to decisive moments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That heightened perceptual awareness is a form of intelligence that doesn't show up on traditional tests but affects how you navigate and understand the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you find joy in the challenge of capturing a fleeting moment or composing a compelling image, you're someone whose brain thrives on complex visual processing and aesthetic decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7. Writing for personal expression&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you write regularly, not because you have to but because you genuinely enjoy it, you're engaging in one of the most cognitively demanding activities possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing requires you to translate nebulous thoughts into precise language, organize complex ideas into logical structures, anticipate how a reader will interpret your words, and revise based on that anticipation. You're essentially creating a mental simulation of communication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there's something else happening too. When you write regularly, you're forced to clarify your own thinking. You can't hide fuzzy reasoning behind vague language when you're committing words to page. Writing makes intellectual sloppiness visible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've found that writing about topics forces me to understand them at a deeper level than I would otherwise. The act of explaining something reveals the gaps in my own knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're someone who journals, writes essays, or works on creative projects because you find the process itself satisfying, you're training yourself to think more clearly and communicate more effectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intelligence isn't just about solving math problems or memorizing facts. It's about curiosity, pattern recognition, cognitive flexibility, and the ability to engage deeply with complex systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hobbies on this list require sustained attention, tolerance for difficulty, and genuine intellectual engagement. They're not passive entertainment. They're active cognitive workouts that happen to be enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If several of these activities bring you real joy, not just obligation or the sense that you "should" do them, you're probably operating with cognitive abilities that exceed most people around you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The smartest people I know don't necessarily have the highest test scores or the most degrees. They're the ones who remain genuinely curious, who pursue interests for their own sake, and who find satisfaction in activities that challenge them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your hobbies say a lot about how your brain is wired. If you're drawn to complexity, creativity, and continuous learning, trust that instinct. You're not wasting time. You're becoming smarter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-3637227058"&gt;&lt;p&gt;				 &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong data-start="380" data-end="431"&gt;If You Were a Healing Herb, Which Would You Be?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="380" data-end="651"&gt;Each herb holds a unique kind of magic — soothing, awakening, grounding, or clarifying.&lt;br data-start="521" data-end="524"&gt;This 9-question quiz reveals the healing plant that mirrors your energy right now and what it says about your natural rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="653" data-end="734"&gt;✨ Instant results. Deeply insightful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 			&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:34:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxNZ3hYNE1QMU9xaWE3Znd2TnVHcjRhS2dtX01icGNVbWFZWlRMbndRcXc4cFBhRDVYMFdnMTJNYmhsVmxJVmxjWmNSRGl3TGxTTUlWbW5JWmhSTV9DWHltMmRuVGtmYjlKY3Bqa21MNkEwOUZoUlFYd0h4ekNfby1pcnFCZFZVZVA1aTdqUjA0N0wtYlJWVXQ5dnlJTy1mb0RxNTQ5TEhJRi1pbTVLV3JaV2hSUXgzdXJCOEpwVkNLdw</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，听音乐与降低痴呆风险有关--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/2025/11/13/dementia-risk-music-listen-study/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SDMKFQULSZEYHH5VV5YYE3QDVU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Regularly listening to music is linked to&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;a lower risk of developing dementia, according to a new study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SGFVJER24JFBPOIMBXBRNJQRTQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In the study, &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/epdf/10.1002/gps.70163" target="_blank"&gt;published in October&lt;/a&gt;, researchers looked at data spanning a decade and involving more than 10,000 relatively healthy people, aged 70 and older, in Australia. People who listened to music most days slashed their risk of developing dementia by 39 percent compared with those who did not regularly listen to music, the study found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:12:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxPQkVmSTFTNFEwVXl4VjdUZkQ2eHNxX0RudTcySHdsb2NFQ21ReWEwSW55SXR2QXFZb1h3ZC1pRVFxdm50VmNOUVo1OHJ4THNHLXhIRTFwQnZkQXVGYUN1Wlh2WGRWNHpYY3lONzhWV0hCNE80N21LdTdLbUhOQ0Z4ZC1RRGJjaGdENU51N1N3</guid></item><item><title>CT扫描预计将导致美国各地10万例新癌症- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/ct-scans-predicted-to-result-in-100000-new-cancers-across-the-us</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;More Americans are receiving computed tomography (CT) scans than ever before, and while this technology &lt;a href="https://www.lung.org/blog/ct-scan-saves-lives"&gt;can save lives&lt;/a&gt;, some scientists are concerned that low doses of ionizing radiation could increase  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="181232" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, at an individual level, the theoretical risk of developing cancer from a CT scan is &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/radiation-emitting-products/medical-x-ray-imaging/what-are-radiation-risks-ct"&gt;thought to be very low&lt;/a&gt;, if it exists at all. Patients should not hesitate to undergo these tests if they are considered medically necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the number of CT examinations performed annually in the US has increased by more than 30 percent since 2007, and researchers suggest that unwarranted tests are exposing the population to unnecessary radiation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-are-hacking-bacteria-to-fight-cancer-then-self-destruct"&gt;Scientists Are Hacking Bacteria to Fight Cancer, Then Self-Destruct&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a study published in April, a team in the US and the UK predicted that low levels of ionizing radiation from CT scans could theoretically account for 5 percent of all new cancer diagnoses in the US. CT scans conducted in 2023 could be responsible for an estimated 103,000 future cases of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's based on some assumptions and historical data from high radiation events, but if right, it would put CT scans on par with other significant &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/radioactive-waste-exposed-children-in-missouri-to-cancer-risks-study-finds"&gt;risk factors for cancer&lt;/a&gt;, like &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/heres-why-every-sip-of-alcohol-increases-your-risk-of-cancer"&gt;alcohol consumption&lt;/a&gt;, at least at a population level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"CT is frequently lifesaving, yet its potential harms are often overlooked, and even very small cancer risks will lead to a significant number of future cancers given the tremendous volume of CT use in the United States," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamainternmed.2025.0505"&gt;writes&lt;/a&gt; the international team of analysts, led by epidemiologist Rebecca Smith-Bindman from the University of California, San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of now, these are just theoretical risks, but that doesn't mean they aren't worth considering. While scientists know that &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2203/dose-response.07-013.Brooks"&gt;high doses of radiation cause cancer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6447446/"&gt;conclusive evidence&lt;/a&gt; to link low-level radiation to cancer is lacking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The potential association is &lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/prehospital-and-disaster-medicine/article/risk-of-cancer-from-ct-scans-and-other-sources-of-lowdose-radiation-a-critical-appraisal-of-methodologic-quality/23464B0D825CD456741B77476F9997F7"&gt;mostly based&lt;/a&gt; on long-term studies of atomic bomb survivors and those exposed to nuclear power plant meltdowns. For instance, in a group of &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/cancer/radiation-risk-from-medical-imaging"&gt;25,000 Hiroshima survivors&lt;/a&gt;, who received a dose of ionizing radiation on par with three or more CT scans, there was a slight but significant increase in cancer risk across a lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether those results extend to CT scans remains &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2672242/"&gt;hotly debated&lt;/a&gt;, and the theoretical risks must be weighed against the benefits of this technology, which can now alert patients and doctors to a whole variety of hidden diseases and injuries with very low doses of radiation (about the same amount &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org.au/iheard/can-radiation-from-medical-tests-cause-cancer"&gt;you absorb from your environment&lt;/a&gt; over three years).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_171762" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-171762" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/bethesda-naval-medical-center-80380_1280-642x444.jpg" alt="A patient undergoing a CT scan, with a technician present" class="size-medium wp-image-171762" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/bethesda-naval-medical-center-80380_1280-642x444.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/bethesda-naval-medical-center-80380_1280-600x415.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/bethesda-naval-medical-center-80380_1280-768x532.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/bethesda-naval-medical-center-80380_1280.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-171762" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The theoretical risks of CT scans must be weighed against the benefits. (&lt;a href="https://www.scimex.org/newsfeed/ct-scans-could-be-responsible-for-5-percent-of-new-cancer-diagnoses-every-year#section--reaction"&gt;Bethesda naval medical center, Maryland, Hospital&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Any risk from a CT scan of a sick patient is likely much less than the risk of the underlying disease," &lt;a href="https://w3.aapm.org/media/releases/AAPMPressRelease_2025_AAPMAddressesConcernsfromPublishedStudyonCTRisk_v2.pdf"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; Cynthia McCollough, CT imaging expert and past president of the American Association of Physicists in Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span aria-label="" data-stringify-type="paragraph-break"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;In a &lt;a target="_blank" data-stringify-link="https://www.nih.gov/news-events/news-releases/nih-funded-study-shows-20-percent-reduction-lung-cancer-mortality-low-dose-ct-compared-chest-x-ray?" delay="150" data-sk="tooltip_parent" href="https://www.nih.gov/news-events/news-releases/nih-funded-study-shows-20-percent-reduction-lung-cancer-mortality-low-dose-ct-compared-chest-x-ray?" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;large national trial&lt;/a&gt;, for instance, there was a 20 percent decrease in lung cancer deaths among smokers and ex-smokers who received low-dose CT scans compared to those who only had a chest X-ray.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent predictions on cancer risk are again based on historical tragedies, but compared to previous analyses, they consider more detail on the actual radiation exposure, which can &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/cancer/radiation-risk-from-medical-imaging"&gt;depend on&lt;/a&gt; the type of CT device, the scanning duration, the size of the patient, and the sensitivity of their targeted body part.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The anonymous data comes from 143 hospitals and outpatient facilities across the US, catalogued in the UCSF International CT Dose Registry. Using statistics from 2016 to 2022, researchers predicted 93 million CT examinations were carried out in 2023, on roughly 62 million patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on the associated radiation risks, the team estimates that CT scans in 2023 may be tied to 103,000 future cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"To empirically quantify lifetime risk would require decades-long follow-up studies of very large populations," the authors &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamainternmed.2025.0505"&gt;acknowledge&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, their results suggest that some people may be more susceptible to cancer from low-dose ionizing radiation than others.  Adults receive the vast majority of CT scans, but estimated radiation-induced cancer risks were higher in children and adolescents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_158133" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-158133" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/04/CancerRiskCT-642x368.png" alt="Cancer Risk CT " class="size-medium wp-image-158133" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/04/CancerRiskCT-642x368.png 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/04/CancerRiskCT-724x415.png 724w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/04/CancerRiskCT-768x440.png 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/04/CancerRiskCT-1536x880.png 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/04/CancerRiskCT-600x344.png 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/04/CancerRiskCT.png 1584w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-158133" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The projected number of future cancers (left axis; dark blue and orange circles) against a conservative estimate of cancer incidence (right axis; light blue circles and triangles). &lt;span&gt;(Smith-Bindman et al., &lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;JAMA Intern. Med., &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt;2025)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those receiving CT scans at under one year of age, for instance, seem to have a higher potential lifetime risk for thyroid cancers, and this appears more common among female patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Far more research is needed to confirm if low-dose ionizing radiation actually impacts a person's cancer risk, and how.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Estimated overall cancer risks from CT radiation doses are similarly high in Australian studies," &lt;a href="https://www.scimex.org/newsfeed/ct-scans-could-be-responsible-for-5-percent-of-new-cancer-diagnoses-every-year"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; medical radiation specialist Pradip Deb from RMIT University. She argues it is important to avoid unnecessary CT scans if radiation-free procedures can do the same job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Radiographer Naomi Gibson, President of the Australian Society of Medical Imaging and Radiation Therapy, agreed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although the findings highlight the need for vigilance around long-term radiation exposure, this should not discourage the use of CT imaging when clinically justified," Gibson &lt;a href="https://www.scimex.org/newsfeed/ct-scans-could-be-responsible-for-5-percent-of-new-cancer-diagnoses-every-year"&gt;explained&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In appropriately selected cases, the diagnostic and therapeutic value of CT scans significantly outweighs the potential radiation-associated risks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamainternmed.2025.0505"&gt;&lt;em&gt;JAMA Internal Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in April 2025.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 12:03:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxNNWdKVVNEN1BCMUlpeEZSeDBUX1I0Vk05T21sWUROd0s0V0xGaFowM2k2N1ZvNGp1UXNjOGxPSGdZcDAzdWltSmlNcHFpNFBPQjdjeURsT1VmSVNrcEY2MkFrWXYyYlpOYXhSZFBfa2hRTDRwdkVxMnBac1NZYkZqRUVvS3ZFdFlNcF9vazY1bmtIX2lLeE9sWg</guid></item><item><title>埃塞俄比亚报告疑似病毒性出血热爆发-世卫组织|非洲区域办事处</title><link>https://www.afro.who.int/news/ethiopia-suspected-viral-haemorrhagic-fever-outbreak</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="field field--name-body field--type-text-with-summary field--label-hidden field--item"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Addis Ababa — &lt;/strong&gt;Health authorities in Ethiopia are carrying out further investigations and ramping up response after suspected cases of viral haemorrhagic fever were reported in the country’s South Ethiopia Region. In support, the World Health Organization (WHO) is deploying an initial team of responders and delivering medical supplies to assist in the ongoing efforts to determine the cause of infection and halt further transmission. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, eight suspected cases have been reported. Laboratory testing is ongoing at the Ethiopia Public Health Institute to determine the exact cause. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To support the national authorities, WHO is deploying a multi-disciplinary team of 11 technical officers with experience in responding to viral haemorrhagic fever outbreaks to help strengthen disease surveillance, investigation, laboratory testing, infection prevention and control, clinical care, outbreak response coordination and community engagement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHO is also providing essential supplies including personal protective equipment for health workers and infection-prevention supplies, as well as a rapidly deployable isolation tent to bolster clinical care and management capacity. Additional technical capacity is being mobilized to support the overall response. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHO has also released US$ 300 000 from its Contingency Fund for Emergencies to provide immediate support to the national authorities.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Viral haemorrhagic fevers refer to a group of epidemic prone diseases that are caused by several distinct families of viruses. They include Marburg and Ebola virus diseases, Crimean Congo haemorrhagic fever and Lassa fever. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Specific signs and symptoms vary by the type of viral haemorrhagic fever, but initial signs and symptoms often include marked fever, fatigue, dizziness, muscle aches, loss of strength and exhaustion. All cases of acute viral haemorrhagic fever syndrome whether single or in clusters, should be immediately notified without waiting for the causal agent to be identified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      
        
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WHO | Regional Office for Africa</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNYzhtNm5NWHY1UGRKOXd6RVdLYjc0cjBkYlRiQnNlSU9IZmcwMUQ1YTVqUWcwcm1WV0REbFo2eXpHWUJTdUpXN21sY1J6bWhFd0JoZndRNjJmYm4wbWJsNXlSbHlUUEtvdWRGOE12NFBidXFsbGtZWHV3OUhieEhMd1lYSUVNQlNXakE</guid></item><item><title>城市当局称，在汉堡污水样本中发现了野生形式的脊髓灰质炎-路透社</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/wild-form-polio-found-hamburg-sewage-sample-city-authority-says-2025-11-13/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Reuters</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:16:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0AFBVV95cUxNSDRQU2VldzUwTENiWXA4NndCdlBVQmZjcFdYdWNWcldXQW9SempkNWN4aUpoTTV4ekNLd05BNl9tUVY2T3Q5MFdZcjkyaTlzQTZ1V3dOZVJWaHBUSHFDU2wxZHIwbFdCY01mYTFGTUE3MVltLVdJMEdrb29OZVMwbXNLSm1CS1doWTBWcVZVeVVMc1Y4OXZWRldMcXJ1MTRSeFRyaS1lWlRZSlBLR3Zzb1ZhbmZ3d1ZsRkpsWmpMUHZuX3ZxenlpQTNnRHdfVVFv</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，狼疮可能是由常见的爱泼斯坦-巴尔病毒引起的- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/lupus-cause-epstein-barr-virus-study-rcna243364</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8c79e4" class="body-graf"&gt;One of the most common viruses in the world could be the cause of lupus, an autoimmune disease with wide-ranging symptoms, according to a study published Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f7aa75" class="body-graf"&gt;Until now, lupus was somewhat mysterious: No single root cause of the disease had been found, and there is no designated treatment for it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c74716" class="body-graf"&gt;The research, &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/scitranslmed.ady0210" target="_blank"&gt;published in the journal Science Translational Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, suggests that Epstein-Barr virus — which 95% of people acquire at some point in life — could cause lupus by driving the body to attack its own healthy cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-02666f" class="body-graf"&gt;It adds to mounting evidence that Epstein-Barr is associated with multiple long-term health issues, including other autoimmune conditions. As this evidence stacks up, scientists have accelerated calls for a vaccine that targets the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-735484" class="body-graf"&gt;“If we now better understand how this fastidious virus is responsible for autoimmune diseases, I think it’s time to figure out how to prevent it,” said Dr. Anca Askanase, clinical director of the Lupus Center at Columbia University, who wasn’t involved in the new research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bd42ea" class="body-graf"&gt;In lupus patients, an autoimmune attack can result in extreme fatigue, joint pain and skin rashes. In rare cases, the disease may lead to fatal or life-threatening issues such as kidney damage, or weaken the immune system so the body can’t fight off infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b10a42" class="body-graf"&gt;Scientists have long suspected a link between Epstein-Barr and lupus, but the exact connection had remained elusive. Dr. William Robinson, a co-author of the new study and chief of the division of immunology and rheumatology at Stanford University, said his new findings solve a major piece of that puzzle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-ec1d19" class="body-graf"&gt;“From our perspective, it’s the key, missing mechanistic link,” Robinson said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-6f7c1c" class="body-graf"&gt;“We think it applies to all lupus cases,” he added. Hundreds of thousands of people in the U.S. are living with the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-72aeb5" class="body-graf"&gt;But Hoang Nguyen, assistant vice president of research at the Lupus Research Alliance, said it’s too soon to know if the mechanism is behind every case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-36a76f" class="body-graf"&gt;“Although the evidence is intriguing and promising, more evidence is needed to demonstrate that the link to EBV applies to all lupus,” Nguyen said. The alliance is a private funder of lupus research and contributed grant funding to Robinson’s study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-860ed7" class="body-graf"&gt;An infection withe Epstein-Barr virus does not necessarily cause symptoms, especially among children, though the virus is also the most common cause of mononucleosis (often referred to as mono).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e4721a" class="body-graf"&gt;It's primarily transmitted by saliva from kissing or sharing drinks, food, utensils or toothbrushes. After someone is infected, the virus lingers permanently in the body, where it usually remains inactive — though not always. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3b388f" class="body-graf"&gt;The new study is not the first to tie Epstein-Barr to autoimmune issues. Past research has &lt;a href="https://www.nih.gov/news-events/nih-research-matters/study-suggests-epstein-barr-virus-may-cause-multiple-sclerosis" target="_blank"&gt;linked it to multiple sclerosis&lt;/a&gt;. Though not the sole trigger of MS, the virus may be part of a chain of events that leads to the disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-6ef538" class="body-graf"&gt;Robinson said a pathway similar to the one described in his new study could also lead to other autoimmune diseases like rheumatoid arthritis and Crohn’s disease, but more research is needed to tease that out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e018b2" class="body-graf"&gt;Of course, the vast majority of people who contract Epstein-Barr do not go on to get lupus, MS or any other autoimmune disease. Robinson said it’s possible that only certain strains of Epstein-Barr trigger autoimmune reactions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d9dbd6" class="body-graf"&gt;To determine the causal link between Epstein-Barr and lupus, Robinson and his co-authors focused on B cells — white blood cells that help fight off infections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c0c09a" class="body-graf"&gt;Even in healthy individuals, Epstein-Barr lies dormant in a tiny portion of B cells. But those virus-containing B cells are far more prevalent in lupus patients, who have a 25 times higher share of them, according to the new research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f8731d" class="body-graf"&gt;The study also highlights a type of protein called antinuclear antibodies, which bind to the nucleus of cells and are one of the hallmarks of lupus. The researchers found that Epstein-Barr infects and reprograms B cells to produce antinuclear antibodies that attack the body’s own tissue, thereby causing lupus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d2cba9" class="body-graf"&gt;Robinson said the findings go hand-in-hand with some other theories about what causes lupus. For instance, scientists suspect that a person’s genetics or hormones can predispose them to the disease, as well. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7f2aeb" class="body-graf"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07627-2" target="_blank"&gt;study published last year in the journal Nature&lt;/a&gt; also found that people with lupus have too much of a particular T cell — another type of white blood cell — that’s associated with cell damage and too little of another T cell associated with repair. Robinson said the pathway described in his study could &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/scientists-say-identified-root-cause-lupus-rcna160862" target="_blank"&gt;activate that T cell response&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b7edf1" class="body-graf"&gt;The new research points to a few potential options for lupus treatment, according to Robinson, who is the co-founder of two drug development companies exploring treatments for autoimmune diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-27444c" class="body-graf"&gt;Many of the current medications given to ease lupus symptoms, such as corticosteroids, broadly focus on reducing inflammation. Robinson said future therapeutics could specifically target B cells infected with Epstein-Barr.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bdd93a" class="body-graf"&gt;But an Epstein-Barr vaccine — several of which are in clinical trials — could someday stop infections in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-33bf99" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“Vaccination to protect people against ever being infected by EBV would be the ultimate, fundamental solution,” Robinson said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOeTRZd0ZiX3F6ZU40LVUwN3VPZ2twRlV1Rzh4cWFrbUstMzloSEh6a1dnbHRBUWpmVW42SF9Lazg0aGNlakZoeVoxdHlWMEhKVVFfY0xDNnBXNVVWcGFfUVRiQlp3MzFWSlNJcG5YM25lQkF5RUdOOG9kQThmaFV0Y21XQmJIa0tOZlJFMDdrUnJ3U2pT0gFWQVVfeXFMTnh1UGJXWHg0SXc1YnZzUnZmTmpQUThWZ1FGbXV1cjV3M25FYUd3NEhEc1dhbWRzZDdkX2VjbkUxa1VIZV9sNVpGR2xsbjFCU3dmNHJiNFE</guid></item><item><title>密歇根州神经外科医生分享与更年期相关的鲜为人知的认知风险： “雌激素保护脑细胞免受……” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/michigan-neurosurgeon-shares-lesser-known-cognitive-risk-linked-to-menopause-101763023377236.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storyMainDiv" class="fullStory tfStory current videoStory story__detail storyAf101763023377236 " data-vars-storyid="101763023377236" data-story-section="lifestyle" data-story-subsection="health" data-vars-author="Eshana Saha" data-premium-story="false" data-performance-type="not-set" data-story-title="Michigan neurosurgeon shares lesser-known cognitive risk linked to menopause: ‘Oestrogen protects brain cells from…’"&gt; &lt;p class="htEchoTopPageBanner dHide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="stickyCard"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;h1 class="hdg1"&gt;Michigan neurosurgeon shares lesser-known cognitive risk linked to menopause: ‘Oestrogen protects brain cells from…’&lt;/h1&gt;  &lt;div class="actionDiv flexElm topTime"&gt; &lt;p class="dateTime secTime storyPage"&gt;Published on: Nov 13, 2025 02:44 pm IST &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="googleFollow mHide"&gt; &lt;button class="htEchoShareBarDesk"&gt;&lt;/button&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;h2 class="sortDec"&gt;While common symptoms of menopause like heat flashes, mood swings and fatigue are widely discussed, Dr Jagannath draws attention to how it affects the brain.&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;div class="storyDetails taboola-readmore"&gt; &lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/michigan-neurosurgeon-shares-lesser-known-cognitive-risk-linked-to-menopause-101763023377236.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/menopause" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Menopause"&gt;Menopause &lt;/a&gt;marks a major transition in a woman’s life, often accompanied by symptoms like hot flashes, &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiac-surgeon-shares-7-subtle-signs-of-heart-failure-that-most-people-ignore-until-too-late-fatigue-bloating-more-101762677511972.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="fatigue"&gt;fatigue&lt;/a&gt;, and mood swings. But beyond these well-known changes, menopause also brings subtle yet significant shifts within the brain - ones that are rarely discussed. These neurological effects can influence memory, focus, and long-term cognitive health.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/13/550x309/menopause_1763024180458_1763024180708.jpg" alt="Read more to discover how oestrogen decline affects the brain.(Pixabay)" title="Read more to discover how oestrogen decline affects the brain.(Pixabay)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/13/550x309/menopause_1763024180458_1763024180708.jpg" alt="Read more to discover how oestrogen decline affects the brain.(Pixabay)" title="Read more to discover how oestrogen decline affects the brain.(Pixabay)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Read more to discover how oestrogen decline affects the brain.(Pixabay)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/health-coach-reveals-simple-activity-that-can-reverse-osteopenic-bones-in-menopausal-women-in-just-12-weeks-101762934129173.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Health coach reveals simple activity that can reverse osteopenic bones in menopausal women in just 12 weeks"&gt;Health coach reveals simple activity that can reverse osteopenic bones in menopausal women in just 12 weeks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Jay Jagannathan is a neurosurgeon at the Michigan Neurosurgery Institute, specialising in multidisciplinary neurosurgery and pain management, with over a decade of experience. He is bringing attention to the often-overlooked neurological changes women face during menopause.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; In an Instagram video shared on October 20, the neurosurgeon explains how declining &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/estrogen-progesterone-and-testosterone-key-hormones-and-expert-tips-for-womens-health-to-balance-them-101721220169516.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="oestrogen"&gt;oestrogen &lt;/a&gt;levels during menopause can contribute to cognitive decline, and offers practical tips to reduce the risks.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;The hidden neurological danger of menopause&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When we talk about menopause, the focus is often on hot flashes, mood swings, or declining &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/photos/lifestyle/international-womens-day-2024-special-heres-how-gut-health-helps-in-improving-bone-density-among-women-101709732538284.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="bone density"&gt;bone density&lt;/a&gt; - while the changes happening inside the brain are rarely addressed. Dr Jagannathan discusses the crucial role of oestrogen in cognitive function - and how its decline during menopause can affect the brain. He explains, “Oestrogen isn’t just a reproductive hormone - it’s a neuroprotective shield. It helps regulate blood flow, reduce inflammation, and protect brain cells from stress. So when oestrogen levels drop, that protection weakens.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hidden health risks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to Dr Jagannathan, the decline in oestrogen plays a major role in raising cognitive health risks for women after menopause. Consequently, the likelihood of the following issues rises during and after this stage:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Silent strokes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Memory decline&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Increased risk of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals/neuroscientist-shares-3-major-risk-factors-for-developing-alzheimers-disease-vitamin-deficiency-inflammation-more-101762864342370.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Alzheimer’s"&gt;Alzheimer’s &lt;/a&gt;and cognitive fog&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/13/original/menopause_graphic_1763023653076.png" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Dr Jagannathan highlights 4 ways you can reduce the risk of cognitive decline during menopause.(Image generated via ChatGPT)" title="Dr Jagannathan highlights 4 ways you can reduce the risk of cognitive decline during menopause.(Image generated via ChatGPT)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Dr Jagannathan highlights 4 ways you can reduce the risk of cognitive decline during menopause.(Image generated via ChatGPT)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;How to reduce risks?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The neurosurgeon states, “Your brain health is deeply connected to your hormonal health. And understanding that connection could be what protects you decades down the road.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Jagannathan notes that while oestrogen-related cognitive decline is a biological repercussion of menopause, it can be managed effectively with a few simple lifestyle adjustments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Control blood pressure and cholesterol since your brain’s vessels depend on it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Stay physically and mentally active.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prioritise restorative &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/mumbai-orthopaedic-surgeon-says-women-actually-need-more-sleep-than-men-and-science-backs-it-20-minutes-more-101763017474256.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="sleep"&gt;sleep&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Talk to your doctor about hormone and vascular health because early monitoring matters.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. It is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="recommendedSliderContextual" id="recommendedSliderContextual-101763023377236" data-vars-story_id="101763023377236" data-vars-story_section="lifestyle" data-vars-author="Eshana Saha" data-vars-story_headline="Michigan neurosurgeon shares lesser-known cognitive risk linked to menopause: ‘Oestrogen protects brain cells from…’"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" class="trendTopsSHow" id="trendTopsSHow-101763023377236"&gt; &lt;div class="trendTops"&gt;  &lt;div class="trendInlineSeo"&gt;&lt;p&gt; Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;label class="moreBtn1" for="trendTopsSHow-101763023377236"&gt;&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="followHT trendSeo__1"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="bottomSeoParaEcho1"&gt; &lt;div id="bottomSeoParaEcho"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="mb5 mt5" id="bottomBreadCrumb"&gt; &lt;div class="breadcrumbs"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Home_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/" data-vars-event-cta="News"&gt;News&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Lifestyle_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle" data-vars-event-cta="Lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Health_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle/health" data-vars-event-cta="Health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Michigan neurosurgeon shares lesser-known cognitive risk linked to menopause: ‘Oestrogen protects brain cells from…’ &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="bottomSeoParaEcho pb0"&gt; &lt;label class="moreBtn" for="trendTopsSHow-101763023377236" id="spanSeeLessEcho"&gt;See Less&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;p class="relatedStoryCricket"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="saranyuPlayer" id="saranyu-player"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="relatedStory2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="us-ad align-center mb10 mt10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="htEchoShortsEntryPoint" data-size="enlarged"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="affiliate-shop-now" id="affiliate-shop-now"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 09:14:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3gFBVV95cUxNX0ItN0VNSnVzQ1dFVl9xY0VYQmQzb2VUZ1NJdlhqeEFlRUJ3U0NtWXhnUjNVcmZBTzZBcXVQcW1jcW13V3loV1JUMUVoaDVNSUxtN3ljODRIMFlBTnFOOU90ZEZnUE5SUkxKcWgxcUNFWDdMNHFBX3RNYWpVZEljZVlKTzltX3RpOUstQUhfT3A1X3hzTHZzT1k5d29LaWlkclZvOHlSaHo0UEZQbnJybWk1XzNTZmF2Q2pYRXlZTkZDemFfWHB6ME10VzhyS2xnVEJLcl85M0FVcUNjOWfSAeMBQVVfeXFMTWFKejB6d1V4TkpDMzhQQzJGUmthamlDSHZqME9yYXNMMUc1RVBJNlR2cmFVd2N2MDh3cjRGamxZZ29RZHk2RHcwN3lDWnZib0tEUGVySmdoYXdqcmNPRXdtMXdRb1pxdUE5Ujg3dnhQdWN1VU52OGJFNXFZS3J6cTZUaWRtNVdxXzRmTVpZNEN5TWVNcl9SZkpySDdHT2Vfamw0TURsNlVxX1F3amxCcEpxTDFVaXliclgxRkh0aVZBTmFIdHpEOWxRakZCY05MNEgyZjl4Sk4xUWZTU093ZlYyaTA</guid></item><item><title>去年有123万人死于肺结核，世卫组织称--半岛电视台</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2025/11/13/tuberculosis-kills-1-23-million-people-last-year-who-says</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;header class="article-header"&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Tuberculosis kills 1.23 million people last year, WHO says&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p class="article__subhead"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The UN health agency warns that recent progress in tackling the disease is under threat due to a shortfall in critical aid.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/header&gt;&lt;div class="article-info m--t-20 m--desktop-b-30 m--b-mobile-20"&gt;&lt;div class="article-dates"&gt;&lt;p class="date-simple"&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;Published On 13 Nov 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span aria-hidden="true"&gt;13 Nov 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="rich-share" data-testid="rich-share"&gt;&lt;div class="rich-share__wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="rich-share__button-wrapper"&gt;&lt;button class="rich-share__button row" aria-expanded="false"&gt;&lt;p class="screen-reader-text"&gt;Click here to share on social media&lt;/p&gt;&lt;svg class="icon icon--share2 icon--primary icon--16 " viewbox="0 0 20 16" version="1.1" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;title&gt;share2&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path fill="#000" fill-rule="evenodd" d="M11.688 9.048c-.659 0-1.252.282-1.673.733l-4.92-2.45c.016-.115.028-.232.028-.352 0-.117-.011-.23-.027-.343l4.913-2.423a2.285 2.285 0 0 0 1.68.739C12.964 4.952 14 3.899 14 2.6 14 1.302 12.965.25 11.688.25S9.377 1.302 9.377 2.601c0 .117.01.23.027.343L4.49 5.367a2.285 2.285 0 0 0-1.68-.739C1.536 4.628.5 5.681.5 6.979c0 1.299 1.035 2.35 2.312 2.35.659 0 1.252-.281 1.673-.731l4.92 2.45a2.357 2.357 0 0 0-.029.351c0 1.299 1.035 2.351 2.312 2.351S14 12.698 14 11.399s-1.035-2.35-2.312-2.35Z" clip-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;p class="rich-share__social-text"&gt;Share&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wysiwyg wysiwyg--all-content" aria-live="polite" aria-atomic="true"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tuberculosis deaths have fallen by 3 percent to 1.23 million people in 2024, the World Health Organization (WHO) says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In its annual TB report published on Wednesday, the United Nations health agency also revealed that overall cases of the disease had dropped by almost 2 percent since 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;section class="more-on"&gt;&lt;h2 class="more-on__heading"&gt;Recommended Stories &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;list of 3 items&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;end of list&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p&gt;It marked the first time since the COVID-19 pandemic that TB cases and deaths had declined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2024, a record 8.3 million people accessed TB treatment after being newly diagnosed while treatment success rates rose from 68 to 71 percent, the WHO said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the health agency warned that recent progress in tackling the disease was under threat due to a shortfall in aid. WHO chief Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus said it could “reverse the hard won gains”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, $5.9bn was available for prevention, diagnosis and treatment, far below the annual target of $22bn by 2027.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Declines in the global burden of TB and progress in testing, treatment, social protection and research are all welcome news after years of setbacks, but progress is not victory,” the WHO chief said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The fact that TB continues to claim over a million lives each year despite being preventable and curable is simply unconscionable,” Tedros added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although TB deaths in 2024 were 29 percent lower than those recorded in 2015, the WHO had hoped to reduce this figure by 75 percent by 2025 and 90 percent by 2030.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of deaths could even rise in the years ahead, warned Tereza Kasaeva, director of WHO’s division for tuberculosis, HIV and related infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Long-term cuts to international donor funding could result in up to 2 million additional deaths and 10 million people falling ill with TB between 2025 and 2035,” Kasaeva said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The agency was dealt a significant financial blow when the United States withdrew from it in January, forcing a 21 percent cut to its proposed spending.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decision by US President Donald Trump’s administration to slash foreign aid, particularly from the US Agency for International Development, has also raised fears about global TB treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, critical international aid helped to prevent 3.65 million deaths from the disease, according to the WHO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Al Jazeera</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 08:37:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxQSzl2NmVwVGc1bTVTd0VpV0hlaHJWeGVoV3BDNC1QdTIxMVFKRTBiNkN4eHFUYUtYTUxZTFFLdFR3MGUxZjFCYmluSmFmdVgzeG1HcENMN0FkRmFFMmFzSmtnUEI0UEx6SE1DOEVwbmktTDBCaDkzRUNLSktsX2l5cDBJWFUzY1prX0U1S0Zjcm94MWQ0VEhXTmpDeUhvejhv0gGmAUFVX3lxTE43a2ZlRUhUSmhkTFNQTFBXTGV4WVlXaUM1Q01pTExuY015ankwREMtS1VRMDNEVjhNTk03MDdaUk0yTUZTcTY1X0FwRVE1T3lCZjJ5WEVkRk00cHo3X2V0dVBWNnA4Ylk2QTNYRVFNaFJ6ZGhnMUt0VElsN2U5bi16Q3NPaUw1WFFjVnlaVHJHS0tLZFg4X2lvbUtLQ0owc3RxMHctenc</guid></item><item><title>去年有123万人死于肺结核，世卫组织称--半岛电视台</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2025/11/13/tuberculosis-kills-1-23-million-people-last-year-who-says</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;header class="article-header"&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Tuberculosis kills 1.23 million people last year, WHO says&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p class="article__subhead"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The UN health agency warns that recent progress in tackling the disease is under threat due to a shortfall in critical aid.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/header&gt;&lt;div class="article-info m--t-20 m--desktop-b-30 m--b-mobile-20"&gt;&lt;div class="article-dates"&gt;&lt;p class="date-simple"&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;Published On 13 Nov 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span aria-hidden="true"&gt;13 Nov 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="rich-share" data-testid="rich-share"&gt;&lt;div class="rich-share__wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="rich-share__button-wrapper"&gt;&lt;button class="rich-share__button row" aria-expanded="false"&gt;&lt;p class="screen-reader-text"&gt;Click here to share on social media&lt;/p&gt;&lt;svg class="icon icon--share2 icon--primary icon--16 " viewbox="0 0 20 16" version="1.1" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;title&gt;share2&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path fill="#000" fill-rule="evenodd" d="M11.688 9.048c-.659 0-1.252.282-1.673.733l-4.92-2.45c.016-.115.028-.232.028-.352 0-.117-.011-.23-.027-.343l4.913-2.423a2.285 2.285 0 0 0 1.68.739C12.964 4.952 14 3.899 14 2.6 14 1.302 12.965.25 11.688.25S9.377 1.302 9.377 2.601c0 .117.01.23.027.343L4.49 5.367a2.285 2.285 0 0 0-1.68-.739C1.536 4.628.5 5.681.5 6.979c0 1.299 1.035 2.35 2.312 2.35.659 0 1.252-.281 1.673-.731l4.92 2.45a2.357 2.357 0 0 0-.029.351c0 1.299 1.035 2.351 2.312 2.351S14 12.698 14 11.399s-1.035-2.35-2.312-2.35Z" clip-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;p class="rich-share__social-text"&gt;Share&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wysiwyg wysiwyg--all-content" aria-live="polite" aria-atomic="true"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tuberculosis deaths have fallen by 3 percent to 1.23 million people in 2024, the World Health Organization (WHO) says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In its annual TB report published on Wednesday, the United Nations health agency also revealed that overall cases of the disease had dropped by almost 2 percent since 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;section class="more-on"&gt;&lt;h2 class="more-on__heading"&gt;Recommended Stories &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;list of 3 items&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;end of list&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p&gt;It marked the first time since the COVID-19 pandemic that TB cases and deaths had declined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2024, a record 8.3 million people accessed TB treatment after being newly diagnosed while treatment success rates rose from 68 to 71 percent, the WHO said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the health agency warned that recent progress in tackling the disease was under threat due to a shortfall in aid. WHO chief Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus said it could “reverse the hard won gains”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, $5.9bn was available for prevention, diagnosis and treatment, far below the annual target of $22bn by 2027.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Declines in the global burden of TB and progress in testing, treatment, social protection and research are all welcome news after years of setbacks, but progress is not victory,” the WHO chief said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The fact that TB continues to claim over a million lives each year despite being preventable and curable is simply unconscionable,” Tedros added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although TB deaths in 2024 were 29 percent lower than those recorded in 2015, the WHO had hoped to reduce this figure by 75 percent by 2025 and 90 percent by 2030.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of deaths could even rise in the years ahead, warned Tereza Kasaeva, director of WHO’s division for tuberculosis, HIV and related infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Long-term cuts to international donor funding could result in up to 2 million additional deaths and 10 million people falling ill with TB between 2025 and 2035,” Kasaeva said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The agency was dealt a significant financial blow when the United States withdrew from it in January, forcing a 21 percent cut to its proposed spending.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decision by US President Donald Trump’s administration to slash foreign aid, particularly from the US Agency for International Development, has also raised fears about global TB treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, critical international aid helped to prevent 3.65 million deaths from the disease, according to the WHO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Al Jazeera</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 08:37:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxQSzl2NmVwVGc1bTVTd0VpV0hlaHJWeGVoV3BDNC1QdTIxMVFKRTBiNkN4eHFUYUtYTUxZTFFLdFR3MGUxZjFCYmluSmFmdVgzeG1HcENMN0FkRmFFMmFzSmtnUEI0UEx6SE1DOEVwbmktTDBCaDkzRUNLSktsX2l5cDBJWFUzY1prX0U1S0Zjcm94MWQ0VEhXTmpDeUhvejhv</guid></item><item><title>我是一名明星运动员，但在我因一种几乎每个人都会接触到的常见病毒而瘫痪后，我的梦想破灭了-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15280981/paralyzed-contracting-common-virus-exposed.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Relly Ladner clutched her shin on the soccer field. At just 17, and playing at one of the top soccer academies in the US, she couldn’t afford to take time off, but something felt wrong. Play on, urged her watching coach, and Ladner did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But that evening, a tingling sensation crept up from her ankles to her knees, then her legs went numb. It’s just dehydration, doctors at a busy &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/new-hampshire/index.html" id="mol-e4d6ee90-bfcc-11f0-9676-938fb839d8a8" class=""&gt;New Hampshire&lt;/a&gt; emergency department assured her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the next morning, when Ladner woke up, she couldn’t move her legs at all. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I was terrified,’ she told Daily Mail. ‘It was the worst feeling I have ever experienced.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She was rushed back to the hospital, where doctors tested the reflexes in her knee, only to find her leg didn't move. They then ordered a spinal tap, a test used to check for complications in the body's nerves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Then came the &lt;span&gt;devastating diagnosis: Ladner had Guillain-Barré syndrome (GBS), a rare disorder that affects one in 100,000 people, in which the immune system attacks the nerves, sometimes &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14805541/Pins-needles-sign-fit-healthy-Luke-31-struck-surprisingly-common-condition-left-paralysed.html"&gt;leaving patients permanently paralyzed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and struggling to breathe. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ladner, now 25, said: 'They were unsure if I was ever going to be able to walk again. They said I might never be able to stand and walk by myself again, or play soccer. [But] I was committed to playing soccer, I had planned my whole life around it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was May 2017, and Ladner was planning to attend Dartmouth College to play soccer after high school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Unwilling to accept the prognosis doctors gave her, Ladner worked tirelessly over eight months to regain her ability to move her legs, painstakingly relearning how to climb out of bed, walk, run and, finally, play soccer again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And ever since then, she has never taken her health for granted, becoming a marathon runner and now completing her second New York City marathon earlier this month. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Relly Ladner, now 22 years old and living in New York City, started to suffer a tingling in her legs while playing with her soccer team, shown above, at age 17 years. Ladner is shown by the red circle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ladner said: 'I felt scared. I felt kind of helpless when doctors told me I might never walk again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'But then, at the same time, I felt like, motivated, from that, that it was going to get better, and I was going to defy those odds and that, if anyone was going to be able to do it, it was going to be me.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After receiving her diagnosis of GBS, Ladner's&lt;span&gt; situation worsened.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She told Daily Mail: 'It was spreading quickly [the numbness]. They wanted it to stop, because... it can spread all the way up [your body], you can become paralyzed everywhere, and people have to be on ventilators.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;GBS is a rare autoimmune disorder where immune system cells misfire and target the peripheral nerves in the arms and legs, causing them to stop transmitting signals properly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the early stages, patients feel a tingling or numbing sensation in the affected limbs before losing the ability to move altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is not clear what causes the condition, but doctors say it may be triggered by the immune system misfiring after attacking a common viral infection that the patient may not even know they had, such as the flu, Covid or Epstein Barr Virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Proteins in the viruses are similar to those on nerve cells, scientists say, which can confuse the immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The tingling turned to numbness and, by the next morning, she was no longer able to walk. Ladner was rushed to the hospital, shown, for treatment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This is a rare reaction, however, with only about 3,000 to 6,000 cases diagnosed in the US every year. The disease can strike at any age, but it is slightly more common among older adults. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 80 percent of GBS patients are able to walk independently six months after their diagnosis, while 60 percent fully recover their muscle abilities within a year, according to the &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/guillain-barre-syndrome/diagnosis-treatment/drc-20363006"&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Physicians say many patients recover because of the intensive treatments offered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About five to 10 percent&lt;span&gt; have very delayed or incomplete recovery, suffering from complications including paralysis, while less than two percent die as a result of the condition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In Ladner's case, doctors infused the patient with &lt;/span&gt;immunoglobulin, proteins in the blood that fight infections, from a healthy donor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Although it is not a cure for GBS, physicians say it may help because the healthy plasma could contain substances that neutralize antibodies that are causing the body to attack its own nerves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Eight hours later, Ladner had a second infusion, and said that the numbness then stopped advancing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Along with GBS, she suffered from aspetic meningitis, inflammation of the membranes that cover the brain and spinal cord. This is not caused by GBS, but can be triggered as a result of blood plasma infusions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Despite the odds and concerns she would never walk again, she overcame them and has now run in three marathons. She is pictured above while competing in the New York City marathon this year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As the treatments worked and her numbness started to ease, Ladner, her doctors and her family breathed a sigh of relief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But while the paralysis wasn't advancing anymore, the virus had severely damaged the nerves in her legs, leaving her with almost no movement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She remained in the hospital for several weeks, during which doctors worked to help her gradually regain the ability to climb out of bed and walk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She was then transferred to a rehabilitation facility, where she remained for several more months working with physical therapists, who helped her walk, run, climb and even kick a soccer ball.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She was discharged in January 2018, eight months after her symptoms first emerged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Today, Ladner says her immune system remains 'weak', and that she frequently contracts viruses like the common cold or flu, but that her athletic ability is much improved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As well as returning to the soccer field, she also found a passion for running after moving to New York City.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Joining New York Road Runners, a nonprofit that promotes running to boost health, she has now competed in three marathons and hopes to do more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She completed the Nashville marathon in April last year, and has now run the New York City marathon twice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She still thinks back to her condition, however, fearing that it could return, but also using it to help motivate her to run more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said:&lt;span&gt; 'People always ask me, why am I motivated to run? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;'And I really think that it's my like, having had Guillain-Barré, and having been told that I was never going to... be able to walk again, that motivates me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Because, you know, there was a time when I was laying in a hospital bed unable to walk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'And so, even on the days when I'm like, not motivated, or when the training gets hard...  I think back to a time when I would have wished that I could have been doing what I am doing now. It helps me and pushes me to finish.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 05:16:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxNWFFYVzNpYk9zTWFBVEhfNnMyQTJCSVlFYmZwb0F2R1ltQkxlblhxcmZ0OGJSZEYzRmZ1ZXhIYU5IdUtZX25GUjhHUVdzaEN0OVNDNFFoTWg1OFVyUzRvQmE5Z3ktbTI2VmlyUHA2ZzhadWtXUzkxQW1hck45eW04eFpCMU9EVkh4NTJ1RlA1UTVtMFAtUGxNUHE5RkpSZXJq0gGmAUFVX3lxTE8wZUJ4V2RCMzlsSG03NGhpWlp2TWhXZnhQdGd3SFVULVoza0hmOTg0RDBnVXNpS0p2el9SQ09WeEo0QVZhTzI0UjF6WGhId1p6eUxrck5obmgtNlFZbUU2aHNsbi10T3lDNDNtRTRCbUlTb0ZpVXZrWWc1QlRuMkJIYUhiQ2Z2QmI3LUw4cmFhRHEyNmVUY3RCbVIwdkRtVlFkaWstcUE</guid></item><item><title>告诉《华盛顿邮报》：您是否正在为更年期或围绝经期而苦苦挣扎？ -《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/11/12/menopause-perimenopause-experiences/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="PTNO4LJZ3JAYHNRZC6Z7KDA3YQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The Washington Post wants to hear about your experiences navigating health care with perimenopause and menopause. Do you have questions about hormone therapy? What gaps in the medical system do you think need to be filled and deserve more attention?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GX4CYBKCKFC3HHOUJJCDE7R7HI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Please use the form below to share your experiences with us. While we will not be able to feature most submissions in news coverage, your contributions will help us identify broader issues to cover. In some instances, we will interview you for articles and potentially spotlight your experiences. We will not publish anything you share with us here without first contacting you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 05:08:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxORzNmU09INV95RnkybGhIaHIydHR3MlZyZC1zSjdoNmx5cmdPMXVzWkxETzB5Qk1uTE12UE9mNWhDOVNyMURmeTNOVVlCRVNMVUxQdVZuUFh3ajJDZFJQV2tScGU3TjZrUER0aHZhUmliVHFxdXhPQW5mTEIwbmU1NURRc1RBWl9XNkFMZk1R</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现为什么1型糖尿病在儿童中更糟糕- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cd679yvee91o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Type 1 diabetes is worse in the young - here's why&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-0 fYJjWP"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-11 ljQVMv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-5 xGeVU"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-7bfdb3c2-7 djOqvY"&gt;James Gallagher&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-8 gvcwmG"&gt;Health and science correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7db0/live/45794a20-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7db0/live/45794a20-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7db0/live/45794a20-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7db0/live/45794a20-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7db0/live/45794a20-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7db0/live/45794a20-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7db0/live/45794a20-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7db0/live/45794a20-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Nye family Young girl in a hospital bed wearing a blue bed-shirt. She looks poorly and has a pink dummy in her mouth. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Nye family&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Gracie Nye in hospital when she was first diagnosed with type 1 diabetes&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Scientists have discovered why type 1 diabetes is more severe and aggressive when it develops in young children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Type 1 is caused by the immune system attacking cells in the pancreas that control blood sugar levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The research team showed the pancreas was still developing in childhood, particularly under the age of seven, making it far more vulnerable to damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;They say newly developed drugs could buy patients time for the pancreas to mature, delaying the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Type 1 diabetes affects around 400,000 people in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Gracie, age eight from Merseyside, became suddenly ill on Halloween in 2018. It started as a slight cold, but rapidly escalated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"She went from being a very happy one-year-old, who would go to nursery and dance and sing, to almost dying in less than 48 hours," says dad Gareth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The diagnosis remains the worst part of our life.Suddenly everything we took for granted was 10-20 times harder," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/0156/live/f4171010-bfea-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/0156/live/f4171010-bfea-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0156/live/f4171010-bfea-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/0156/live/f4171010-bfea-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/0156/live/f4171010-bfea-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/0156/live/f4171010-bfea-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/0156/live/f4171010-bfea-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0156/live/f4171010-bfea-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Nye family A family holiday photo including one man, one woman, two girls and a young boy. All of them are smiling. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Nye family&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Nye family, with Gracie wearing pink glasses&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The Nye family had to adapt quickly - keeping on top of everything Gracie had to eat or drink, checking blood sugar levels and giving the hormone insulin to tell her body to absorb the sugar in her blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Gracie now has a glucose monitor and an insulin pump and is "bossing diabetes", says her dad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Gracie's a superstar," he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But why children diagnosed young like Gracie, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00125-020-05115-6" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;especially those under the age of seven&lt;/a&gt;, have a more aggressive disease than those diagnosed in their teenage years or later, has remained a mystery.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The study, published in the journal Science Advances, shows it is down to the development of the beta cells living in the pancreas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;These are the cells that release the hormone insulin when sugar levels rise in the blood after we eat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Researchers at the University of Exeter studied pancreas samples from 250 donors, allowing them to see how the beta cells formed normally as people got older, and in type 1 diabetes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 GunZh"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/c46d/live/d1e3a3c0-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/c46d/live/d1e3a3c0-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c46d/live/d1e3a3c0-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/c46d/live/d1e3a3c0-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/c46d/live/d1e3a3c0-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/c46d/live/d1e3a3c0-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/c46d/live/d1e3a3c0-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c46d/live/d1e3a3c0-bfe8-11f0-99d4-1742bdf50d15.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Diabetes UK A black tray with three rows of seven glass slides that can be placed under a microscope. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Diabetes UK&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Earlier in life these beta cells were shown to exist as small clusters or as individual cells, but as we age they grow in number and mature into larger groups known as Islets of Langerhans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The study was able to see what happened after the immune system turned against a patient's own beta cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Beta cells in small clusters were picked off and destroyed so they never had the chance to mature. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Those in larger islets were still attacked, but were more durable allowing patients to still produce low levels of insulin which reduced the severity of their disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I think this is a really significant finding for type 1 diabetes - this research really sheds light on why the disease is more aggressive in children," Dr Sarah Richardson, from the University of Exeter, told the BBC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She said "the future is much brighter" for children being diagnosed with type 1 now. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This includes the possibility of screening healthy children for the disease and of new immunotherapy drugs to delay it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The UK has licensed teplizumab - an immunotherapy that can stop the immune system attacking beta cells and may be able to give them time to mature - although it is not available on the NHS. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Because we have new drugs for the treatment of type 1 diabetes in children, we hope that these will be able to prevent or delay the onset in those young people," said Dr Richardson.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Missing piece of the puzzle&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The research was part of the Type 1 Diabetes Grand Challenge organised by the Steve Morgan Foundation, Diabetes UK, and Breakthrough T1D. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Rachel Connor, director of research partnerships at Breakthrough T1D, said: "This study gives us a missing piece of the puzzle, explaining why type 1 diabetes progresses so much faster in children than in adults."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Elizabeth Robertson, director of research and clinical at Diabetes UK, said: "Uncovering why type 1 diabetes is so aggressive in young children opens the door to developing new immunotherapies aimed at slowing or stopping the immune attack, potentially giving children more precious years without insulin therapy and, one day, preventing the need for it entirely."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 02:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1RWnN2NEd4N0NkM2tDNk5MaTB1VVFZQXFOck9yWlpGR2gzTS1ZNVlhclBRQXpZZ09YUWhlejhxaTFwMUZWYTZZb1lacWdjeWMtaWk3aXUyT0JpQdIBX0FVX3lxTE9yRnZFNUN3UUt1Z0pBZ2V6MEd3NlBSVzdUQzNHQlBzSFRSTFJFN3llYWhNOWNCOUdHR1VtN01ielJ1Q1RzWWdDdmY1S2JuM1YtNGFHcUwwMXJ6eW8zYkx3</guid></item><item><title>大量同行评审研究显示，新冠疫苗与流感、肾脏疾病有关-华盛顿立场</title><link>https://washingtonstand.com/article/huge-peerreviewed-studies-show-covid-vaccine-linked-to-flu-kidney-disease</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who got the COVID vaccine are significantly more likely to become afflicted with upper respiratory ills like flu, pneumonia, and tuberculosis, as well as acute kidney injury (AKI), according to reports in two international peer-reviewed medical journals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This retrospective cohort study provides robust evidence of dynamic changes in respiratory infection patterns during and after the COVID-19 pandemic in Korea. While COVID-19 vaccination appears to confer partial protection against certain respiratory infections, such as ILI and pertussis, a paradoxical increase in the risk of URI and common cold with higher vaccine doses was noted,” &lt;a href="https://www.ijidonline.com/article/S1201-9712(25)00416-3/fulltext?utm_source=substack&amp;amp;utm_medium=email"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; The International Journal of Infectious Diseases (IJID).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The IJID is a publication of the International Society for Infectious Diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These findings identify the complex interplay between vaccination, immunity, and pathogen ecology in the post-COVID era and highlight the need for tailored public health strategies to manage respiratory infections in a transitioning global health landscape,” the report said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The IJID report was based on analysis of more than 39 million South Koreans, thus making it one of the biggest such analyses ever conducted regarding the effects of the COVID-19 mRNA vaccine. The study found distinct differences in an individual’s susceptibility to multiple illnesses that were seemingly linked to how many vaccines he or she received during the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Non-COVID-19-indicated children who received four or more vaccines, for example, were 559% more likely to subsequently come down with the common cold, 91% more likely to get pneumonia, 83% more likely to have upper respiratory infections (URI), and 35% more likely to get tuberculosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among non-positive older adults, those with four or more vaccines were 58% more likely to have common colds and 57% more likely to develop URIs. Older adults who were positive for COVID-19 were 35% more likely to come down with tuberculosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the second study, published by the &lt;a href="https://www.medsci.org/v22p4483.htm?utm_source=substack&amp;amp;utm_medium=email"&gt;International Journal of Medical Science&lt;/a&gt; (IJMS), 2.9 million American adults were included, evenly divided between those with and without at least one COVID-19 vaccination. The study found that “after adjustment for confounding factors, the incidence of AKI … and dialysis was significantly higher in the vaccinated than in the unvaccinated group. At the one-year follow-up, the number of deaths among vaccinated individuals was 7,693, while the number of deaths among unvaccinated individuals was 7,364.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The case total for AKI was 15,809 among vaccinated individuals, compared to 11,081 unvaccinated individuals. For kidney failure requiring dialysis, the vaccinated case total was 1,513 versus 619 among unvaccinated persons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, the study authors concluded that “COVID-19 vaccination was associated with a higher risk of subsequent renal dysfunction, including AKI and dialysis treatment. The cumulative incidence of renal dysfunction was significantly higher in vaccinated than in unvaccinated patients.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The IJMS is an open-access, peer-reviewed academic journal published by IvySpring International Publisher, which is based in Sydney, Australia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results of the two studies are likely to intensify an often vociferous and intense debate within the medical, political, and scientific communities on the record compiled by the COVID-19 mRNA vaccines hastily developed in response to the deadly virus that killed more than one million Americans between 2020 and 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The COVID-19 virus most likely originated in the Wuhan Institute of Virology in China, according to U.S. intelligence experts, and spread throughout the world from there. Officials with the Chinese Communist Party insisted the virus originated in an open-air meat market near the Wuhan lab as a disease transmitted from bats to humans via food consumption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump was in the middle of his first term in the White House when the COVID-19 outbreak began, and he oversaw the rapid vaccine development that ensued. He lost his re-election bid to former Vice President Joe Biden, and when Trump was returned to the Oval Office for a second term as chief executive in the 2024 election, the White House website added an extensively documented report entitled “Lab Leak: The True Origins of Covid-19.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That report &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/lab-leak-true-origins-of-covid-19/"&gt;notes&lt;/a&gt;, among much else, that “the virus possesses a biological characteristic that is not found in nature” as well as additional facts that point to a lab leak at Wuhan as the most likely source for the outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Stand</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 02:05:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPTkE5WUxGcTZLVldtMDNxaFdtMDVHWTlDRmlpVS1NUUU3QU9vd0x4djFwVDFnRXBwMm9TOXdXa1VJSEpCa3d4dFFBVVJCZ0VZVDNKdHlGa0t3Q2E3aWNfYU5WRGhLOUxqM0l4UDhPUGtnelZZd0prZndrSklJVEU0TS0ya1VUajFWcFV6ai02aDNYb2dyeFRMS3JRR0NBa3F1bFctUjNTUEI4aHk5Mnc</guid></item><item><title>马里科帕县官员报告的麻疹暴露- KTAR新闻92.3 FM</title><link>https://ktar.com/arizona-health-news/measles-exposure/5775236/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story_body"&gt;

                        &lt;p&gt;PHOENIX — The Maricopa County Department of Public Health is warning that a measles exposure was reported at the Mortgage Matchup Center during a concert on Nov. 5.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Nick Staab, Chief Medical Officer for MCDPH, said that the state notified the county that an individual infected with the virus visited the Phoenix area while they were infected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“In cases like this where they were in large public spaces, we typically do a release like this to get the word out to as many people who may have been in that space as possible,” Dr. Staab told &lt;em&gt;KTAR News 92.3 FM&lt;/em&gt; on Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Measles exposure reported at two locations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maricopa County is warning of possible exposures at two venues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mortgage Matchup Center hosted a Tate McRae concert on Nov. 5, the night of one of the exposures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second exposure was at &lt;a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/g1KB4qZZPkoY44BC7" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Home2 Suites by Hilton&lt;/a&gt; at 1&lt;span data-olk-copy-source="MessageBody"&gt;25 Jackson Street in downtown Phoenix Nov. 5-6.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Maricopa County does not have any indication of any additional cases from any of these exposures,” Dr. Staab said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Symptoms of measles include fever, cough, runny nose and a rash that typically starts on the forehead or face and then travels down the body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone who has been exposed may not see symptoms for seven to 12 days after exposure, and some symptoms take 21 days to appear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Measles is one of the most infectious viruses,” Dr. Staab said. “So if you are unimmunized and exposed to someone with measles there is a very high likelihood you will get infected.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Measles is preventable&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the virus is extremely problematic, and can be deadly, there is good news for those concerned about their health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It is vaccine preventable. We have a very safe and effective vaccine for measles. If you are vaccinated, this is a low risk exposure for you,” Dr. Staab added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                        			&lt;div class="textwidget"&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;We want to hear from you.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have a story idea or tip? Pass it along to the KTAR News team &lt;a href="mailto:stories@ktar.com" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
		
                        
                    &lt;/div&gt;

                    
                                            
                    
                    
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KTAR News 92.3 FM</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 01:57:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBUUE4zemVFVjE3X3JkSW54NnRRZTVBd3lfdVFTZDBSckNENXBqeDJxX2VaWWFQWUV6WEhBZmtwSXBabWpGazNCMGZkVWdmVjRRTVN3UTdoMEdFUUtfZ0VqSFJzMjR3NUJDczdMZm1uUQ</guid></item><item><title>世界头号传染病杀手去年宣称有123万人死亡，世卫组织称- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/worlds-top-infectious-killer-claimed-1-23-million-lives-last-year-who-says</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Tuberculosis remains the world's leading infectious killer, claiming an estimated 1.23 million lives last year, the UN health organisation &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/12-11-2025-global-gains-in-tuberculosis-response-endangered-by-funding-challenges"&gt;said Wednesday&lt;/a&gt; as it warned that recent gains made against the disease were fragile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deaths from TB were down three percent from 2023, while cases dropped by nearly two percent, the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-does-the-world-health-organisation-do" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73079" data-postid="181229" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt; (WHO) said in its annual overview.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An estimated 10.7 million people worldwide fell ill with TB in 2024: 5.8 million men, 3.7 million women, and 1.2 million children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/an-ancient-disease-has-reappeared-in-the-us-this-could-be-why"&gt;An Ancient Disease Has Reappeared in The US. This Could Be Why.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A preventable and curable disease, tuberculosis is caused by bacteria that most often affect the lungs. It spreads through the air when people with TB cough, sneeze, or spit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_181235" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-181235" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/tuberculosis_killer_642.jpg" alt="illustration of tuberculosis in the lungs" class="wp-image-181235 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/tuberculosis_killer_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/tuberculosis_killer_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-181235" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Tuberculosis is caused by bacteria infecting the lungs. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MADq345njmo/"&gt;Science Photo Library/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, TB cases and deaths are both declining "for the first time since the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/coronavirus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73041" data-postid="181229" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Covid-19&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pandemic" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73047" data-postid="181229" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;pandemic&lt;/a&gt;", which disrupted services, said Tereza Kasaeva, head of the WHO department for  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/hiv" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73049" data-postid="181229" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;HIV&lt;/a&gt;, TB, hepatitis, and sexually transmitted infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Funding cuts and persistent drivers of the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pandemic" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73047" data-postid="181229" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;epidemic&lt;/a&gt; threaten to undo hard-won gains, but with political commitment, sustained investment, and global solidarity, we can turn the tide and end this ancient killer once and for all," she &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/12-11-2025-global-gains-in-tuberculosis-response-endangered-by-funding-challenges"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Funding for the fight against TB has stagnated since 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, $5.9 billion was available for prevention, diagnosis, and treatment – way off the target of $22 billion annually by 2027.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Heaviest burden in India&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, eight countries accounted for two-thirds of global TB cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were India (25 percent),  Indonesia (10 percent), the Philippines (6.8 percent), China (6.5 percent), Pakistan (6.3 percent), Nigeria (4.8 percent), the Democratic Republic of Congo (3.9 percent), and Bangladesh (3.6 percent).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The five major risk factors driving the epidemic are undernutrition, HIV infection,  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="181229" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, smoking, and alcohol use disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TB is the leading killer of people with HIV, with last year's death toll standing at 150,000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2024, 8.3 million people were newly diagnosed with TB and accessed treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a record high, which the WHO attributed to reaching more of the people who fell ill with the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, treatment success rates rose from 68 percent to 71 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The WHO estimates that timely TB treatment has saved 83 million lives since 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Vaccine research, AI tools&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Declines in the global burden of TB, and progress in testing, treatment, social protection and research are all welcome news after years of setbacks, but progress is not victory," &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/12-11-2025-global-gains-in-tuberculosis-response-endangered-by-funding-challenges"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; WHO chief Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The fact that TB continues to claim over a million lives each year, despite being preventable and curable, is simply unconscionable."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for the pipeline of TB tests, treatments, and vaccines, as of August this year, 63 diagnostic tests were in development and 29 drugs were in  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="181229" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trials&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some 18 candidate vaccines are being tested on humans, including six in Phase III – the final stage before regulatory approval.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The BCG vaccine has long been part of routine childhood immunisation programmes in many countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_181236" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-181236" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/bcg_vaccine_642.jpg" alt="bcg vaccine" class="wp-image-181236 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/bcg_vaccine_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/bcg_vaccine_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-181236" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;BCG vaccine is a part of routine childhood immunisation. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAE8OhAeQrU/"&gt;angelp/Getty Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But despite TB's devastating global impact, no new vaccines have been licensed in over a century, and there are no vaccines for adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peter Sands, head of the Global Fund to Fight  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/hiv" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73049" data-postid="181229" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;AIDS&lt;/a&gt;, TB, and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/malaria" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73073" data-postid="181229" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Malaria&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theglobalfund.org/en/updates/2025/2025-11-12-global-tb-report-progress-is-possible/"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;: "We now have shorter, more effective treatment regimens, improved prevention strategies, and cutting-edge diagnostics, including AI-powered tools that can detect TB faster and more accurately than ever before," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These innovations are transforming how we fight TB, especially in resource-limited settings."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;© &lt;a href="terms-and-conditions"&gt;Agence France-Presse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:33:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPaklKV3JaTjN1VXExVHBGT2E1VWZpRkVlenBGQmxtaElGYzBLV0VycFFMaExRbGZRTzJLYXdPTXdKd1JfWFpJZEk5S3FmamFMWTJYdUxQMmRqNW00d3pCUE53Wm5WeHN5djkzSUF2Sl9TbGwxZ0Z5V2xrbE5DbHduYzdObC1fLUpwTTNwQldURXp4Z3JhSTh5RmMxTzgtcWtwTGFyeGhR</guid></item><item><title>全球评论发现，儿童高血压率在20年内几乎翻了一番--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/nov/12/young-people-high-blood-pressure-doubled-globally-obesity</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The rate of children and teenagers living with high blood pressure globally has nearly doubled because of a toxic combination of unhealthy diets, mass inactivity and soaring levels of obesity, according to the largest review of its kind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Experts said 114 million children who have developed hypertension even before reaching adulthood were facing potentially deadly and lifelong harm, including cardiovascular disease, kidney disease and a myriad of serious health complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The prevalence of high blood pressure in children and teenagers under 19 has increased to 6.2%, rising from 3.2% in the space of just 20 years. The findings, based on a meta analysis of data from 96 studies involving more than 400,000 children across 21 countries, &lt;a href="http://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanchi/article/PIIS2352-4642(25)00281-0/fulltext" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;were published in The Lancet Child and Adolescent Health journal&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The review suggests obesity was a “substantial driver” of the sharp uptick in childhood hypertension, with nearly 19% of those living with obesity affected by the condition, compared with fewer than 3% in children and teenagers considered a healthy weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“The nearly twofold increase in childhood high blood pressure over 20 years should raise alarm bells for healthcare providers and caregivers,” said study author Prof Igor Rudan, the director of the Centre for Global &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/health" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; Research at Edinburgh University’s Usher Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The study also suggests a further 8.2% of children and teenagers have prehypertension, meaning blood pressure levels are higher than normal but do not yet meet the criteria for hypertension.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prehypertension is especially prevalent during adolescence, with rates reaching 11.8% among teenagers, compared with about 7% in younger children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Doctors said blood pressure levels rose sharply in early adolescence, peaking about the age of 14, especially among boys. This underlined the critical importance of regular screening during these critical years, they said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="79b1baab-ee9b-44d1-86a9-75e094011fb9" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":8,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Junk food leads to more children being obese than underweight for first time","elementId":"79b1baab-ee9b-44d1-86a9-75e094011fb9","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/sep/10/junk-food-upf-more-children-obese-than-underweight-unicef"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Children and teenagers with prehypertension are more likely to progress to full hypertension.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Steve Turner, the president of the Royal College of Paediatrics and Child Health, who was not involved with the review, said: “This sharp rise in high blood pressure among children is deeply concerning and largely driven by increasing childhood obesity – an entirely preventable condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“These findings mirror what paediatricians are seeing on the frontline. Children are presenting not only with hypertension, but also other serious conditions linked to obesity such as type 2 diabetes – once unheard of in children – asthma and mental health problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We know that persistent hypertension is a risk factor for an early death due to damage to the cardiovascular system and other organs. Healthy children grow into healthy adults, but with trends like these, I fear that without urgent action we are hurtling towards a public health emergency.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The rate of children and teenagers experiencing high blood pressure globally nearly doubled between 2000 and 2020, according to the meta analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In 2000, about 3.2% of children had hypertension, but by 2020, the prevalence had increased to more than 6.2% of children and teenagers under 19, affecting 114 million young people across the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Study author Dr Peige Song, of Zhejiang University School of Medicine, said the uptick in cases was “driven largely by lifestyle factors such as unhealthy diets, decreased physical activity, and the increasing prevalence of childhood obesity”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Hypertension in children and adolescents has emerged as a substantial public health concern,” she said, adding that parents had a pivotal role in preventing and managing high blood pressure in children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Promoting healthy habits, such as a balanced diet rich in fruits, vegetables and whole grains while minimising salt and sugar intake, can substantially reduce the risk of hypertension. Encouraging regular physical activity and limiting sedentary behaviours, such as excessive screen time, are equally crucial,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“For families with a history of hypertension, regular blood pressure monitoring for children is strongly recommended. Early detection of elevated blood pressure, particularly through home monitoring, can help mitigate the risk of long-term complications.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Bryan Williams, the chief scientific and medical officer of the British Heart Foundation, who was not involved with the review, said he was very concerned about the rise: “Elevated blood pressure in childhood often persists into adulthood, increasing the risk of heart disease and stroke later in life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The good news was that obesity-related high blood pressure could be reversed, he said. But bold action was also needed from governments to prevent so many children from having obesity in the first place. “This includes expanding restrictions on the marketing of unhealthy products and exploring further measures to drive the food industry to make our everyday foods healthier.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:04:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxPbFNWaHY2TlVWNFNWSGZxZ0ZWR3QxcFoyQUxaTHNLa3RRX3VqY3JZNDFKMTh1QmdhX2FNUC1HcjFxTkxxVjFmTmFWeWp2T2lmQndPbFJTZjFoLTBvS3gwTldUaXgzamUyNVdkc3JTNVdFOFVBNXNzTlp2bEV2V2tNV1gtNjUwWWNpUDN3eF9QQkxGWjhhamhvMlp3RnV5cy1yRFhuN3BHYXU</guid></item><item><title>裂孔性疝气是什么感觉？ 50岁以上的女性不应忽视的4个症状-女性世界</title><link>https://www.womansworld.com/wellness/hiatal-hernia-symptoms-and-treatments-for-women-over-50</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body class="post-template-default single single-post postid-591114 single-format-standard post-hiatal-hernia-symptoms-and-treatments-for-women-over-50 theme-womans-world has-custom-search article-format-posts" id="readabilityBody"&gt;
				
			&lt;noscript&gt;
				
			&lt;/noscript&gt;		
				

	
		
	

	




	
			&lt;p class="screen-reader-only"&gt;
							&lt;span id="ac-describe-top-level-help"&gt;
					Use left and right arrow keys to navigate between menu items.				&lt;/span&gt;
							
							&lt;span id="ac-describe-esc-help"&gt;
					Use escape to exit the menu.				&lt;/span&gt;
							
							
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
	
	
&lt;span id="recommended-posts-config" data-config='{"appName":"womansworld_non_commerce_oyml","ab_percentage":50,"tracking_event":"recommended-item-clicked-v2","post_type":"non_commerce","api_key":"AIzaSyARaAm8QMYecpd36kg0Jg7H1TwKE7_DofY","post_id":591114,"blacklist":""}'&gt; &lt;/span&gt;



	







&lt;p class="feedback-wrapper" id="feedback-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="login-body sso-ww" id="login-body"&gt;
	
	
	
	

&lt;div class="login-request" id="login"&gt;
			&lt;svg class="login-logo logo-ww" aria-label="Woman's World" focusable="false" aria-hidden="true" viewbox="0 0 148 20" role="presentation"&gt;
			&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d="m91.8888889 19.3333333h-2.0277778l-1.2222222-13.36111108c-.1111111-1.19444444-.5277778-1.30555555-2.1388889-1.30555555l.2777778-.94444445h8.5555555l-.2777777.94444445c-1.5555556 0-2.1388889.19444444-2.1388889.88888889.0011281.82599168.0474938 1.6513017.1388889 2.47222222l.6111111 6.30555552h.0555555l4.1666667-6.49999997-.2222222-2.5c-.0555556-.47222222-.2222223-.69444444-1.6666667-.69444444l.2777778-.94444445h8.5555552l-.277777.94444445c-1.916667 0-2.416667.13888889-2.416667 1.11111111 0 .55555556.111111 1.25.138889 1.69444444l.555555 7.11111116h.055556l4.638889-7.27777782c.666666-1.13888889 1.055555-1.66666667 1.055555-2.02777778 0-.44444444-.222222-.61111111-2.305555-.61111111l.277778-.94444445h6.361111l-.277778.94444445c-1.805556 0-2.111111.25-2.722222 1.16666667l-8.833334 13.52777774h-2.083333l-.8611111-9.5833333h-.0555556z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m113.777778 8.38888889c2.605007-.02319741 4.739683 2.06183461 4.777778 4.66666671 0 3.5555555-3.194445 6.5555555-6.861112 6.5555555-2.605007.0231974-4.739683-2.0618346-4.777777-4.6666667 0-3.5833333 3.555555-6.55555551 6.861111-6.55555551zm1.5 2.61111111c0-1.27777778-.444445-1.77777778-1.444445-1.77777778-2.194444 0-3.638889 5.44444448-3.638889 7.72222218 0 1.2777778.444445 1.7777778 1.444445 1.7777778 2.111111.0277778 3.638889-4.8888889 3.638889-7.7222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m118.472222 19.3333333 1.944445-7.8333333c.116623-.3974592.181967-.8081944.194444-1.2222222 0-.5277778-.333333-.69444447-1.277778-.75000002l.222223-.80555556 4.5-.08333333-.555556 2.80555551.055556.0555556c.861111-1.91666667 2.361111-3.08333333 3.75-3.08333333.480391-.0127098.945638.16869666 1.290632.50323645.344994.33453978.540627.79398588.542701 1.27454128.015623.4761137-.166656.9374326-.503501 1.2742771-.336844.3368444-.798163.5191237-1.274277.5035007-.916667 0-1.305555-.5-1.305555-1.2777778.000887-.3187878.077026-.6328625.222222-.91666662l-.055556-.05555556c-1.222222.44444448-2.833333 3.27777778-3.833333 6.69444448l-.861111 2.9444444h-3.055556z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m132.416667 15.3055556c-.416667 1.5277777-.694445 2.5-.694445 2.8055555 0 .1944445.138889.3055556.361111.3055556.527778 0 1.277778-1.0833334 2.055556-2.3333334l.638889.4444445c-.722222 1.4444444-1.944445 3.0833333-3.75 3.0833333-1.527778 0-2.277778-1-2.277778-2.3055555 0-1.5277778.388889-2.5833334.944444-4.6666667l1.694445-6.16666668c.088503-.30004703.153514-.60652843.194444-.91666666 0-.52777778-.333333-.69444445-1.583333-.75l.222222-.80555556 5.305556-.08333333z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m142.444444 4.02777778 5.166667-.08333334-3.222222 12.58333336c-.222222.9444444-.305556 1.2222222-.305556 1.5555555 0 .1944445.055556.4444445.333334.4444445.805555 0 1.916666-2.2777778 2.166666-2.8055556l.75.4722222c-.694444 1.6388889-1.805555 3.4166667-3.805555 3.4166667-1.222222 0-2.111111-.8055555-2.333334-2.4166667h-.055555c-.527778 1.3055556-1.694445 2.4166667-3.25 2.4166667-2.25 0-3.972222-1.6388889-3.972222-4.4444444 0-3.9444445 3.416666-6.77777781 6.166666-6.77777781 1.305556 0 2.055556.61111111 2.444445 1.63888891h.055555c.416667-1.72222224 1.083334-3.91666669 1.083334-4.25000002 0-.55555556-.333334-.88888889-1.5-.94444445zm-.5 7.30555552c0-1.44444441-.555555-1.86111108-1.305555-1.86111108-1.555556 0-3.444445 4.49999998-3.444445 7.58333338 0 .9444444.472223 1.4444444 1.138889 1.4444444 1.472223 0 3.611111-3.5 3.611111-7.1666667z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m33.7222222 5.11111111c-2.25 0-1.5277778-1.83333333-4.7222222-2.16666667-2.8888889-.30555555-5.6944444 3.05555556-5.6944444 3.05555556l-8.75 13.25h-2.0833334l-.8611111-9.58333333h-.0555555l-6.16666671 9.58333333h-2.02777778l-1.22222222-13.36111111c-.11111111-1.19444445-.52777778-1.30555556-2.13888889-1.30555556l.27777778-.97222222h8.55555555l-.27777777.94444445c-1.55555556 0-2.13888889.19444444-2.13888889.88888888.00112815.82599169.04749388 1.65130171.13888889 2.47222223l.61111111 6.30555553h.05555555l4.16666668-6.49999998-.2222222-2.5c-.0555556-.47222222-.2222223-.69444444-1.6666667-.69444444l.27777778-.94444445h8.55555552l-.2777777.94444445c-1.9166667 0-2.4166667.13888889-2.4166667 1.11111111 0 .55555555.1111111 1.25.1388889 1.69444444l.5555555 7.11111107h.0555556l4.6388889-7.27777773s4.0833333-6.86111111 10.2777778-6.91666667c5.0833333.02777778 4.6666666 4.86111111 2.4166666 4.86111111z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m26.6944444 8.27777778c2.6144808-.02004059 4.7518163 2.08001582 4.7777778 4.69444442 0 3.5555556-3.1944444 6.5555556-6.8611111 6.5555556-2.6144807.0200406-4.7518162-2.0800158-4.7777778-4.6944445 0-3.5833333 3.5555556-6.55555552 6.8611111-6.55555552zm1.5 2.63888892c0-1.27777781-.4444444-1.77777781-1.4444444-1.77777781-2.1944444 0-3.6388889 5.44444441-3.6388889 7.72222221 0 1.2777778.4444445 1.7777778 1.4444445 1.7777778 2.1111111 0 3.6388888-4.8888889 3.6388888-7.7222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m31.2777778 19.25 1.8611111-7.0555556c.3888889-1.4444444.4444444-1.8611111.4444444-2.1111111 0-.41666663-.1944444-.5833333-1.2777777-.63888886l.2222222-.80555555 4.4444444-.08333333c-.1388889.5-.2777778 1.41666666-.5555555 2.41666664l.0555555.0555556c1.0833334-1.72222224 2.0833334-2.69444447 3.7222222-2.69444447 1.6944445 0 2.3611112 1.08333334 2.3888889 2.72222227h.0555556c1.0555555-1.69444449 2.1944444-2.72222227 3.8055555-2.72222227 1.3611112 0 2.5833334 1.27777778 2.5833334 3.05555557 0 1.7777778-1.8055556 4.9722222-1.8055556 6.2777778 0 .3055555.1111111.4444444.3333334.4444444.6111111 0 1.75-1.8055555 1.9444444-2.2777778l.7222222.4444445c-.8055555 1.5-2.0277778 3.2777778-3.9444444 3.2777778-1 0-2.0833334-.6944445-2.0833334-2.4166667 0-2.0277778 1.9166667-5.3055556 1.9166667-6.6666667.0227162-.2100288-.0469496-.4195642-.1909018-.57417953s-.3479839-.23905139-.5590982-.231376c-1.3055555 0-3.1111111 3.33333333-4.3611111 8.08333333l-.4166667 1.5555556h-3.1388889l1.8611112-6.9444445c.2086249-.6724026.3664759-1.3595186.4722222-2.0555555.0194795-.1723714-.0426735-.34394811-.1680291-.46385348s-.299524-.17437514-.4708598-.14725768c-1.3055556 0-3.2777778 3.19444446-4.8055556 9.63888886h-3.0555555z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m62 8.5-2 8.1111111c-.1036623.4296284-.1779085.8658253-.2222222 1.3055556 0 .1944444.0555555.4166666.3055555.4166666.8611111 0 1.9722223-2.0833333 2.8333334-2.4444444l.75.4166667c-1.3611111 1.3333333-2.4166667 3.2222222-4.5 3.2222222-1.2777778 0-2.0555556-.8611111-2.2777778-2.4166667h-.0555556c-.9166666 1.4166667-1.8055555 2.4166667-3.4444444 2.4166667-1.9444445 0-4.0555556-1.2222222-4.0555556-4.3888889 0-3.4722222 3.2222223-6.83333334 6.4166667-6.83333334 1.4166667 0 2.0833333.75 2.4444444 1.80555554h.0555556l.3611111-1.58333332h3.3888889zm-5.7222222.97222222c-2.0833334 0-3.4166667 5.05555558-3.4166667 7.22222218 0 1.1388889.3611111 1.6388889 1.1388889 1.6388889 2.0277778 0 3.6944444-4.5 3.6944444-6.8888889 0-1.3333333-.5-1.97222218-1.4166666-1.97222218z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m74.2222222 8.88888889c.8888889-.47222222 2.0277778-1 2.0833334-2.16666667-.1526535.04739195-.312738.06622543-.4722223.05555556-.6944444 0-1.1111111-.52777778-1.1111111-1.19444445-.0097931-.3664445.1295472-.72117485.3861237-.98298767.2565766-.26181281.6084199-.40829022.9749874-.40592999 1.0555556 0 1.6111111.77780655 1.6111111 1.77780655 0 1.77777778-1.6944444 2.94444445-3.1944444 3.52777778-.6111111-.05555556-.2777778-.61111111-.2777778-.61111111z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m73.5555556 18.3333333c-.6944445.6944445-1.5 1.1666667-2.5277778 1.1666667s-2.1944445-.6388889-2.1944445-2.3333333c0-1.8055556 2-5.1666667 2-6.6944445.0280553-.2358712-.0536058-.4715817-.2215676-.63954351-.1679617-.16796178-.4036723-.24962286-.6395435-.22156758-1.3611111 0-3.2222222 2.94444449-4.3611111 7.33333329l-.5833333 2.3055556h-3.2222222l1.8888888-6.8611111c.25-.9444445.6111112-2 .6111112-2.3055556 0-.41666663-.1666667-.5833333-1.3055556-.63888886l.2222222-.80555555 4.5833334-.08333333c-.1388889.55555555-.3055556 1.41666666-.5 2.22222224l.0555555.0555555c.9722222-1.30555552 1.9722222-2.49999997 3.7222222-2.49999997s2.8055556 1.41666667 2.8055556 3.05555557c0 1.8055555-1.9166667 5.1944444-1.9166667 6.2777778 0 .2222222.0833334.4444444.4166667.4444444-.0277778-.0555555 1.6111111-.9166667 1.1666667.2222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m80.1111111 8.27777778c3.2777778 0 4.2222222 1.41666666 4.2222222 2.30555552 0 1.0277778-.5277777 1.5555556-1.6388889 1.5555556-.9166666 0-1.5555555-.5277778-1.5555555-1.3055556 0-1.0833333.9722222-1.13888886.9722222-1.22222219s-.6666667-.41666667-1.8333333-.41666667c-1.1666667 0-2.3055556.69444445-2.3055556 1.66666666 0 2.0277778 5.7222222 1.6666667 5.7222222 5.1944445 0 2.1111111-2.3055555 3.8611111-6.25 3.8611111-2.1666666 0-4.3055555-.9722223-4.3055555-2.9444445 0-.9722222.6944444-1.6111111 1.8333333-1.6111111.8160985-.025586 1.5049253.6017385 1.5555556 1.4166667 0 1.2777778-1.1666667 1.4444444-1.1666667 1.5277778 0 .3611111.8055556.7222222 2.25.7222222 1.9166667 0 2.9166667-.8888889 2.9166667-1.5833334 0-2.4444444-5.6388889-1.8333333-5.6388889-5.4444444.0277778-2.22222222 2.3888889-3.72222222 5.2222222-3.72222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;
		&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;p class="login-body__title"&gt;Sign In&lt;/p&gt;
	
	&lt;div class="login-form__wrapper"&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="social-login"&gt;
	&lt;p class="social-login__title"&gt;Sign &lt;b class="title--sign-in"&gt;In&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b class="title--sign-up"&gt;Up&lt;/b&gt; with your social account&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;button name="googleSignUpButton" class="btn google-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;
		&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 256 262" preserveaspectratio="xMidYMid"&gt;
			&lt;path d="M255.878 133.451c0-10.734-.871-18.567-2.756-26.69H130.55v48.448h71.947c-1.45 12.04-9.283 30.172-26.69 42.356l-.244 1.622 38.755 30.023 2.685.268c24.659-22.774 38.875-56.282 38.875-96.027" fill="#4285F4"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M130.55 261.1c35.248 0 64.839-11.605 86.453-31.622l-41.196-31.913c-11.024 7.688-25.82 13.055-45.257 13.055-34.523 0-63.824-22.773-74.269-54.25l-1.531.13-40.298 31.187-.527 1.465C35.393 231.798 79.49 261.1 130.55 261.1" fill="#34A853"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M56.281 156.37c-2.756-8.123-4.351-16.827-4.351-25.82 0-8.994 1.595-17.697 4.206-25.82l-.073-1.73L15.26 71.312l-1.335.635C5.077 89.644 0 109.517 0 130.55s5.077 40.905 13.925 58.602l42.356-32.782" fill="#FBBC05"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M130.55 50.479c24.514 0 41.05 10.589 50.479 19.438l36.844-35.974C195.245 12.91 165.798 0 130.55 0 79.49 0 35.393 29.301 13.925 71.947l42.211 32.783c10.59-31.477 39.891-54.251 74.414-54.251" fill="#EA4335"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
		&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Google&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;














	&lt;button name="amazonSignUpButton" class="btn amazon-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;
		&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 175 181" version="1.1" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;
			&lt;defs&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;
			&lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;
				&lt;g fill="#000"&gt;
					&lt;path d="M153.507609,149.082589 C154.515676,148.678569 155.38932,148.577566 156.128569,148.779576 C156.867818,148.981586 157.237437,149.570773 157.237437,150.547154 C157.237437,151.523535 156.733411,152.651407 155.725344,153.930804 C154.851687,155.00819 153.373211,156.47274 151.289874,158.324498 C149.206536,160.176256 145.997572,162.465667 141.662886,165.192801 C137.3282,167.919936 132.590358,170.411354 127.449219,172.667132 C122.308079,174.922909 115.990957,176.875643 108.497662,178.525391 C101.004367,180.175138 93.2927738,181 85.3626502,181 C77.3653221,181 69.368114,179.956298 61.370786,177.868862 C53.3734579,175.781426 46.3506996,173.205837 40.3023002,170.14202 C34.2539008,167.078203 28.457605,163.57675 22.913239,159.637556 C17.3688729,155.698362 12.9166457,152.163241 9.5564238,149.032087 C6.19620193,145.900933 3.3736579,142.954999 1.08870702,140.194196 C0.551071524,139.588167 0.215054377,139.032648 0.0806455023,138.527623 C-0.0537633725,138.022598 -0.0201616578,137.618584 0.181451654,137.315569 C0.383064967,137.012554 0.651878684,136.77688 0.987900871,136.608538 C1.32392306,136.440196 1.71034278,136.372861 2.14717162,136.406529 C2.58400046,136.440197 2.97042018,136.591703 3.30644237,136.861049 C16.2096944,144.739437 26.2902088,150.328295 33.548288,153.62779 C59.6908142,165.47904 86.5385842,168.509144 114.092404,162.718192 C126.861247,160.024726 139.999517,155.479571 153.507609,149.082589 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
					&lt;path d="M174.374483,137.467076 C175.113731,138.544462 175.197736,140.884376 174.626498,144.486886 C174.05526,148.089397 173.097611,151.540348 171.753523,154.839844 C169.468572,160.428785 166.612426,164.603595 163.185,167.364397 C162.042524,168.30711 161.16888,168.610121 160.56404,168.273437 C159.9592,167.936754 159.9592,167.128727 160.56404,165.84933 C161.975333,162.819181 163.470609,158.728541 165.049913,153.577288 C166.629218,148.426035 166.847629,145.109754 165.705153,143.628348 C165.369131,143.156992 164.848305,142.769812 164.142658,142.466797 C163.437011,142.163782 162.529765,141.961775 161.420892,141.86077 C160.312019,141.759765 159.320768,141.675596 158.44711,141.608259 C157.573453,141.540922 156.397393,141.540922 154.918895,141.608259 C153.440398,141.675596 152.381944,141.742931 151.743501,141.810268 C151.105059,141.877605 150.063406,141.978608 148.618511,142.113281 C147.173615,142.247955 146.417577,142.31529 146.350372,142.31529 C145.947146,142.382627 145.510323,142.433129 145.039892,142.466797 C144.569461,142.500465 144.199842,142.534133 143.931025,142.567801 C143.662207,142.60147 143.376592,142.635137 143.074172,142.668806 C142.771752,142.702474 142.53654,142.719308 142.368529,142.719308 L141.360468,142.719308 C141.259661,142.719308 141.158856,142.702474 141.058049,142.668806 C140.957243,142.635137 140.890039,142.584636 140.856437,142.517299 L140.705228,142.214286 C140.302001,141.136899 141.881282,139.790187 145.443117,138.174107 C149.004952,136.558028 152.465929,135.547993 155.826151,135.143973 C158.917555,134.672617 162.54654,134.638949 166.713215,135.042969 C170.87989,135.446989 173.43362,136.255016 174.374483,137.467076 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
					&lt;path d="M134.656859,92.7220982 C134.656859,94.8095342 135.110482,96.9642746 136.017742,99.1863839 C136.925002,101.408493 138.000256,103.361227 139.243539,105.044643 C140.486821,106.728059 141.746885,108.276779 143.023769,109.690848 C144.300654,111.104918 145.40951,112.182288 146.350372,112.922991 L147.660852,114.03404 L124.777856,136.65904 C122.089678,134.167584 119.435143,131.625664 116.81417,129.033203 C114.193197,126.440742 112.244297,124.471175 110.967413,123.124442 L109.052096,121.104353 C108.312847,120.36365 107.472804,119.252612 106.531942,117.771205 C103.978174,121.744067 100.702006,125.195019 96.7033423,128.124163 C92.7046783,131.053307 88.4204597,133.191214 83.8505579,134.537946 C79.2806562,135.884679 74.5764161,136.659039 69.7376966,136.861049 C64.8989771,137.063059 60.2787414,136.356035 55.8768507,134.739955 C51.4749601,133.123876 47.5267586,130.918634 44.0321278,128.124163 C40.5374971,125.329692 37.7485548,121.525229 35.6652172,116.710658 C33.5818796,111.896088 32.5402265,106.425068 32.5402265,100.297433 C32.5402265,94.6411548 33.4810745,89.4563108 35.3627987,84.7427455 C37.244523,80.0291803 39.6638465,76.1068795 42.6208417,72.9757254 C45.5778369,69.8445714 49.1564196,67.0501425 53.3566969,64.5923549 C57.5569742,62.1345673 61.6731843,60.2155017 65.7054505,58.8351004 C69.7377168,57.4546992 74.1059397,56.2931595 78.8102503,55.3504464 C83.5145609,54.4077334 87.5299658,53.7848787 90.8565855,53.4818638 C94.1832051,53.1788489 97.5265758,52.9600081 100.886798,52.8253348 L100.886798,39.9977679 C100.886798,35.6208859 100.181162,32.3551075 98.7698684,30.2003348 C96.4849176,26.6314926 92.4191101,24.8470982 86.572324,24.8470982 C86.1690974,24.8470982 85.6146691,24.880766 84.9090225,24.9481027 C84.2033759,25.0154393 82.8425065,25.4194531 80.8263734,26.1601562 C78.8102402,26.9008594 76.9285442,27.89406 75.1812288,29.1397879 C73.4339135,30.3855159 71.5522174,32.3887511 69.5360843,35.1495536 C67.5199512,37.9103561 65.9070689,41.1424666 64.697389,44.8459821 L35.0603803,42.1188616 C35.0603803,38.0786628 35.799618,34.0721925 37.2781156,30.0993304 C38.7566133,26.1264682 41.0079281,22.3220048 44.0321278,18.6858259 C47.0563275,15.049647 50.6853127,11.8512043 54.9191923,9.09040179 C59.1530718,6.32959929 64.2437316,4.12435721 70.1913243,2.47460938 C76.138917,0.824861543 82.5400437,0 89.3948963,0 C96.11534,0 102.19725,0.841695452 107.64081,2.52511161 C113.084369,4.20852776 117.435791,6.27909857 120.695207,8.73688616 C123.954622,11.1946737 126.676361,13.9891026 128.860505,17.1202567 C131.044649,20.2514107 132.556726,23.1468431 133.396782,25.8066406 C134.236837,28.4664382 134.656859,30.9410228 134.656859,33.2304688 L134.656859,92.7220982 Z M66.9151244,94.843192 C66.9151244,100.634144 69.2672444,105.111963 73.971555,108.276786 C78.4070479,111.239598 83.0776862,111.98029 87.9836102,110.498884 C93.6287829,108.815468 97.4593784,104.674326 99.4755115,98.0753348 C100.416374,95.0451857 100.886798,91.6447361 100.886798,87.8738839 L100.886798,71.5111607 C96.9217358,71.645834 93.1919455,72.0498478 89.6973147,72.7232143 C86.202684,73.3965807 82.6241014,74.5244527 78.9614595,76.1068638 C75.2988177,77.689275 72.3754685,80.0796901 70.1913243,83.2781808 C68.0071801,86.4766715 66.9151244,90.3316367 66.9151244,94.843192 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
				&lt;/g&gt;
			&lt;/g&gt;
		&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Amazon&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;

	&lt;button name="appleSignUpButton" class="btn apple-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;

                &lt;span&gt;&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 170 170" version="1.1"&gt;
    &lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;
        &lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;
            &lt;path d="m150.37 130.25c-2.45 5.66-5.35 10.87-8.71 15.66-4.58 6.53-8.33 11.05-11.22 13.56-4.48 4.12-9.28 6.23-14.42 6.35-3.69 0-8.14-1.05-13.32-3.18-5.197-2.12-9.973-3.17-14.34-3.17-4.58 0-9.492 1.05-14.746 3.17-5.262 2.13-9.501 3.24-12.742 3.35-4.929 0.21-9.842-1.96-14.746-6.52-3.13-2.73-7.045-7.41-11.735-14.04-5.032-7.08-9.169-15.29-12.41-24.65-3.471-10.11-5.211-19.9-5.211-29.378 0-10.857 2.346-20.221 7.045-28.068 3.693-6.303 8.606-11.275 14.755-14.925s12.793-5.51 19.948-5.629c3.915 0 9.049 1.211 15.429 3.591 6.362 2.388 10.447 3.599 12.238 3.599 1.339 0 5.877-1.416 13.57-4.239 7.275-2.618 13.415-3.702 18.445-3.275 13.63 1.1 23.87 6.473 30.68 16.153-12.19 7.386-18.22 17.731-18.1 31.002 0.11 10.337 3.86 18.939 11.23 25.769 3.34 3.17 7.07 5.62 11.22 7.36-0.9 2.61-1.85 5.11-2.86 7.51zm-31.26-123.01c0 8.1021-2.96 15.667-8.86 22.669-7.12 8.324-15.732 13.134-25.071 12.375-0.119-0.972-0.188-1.995-0.188-3.07 0-7.778 3.386-16.102 9.399-22.908 3.002-3.446 6.82-6.3113 11.45-8.597 4.62-2.2516 8.99-3.4968 13.1-3.71 0.12 1.0831 0.17 2.1663 0.17 3.2409z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
        &lt;/g&gt;
    &lt;/g&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Apple&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;

	&lt;p class="social-login__legal"&gt;We won't post to any of your accounts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

	
	&lt;div class="login-register" id="register"&gt;
					&lt;svg class="login-logo logo-ww" aria-label="Woman's World" focusable="false" aria-hidden="true" viewbox="0 0 148 20" role="presentation"&gt;
				&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d="m91.8888889 19.3333333h-2.0277778l-1.2222222-13.36111108c-.1111111-1.19444444-.5277778-1.30555555-2.1388889-1.30555555l.2777778-.94444445h8.5555555l-.2777777.94444445c-1.5555556 0-2.1388889.19444444-2.1388889.88888889.0011281.82599168.0474938 1.6513017.1388889 2.47222222l.6111111 6.30555552h.0555555l4.1666667-6.49999997-.2222222-2.5c-.0555556-.47222222-.2222223-.69444444-1.6666667-.69444444l.2777778-.94444445h8.5555552l-.277777.94444445c-1.916667 0-2.416667.13888889-2.416667 1.11111111 0 .55555556.111111 1.25.138889 1.69444444l.555555 7.11111116h.055556l4.638889-7.27777782c.666666-1.13888889 1.055555-1.66666667 1.055555-2.02777778 0-.44444444-.222222-.61111111-2.305555-.61111111l.277778-.94444445h6.361111l-.277778.94444445c-1.805556 0-2.111111.25-2.722222 1.16666667l-8.833334 13.52777774h-2.083333l-.8611111-9.5833333h-.0555556z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m113.777778 8.38888889c2.605007-.02319741 4.739683 2.06183461 4.777778 4.66666671 0 3.5555555-3.194445 6.5555555-6.861112 6.5555555-2.605007.0231974-4.739683-2.0618346-4.777777-4.6666667 0-3.5833333 3.555555-6.55555551 6.861111-6.55555551zm1.5 2.61111111c0-1.27777778-.444445-1.77777778-1.444445-1.77777778-2.194444 0-3.638889 5.44444448-3.638889 7.72222218 0 1.2777778.444445 1.7777778 1.444445 1.7777778 2.111111.0277778 3.638889-4.8888889 3.638889-7.7222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m118.472222 19.3333333 1.944445-7.8333333c.116623-.3974592.181967-.8081944.194444-1.2222222 0-.5277778-.333333-.69444447-1.277778-.75000002l.222223-.80555556 4.5-.08333333-.555556 2.80555551.055556.0555556c.861111-1.91666667 2.361111-3.08333333 3.75-3.08333333.480391-.0127098.945638.16869666 1.290632.50323645.344994.33453978.540627.79398588.542701 1.27454128.015623.4761137-.166656.9374326-.503501 1.2742771-.336844.3368444-.798163.5191237-1.274277.5035007-.916667 0-1.305555-.5-1.305555-1.2777778.000887-.3187878.077026-.6328625.222222-.91666662l-.055556-.05555556c-1.222222.44444448-2.833333 3.27777778-3.833333 6.69444448l-.861111 2.9444444h-3.055556z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m132.416667 15.3055556c-.416667 1.5277777-.694445 2.5-.694445 2.8055555 0 .1944445.138889.3055556.361111.3055556.527778 0 1.277778-1.0833334 2.055556-2.3333334l.638889.4444445c-.722222 1.4444444-1.944445 3.0833333-3.75 3.0833333-1.527778 0-2.277778-1-2.277778-2.3055555 0-1.5277778.388889-2.5833334.944444-4.6666667l1.694445-6.16666668c.088503-.30004703.153514-.60652843.194444-.91666666 0-.52777778-.333333-.69444445-1.583333-.75l.222222-.80555556 5.305556-.08333333z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m142.444444 4.02777778 5.166667-.08333334-3.222222 12.58333336c-.222222.9444444-.305556 1.2222222-.305556 1.5555555 0 .1944445.055556.4444445.333334.4444445.805555 0 1.916666-2.2777778 2.166666-2.8055556l.75.4722222c-.694444 1.6388889-1.805555 3.4166667-3.805555 3.4166667-1.222222 0-2.111111-.8055555-2.333334-2.4166667h-.055555c-.527778 1.3055556-1.694445 2.4166667-3.25 2.4166667-2.25 0-3.972222-1.6388889-3.972222-4.4444444 0-3.9444445 3.416666-6.77777781 6.166666-6.77777781 1.305556 0 2.055556.61111111 2.444445 1.63888891h.055555c.416667-1.72222224 1.083334-3.91666669 1.083334-4.25000002 0-.55555556-.333334-.88888889-1.5-.94444445zm-.5 7.30555552c0-1.44444441-.555555-1.86111108-1.305555-1.86111108-1.555556 0-3.444445 4.49999998-3.444445 7.58333338 0 .9444444.472223 1.4444444 1.138889 1.4444444 1.472223 0 3.611111-3.5 3.611111-7.1666667z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m33.7222222 5.11111111c-2.25 0-1.5277778-1.83333333-4.7222222-2.16666667-2.8888889-.30555555-5.6944444 3.05555556-5.6944444 3.05555556l-8.75 13.25h-2.0833334l-.8611111-9.58333333h-.0555555l-6.16666671 9.58333333h-2.02777778l-1.22222222-13.36111111c-.11111111-1.19444445-.52777778-1.30555556-2.13888889-1.30555556l.27777778-.97222222h8.55555555l-.27777777.94444445c-1.55555556 0-2.13888889.19444444-2.13888889.88888888.00112815.82599169.04749388 1.65130171.13888889 2.47222223l.61111111 6.30555553h.05555555l4.16666668-6.49999998-.2222222-2.5c-.0555556-.47222222-.2222223-.69444444-1.6666667-.69444444l.27777778-.94444445h8.55555552l-.2777777.94444445c-1.9166667 0-2.4166667.13888889-2.4166667 1.11111111 0 .55555555.1111111 1.25.1388889 1.69444444l.5555555 7.11111107h.0555556l4.6388889-7.27777773s4.0833333-6.86111111 10.2777778-6.91666667c5.0833333.02777778 4.6666666 4.86111111 2.4166666 4.86111111z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m26.6944444 8.27777778c2.6144808-.02004059 4.7518163 2.08001582 4.7777778 4.69444442 0 3.5555556-3.1944444 6.5555556-6.8611111 6.5555556-2.6144807.0200406-4.7518162-2.0800158-4.7777778-4.6944445 0-3.5833333 3.5555556-6.55555552 6.8611111-6.55555552zm1.5 2.63888892c0-1.27777781-.4444444-1.77777781-1.4444444-1.77777781-2.1944444 0-3.6388889 5.44444441-3.6388889 7.72222221 0 1.2777778.4444445 1.7777778 1.4444445 1.7777778 2.1111111 0 3.6388888-4.8888889 3.6388888-7.7222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m31.2777778 19.25 1.8611111-7.0555556c.3888889-1.4444444.4444444-1.8611111.4444444-2.1111111 0-.41666663-.1944444-.5833333-1.2777777-.63888886l.2222222-.80555555 4.4444444-.08333333c-.1388889.5-.2777778 1.41666666-.5555555 2.41666664l.0555555.0555556c1.0833334-1.72222224 2.0833334-2.69444447 3.7222222-2.69444447 1.6944445 0 2.3611112 1.08333334 2.3888889 2.72222227h.0555556c1.0555555-1.69444449 2.1944444-2.72222227 3.8055555-2.72222227 1.3611112 0 2.5833334 1.27777778 2.5833334 3.05555557 0 1.7777778-1.8055556 4.9722222-1.8055556 6.2777778 0 .3055555.1111111.4444444.3333334.4444444.6111111 0 1.75-1.8055555 1.9444444-2.2777778l.7222222.4444445c-.8055555 1.5-2.0277778 3.2777778-3.9444444 3.2777778-1 0-2.0833334-.6944445-2.0833334-2.4166667 0-2.0277778 1.9166667-5.3055556 1.9166667-6.6666667.0227162-.2100288-.0469496-.4195642-.1909018-.57417953s-.3479839-.23905139-.5590982-.231376c-1.3055555 0-3.1111111 3.33333333-4.3611111 8.08333333l-.4166667 1.5555556h-3.1388889l1.8611112-6.9444445c.2086249-.6724026.3664759-1.3595186.4722222-2.0555555.0194795-.1723714-.0426735-.34394811-.1680291-.46385348s-.299524-.17437514-.4708598-.14725768c-1.3055556 0-3.2777778 3.19444446-4.8055556 9.63888886h-3.0555555z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m62 8.5-2 8.1111111c-.1036623.4296284-.1779085.8658253-.2222222 1.3055556 0 .1944444.0555555.4166666.3055555.4166666.8611111 0 1.9722223-2.0833333 2.8333334-2.4444444l.75.4166667c-1.3611111 1.3333333-2.4166667 3.2222222-4.5 3.2222222-1.2777778 0-2.0555556-.8611111-2.2777778-2.4166667h-.0555556c-.9166666 1.4166667-1.8055555 2.4166667-3.4444444 2.4166667-1.9444445 0-4.0555556-1.2222222-4.0555556-4.3888889 0-3.4722222 3.2222223-6.83333334 6.4166667-6.83333334 1.4166667 0 2.0833333.75 2.4444444 1.80555554h.0555556l.3611111-1.58333332h3.3888889zm-5.7222222.97222222c-2.0833334 0-3.4166667 5.05555558-3.4166667 7.22222218 0 1.1388889.3611111 1.6388889 1.1388889 1.6388889 2.0277778 0 3.6944444-4.5 3.6944444-6.8888889 0-1.3333333-.5-1.97222218-1.4166666-1.97222218z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m74.2222222 8.88888889c.8888889-.47222222 2.0277778-1 2.0833334-2.16666667-.1526535.04739195-.312738.06622543-.4722223.05555556-.6944444 0-1.1111111-.52777778-1.1111111-1.19444445-.0097931-.3664445.1295472-.72117485.3861237-.98298767.2565766-.26181281.6084199-.40829022.9749874-.40592999 1.0555556 0 1.6111111.77780655 1.6111111 1.77780655 0 1.77777778-1.6944444 2.94444445-3.1944444 3.52777778-.6111111-.05555556-.2777778-.61111111-.2777778-.61111111z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m73.5555556 18.3333333c-.6944445.6944445-1.5 1.1666667-2.5277778 1.1666667s-2.1944445-.6388889-2.1944445-2.3333333c0-1.8055556 2-5.1666667 2-6.6944445.0280553-.2358712-.0536058-.4715817-.2215676-.63954351-.1679617-.16796178-.4036723-.24962286-.6395435-.22156758-1.3611111 0-3.2222222 2.94444449-4.3611111 7.33333329l-.5833333 2.3055556h-3.2222222l1.8888888-6.8611111c.25-.9444445.6111112-2 .6111112-2.3055556 0-.41666663-.1666667-.5833333-1.3055556-.63888886l.2222222-.80555555 4.5833334-.08333333c-.1388889.55555555-.3055556 1.41666666-.5 2.22222224l.0555555.0555555c.9722222-1.30555552 1.9722222-2.49999997 3.7222222-2.49999997s2.8055556 1.41666667 2.8055556 3.05555557c0 1.8055555-1.9166667 5.1944444-1.9166667 6.2777778 0 .2222222.0833334.4444444.4166667.4444444-.0277778-.0555555 1.6111111-.9166667 1.1666667.2222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m80.1111111 8.27777778c3.2777778 0 4.2222222 1.41666666 4.2222222 2.30555552 0 1.0277778-.5277777 1.5555556-1.6388889 1.5555556-.9166666 0-1.5555555-.5277778-1.5555555-1.3055556 0-1.0833333.9722222-1.13888886.9722222-1.22222219s-.6666667-.41666667-1.8333333-.41666667c-1.1666667 0-2.3055556.69444445-2.3055556 1.66666666 0 2.0277778 5.7222222 1.6666667 5.7222222 5.1944445 0 2.1111111-2.3055555 3.8611111-6.25 3.8611111-2.1666666 0-4.3055555-.9722223-4.3055555-2.9444445 0-.9722222.6944444-1.6111111 1.8333333-1.6111111.8160985-.025586 1.5049253.6017385 1.5555556 1.4166667 0 1.2777778-1.1666667 1.4444444-1.1666667 1.5277778 0 .3611111.8055556.7222222 2.25.7222222 1.9166667 0 2.9166667-.8888889 2.9166667-1.5833334 0-2.4444444-5.6388889-1.8333333-5.6388889-5.4444444.0277778-2.22222222 2.3888889-3.72222222 5.2222222-3.72222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;
			&lt;/svg&gt;
				&lt;p class="login-body__title" id="titleheader"&gt;Sign Up&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;span class="login-registration-cta"&gt;Create a free account to access exclusive content, play games, solve puzzles, test your pop-culture knowledge and receive special offers.&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;span class="already-have-acc"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a id="signin-already-have-account" class="signin-already-have-account" role="button" name="Login" tabindex="0"&gt;Login&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
		
		
		&lt;div class="social-login"&gt;
	&lt;p class="social-login__title"&gt;Sign &lt;b class="title--sign-in"&gt;In&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b class="title--sign-up"&gt;Up&lt;/b&gt; with your social account&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;button name="googleSignUpButton" class="btn google-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;
		&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 256 262" preserveaspectratio="xMidYMid"&gt;
			&lt;path d="M255.878 133.451c0-10.734-.871-18.567-2.756-26.69H130.55v48.448h71.947c-1.45 12.04-9.283 30.172-26.69 42.356l-.244 1.622 38.755 30.023 2.685.268c24.659-22.774 38.875-56.282 38.875-96.027" fill="#4285F4"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M130.55 261.1c35.248 0 64.839-11.605 86.453-31.622l-41.196-31.913c-11.024 7.688-25.82 13.055-45.257 13.055-34.523 0-63.824-22.773-74.269-54.25l-1.531.13-40.298 31.187-.527 1.465C35.393 231.798 79.49 261.1 130.55 261.1" fill="#34A853"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M56.281 156.37c-2.756-8.123-4.351-16.827-4.351-25.82 0-8.994 1.595-17.697 4.206-25.82l-.073-1.73L15.26 71.312l-1.335.635C5.077 89.644 0 109.517 0 130.55s5.077 40.905 13.925 58.602l42.356-32.782" fill="#FBBC05"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M130.55 50.479c24.514 0 41.05 10.589 50.479 19.438l36.844-35.974C195.245 12.91 165.798 0 130.55 0 79.49 0 35.393 29.301 13.925 71.947l42.211 32.783c10.59-31.477 39.891-54.251 74.414-54.251" fill="#EA4335"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
		&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Google&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;














	&lt;button name="amazonSignUpButton" class="btn amazon-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;
		&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 175 181" version="1.1" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;
			&lt;defs&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;
			&lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;
				&lt;g fill="#000"&gt;
					&lt;path d="M153.507609,149.082589 C154.515676,148.678569 155.38932,148.577566 156.128569,148.779576 C156.867818,148.981586 157.237437,149.570773 157.237437,150.547154 C157.237437,151.523535 156.733411,152.651407 155.725344,153.930804 C154.851687,155.00819 153.373211,156.47274 151.289874,158.324498 C149.206536,160.176256 145.997572,162.465667 141.662886,165.192801 C137.3282,167.919936 132.590358,170.411354 127.449219,172.667132 C122.308079,174.922909 115.990957,176.875643 108.497662,178.525391 C101.004367,180.175138 93.2927738,181 85.3626502,181 C77.3653221,181 69.368114,179.956298 61.370786,177.868862 C53.3734579,175.781426 46.3506996,173.205837 40.3023002,170.14202 C34.2539008,167.078203 28.457605,163.57675 22.913239,159.637556 C17.3688729,155.698362 12.9166457,152.163241 9.5564238,149.032087 C6.19620193,145.900933 3.3736579,142.954999 1.08870702,140.194196 C0.551071524,139.588167 0.215054377,139.032648 0.0806455023,138.527623 C-0.0537633725,138.022598 -0.0201616578,137.618584 0.181451654,137.315569 C0.383064967,137.012554 0.651878684,136.77688 0.987900871,136.608538 C1.32392306,136.440196 1.71034278,136.372861 2.14717162,136.406529 C2.58400046,136.440197 2.97042018,136.591703 3.30644237,136.861049 C16.2096944,144.739437 26.2902088,150.328295 33.548288,153.62779 C59.6908142,165.47904 86.5385842,168.509144 114.092404,162.718192 C126.861247,160.024726 139.999517,155.479571 153.507609,149.082589 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
					&lt;path d="M174.374483,137.467076 C175.113731,138.544462 175.197736,140.884376 174.626498,144.486886 C174.05526,148.089397 173.097611,151.540348 171.753523,154.839844 C169.468572,160.428785 166.612426,164.603595 163.185,167.364397 C162.042524,168.30711 161.16888,168.610121 160.56404,168.273437 C159.9592,167.936754 159.9592,167.128727 160.56404,165.84933 C161.975333,162.819181 163.470609,158.728541 165.049913,153.577288 C166.629218,148.426035 166.847629,145.109754 165.705153,143.628348 C165.369131,143.156992 164.848305,142.769812 164.142658,142.466797 C163.437011,142.163782 162.529765,141.961775 161.420892,141.86077 C160.312019,141.759765 159.320768,141.675596 158.44711,141.608259 C157.573453,141.540922 156.397393,141.540922 154.918895,141.608259 C153.440398,141.675596 152.381944,141.742931 151.743501,141.810268 C151.105059,141.877605 150.063406,141.978608 148.618511,142.113281 C147.173615,142.247955 146.417577,142.31529 146.350372,142.31529 C145.947146,142.382627 145.510323,142.433129 145.039892,142.466797 C144.569461,142.500465 144.199842,142.534133 143.931025,142.567801 C143.662207,142.60147 143.376592,142.635137 143.074172,142.668806 C142.771752,142.702474 142.53654,142.719308 142.368529,142.719308 L141.360468,142.719308 C141.259661,142.719308 141.158856,142.702474 141.058049,142.668806 C140.957243,142.635137 140.890039,142.584636 140.856437,142.517299 L140.705228,142.214286 C140.302001,141.136899 141.881282,139.790187 145.443117,138.174107 C149.004952,136.558028 152.465929,135.547993 155.826151,135.143973 C158.917555,134.672617 162.54654,134.638949 166.713215,135.042969 C170.87989,135.446989 173.43362,136.255016 174.374483,137.467076 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
					&lt;path d="M134.656859,92.7220982 C134.656859,94.8095342 135.110482,96.9642746 136.017742,99.1863839 C136.925002,101.408493 138.000256,103.361227 139.243539,105.044643 C140.486821,106.728059 141.746885,108.276779 143.023769,109.690848 C144.300654,111.104918 145.40951,112.182288 146.350372,112.922991 L147.660852,114.03404 L124.777856,136.65904 C122.089678,134.167584 119.435143,131.625664 116.81417,129.033203 C114.193197,126.440742 112.244297,124.471175 110.967413,123.124442 L109.052096,121.104353 C108.312847,120.36365 107.472804,119.252612 106.531942,117.771205 C103.978174,121.744067 100.702006,125.195019 96.7033423,128.124163 C92.7046783,131.053307 88.4204597,133.191214 83.8505579,134.537946 C79.2806562,135.884679 74.5764161,136.659039 69.7376966,136.861049 C64.8989771,137.063059 60.2787414,136.356035 55.8768507,134.739955 C51.4749601,133.123876 47.5267586,130.918634 44.0321278,128.124163 C40.5374971,125.329692 37.7485548,121.525229 35.6652172,116.710658 C33.5818796,111.896088 32.5402265,106.425068 32.5402265,100.297433 C32.5402265,94.6411548 33.4810745,89.4563108 35.3627987,84.7427455 C37.244523,80.0291803 39.6638465,76.1068795 42.6208417,72.9757254 C45.5778369,69.8445714 49.1564196,67.0501425 53.3566969,64.5923549 C57.5569742,62.1345673 61.6731843,60.2155017 65.7054505,58.8351004 C69.7377168,57.4546992 74.1059397,56.2931595 78.8102503,55.3504464 C83.5145609,54.4077334 87.5299658,53.7848787 90.8565855,53.4818638 C94.1832051,53.1788489 97.5265758,52.9600081 100.886798,52.8253348 L100.886798,39.9977679 C100.886798,35.6208859 100.181162,32.3551075 98.7698684,30.2003348 C96.4849176,26.6314926 92.4191101,24.8470982 86.572324,24.8470982 C86.1690974,24.8470982 85.6146691,24.880766 84.9090225,24.9481027 C84.2033759,25.0154393 82.8425065,25.4194531 80.8263734,26.1601562 C78.8102402,26.9008594 76.9285442,27.89406 75.1812288,29.1397879 C73.4339135,30.3855159 71.5522174,32.3887511 69.5360843,35.1495536 C67.5199512,37.9103561 65.9070689,41.1424666 64.697389,44.8459821 L35.0603803,42.1188616 C35.0603803,38.0786628 35.799618,34.0721925 37.2781156,30.0993304 C38.7566133,26.1264682 41.0079281,22.3220048 44.0321278,18.6858259 C47.0563275,15.049647 50.6853127,11.8512043 54.9191923,9.09040179 C59.1530718,6.32959929 64.2437316,4.12435721 70.1913243,2.47460938 C76.138917,0.824861543 82.5400437,0 89.3948963,0 C96.11534,0 102.19725,0.841695452 107.64081,2.52511161 C113.084369,4.20852776 117.435791,6.27909857 120.695207,8.73688616 C123.954622,11.1946737 126.676361,13.9891026 128.860505,17.1202567 C131.044649,20.2514107 132.556726,23.1468431 133.396782,25.8066406 C134.236837,28.4664382 134.656859,30.9410228 134.656859,33.2304688 L134.656859,92.7220982 Z M66.9151244,94.843192 C66.9151244,100.634144 69.2672444,105.111963 73.971555,108.276786 C78.4070479,111.239598 83.0776862,111.98029 87.9836102,110.498884 C93.6287829,108.815468 97.4593784,104.674326 99.4755115,98.0753348 C100.416374,95.0451857 100.886798,91.6447361 100.886798,87.8738839 L100.886798,71.5111607 C96.9217358,71.645834 93.1919455,72.0498478 89.6973147,72.7232143 C86.202684,73.3965807 82.6241014,74.5244527 78.9614595,76.1068638 C75.2988177,77.689275 72.3754685,80.0796901 70.1913243,83.2781808 C68.0071801,86.4766715 66.9151244,90.3316367 66.9151244,94.843192 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
				&lt;/g&gt;
			&lt;/g&gt;
		&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Amazon&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;

	&lt;button name="appleSignUpButton" class="btn apple-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;

                &lt;span&gt;&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 170 170" version="1.1"&gt;
    &lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;
        &lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;
            &lt;path d="m150.37 130.25c-2.45 5.66-5.35 10.87-8.71 15.66-4.58 6.53-8.33 11.05-11.22 13.56-4.48 4.12-9.28 6.23-14.42 6.35-3.69 0-8.14-1.05-13.32-3.18-5.197-2.12-9.973-3.17-14.34-3.17-4.58 0-9.492 1.05-14.746 3.17-5.262 2.13-9.501 3.24-12.742 3.35-4.929 0.21-9.842-1.96-14.746-6.52-3.13-2.73-7.045-7.41-11.735-14.04-5.032-7.08-9.169-15.29-12.41-24.65-3.471-10.11-5.211-19.9-5.211-29.378 0-10.857 2.346-20.221 7.045-28.068 3.693-6.303 8.606-11.275 14.755-14.925s12.793-5.51 19.948-5.629c3.915 0 9.049 1.211 15.429 3.591 6.362 2.388 10.447 3.599 12.238 3.599 1.339 0 5.877-1.416 13.57-4.239 7.275-2.618 13.415-3.702 18.445-3.275 13.63 1.1 23.87 6.473 30.68 16.153-12.19 7.386-18.22 17.731-18.1 31.002 0.11 10.337 3.86 18.939 11.23 25.769 3.34 3.17 7.07 5.62 11.22 7.36-0.9 2.61-1.85 5.11-2.86 7.51zm-31.26-123.01c0 8.1021-2.96 15.667-8.86 22.669-7.12 8.324-15.732 13.134-25.071 12.375-0.119-0.972-0.188-1.995-0.188-3.07 0-7.778 3.386-16.102 9.399-22.908 3.002-3.446 6.82-6.3113 11.45-8.597 4.62-2.2516 8.99-3.4968 13.1-3.71 0.12 1.0831 0.17 2.1663 0.17 3.2409z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
        &lt;/g&gt;
    &lt;/g&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Apple&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;

	&lt;p class="social-login__legal"&gt;We won't post to any of your accounts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	

&lt;/div&gt;

		
			
	














		

				

		&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Woman's World</author><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxOZEl0dDUyZ1BVd0JYTE5hamRMeG55MV9zejhKd3JpcHpyc1VLRGc2b2tLZk9MOTY2QmJRVThDNGhmdVlrNFV1TW5fV29KUzA4RUJKaDFOMVIyXzFUUm9PVThZYXpIMFd1ajd2ekQyNmd3bUdDSWxwTHMtY1VybVFZN3VtUDBRaFdtT1Z2NlphOGlfQ2RoVk04</guid></item><item><title>儿童高血压发病率在20年内几乎翻了一番- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/11/12/health/hypertension-rates-children-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5fggj000x26qgfklo2d6v@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Global rates of hypertension, or &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/10/health/childhood-obesity-cognitive-decline-wellness"&gt;high blood pressure, in childhood&lt;/a&gt; and adolescence have nearly doubled since 2000, putting more kids at risk for poor health later in life.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge7900083b6nsaiqi8jn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “In 2000, about 3.4% of boys and 3% of girls had hypertension. By 2020, those numbers had risen to 6.5% and 5.8% respectively,” said Dr. Peige Song, a researcher from the School of Public Health at Zhejiang University School of Medicine in China. Song is one of the authors of a study describing the findings that published Wednesday in the journal The Lancet Child and Adolescent Health.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge7900093b6n6ea4r93c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Children who have hypertension could be at greater risk later on of developing heart disease –– &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/fastats/leading-causes-of-death.htm" target="_blank"&gt;the No. 1 cause of death&lt;/a&gt; in the United States, said Dr. Mingyu Zhang, assistant professor of medicine at Harvard Medical School and Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center. He was not involved in the research.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000a3b6nd46b1zll@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The good news is that this is a modifiable risk,” Song said in an email. “With better screening, earlier detection, and a stronger focus on prevention, especially around healthy weight and nutrition, we can intervene before complications arise.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000b3b6n4hcld71t@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The rise in hypertension in children is likely due to many factors.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000c3b6nu1288h8z@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Childhood obesity is a significant risk factor, because it is associated with factors like insulin resistance, inflammation and vascular function, Song said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000d3b6n52urp9lc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dietary factors such as consuming high levels of sodium and ultraprocessed food can also contribute to hypertension risk, as well as poor sleep quality, stress and genetic predisposition, she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000e3b6nz52l7v5e@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Many children also get less movement than past generations and spend more time on sedentary activities, like screen use, which may be affecting risk, she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000f3b6npefll77w@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We are also starting to know that other factors, including environmental pollutants, can contribute,” Zhang added.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw7fvby00023b6n82iayngg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Zhang served as senior author on &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/06/12/health/pfas-blood-pressure-teens-wellness" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;a previous study&lt;/a&gt; that showed a connection between prebirth exposure to chemicals called PFAS — a class of about 15,000 human-made compounds linked to cancers, endocrine-related conditions and developmental issues in children — and childhood hypertension. Short for perfluoroalkyl and polyfluoroalkyl substances, PFAS are sometimes called “forever chemicals” because they don’t fully break down in the environment.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000g3b6nnzu0m8du@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The biggest takeaway of this research for families is not to assume high blood pressure is only a problem for adults, Song said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000h3b6ntmk3wskw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            If you are worried about your child’s risk for obesity or hypertension, pressure, shame and restriction are not the best approaches.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000i3b6ng2y4iswg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Instead, focus on increasing healthy behaviors in a happy way, said Jill Castle, a pediatric dietitian in Massachusetts, in &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/08/13/health/kids-size-health-wellness"&gt;a previous CNN article&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000j3b6nrto53sp5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The goal of the food pillar is really to embrace flexibility with food and to emphasize foods that are highly nutritious and … to allow foods also that might be minimally nutritious within the diet in ways that can be fully enjoyed and flexible,” Castle said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000k3b6nlzirsnbi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Try to prioritize sitting down as a family for meals and avoid labeling foods as “good” or “bad,” said Castle, author of “&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Kids-Thrive-Every-Size-Between/dp/152352183X" target="_blank"&gt;Kids Thrive at Every Size&lt;/a&gt;.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000l3b6nbgm4zqvu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The clean plate club or rewarding with sweets — they might work in the moment, but they don’t do a good job of establishing the self-trust and an intuitive, good relationship with food as kids grow up,” Castle said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000m3b6n5jerqgql@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The study didn’t just track rates in the United States. Instead, researchers analyzed data from 96 studies across 21 countries.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000n3b6nqooncpgr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Another important consideration the study team made is how blood pressure differs in and outside the doctor’s office. Some children might have normal blood pressure at home, but a higher reading in the office, while others might have a lower blood pressure in the office than they normally would.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000o3b6ng9l747cf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            By including data from both office visits and at-home blood pressure readings, the researchers were able to include hypertension rates that are “masked,” or wouldn’t be caught in a doctor’s visit, Zhang said. Masked hypertension was found to be the most common kind, according to the data.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000p3b6n8hf6cjkc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This is important because it means that many children with true hypertension could go undetected if we rely only on office blood pressure readings,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhw5ge79000q3b6nmhrf70r3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The result show that one reading may not be enough, and there may be a need for more scalable solutions for better monitoring and care of hypertension around the world, Song added.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmhw5goqk000v3b6nry9b47ha@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note_elevate inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    Get inspired by a weekly roundup on living well, made simple. Sign up for &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/newsletters/life-but-better?source=nl-acq_article"&gt;CNN’s Life, But Better newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for information and tools designed to improve your well-being.
&lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 23:30:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTFBqeWdZdmdzVGM5TDUtSno4bG1heEl1TllPckhMTnlKbXFNWHVBcDlVMGtPVWlwamUxTlNjazlna3FlVUgyYllqd19wQVJGUDJGcVVkNTNIWjNjOTZhdHRXOFowcFV1Y1B4ang0UmxkZWs0TVBhRDZoQUlScTJpUG8</guid></item></channel></rss>