<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>便宜的每日补充剂似乎可以增强老年人的大脑功能- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/cheap-daily-supplement-appears-to-boost-brain-function-in-older-adults</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;What's good for your aging gut may also be good for your aging brain. A first-of-its-kind study in twins found that taking daily protein and prebiotic supplements can improve memory test scores in people over age 60.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Published early last year, the findings are food for thought, especially as the same visual memory and learning test is used to detect &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/losing-your-sense-of-smell-may-be-an-early-sign-of-alzheimers"&gt;early signs of Alzheimer's disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The double-blind trial tested two inexpensive plant-fiber prebiotics that are available over the counter in many countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/probiotics-vs-prebiotics-whats-the-difference-and-do-you-need-both"&gt;Prebiotics are non-digestible consumables&lt;/a&gt; that help stimulate &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-people-in-your-life-are-sharing-their-gut-microbes-with-you"&gt;our gut microbes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/117-year-old-womans-diet-could-help-us-all-live-longer"&gt;117-Year-Old Woman's Diet Could Help Us All Live Longer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the supplements was &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Inulin"&gt;inulin&lt;/a&gt;, a dietary fiber in the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fructan"&gt;fructan&lt;/a&gt; class. The other, &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fructooligosaccharide"&gt;fructooligosaccharide&lt;/a&gt; (FOS), is a plant carbohydrate often used as a natural low-calorie sweetener.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below for a summary of the research:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To look into how these supplements affect &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-reveals-critical-age-when-your-thinking-begins-to-decline"&gt;the aging brain&lt;/a&gt;, researchers at King's College London enrolled 36 pairs of twins, all at least 60 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each duo was randomly split: one twin received a daily prebiotic mixed into protein powder, while the other received a  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-a-placebo" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="102371" data-postid="182065" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;placebo&lt;/a&gt; powder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The twins who unknowingly took inulin or FOS generally scored higher on a cognitive test three months later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, the daily fiber supplements were linked to subtle changes in the gut microbiome between twins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-181305" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-600x315.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The beneficial &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/microbiology/articles/10.3389/fmicb.2016.00925/full"&gt;Bifidobacterium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, for instance, were more plentiful in those taking inulin or FOS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies on mice suggest &lt;em&gt;Bifidobacterium&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.jafc.3c00652"&gt;reduces cognitive deficits&lt;/a&gt; by regulating gut-brain connections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are excited to see these changes in just 12 weeks. This holds huge promise for enhancing brain health and memory in our aging population," &lt;a href="https://www.kcl.ac.uk/news/daily-fibre-supplement-improves-older-brain-12-weeks"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; Mary Ni Lochlainn, a geriatric medicine researcher at King's College London, when the findings were published in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Unlocking the secrets of the gut-brain axis could offer new approaches for living more healthily for longer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;King's College is home to the United Kingdom's largest adult twin registry, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/identical-twins-mystery-when-1-has-dementia-both-face-a-shorter-life"&gt;twin studies are highly valuable&lt;/a&gt; when it comes to differentiating between &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/identical-twins-can-have-significant-iq-differences-shock-study-reveals"&gt;the effect of genetics and the environment&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pair-of-twins-raised-in-different-countries-reveal-significantly-different-cognitive-abilities"&gt;on human health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_182714" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-182714" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/gut_microbiome_with_inset_642.jpg" alt="Diagram of human intestines in the background, with gut bacteria shown in a circle at the foreground" class="size-full wp-image-182714" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/gut_microbiome_with_inset_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/gut_microbiome_with_inset_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-182714" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The microbes in each person's gut make up their individual microbiome. (Science Photo Library/Canva)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/nutritionreviews/article/77/2/81/5237462?login=false#127953545"&gt;Past studies on rodents&lt;/a&gt; suggest that high-fiber supplements, like inulin and FOS, can 'feed' the colon's microbiome, allowing 'good' bacteria to thrive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of these bacterial players are &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.jafc.3c00652"&gt;also linked&lt;/a&gt; to improved cognitive function in both mice and &lt;a href="https://content.iospress.com/articles/journal-of-alzheimers-disease/jad200488"&gt;humans&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/massive-study-pinpoints-specific-gut-bacteria-linked-to-alzheimers"&gt;Evidence for the close relationship&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/evidence-piles-up-linking-parkinson-s-disease-with-the-bacteria-in-our-gut"&gt;between the gut&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-connection-between-autism-and-the-gut-microbiome-is-clearer-than-ever"&gt;and the brain&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/gut-inflammation-linked-to-alzheimers-disease-yet-again"&gt;is growing&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/obesity-can-trigger-lasting-changes-in-the-brains-nutrient-response-study-finds"&gt;year after year&lt;/a&gt;. Some experts are now so convinced by the results, they &lt;a href="https://hms.harvard.edu/news-events/publications-archive/brain/gut-brain"&gt;refer to the gut&lt;/a&gt; as &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/hidden-rhythms-between-your-stomach-and-brain-could-shape-your-mood"&gt;the body's 'second brain'&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the way these two nervous systems work together remains a mystery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The twin study at KCL hints that consuming certain '&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-finds-eggs-might-protect-brain-health-and-lower-cholesterol"&gt;brain foods&lt;/a&gt;' could be a promising way to treat cognitive decline, adding to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-discover-key-food-nutrients-linked-to-slower-brain-aging"&gt;research suggesting key food nutrients&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-say-this-one-particular-diet-may-slow-the-decline-of-the-brain"&gt;may be able to slow its progress&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These plant fibers, which are cheap and available over the counter, could benefit a wide group of people in these cash-strapped times. They are safe and acceptable too," &lt;a href="https://www.kcl.ac.uk/news/daily-fibre-supplement-improves-older-brain-12-weeks"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; geriatrician Claire Steves at KCL.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our next task is to see whether these effects are sustained over longer periods and in larger groups of people."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While prebiotics appeared to improve some aspects of cognitive function in an &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/an-expert-reveals-how-to-keep-your-brain-sharp-as-you-age"&gt;aging brain&lt;/a&gt;, like &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-memory-technique-primes-the-brain-to-absorb-more-information"&gt;memory and processing&lt;/a&gt; times, the study didn't identify significant physical benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/protecting-your-muscle-mass-is-vital-for-healthy-aging-heres-why"&gt;Muscle loss&lt;/a&gt; didn't improve among aging twins taking high-fiber supplements, although inulin and FOS are important factors in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/mysterious-neglected-part-of-our-bodies-is-vital-to-our-health-scientists-discover"&gt;musculoskeletal maintenance&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_144937" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-144937" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/TwinsSmiling642.jpg" alt="Twin sisters smiling with arms around each other" class="size-full wp-image-144937" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/TwinsSmiling642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/TwinsSmiling642-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/TwinsSmiling642-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-144937" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Twin studies are highly valuable when it comes to differentiating between the effect of genetics and the environment on human health. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEJEFwhdc0/"&gt;recep-bg/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The twins that participated in the current trial were mostly female, and even though the researchers adjusted for sex differences in their findings, they acknowledge that there may be some selection bias amongst KCL's twin cohort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-is-more-common-in-women-and-this-may-help-explain-why"&gt;females are more susceptible to Alzheimer's disease&lt;/a&gt;, and studies like this one support the emerging idea that cognitive decline is &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-might-not-actually-be-a-brain-disease-expert-reveals"&gt;not always a disease of the brain&lt;/a&gt;, but may involve &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/stressful-life-events-linked-to-alzheimers-biomarkers-study-finds"&gt;external factors&lt;/a&gt;, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/levels-of-omega-3-could-help-explain-womens-alzheimers-risk"&gt;Levels of Omega-3 Could Help Explain Women's Alzheimer's Risk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-balance-of-gut-bacteria-could-play-a-crucial-role-in-how-ms-develops"&gt;In 2025, researchers reported&lt;/a&gt; that in humans and mice, a lower ratio of &lt;em&gt;Bifidobacterium&lt;/em&gt; to &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Akkermansia_muciniphila"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Akkermansia&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in the gut bacteria is linked to multiple sclerosis, and this imbalance was also associated with more severe disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-guts-methane-making-microbes-could-secretly-turn-fiber-into-extra-calories"&gt;gut has its fingers in many bodily 'pies'&lt;/a&gt;, including the immune system and the central nervous system. &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/sweetening-your-yogurt-with-honey-could-boost-its-probiotic-benefits"&gt;Feeding its microbiome&lt;/a&gt; certain &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC10410452/"&gt;prebiotics and probiotics&lt;/a&gt; could open the door to treating &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/chemical-produced-by-gut-microbes-seems-to-prevent-obesity-in-mice"&gt;a plethora of illnesses&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-are-hacking-bacteria-to-fight-cancer-then-self-destruct"&gt;and diseases&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-024-46116-y"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature Communications&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in March 2024.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 12:00:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxNVGFVMThVNUtVVW1TNkl5Q1dCdVFkekExM251VDd6azhtOXNDb2tCS01BVU54ZnVZMEU3UFhsUHlRbF9YTnotZVlSM3lvaGM3NEpuZFEyV1o0SEpjdW1XZG9GWi1lZldhLWlYLTJ3andvTmYyeHoxUlI3RXh3TWxZcEhtaWliOGE0N0lKdlRCZkpDc0dENTRsOWJhYWxhVXF5</guid></item><item><title>医生对更年期激素治疗的“无数据”决定做出回应： “这不是真的” -《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/nov/24/menopause-hormone-therapy</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Estrogen-related medications for menopause will no longer carry broad black-box warnings, Marty Makary, commissioner of the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA), announced last week, bypassing the regulatory agency’s typical process and, according to experts, overstating the science behind the medications – with troubling implications for future drug decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The decision to remove an ominous warning from 2003 about the risks of cardiovascular disease, breast cancer and dementia makes sense for local vaginal estrogen products, but systemic estrogen is more complicated, menopause experts said – and more than these nuances, they worried about the scientific process, or lack thereof, in making the decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Hormone therapy can ease symptoms of menopause, including hot flashes, insomnia and joint pain. But health officials took claims of the benefits a major step forward, indicating the therapy can also prevent heart disease, osteoporosis, Alzheimer’s disease and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“There may be no other medication in the modern era that can improve the health outcomes of women on a population level than hormone replacement therapy,” Makary said, calling it a “life-changing, even life-saving treatment” and positioning the announcement as a “medical breakthrough”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Other officials at the press conference offered similarly rosy perspectives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Hormone therapy is “extending the lives for as much as 10 years”, said &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/robert-f-kennedy-jr" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Robert F Kennedy Jr&lt;/a&gt;, secretary of the US Department of Health and Human Services (HHS).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Today, we have the opportunity to add up to a decade of healthy years to the life of every woman that you love,” said Alicia Jackson, head of the Advanced Research Projects Agency for &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/health" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; and founder of Evernow, a startup that provides virtual menopause care. “Estrogen is one of the most effective longevity interventions for women.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Yet there is no evidence that hormone therapy has benefits among the wider population of menopausal women beyond those who have symptoms, researchers said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“To make that blanket statement that every woman should take this to prevent heart disease – it’s not true,” said Lauren Streicher, clinical professor of obstetrics and gynecology and founding medical director of the Center for Sexual Medicine and &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/menopause" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Menopause&lt;/a&gt; at the Northwestern University school of medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The “data-free” decision sends a “harmful” and confusing message, said Pauline Maki, professor of psychiatry, psychology and obstetrics and gynecology at the University of Illinois college of medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Women are trying desperately to get the truth, and they’re having a really difficult time,” she said. When it comes to using menopause hormone therapy for dementia, her area of expertise, “the harm is maybe real, but certainly it’s not showing benefit”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;An HHS spokesperson said that “randomized studies show that women who initiate HRT within 10 years of the onset of menopause (generally before age 60) have a reduction in all-cause mortality and fractures”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The HHS did not respond to questions about officials’ statements on purported protection against dementia and other issues or the evidence for using the medications widely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;This is the first time the FDA has relied on a roundtable panel, which was not open to public comments in advance, to inform their regulatory decision-making, &lt;a href="https://insights.citeline.com/pink-sheet/drug-safety/makarys-expert-panel-sparks-regulatory-action-for-menopause-hormonal-therapy-GV4D4PKRVFHSZEICZVQ7X3IITM/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;according&lt;/a&gt; to Pink Sheet. Streicher, who has long advocated for changes to the black-box warning, was going to be on the panel in July, but after a few preliminary meetings, she dropped out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It became very clear to me that this was not going to be a scientific panel. This isn’t the scientific approach,” she said. “I said: ‘I’m out. I don’t want any part of this.’”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Streicher attended the press conference earlier this month. “They were trying to get people to pack the room,” she said. The organizers urged attendees to wear their white coats to give the event the imprimatur of expertise, Streicher said. She didn’t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;She says she’s worried about the precedent set by the decision. The agency is also re-examining medications like mifepristone, which is a safe and effective medication for abortion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It was very clear that Makary already had an agenda, that he was going to want to remove these labels, and was just kind of doing this public discourse of passionate people saying: ‘This is why it should happen,’” she said. “They handpick the people who they know are going to say what they want them to say.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Makary’s most recent book has a chapter on hormone replacement therapy, titled OMG HRT, arguing that hormone therapy has been shown to “increase a woman’s longevity by three years”. The more accepted medical term for the treatment for women over 40 is menopause hormone therapy (MHT). The July &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/patients/fda-expert-panels/fda-expert-panel-menopause-and-hormone-replacement-therapy-women-07172025" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;panel&lt;/a&gt; included researchers who have published on menopause as well as doctors with large social media followings; no oncologists participated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The process involved letting panelists “express their opinions”, Makary said, followed by a literature review at FDA and the recommendation to “remove certain blackbox warnings”, which Makary himself signed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Typically, expert advisory committees hold public discussions on the evidence and then make recommendations to the FDA, which subject-matter experts at the agency – rarely the commissioner – may or may not accept.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The FDA opted for the panel because advisory committee meetings are “bureaucratic, long, often conflicted and very expensive”, Makary said in response to a question about the process. More panels with guests who “​​speak [their] mind passionately” will happen in the future, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The evidence itself on the medications is nuanced. Streicher notes “there’s really two very separate issues, and they muddy those”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Local vaginal estrogen, which is usually a cream, tablet, insert, suppository or vaginal ring, treats symptoms like dryness and irritation as well as recurrent urinary tract infections and urgency. “Those products are really totally safe,” Streicher said, adding that they never should have had the warning applied to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Systemic estrogen is more complicated. There are many preparations, applications and ways it’s metabolized. Some specific medications do have risks – oral estrogen, for example, increases the risk of getting a blood clot, while a transdermal patch doesn’t. These labels need to be modified in a thoughtful, product-specific way, Streicher said. There’s also a small increased risk of breast cancer with synthetic progesterone. The medications are not suitable for everyone, especially people with a history of breast or uterine cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Maki, a leading researcher on menopause and dementia, once believed memory issues could be linked to the loss of estrogen that occurs during menopause. Research indicated that women who used hormone therapy to treat menopause symptoms saw improvements to their memory. Maki conducted a large randomized &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17893293/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; among a bigger group of menopausal women, not just those with symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Far from showing benefit, it actually showed a trend toward harm,” Maki said. Three other large randomized trials had similar results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Symptoms like hot flashes can be incredibly disruptive, with three-quarters of sufferers saying they have trouble sleeping – which can contribute to memory issues, especially over the course of seven or eight years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Maki now believes that treating those symptoms – whether with hormone therapy or other medications – is key to improving memory, as demonstrated in another study of hers with a non-hormonal treatment. To use hormone therapy for dementia prevention more widely is “just not based in science”, Maki said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="833732f4-62b4-417c-815f-85a2e9354e12" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":29,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"CDC website altered to reflect RFK Jr’s belief in link between vaccines and autism","elementId":"833732f4-62b4-417c-815f-85a2e9354e12","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/nov/20/cdc-website-vaccines-autism"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Yet in a “stunning” move, Maki said, health officials cherry-picked data from a small study in one community while ignoring larger randomized trials. Officials positioned the decision as a move against “medical group think” and “medical dogma”, as Makary put it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“For the first time in a generation, the FDA is standing with science and standing with women,” said Kennedy. “Today, we are restoring integrity to medicine, restoring faith in public health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The American medical establishment turned its back on women, said Kennedy, who recently sought to link women’s use of Tylenol in pregnancy to autism. “The label was designed to frighten women and to silence doctors,” Kennedy said, decrying “a culture of fear”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Makary said the decision was “challenging the paternalism of medicine”, but then said hormone therapy “​​has saved marriages”, indicating that one of the key outcomes of the medication is marital satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It was not only scientifically wrong, but it was offensive,” Streicher said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Hormone therapy is safe and effective for those with menopause symptoms, she said: “But do I tell every single woman who goes through menopause that she needs to be on hormone therapy? Absolutely not.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE5yOVF2NnJqblVWNG5nUHhQYXNNOVh4WXE2Q0ZlTzk3dVFLeUVoUlRzeEFqR3pxZ1ZRc05xdGdkLXVwS0U4Y2hKOTk1NjRqVGFLWGFEeDR5RjRyaHFuX0RORlJ6azhSV3pBS1pydmVrS2MtaWltYjdQQk1od1V2dw</guid></item><item><title>为什么筛查美国最致命的癌症漏掉了大多数病例--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/11/24/lung-cancer-screening-guidelines/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TCQFICVZ3FF7DMYOQJXOAUXWQQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Jessie Creel’s cough started in May last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GQSCXSIJSRHXRFLKRRWNQIGY3Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;At the time, a primary care physician diagnosed the mother of three with pneumonia. But the antibiotics didn’t work and her cough persisted. During a camping trip in the summer, she coughed up blood. She kept losing weight. She wasn’t able to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 11:31:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNVEpCT040M2U3RmkwdnVRSEptRVd4MF8wbGVMUmE5NXdUVUN6Z2drODNzQm50NkF3NW9lSjVJNGpsQWxBZkNiUlo0TzhsMHF5OVNNb2YwWmNoWDFsZzdQYnB1bWFtNWpTMXBSSFphZ1E5aVBjdUpQOGxHQXhCNWZKa1cydzAwaVN5OHc</guid></item><item><title>假期要问长辈的5个问题-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/24/well/interviewing-older-relatives-questions.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 10:00:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxONkZZWnNGWTdwMkFvQTNnTlRvcTlnVU03eHQxZDBobGMwQmdDSjBEeUcxOVJianVzNHh2NElJbzRtUjYwZGYtZWVkeElWWjVNcUgwQzV5WkhDUXBHZ2R4RkxKOVRhTTVCWGhWN2d2UUJfQ0pvWWUxT3d5Zmw5WkpvcU1ZR3VzX1pHbENv</guid></item><item><title>新的人工智能模型可增强罕见疾病的诊断-《金融时报》</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/bc49e334-776b-41d0-a9be-fb0c29c54853</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="o-grid-row details-section o3-type-body-base css-pmzbjb"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Complete digital access to quality FT journalism with expert analysis from industry leaders. Pay a year upfront and save 20%.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Financial Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 10:00:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE9aQTlZRFYzc2k3eDNKNGhuSS1aMVVlVTAyVGtFNnJIZ2syaWV3MW42RU8wemZmbjcyZkZKVUUwOE04ZmtWOWQ3T2pCbEhfdlppRUFRdWZtcmhYTF92ZTB6SmRQNnNjaVhicldvSVdfZW8</guid></item><item><title>肯尼迪在没有科学支持的情况下加强疫苗攻击- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/rfk-jr-vaccine-safety-aluminum-ingredients/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As the federal government prepares for the next meeting of its Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices, Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has intensified his attacks on aluminum vaccine components used in many shots to boost the body's immune response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy, a longtime anti-vaccine activist before seeking public office, &lt;a href="https://podscripts.co/podcasts/the-joe-rogan-experience/1999-robert-kennedy-jr" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;claims that aluminum&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://podscripts.co/podcasts/the-joe-rogan-experience/1999-robert-kennedy-jr&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;source=docs&amp;amp;ust=1763737175066729&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw0kM5Ir0tjfudsVdspksPQO" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt; adjuvants&lt;/a&gt; are neurotoxic and tied to autism, asthma, autoimmune disease, and &lt;a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/rfk-jr-says-peanut-allergies-may-be-tied-to-aluminum-in-vaccines-and/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;food allergies&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But science and medicine advances a different view. Strong recommendations that parents introduce peanut-containing foods to infants early, for instance, have led to &lt;a href="https://publications.aap.org/pediatrics/article/156/5/e2024070516/204636/Guidelines-for-Early-Food-Introduction-and?autologincheck=redirected" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;a drop&lt;/a&gt; in the incidence rate of peanut allergies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since taking office, Kennedy has ordered reviews of vaccine ingredients, citing aluminum as a top concern. A discussion of "adjuvants and contaminants" is on the vaccine advisory panel's &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/downloads/agendas/draft-posted-2025-11-14-508.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;draft agenda&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Centers for Disease Control and Prevention &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccine-safety/about/autism.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;webpage&lt;/a&gt; that for years has assured the public vaccines do not cause autism was &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cdc-website-change-vaccines-autism/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;updated Nov. 19 with new language&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; stating that studies have not definitively ruled out a link between vaccines and autism.&lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He has also targeted scientists who have published studies showing aluminum adjuvants are safe. In August, Kennedy denounced &lt;a href="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/ANNALS-25-00997" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;a large Danish study&lt;/a&gt; finding no link between aluminum in vaccines and childhood disease, calling it a "&lt;a href="https://childrenshealthdefense.org/defender/rfk-jr-breaks-down-danish-study-autism-aluminum-vaccines/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;deceitful propaganda stunt&lt;/a&gt;" and demanding its retraction. The Annals of Internal Medicine rejected the claim and refused to retract the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And, regarding the upcoming &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/rfk-jr-cdc-vaccine-advisory-panel-names/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;advisory pane&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;l meeting, HHS spokesperson Emily HIlliard said ACIP "is independently reviewing the full body of evidence on adjuvants and other vaccine components to ensure the highest safety standards."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The stakes are high because Kennedy's push to cast doubt on aluminum isn't just about the ingredient itself. It's part of a &lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/news/article/trump-rfk-maha-prasad-vaccine-injury-compensation-program-autism-allergies/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;broader strategy&lt;/a&gt; to foster uncertainty about vaccine safety and lay the groundwork to challenge the &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/vaccine-injury-compensation-program-autism-rfk-jr/" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;National Vaccine Injury Compensation Program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, which drug manufacturers say is essential to ensure a stable market for shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But researchers across infectious diseases, immunology, pediatrics, and epidemiology say the data is clear: Aluminum adjuvants are safe.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Aluminum is the third most common element on the Earth's surface," said Dr. Paul Offit, a pediatrician and director of the Vaccine Education Center at Children's Hospital of Philadelphia. "So we're all exposed to aluminum all the time. The water that we drink has aluminum in it. The food that we eat has aluminum in it." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vaccines add only a tiny amount of aluminum to the body — a combined total of about 8 milligrams — after the schedule of childhood vaccines is complete. Offit said that over the first 18 years of life, people naturally take in about 400 milligrams of aluminum from everyday sources. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't know why there is so much concern," said Dr. Rajesh Gupta, a former FDA vaccine scientist. "Aluminum gets distributed in the body everywhere. It is ultimately excreted by the kidneys in the urine. So, it is not that aluminum stays in the body."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How they work&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The aluminum in vaccines isn't foil or metal. It's a compound of aluminum salts, such as aluminum hydroxide or aluminum phosphate, that help the vaccine work better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's a bit like zinc in cold tablets: Patients don't swallow chunks of metal, instead ingesting a zinc salt that dissolves safely in the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In vaccines, these aluminum salts give the immune system an extra nudge so it learns to recognize the target germ more effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When injected, the vaccine stays near the injection site and causes mild, short-lived inflammation that summons immune cells. Those cells pick up the vaccine antigen, a harmless piece of a virus or bacterium, and carry it to nearby lymph nodes. There, the adjuvants show it around like a wanted poster so the body can identify and destroy the germ quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Harm HogenEsch, a professor of immunopathology at the Purdue University College of Veterinary Medicine, said that aluminum adjuvants work only when they're injected in the same spot as the vaccine ingredient they're meant to boost, to help nearby immune cells learn to recognize the germ. If the two shots are given in different places, he said, "you don't see that effect."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In response to Kennedy's claims, scientists say that anything that acts as an adjuvant can, in principle, also boost an allergic response. But that doesn't mean aluminum-adjuvanted vaccines are turning children into food-allergic time bombs. Antigens in vaccines such as the hepatitis B surface antigen or HPV proteins are not allergens, and no food proteins are put into vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Animal experiments &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Animal studies form the basis of Kennedy's claim that aluminum adjuvants in vaccines can create allergies. In these experiments, scientists deliberately sensitize rats or mice by injecting them with a food protein mixed with aluminum. The aluminum strengthens the immune response, but it does not cause an allergy by itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's the basis for a lot of the experimental mouse models, where you inject a food allergen with an aluminum adjuvant to sensitize the mice," HogenEsch said. "I'm not aware of any food antigen being included in vaccines, and so I don't really see a way by which this could happen."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Ross Kedl, a professor of immunology and microbiology at the University of Colorado Anschutz School of Medicine, went further, noting that there is no plausible route for vaccines to create a peanut allergy out of thin air. "Someone would have had to mix peanut proteins in with the actual vaccine prior to injection."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Stefan H. E. Kaufmann, director emeritus at the Max Planck Institute for Infection Biology in Berlin, said results from mice often don't match what happens in people, because "mice are much easier to push into allergic reactions than humans." In other words, what looks dramatic in a rodent study doesn't automatically apply to human immune systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And in this case, it's "important to distinguish between how aluminum behaves in lab animals versus people," Kaufmann said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc5" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",5]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Human studies&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond animal models and theoretical scenarios, scientists have looked hard for signals of harm in large human datasets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2023, &lt;a href="https://www.academicpedsjnl.net/article/S1876-2859%2822%2900417-X/fulltext" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;a study&lt;/a&gt; by the Vaccine Safety Datalink, a collaboration coordinated by the CDC, reported a slight increase in asthma among children with higher aluminum exposure before age 2, but the association disappeared in further analyses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That paper was roundly criticized," Offit said. "When they controlled for breastfeeding, the association between asthma and receipt of aluminum-adjuvant-containing vaccines disappeared." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It should have never been published," he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Kathy Edwards, professor emerita of pediatrics at Vanderbilt University, said that false signals are common when large databases are mined for dozens of outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When you look at a hundred different things, just by the law of percentages, some of those may look like there is a signal," she said. "The whole RFK Jr. assessment is really prone to cherry-picking," she said, adding that "there does need to be some kind of basic understanding of statistics for people to interpret this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soon after the 2023 U.S. findings drew attention, scientists at the CDC contacted Dr. Anders Hviid, head of epidemiology research at the Statens Serum Institut in Copenhagen, Denmark, to see whether his team could replicate the work.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc6" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",6]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It makes perfect sense to try to replicate findings of any kind in different data sources," Hviid said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/ANNALS-25-00997" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Hviid's nationwide Danish study&lt;/a&gt; followed 1.2 million children over two decades, using linked national health registries that record every vaccination and diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our health care system is quite egalitarian. It's free, and there's universal access. And everyone is in these nationwide registers," he said. Their findings: no increased risk of these conditions associated with increasing amounts of aluminum received through the vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Rare bumps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors have documented one genuine reaction to aluminum adjuvants: itchy nodules at the injection site, called "pruritic granulomas." These small bumps are so rare that most allergists and pediatricians will never see a single case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This reaction "doesn't lead to something bad, and it really isn't associated with anything other than that local irritation," Edwards said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers believe these bumps represent a localized immune response — meaning only in the area of the injection, not a body-wide allergy — that is very different from the kind of immediate allergic reaction people treat with antihistamines. These include the reactions driven by food or beestings, when histamine, the body's own alarm signal, floods the system within minutes and causes hives, swelling, or breathing trouble. Kedl said that distinction often gets lost in public debate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Eliminating aluminum adjuvants&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For many experts, the real issue is not just whether aluminum is safe but what happens to the entire vaccine program if aluminum adjuvants are stripped out. For many modern vaccines that rely on a single purified protein — such as those for diphtheria and tetanus toxoids, &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/bill-cassidy-hepatitis-b-vaccine-schedule-change/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;hepatitis B,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and HPV — adjuvants are crucial.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc7" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",7]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Edwards said that simply swapping in a different adjuvant isn't realistic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They're kind of all built on one another," she said. Once a vaccine has been proved to work and become the standard of care, new or updated versions are generally no longer tested against a placebo in people who should be getting that vaccine. Instead, they're tested against the existing product, which means each approval rests on the one before it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Core childhood vaccines would probably have to be reformulated, and large clinical trials would have to be repeated to prove the new products are safe and effective. Meanwhile, production gaps and shortages would have to be managed, potentially for years, while manufacturers and regulators start over — all while diseases such as &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/whooping-cough-deaths-us-most-since-2017/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;whooping cough&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, hepatitis B, and HPV-related cancers gain more room to spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The aluminum adjuvants have sort of hit the sweet spot in terms of being effective at inducing a robust antibody response that is protective for those vaccines in which they're being used and being very safe," HogenEsch said. "It would be quite frankly foolish to try to eliminate them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A century of safe use&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The DTaP, hepatitis B, and HPV vaccines all contain aluminum adjuvants and have been in use for nearly a century. Large-scale studies show no link between aluminum and systemic allergic disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We have had aluminum adjuvants in vaccines for decades," Edwards said. "I have grandchildren. My grandchildren have received all of their vaccines. And I do not worry about the safety of them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If aluminum is falsely cast as the villain and vaccine uptake falls, experts warn, the consequences will not be theoretical: more measles in schools, more meningitis in college dorms, and more young adults dying of cancers that HPV shots could have prevented.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc8" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",8]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In their view, the real danger isn't the trace amounts of a metal that children already encounter every day. It's &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/how-many-lives-vaccines-have-saved/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;rolling back the protection&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; aluminum-adjuvanted vaccines have provided for generations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's the trade-off Offit hopes parents will see. "A choice not to get a vaccine is not a risk-free choice," he said. "It's just a choice to take a different risk."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/about-us/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;KFF Health News&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; is a national newsroom that produces in-depth journalism about health issues and is one of the core operating programs at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/about-us/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;KFF&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; — the independent source for health policy research, polling, and journalism.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    

                    
        
  
          
  
  



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

  
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 10:00:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTFBqWjBQWlh4cjdNVXltcnQ3czR1ZExtS2FvWkdBQkhiUmgxeHZTdkpOdFJVUEEtbDJCRDUyQ0ZfZWN3a05kemdXRy1JU203T2oyQTV0dmloLURpeEp4VjhWaUMtZVZYQzJQd25raDVzVFVpRDUxcExZbGFZeU3SAYIBQVVfeXFMUHhxVndnWlhKX1JiU19kTXJhMWFVWHZDempRUzF0M0U0UlNsdS1STEhjaklib1JiTW5FdGQtSUUzcmdpSmRuS0wzQWxxNkJEQ0RWVTV1X2tRYXZkdm02Xzd6WnBBbHBrVGZyUi1ZeUxGdmtkdmVlVEpFSWZhTVBMUnVjZw</guid></item><item><title>哪些食物让你最快乐？不是你想的那样- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/11/24/nx-s1-5615440/food-mood-mental-health</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      
   &lt;p&gt;When you hear the phrase "happy foods," which dishes come to mind? Many people think of sugary desserts or fatty fast foods, says &lt;a href="https://foodandmoodcentre.com.au/team/felice-jacka/" target="_blank"&gt;Felice Jacka &lt;/a&gt;with the Food and Mood Centre at Deakin University, in Geelong, Australia. After all, in the U.S., we celebrate with cake and ice cream. Parties often feature pizza. Our Thanksgiving feasts usually end in an array of pies and whipped cream.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But the idea that these foods will make you happy comes &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/full/10.1177/13591053231168340" target="_blank"&gt;directly from advertisers&lt;/a&gt;, Jacka says. "People are like &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/02/04/nx-s1-5285413/cereal-sugar-kids-advertising-health" target="_blank"&gt;walking wallets to food companies&lt;/a&gt;," and they sell you this myth that eating these foods will make you feel good.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"It's a bit like if you gave someone a glass of champagne. Feels good in the short term, but the long-term impact is the opposite," Jacka says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Food impacts mood&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;For the past fifteen years, Jacka and her colleagues have pioneered the field of nutritional psychiatry. They study how various&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2024/03/18/1238939706/ultra-processed-food-junk-food-disease-cancer-anxiety-depression-diet" target="_blank"&gt; foods affect people's moods&lt;/a&gt; and mental health. And they've found some foods are uplifting and protect us from depression. While others sour our mood and increase our risk of depression.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There's mounting evidence that sweets and ultra-processed foods fall squarely in the second category.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s42255-021-00383-x" target="_blank"&gt;Studies have found&lt;/a&gt; that people can feel anxious, irritable, angry or lethargic several hours after eating foods packed in refined carbohydrates and sugars. "For example, some weekend mornings, I go to a diner and have a waffle. By 10 o'clock, I feel terrible," says pediatric gastroenterologist &lt;a href="https://dental.nyu.edu/faculty/ft/km5994.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Kara Margolis &lt;/a&gt;at New York University, who studies how gut health connects to mood disorders.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;And over the long-run — say months and years — too many of these foods may affect your mental health. &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39426518/" target="_blank"&gt;Large epidemiological studies&lt;/a&gt; across several cultures have shown that a diet high in ultra-processed foods and refined carbohydrates &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2809727" target="_blank"&gt;raises a person's risk for depression&lt;/a&gt;. "We can see that it's associated with a 20 to 30 percent higher risk," Margolis says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;At the same time, several &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/1028415X.2017.1411320" target="_blank"&gt;randomized control studies &lt;/a&gt;have found that when people remove ultra-processed foods from their diet and replace them with more whole and minimally processed foods,&lt;a href="https://bmcmedicine.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s12916-017-0791-y" target="_blank"&gt; their depression decreases&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Here's the conundrum: when people &lt;em&gt;believe&lt;/em&gt; these ultra-processed foods make them happier, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35003906/" target="_blank"&gt;studies have found&lt;u&gt;,&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; people tend to eat more of them.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Happy microbes, happy people?&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So if ice cream, cake and processed French fries aren't the happiest foods out there, what are? Scientists are still trying to nail down that answer. But the doctors and scientists interviewed for this story all pointed to one top candidate: "Whole grains seem to be particularly important," Jacka says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Whole grains contain a special type of fiber, called &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10498976/" target="_blank"&gt;fermentable fiber&lt;/a&gt;, which bacteria in your gut can digest. It improves the health of your microbiome, Margolis explains, by feeding the "good versus bad bacteria." When the microbes eat this fiber, they produce &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9498509/" target="_blank"&gt;small molecules&lt;/a&gt; that are linked to a whole host of benefits, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11242198/#:~:text=GPR43%20is%20a%20functional%20receptor,infiltration/activation%20%5B41%5D." target="_blank"&gt;including decreased inflammation&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10041598/#:~:text=SCFAs%20and%20obesity,essential%20role%20in%20human%20health.&amp;amp;text=Studies%20have%20revealed%20that%20on,insulin%20sensitivity%20%28Figure%204A%29.&amp;amp;text=While%20SCFA%2Ddependent%20GPR43%20signaling,1%29%20%28Figure%204A%29.&amp;amp;text=Pingitore%20et%20al83%20show,C/protein%20kinase%20C%20pathway." target="_blank"&gt;improved insulin sensitivity,&lt;/a&gt; and better communication between the gut and the brain. All of these effects have been associated with improved mood and a decreased risk of mood disorders, Margolis says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;"Making the environment in your gut right for good bacteria not only can affect mood, but it can protect you from nearly every medical condition that's been studied," she adds, including heart disease and diabetes. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So if you are looking to boost your holiday mood, here are a few things to try.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;1. Go home made&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There are two fundamental ways you can influence your mood with your diet, says Felice Jacka at Deakin University. "They're both quite independent of each other."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;First off, she says, you can cut back on&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2024/10/21/1211165439/low-ultra-processed-foods-diet" target="_blank"&gt; ultra-processed foods.&lt;/a&gt; That includes foods with added preservatives, artificial sweeteners, refined carbohydrates and white flours, natural and artificial flavors, and emulsifiers, such as soy lecithin, xanthan gum and guar gum.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Over Thanksgiving, skip the store-bought pastries, pies, crackers, and white breads. Avoid fast-food pizzas and burgers. Try making your favorite foods in your kitchen with traditional ingredients, Jacka says. "For example, make a beautiful, flour-free cake using almond meal and honey. It's still going to be sweet, but it's going to be a heck of a lot better for your mood, than what you'll find in the supermarket.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;2. Don't make the holidays white&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The second way to boost your mood with your diet, Jacka says, is increase your consumption of whole grains.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Instead of grabbing a croissant or sugary cereal for breakfast, have a bowl of overnight oats or a savory congee (made with brown rice). Toss corn or barley into your salads. Eat corn tortillas instead of flour ones. Swap out biscuits and dinner rolls for 100% whole wheat breads or pastas.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;When you're baking pies, cookies, and cakes, you can substitute the white flour in the recipe for whole grain flours, such oat, barley, or whole wheat. Same goes with pizza: have the kids create a 100% whole wheat pizza from scratch this holiday. Or make whole wheat bread in a bread machine.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;3. Beef up on beans &amp;amp; lentils&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There's another major way to eat this mood-boosting fiber, says&lt;a href="https://faculty.mdanderson.org/profiles/meroe_morse.html" target="_blank"&gt; Dr. Meroë Morse &lt;/a&gt;at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center: Eat beans and lentils. "Your microbiome loves beans," she says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"In our research, we see that a very small amount of beans in your diet can actually greatly impact your microbiome in a good way," Morse says. Unlike many leafy greens or many vegetables, you don't have to eat many beans to get a hefty dose of fiber. For example, a quarter cup of cooked black beans contains about five to seven grams of fiber.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Dried beans and lentils are also a super inexpensive way to boost fiber,&lt;a href="https://fshn.illinois.edu/directory/hholsche" target="_blank"&gt; says Hannah Holscher&lt;/a&gt;, who's a microbiome scientist and dietitian at the University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign. "Now that we're getting into soup season, just pick your favorite soup, pick your favorite bean and add them into the soup."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Dried lentils cook up quickly because they don't need soaking. "We frequently eat lentils in our house," she says. "You can saute some onions with tomatoes and olive oil. Then add lentils with different Indian spices," she says. "It's delicious." Or make a big pot of Thanksgiving chili with both beans and lentils.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;4. Take it slowly&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Keep in mind, beans, lentils, and dense whole grains are powerful foods for your gut, Holsher says. Start off with a small serving and titrate up slowly over time.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;With beans, some individuals will get a bit of gas and bloating if they eat too many or they're not used to eating them. "Try a few different varieties," Holscher recommends. "Or soak the beans beforehand. That can help to reduce any types of unwanted side effects."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;You can also find high amounts of fermentable fiber in chia seeds, berries, apples, pears, avocados and unripe bananas.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;After your microbiome adjusts, the bacteria will thank you by raising up your mood long-term. After all,&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6469458/" target="_blank"&gt; studies suggest &lt;/a&gt;that when your gut bacteria are happy — they make you happy as well.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   
   

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE1tUTJlSjlJc1FTZEYwZXV4ZUpRUEZ3MWZpRzdQcDVCcENMczlULUYyVmdlRms0WDQyRDZMSktmVmlyV0FlZzdCTHlnZnlFa2JFNGFIN3F1d0V1eTRndkt4V2duN0ktaGlNdGdfaDhHZHZvQzJIZlkw</guid></item><item><title>新的肥胖症发现重写了数十年的脂肪代谢科学- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/11/251123115712.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Our fat cells, known as adipocytes, do far more than store extra body weight. They serve as an important energy reserve for the body. Inside each adipocyte, fat is packed into lipid droplets that can be tapped when fuel is needed -- for example, during the hours between meals. To release this stored energy, the body relies on a protein called HSL, which functions much like a switch. When energy is running low, hormones such as adrenaline activate HSL, prompting it to free fat that can then supply various organs.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without HSL, it would be reasonable to expect fat to build up, as though the body had lost access to its energy supply. Surprisingly, this is not what happens. Research involving both mice and patients with mutations in the HSL gene shows that the lack of this protein does not lead to excess fat or obesity. Instead, affected individuals experience a loss of fat mass, a condition known as lipodystrophy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although obesity and lipodystrophy appear to be complete opposites, both involve fat cells that do not function properly. As a result, each condition can contribute to metabolic disturbances and cardiovascular problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HSL Found in an Unexpected Location Inside Fat Cells&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To understand this surprising behavior, a team led by Dominique Langin, professor at the University of Toulouse within the I2MC, took a closer look at where HSL is found inside adipocytes. The protein is well known for its role at the surface of lipid droplets, where it helps break down stored fat. However, the study revealed that HSL also resides inside the nucleus of fat cells. "In the nucleus of adipocytes, HSL is able to associate with many other proteins and take part in a program that maintains an optimal amount of adipose tissue and keeps adipocytes 'healthy'," explains Jérémy Dufau, co-author of the study, who completed his doctoral thesis on this topic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers also found that nuclear HSL levels are tightly controlled. Adrenaline, which activates the form of HSL located on lipid droplets, also encourages the protein to leave the nucleus. This process occurs naturally during fasting. In contrast, obese mice show elevated levels of HSL within the nucleus, suggesting a shift in this regulatory system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Revised Understanding of HSL's Role in Metabolism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"HSL has been known since the 1960s as a fat-mobilizing enzyme. But we now know that it also plays an essential role in the nucleus of adipocytes, where it helps maintain healthy adipose tissue," says Dominique Langin. This additional responsibility helps explain why the absence of HSL results in lipodystrophy, and it offers new insights into metabolic disorders such as obesity and related health complications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This discovery appears at a critical time. In France, one in two adults is overweight or obese, and globally the number reaches two and a half billion people. Obesity increases the risk of a range of diseases, including diabetes and heart problems, and often reduces overall quality of life. Continued scientific research is crucial to improving prevention efforts and patient care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 07:23:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE5pNWliVG42QlpIdjRkQ09KVlBrdU5nVDZ0UXhMNVQ4WWM3bmlnUzFMVnFJQUVHOHdadk9CaTNldEdfcEZuU0E2MUtTbFY5Sjl6a1h2WDJ0Y2hGMGprek1QOVJDYkJ2OVdISFozdnlpOA</guid></item><item><title>一位私人教练说： “每天只需30分钟的练习就可以带来有意义的改变” - Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://www.fitandwell.com/exercise/walking/a-personal-trainer-says-that-just-30-minutes-a-day-of-this-exercise-can-make-a-meaningful-difference</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p id="80779869-78fa-45f0-9ea7-fb8793f51030"&gt;If I told you that lifting heavy weights for 30 minutes a day would make a meaningful difference to your health, you'd probably say, “Tell me something I don’t know”. Same with running and cycling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what about that perennially underestimated form of exercise—walking? Would you think there’s as much to be gained?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="80779869-78fa-45f0-9ea7-fb8793f51030-2"&gt;“Walking workouts support cardiovascular health, maintain joint mobility and help manage weight, all without putting undue strain on the body,” says &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://welltech.com/experts/david-j-sautter/" target="_blank" data-url="https://welltech.com/experts/david-j-sautter/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;David Sautter&lt;/a&gt;, a NASM-certified personal trainer at&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://walkfit.welltech.com/" target="_blank" data-url="https://walkfit.welltech.com/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;WalkFit&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Even just 30 minutes a day of this exercise can make a meaningful difference and be the perfect starting point for a healthier, more consistent fitness routine,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do you want to start regular walking but have no idea where to start? Sautter shared his go-to walking workout recommendation from the WalkFit app. It’s perfect for beginners or those who need a low-impact option to help them burn calories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s a steady pace walk, which takes 31 minutes, including the warm-up and cool-down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-1-warm-up" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-1-warm-up"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Warm-up&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="3649643d-e3cc-4951-b1ae-9d30855203ac"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 6min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-rzpQdZ6eDEnPwVLJeXxL46" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-rzpQdZ6eDEnPwVLJeXxL46 slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This warm-up comprises six dynamic stretches to get your muscles working and your joints lubricated before your walk. Do each stretch for one minute and then move on to the next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol start="1" id="ec4d9413-7ad2-41fd-8a13-08965fe7ba93"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rolls in split stance: &lt;/strong&gt;Step one foot forward, your other foot back, and gently roll your weight through each foot before switching position of your feet halfway through the minute.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knee circles:&lt;/strong&gt; Lift one knee slightly and draw small circles in the air with your foot, then switch sides.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hamstring stretch:&lt;/strong&gt; Slightly bend your left knee and place your right heel on the floor in front of your, keeping your right leg straight. Hinge forward from your hips to feel a stretch in your right hamstring. Return to the start and repeat on the other side. Continue alternating sides, coming in and out of the stretch.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knee ups:&lt;/strong&gt; Lift one knee to hip height, then the other, continuing as if marching in place.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Side tilts:&lt;/strong&gt; Stand up straight and slowly bend your torso to one side, then the other.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shoulder rotations:&lt;/strong&gt; Circle your shoulders forward and backwards to loosen the joints.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;a id="elk-2-steady-walk" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-2-steady-walk"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Steady walk&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="82bc8b30-4b4a-485a-957c-5b70b6d4b3c3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 17min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walk at a comfortable, but purposeful pace that is enough to raise your heart rate slightly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-3-slow-walk" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-3-slow-walk"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Slow walk&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="0114bb1a-63e8-49b6-aad2-51c4d5d71924"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 3min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walk at a relaxed pace to start easing your heart rate down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-4-cool-down" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-4-cool-down"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4. Cool-down&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="2977d9d8-1c61-462a-a69e-7db1f75e1bcc"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 5min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This cool-down has five static stretches to help release tension in your muscles to speed up your post-walk recovery. Hold each stretch for a minute (or 30 seconds each side), then move on to the next one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="fed0b5d6-78dc-4fa7-992e-a6a2a365d10a"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Standing chest stretch:&lt;/strong&gt; Clasp your hands behind you or place them on your lower back and gently lift your chest.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upper-back stretch&lt;/strong&gt;: Interlace your hands in front of you and round your upper back while pushing your hands forward.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wide-stance leg stretch&lt;/strong&gt;: Stand with your feet wider than hip-width apart and gently hinge forward to stretch your inner thighs and hamstrings.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quad stretch&lt;/strong&gt;: Bend your knee and hold one foot behind you and gently pull it toward your buttocks to stretch the front of your thigh. Switch sides halfway through.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Side neck stretch&lt;/strong&gt;: Tilt your head toward one shoulder, keeping the opposite shoulder relaxed. Switch sides halfway through.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;a id="elk-shop-walking-shoes" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-shop-walking-shoes"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Shop walking shoes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="97889e1c-aee4-405a-a342-256ca19612ef"&gt;If you need walking shoes, here are three picks from &lt;em&gt;Fit&amp;amp;Well&lt;/em&gt;’s guide to the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.fitandwell.com/buying-guides/best-shoes-for-walking" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.fitandwell.com/buying-guides/best-shoes-for-walking"&gt;best walking shoes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-collectionwidget-c86e6ca31db0a845992b90cfc18e0537" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;div class="product-container hero-product-container product-block-no-wrap"&gt;&lt;div class="product-block-row"&gt;&lt;div class="featured_product_block featured_block_hero" data-id="9d97f4af-6754-4c6f-afcc-ddc9fb449ad8" id="9d97f4af-6754-4c6f-afcc-ddc9fb449ad8"&gt;
&lt;div class="product-image-widthsetter"&gt;&lt;p class="vanilla-image-block" data-bordeaux-image-check&gt; &lt;picture data-new-v2-image="true"&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-1920-80.png.webp 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-1600-80.png.webp 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-1280-80.png.webp 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-1024-80.png.webp 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-768-80.png.webp 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-415-80.png.webp 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-360-80.png.webp 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-320-80.png.webp 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh.png" alt="Brooks Glycerin 22 trainer with white midsole and black upper on white background" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-1920-80.png 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-1600-80.png 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-1280-80.png 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-1024-80.png 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-768-80.png 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-415-80.png 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-360-80.png 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh-320-80.png 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)" loading="lazy" data-new-v2-image="true" data-original-mos="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh.png" data-pin-media="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/aS5uoV7WvUiAAm55Ji3aSh.png" class="featured_image"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;span class="featured__label hero__label"&gt;Best Overall&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="product-block-row"&gt;&lt;div class="featured_product_block featured_block_hero" data-id="f8f8d794-bb36-47fc-92cb-4273868e1ce0" id="f8f8d794-bb36-47fc-92cb-4273868e1ce0"&gt;
&lt;div class="product-image-widthsetter"&gt;&lt;p class="vanilla-image-block" data-bordeaux-image-check&gt; &lt;picture data-new-v2-image="true"&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1920-80.jpg.webp 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1600-80.jpg.webp 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1280-80.jpg.webp 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1024-80.jpg.webp 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-768-80.jpg.webp 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-415-80.jpg.webp 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-360-80.jpg.webp 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-320-80.jpg.webp 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL.jpg" alt="Columbia Konos TRS Hiking Shoe" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1920-80.jpg 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1600-80.jpg 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1280-80.jpg 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1024-80.jpg 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-768-80.jpg 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-415-80.jpg 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-360-80.jpg 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-320-80.jpg 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)" loading="lazy" data-new-v2-image="true" data-original-mos="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL.jpg" data-pin-media="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL.jpg" class="featured_image"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;span class="featured__label hero__label"&gt;Best on a budget&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="product-block-row"&gt;&lt;div class="featured_product_block featured_block_hero" data-id="e079cdb8-1496-4509-bc8b-b936e0163207" id="e079cdb8-1496-4509-bc8b-b936e0163207"&gt;
&lt;div class="product-image-widthsetter"&gt;&lt;p class="vanilla-image-block" data-bordeaux-image-check&gt; &lt;picture data-new-v2-image="true"&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-1920-80.jpg.webp 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-1600-80.jpg.webp 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-1280-80.jpg.webp 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-1024-80.jpg.webp 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-768-80.jpg.webp 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-415-80.jpg.webp 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-360-80.jpg.webp 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-320-80.jpg.webp 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH.jpg" alt="Adidas Terrex Free Hiker Low" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-1920-80.jpg 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-1600-80.jpg 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-1280-80.jpg 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-1024-80.jpg 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-768-80.jpg 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-415-80.jpg 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-360-80.jpg 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH-320-80.jpg 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)" loading="lazy" data-new-v2-image="true" data-original-mos="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH.jpg" data-pin-media="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/MRYrJqFPkeCkcDWKSM6ivH.jpg" class="featured_image"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;span class="featured__label hero__label"&gt;Best for waterproofing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="featured_product_details_wrapper"&gt;
&lt;div class="featured_product_title_wrapper"&gt;
&lt;p class="featured__title"&gt;3. Adidas Terrex Free Hiker Low&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="stars__reviews"&gt;&lt;span itemprop="reviewRating" itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/Rating" class="chunk rating"&gt;&lt;span class="icon icon-star"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="icon icon-star"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="icon icon-star"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="icon icon-star"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;meta itemprop="bestRating" content="100.0"&gt;&lt;meta itemprop="worstRating" content="0.0"&gt;&lt;meta itemprop="ratingValue" content="80"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3AFBVV95cUxQaFA1bEtwcjlyRHdPMWFabDhEb2M3eXZJUFhvT204dDloVmlVd05GZHRxRnVxVWFSVk52WTBnckFuWlNSaWRudHBHRWJvY0N4cV9KdzBtRUZBUW9pRl9TR1NzN0QwSzhFM1I3RnRjMUlSZnJtZlJaZm9US2Q4azF6ZXU0OFRwdlYtRmRYeS1YdmZtaGdTaDh1QWVaU1Z3eG1KNFh3VjRkSEdidU9ERkVLU2Q0TWVZVW9EV1BiX0dnWm9VUzVUZkdLdU80MHdGaVMzMWZ0VDBNdHQ1NTNf</guid></item><item><title>美国心脏病专家说： “没有坏胆固醇这样的东西，原因是...... -印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/there-is-no-such-thing-as-bad-cholesterol-says-us-cardiologist-and-the-reason-is-/articleshow/125530850.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cholesterol is vital for the human body and serves many important functions. Dr. Jack Wolfson, a US cardiologist with over 20 years of experience known as "The Paleo Cardiologist," explains that cholesterol is fundamental to life, helping form cell membranes, producing hormones, and supporting brain and heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cholesterol itself is essential for the body and carries out multiple vital functions. LDL, commonly labelled as "bad cholesterol", is actually necessary to health because it transports fats, fat soluble vitamins such as A,D,E,K, triglycerides, CoQ10 and cholesterol to tissues that are in need of these nutrients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Rather than being harmful, LDL is a part of an intricate nutrient delivery system in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;5 Things that show you have a healthy heart&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;"There is no such thing as bad cholesterol"&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;LDL is not inherently bad, according to Dr. Wolfson. LDL particles act as antioxidants and are integral components of the immune system. One of the key functions of LDL is to attach to the endothelium tissues and deliver all the essential nutrients, thereby removing waste from smooth muscle tissues. This transports role is essential for maintaining healthy blood vessels and improve overall cardiovascular function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The negative reputation around LDL mostly comes from the fact that elevated cholesterol levels, especially all the dense forms of LDL, can contribute to plaque buildup in the arteries, but the molecule itself is designed to support our heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The real problem: Endothelial health&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The body has relied on LDL since the beginning of human biology. It supports hormone production, immune function and tissue repair by transporting cholesterol, antioxidants and nutrients to your cells. So why does modern medicine call it "bad"? The simple answer, according to the doctor, is that pharmaceutical companies needed a villain to sell a trillion dollars' worth of statin drugs. The real truth is that LDL's interaction with the endothelium, the inner lining of the arteries, is normal and healthy. Plaque only forms when the endothelium is injured by inflammation, toxins, high insulin levels, mold exposure, poor sleep, and oxidative stress. The problem lies not with LDL itself but with the unhealthy environment in which it circulates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Misconceptions and pharmaceutical influence&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Wolfson criticises the pharma industry's narrative that "LDL is bad" and the widespread use of statin drugs to artificially lower cholesterol levels. He argues that these medications DO NOT promote heart health but rather manage symptoms and often cause side effects. His approach focuses on natural optimization of cholesterol levels through lifestyle, nutrition, and stress management, emphasizing "eat well, live well, think well" to find the right and balanced cholesterol levels for an individual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A natural approach to heart health&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his public messages and social media posts, Dr. Wolfson highlights natural factors that contribute to heart health beyond LDL numbers. He recommends sensible sunlight exposure to convert cholesterol into vitamin D, a nutrient essential to cardiovascular and immune health. His protocols often include nutritional dietary adjustments, toxin avoidance, and physical activity to prevent heart disease naturally. Dr. Wolfson’s holistic and functional medicine approach challenges the traditional focus on drug therapy, aiming to address root causes for long-term well-being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Sunlight and natural cholesterol balance&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Dr. Wolfson's notable recommendations for managing cholesterol naturally involves sunlight exposure. Research and his clinical experience shows that UVB rays from sunlight convert cholesterol in the skin into vitamin D. This process raises the vitamin D levels in the body, while naturally lowering cholesterol. Dr. Wolfson says 15 to 20 minutes of sunlight a few times a week, can make all the difference in supporting cardiovascular health, enhancing immunity, and reducing chronic disease risks. This simple lifestyle adjustment highlights how the body is designed to work with nature, rather than against it when it comes to cholesterol balance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Dr. Wolfson says, LDL is not "bad" but is plays a critical role in transporting antioxidant defense and immune regulation. The demonisation of LDL results largely from misunderstandings and pharmaceutical interests. Dr. Wolfson offers a fresh perspective and encourages natural methods to optimise LDL levels, emphasising lifestyle and foundational health principles rather than relying on statins. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_gFBVV95cUxPaUlnZEdUUElqLVByeS1wREFHRzhjLVhYb2pmbi0yVDh2MnZiLW9xaVM5RzY3WHFTV19wUWF2ekRCdldGTF8zUUVvMWdhejVLM2kzUU9SU1lsWmV2TjZIQTVhUEZaSDRxSWFoRVJrcHNSLVJlZ2JJUy1XXy1HeWJfUE1DMXVCNERncjg0ZGxFa25sUFpJLU5wN1NlV1MxaFhZVlUzOENINHVWRHNKb09lZ2NyUWhYck9UUnJsWnJuZkpKX280M0dndmFiSGQwZ3lUX2J4TVpmQnlJMzlRYXhNNTRxbHBnYnhzQjh6QmtheGI2ZkxpckJuYVo4aFJodw</guid></item><item><title>品尝奶酪可能会揭示您未来患痴呆症的风险- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/a-taste-for-cheese-may-reveal-your-future-risk-of-dementia</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;We don't yet have a cure for dementia, but we do have a growing list of factors that may influence risk – including &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/exercise-at-one-stage-of-life-may-cut-dementia-risk-by-up-to-45"&gt;exercise&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/major-study-links-4-healthy-diets-with-up-to-28-lower-dementia-risk"&gt;diet&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/there-may-be-no-safe-amount-of-booze-when-it-comes-to-dementia-risk"&gt;drinking&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/6-things-gen-z-should-be-doing-right-now-to-stave-off-dementia-later"&gt;social circles&lt;/a&gt;, and even &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/listening-to-music-has-a-surprising-impact-on-dementia-risk-study-shows"&gt;how you listen to music&lt;/a&gt; – and we can now add eating cheese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a study commissioned by Japanese food company Meiji Co., researchers in Japan crunched the numbers on 7,914 people aged 65 or over. Half reported &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cheese-may-actually-fuel-nightmares-surprising-study-confirms"&gt;eating cheese&lt;/a&gt; at least once a week, while half said they didn't eat it at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The health of these participants was tracked for three years. Of the cheese-eating group, 134 people &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/has-dementia-risk-declined-over-generations-heres-the-science"&gt;developed dementia&lt;/a&gt; (3.4 percent); among cheese abstainers, 176 developed dementia (4.5 percent). That's a difference of around 10 or 11 extra cases in every 1,000 people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/117-year-old-womans-diet-could-help-us-all-live-longer"&gt;117-Year-Old Woman's Diet Could Help Us All Live Longer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While that's not a huge variation, and shows an association rather than cause and effect, it adds to what we &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-diet-helps-lower-dementia-risk-and-we-may-finally-know-why"&gt;already know&lt;/a&gt; about &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/which-junk-foods-are-worst-for-brain-health"&gt;diet and dementia&lt;/a&gt; – and how eating habits relate to physical &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-food-choices-can-fuel-anxiety-and-depression-heres-how"&gt;and mental health&lt;/a&gt; in general.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These findings are consistent with prior observational evidence linking dairy intake to cognitive health," Seungwon Jeong, a geriatrics researcher at Niimi University in Japan, and colleagues &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu17213363"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although the effect for each person is modest, at a population scale, especially in countries [like Japan] with low cheese intake, such differences could contribute meaningfully to dementia prevention strategies."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_182557" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-182557" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/DementiaChart.jpg" alt="Dementia chart" class="wp-image-182557 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/DementiaChart.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/DementiaChart-600x494.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-182557" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Dementia diagnoses were more common among people who rarely or never ate cheese, but only slightly. (Jeong et al., &lt;em&gt;Nutrients&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers accounted for several factors that can influence dementia risk, including age, sex, education level, and income.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a secondary analysis, they also controlled for &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/sticking-to-the-mind-diet-could-reduce-your-risk-of-developing-dementia"&gt;healthy eating&lt;/a&gt;: Cheese abstainers tended to have less healthy diets, which might contribute to the link. The association was less strong in this analysis, but was still significant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, there seems to be something about cheese in particular that can prevent dementia from developing, aside from the beneficial effects we know that a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-30-year-study-may-have-found-the-single-best-diet-for-healthy-aging"&gt;nutritious diet&lt;/a&gt; can have. This isn't something the researchers looked at specifically, but past studies offer some clues as to what might be going on here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cheese contains nutrients known to help brain health, for example, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3945/an.111.001784"&gt;including vitamin K&lt;/a&gt;. It's also rich in beneficial bacteria for the gut, and plenty of earlier research has found a connection between &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/here-s-one-more-link-between-our-gut-and-our-brain-that-could-help-avoid-dementia"&gt;gut health and dementia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There's also strong evidence that fermented dairy foods like cheese are &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/advances/nmaa030"&gt;good for the heart&lt;/a&gt;, and heart health is something that has long been &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-heart-health-in-middle-age-could-predict-your-later-dementia-risk"&gt;thought to be important&lt;/a&gt; in dementia risk. As usual with dementia, there are likely many different contributors acting together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-181305" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-600x315.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although the present study did not include biomarker or mechanistic assessments, several nutritional characteristics of cheese may provide a plausible explanation for the observed association," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu17213363"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dementia has been declared a &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/global-action-plan-on-the-public-health-response-to-dementia-2017---2025"&gt;key public health priority&lt;/a&gt; by the United Nations, and it's thought that &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/dementia"&gt;at least 50 million people&lt;/a&gt; are currently living with the condition worldwide. That's likely to increase as the population ages, which is a particular concern in Japan, where the research was carried out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/strange-rocks-clinging-to-mummies-could-be-worlds-oldest-cheese"&gt;Strange Rocks Clinging to Mummies Could Be World's Oldest Cheese&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The statistics certainly aren't strong enough to suggest a regular cheesy snack is guaranteed to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/time-itself-could-be-a-crucial-element-in-preventing-dementia-study-finds"&gt;ward off dementia&lt;/a&gt;, but the indications are that it could help. The researchers are keen to expand their work to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Further research is warranted to clarify dose-response relationships, cheese subtypes, and underlying mechanisms," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu17213363"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu17213363"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nutrients&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:25:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxOVzFfeE9nLUdYWWNJdkhwYnlSLW5qOThvRmQ4Z2NjenFpel9yRUJiQVRWbi1COU4zc3dWTVFpNC02ZnZfTmFyMW1rM0JNOGlwaVRPZ2NHd2FYUHlHLVJkUWoxYTFNMG1mSldDMWE0V1NZWTI2YjZndnk3ZXJLRVd5YmloT3hDUGstODQ3R0lqdVk</guid></item><item><title>使犹他州人变得越来越胖和病态的4个神话- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51408419/the-4-myths-that-make-utahns-fatter-and-sicker</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone has heard questionable information and advice about health and weight loss over the years. It could be from well-intentioned friends, a story on the Internet, celebrity statements on social media, or the latest media story. But Joel Bikman and his scientist brother, the co-founders of an innovative new health and weight loss company, are using the latest science to help set the record straight to help people get much healthier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Myth #1 — My metabolism is slowing down&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people believe that as they age, their metabolism (the rate at which they utilize calories for energy) decreases. Not so, says Bikman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Contrary to popular belief, we've discovered that our metabolic rate doesn't change as we age," Bikman says. "Instead, metabolism is almost always coupled to our body weight. Interestingly, when someone starts to gain weight, their metabolic rate will actually go up. And if they lose weight, their metabolic rate will go down."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bikman says that instead of metabolism slowing down, far more people break their metabolism by following poor advice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's a popular weight loss reality show where people starve themselves and exercise like crazy to lose an incredible amount of weight in a relatively short period of time," Bikman says. "That can certainly work in the short-term, but there's a reason you never see reunion shows on these weight loss programs — they don't work long-term. As they inevitably get back in the real world, they start gaining weight again and their metabolism doesn't match it; it doesn't come back up with this incredible yo-yo in body weight."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They've effectively broken their metabolic rate," Bikman says. "That's when you have real problems. Fortunately, by carefully managing macros [protein, fats and carbohydrates], you can get things back to normal."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt; Photo: Sorapop Udomsri/Shutterstock.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Myth #2 — Exercise can make up for a bad diet&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may be tempted to buy-in to the idea that a good workout can compensate for a bad diet. That's simply not the case for almost anyone, according to Bikman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Everyone should get some amount of exercise 5-6 times a week," he says. "Though it's less for weight loss than it is for a host of other health benefits including cardio and brain health, your ability to maintain balance as you age, and especially for hormones and proper nutrient absorption."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Bikman, the best kind of exercise is the kind you'll actually do on a regular basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But that doesn't mean you can outrun, or out-exercise a bad diet — that's a particularly dangerous myth," Bikman says. "Even the heaviest workouts will only burn a few hundred calories, while eating the wrong kinds of food are not only resistant to being 'burned', they actively encourage your body to store body fat."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bikman adds that if you want to "burn" more calories, you can actually do it more effectively through a proper diet. "Your diet likely got you into the shape you're in, but it also can help get you into much better shape now and in the future."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Myth #3 — All calories are the same&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The expression, "A calorie is a calorie," is one saying that's particularly concerning, Bikman says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In a chemistry setting that may be correct, but it is absolutely misunderstood in the context of human nutrition and certainly in the context of what we do with energy in the body," Bikman says. "Yet people and experts repeat the same 'calories in, calories out' myth. By that same logic, you could argue that 2,000 calories of soda pop are treated the same within the body as 2,000 calories of properly balanced macronutrients. One essentially kills the body and makes you fat and sick, while the other sustains life and helps you thrive."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And that saying completely ignores the impact on your body's systems and hormones," Bikman says. "Experts have clearly shown that hormones, like insulin, have a profound effect on what our body does by way of burning calories, storing calories or even efficiently wasting calories."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"By limiting carbs, and consuming the right blend of proteins and healthy fats, you'll not only have much more sustainable energy," he says. "It will help accelerate your metabolism, help strengthen your immune system, and even aid in gut health and brain health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt; Photo: Jacek Chabraszewski/Shutterstock.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Myth #4 — A low-fat diet is the best for weight loss&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you've ever tried to lose weight, there is a good chance that you've at least considered a low-fat diet. In 1977, the US Dietary Guidelines were published and even without significant evidence from randomized controlled trials and testing, these guidelines recommended a significant reduction in dietary fat, and thus began the nationwide mentality to fear fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"People have been told to not eat fats that are clinically shown to be healthy in favor of refined carbohydrates, and the results have been devastating," Bikman says. "Since 1977, the average adult American is nearly 30 pounds heavier; as reported by the Centers for Disease Control, a government agency."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bikman shares that there's overwhelming evidence of the benefits of a high-fat diet for overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fats not only help you feel full, they help with brain health, gut health and metabolic health," Bikman says. "This doesn't mean that you can't enjoy carbs, but you need to realize that there are no essential carbs; just essential amino acids (from protein), and essential fatty acids."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Focus on a wide spectrum of healthy fats from animal sources (like eggs, beef, salmon) and fruit sources (olive, coconut and avocado)," Bikman says. "Refined seed and vegetable oils should be avoided at all costs; they're particularly harmful."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt; Photo: HLTH Code&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Bringing solutions from the lab to the real world&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even with all of the information that Bikman and others share, people around the world constantly ask what they should do for their health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ideally, we all would have the knowledge, time, discipline and budget to plan, purchase and prepare perfect meals," Bikman says. "But it simply doesn't happen; people get busy, they get stressed and they make unhealthy choices that derail their health goals."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It became apparent to Bikman that he needed to be part of the solution to help people achieve their best health more quickly, and especially to assist those that don't always have the time, knowledge or discipline to eat healthy. In response, Bikman and the co-founding team of metabolic and industry experts recently created &lt;a href="https://gethlth.com/?utm_source=KSL&amp;amp;utm_medium=advertorial" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;HLTH Code Complete Meal&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bikman says these carefully formulated meal shakes are designed to promote healthy weight management, gut health, brain health, even hair, skin and nail health. HLTH Code Complete Meal features an optimized, science-backed blend of protein, collagen, healthy fats, apple cider vinegar, probiotics, fiber, vitamins and minerals—with no added sugar or any artificial ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We're very fortunate to have a leading metabolic scientist as our formulator," he says. "An incredible amount of work went into making this nutritionally balanced and optimized, yet we knew that if it didn't taste good, no one would use them consistently."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Solving hunger pangs the right way&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to eating, Bikman says it's easy to consume plenty of calories and still feel hungry. This is because the calories consumed are not the right types of calories to provide essential nutrition. He refers to this as "mis-nourishment" and he says it's ruining many people's health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Each HLTH Code Complete Meal shake is packed with optimized amounts of these ingredients to leave you feeling full and energized for hours," Bikman says. "Yet it's more convenient and affordable than virtually any meal you could make or buy."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bikman says the shakes are quick and easy to make: Just add two scoops of Creamy Vanilla or Chocolate Macadamia Complete Meal Powder to 8 oz. of cold water and shake or blend. For general wellness, he recommends replacing one meal daily. To reset your health or for weight loss, replace up to two meals per day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These are by FAR the BEST meal replacement shakes I've EVER had. and I've tried many. These win by a long shot. They taste like heaven PLUS they're keto-friendly, and I'm keto so win, win, win. 100% HIGHLY recommend them. Couldn't love them more," said &lt;a href="https://gethlth.com/?utm_source=KSL&amp;amp;utm_medium=advertorial" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;one reviewer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another reviewer shares, "They are tasty. In addition, they fill me up and keep me full for the entire afternoon. I have managed to pass a weight loss plateau by using these as my lunch every day at work."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet another review said, "I've been drinking this for 5 months to break my intermittent fast and I'm in my best shape and down 21 pounds. I can't recommend this enough!! Plus it has a great flavor!! What's not to love??"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Does HLTH Code make weight loss easier?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Bikman, the best health starts with the right blend of nutrition. Increased energy, feeling more vibrant, a stronger immune system, a clearer mind, improved gut health, and an improved appearance are some of the benefits from improving one's nutrition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt; Photo: HLTH Code&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The comprehensive benefits of HLTH Code Complete Meal are especially helpful if you're trying to lose weight," Bikman says. "Weight loss is rarely easy. There has to be the right changes in both hormones and caloric balance to signal to the body that it's time to start burning, not storing, body fat."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bikman adds that based on the best available studies on human metabolism, along with exercise, &lt;a href="https://gethlth.com/?utm_source=KSL&amp;amp;utm_medium=advertorial" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;HLTH Code Complete Meal&lt;/a&gt; helps people lose weight without the need for counting every calorie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your satisfaction is guaranteed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're nervous about trying something new and making changes to your nutrition plan, don't be. Bikman stands by his HLTH Code Meal Replacement products and is willing to guarantee your satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You have nothing to lose (except those extra pounds) and everything to gain—in terms of wellness and confidence," Bikman says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, if you've been looking for improved wellness and healthy weight management, then &lt;a href="https://gethlth.com/?utm_source=KSL&amp;amp;utm_medium=advertorialhttps://gethlth.com/shop/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;HLTH Code Meal Replacement&lt;/a&gt; could well be your answer. For exclusive savings on your first order, visit &lt;a href="https://gethlth.com/?utm_source=KSL&amp;amp;utm_medium=advertorial" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;getHLTH.com&lt;/a&gt; and enter the discount code KSL at checkout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;The opinions and conclusions expressed in this article are the sponsor's own and do not reflect the views or opinions of KSL.com. This Site Does Not Provide Medical Advice. Any content on this Site, such as text, graphics, images, information obtained from, or contained on this Site are for informational purposes only. The content is not intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the advice of your physician or other qualified health provider with any questions you may have regarding a medical condition. Never disregard professional medical advice or delay in seeking it because of something you have read on this site! The owner and operator of this site do not recommend or endorse any specific tests, physicians, products, procedures, opinions, or other information that may be mentioned on the site. Reliance on any information provided by the Operator, including their employees, contractors or others appearing on the Site at the invitation of the Operator, or other visitors to the Site is solely at your own risk. If you think you may have a medical emergency, call your doctor or 911 immediately.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:09:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQNVpfcnNsMkNmeTZuTjJsZGdCTUFvVWtPeVRNa3Z5cHFXU2wtNlVQdHBXeEJFQ2pMbEtKaU02VTNaeFh4c2NmWEwzMEFqR0NmLTIzb1VvU2QteEo1S0pySUVYOFJCS3hPTWVvcWJ2US16U0drenRZZjdjVTM1ZTJVblZoVERlblR2a0tV</guid></item><item><title>享受橙子吸收维生素C和免疫支持的最佳时间是什么时候-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/what-is-the-best-time-to-enjoy-oranges-for-vitamin-c-absorption-and-immune-support/articleshow/125524949.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oranges are one of the most reliable and delicious sources of vitamin C, a nutrient essential for keeping your immune system strong and protecting your cells from everyday damage. Many people wonder whether eating an orange at a specific time, such as in the morning or on an empty stomach, can increase vitamin C absorption or improve immunity. In reality, timing matters far less than consistency. What truly supports your health is regularly including oranges and other vitamin C-rich foods in your daily diet. Because vitamin C is water-soluble and not stored in the body, you need a steady intake to maintain healthy levels. Eating oranges frequently also provides fibre, antioxidants, and hydration, all of which play a role in overall wellbeing and immune support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;When to eat oranges for better digestion and nutrient uptake&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;There isn’t a single “perfect” time to eat an orange, but what truly matters is including oranges and other vitamin C-rich foods regularly as part of a balanced diet. Because vitamin C is water-soluble and not stored in the body, consistent intake throughout the week is essential for maintaining healthy levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You don’t need to eat oranges on an empty stomach for better absorption, and for some people, doing so may even cause discomfort due to the fruit’s natural acidity. Oranges can be enjoyed at any point in the day, whether in the morning, afternoon, or as a refreshing snack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;The Future of Vitamin C: Enhanced Formulations And Advancements for Brighter Skin in 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, those prone to acid reflux should avoid eating them right before bed or immediately after a heavy meal, as citrus can aggravate symptoms. Eating oranges earlier in the day or between meals is often a more comfortable choice. You can also increase your vitamin C intake by pairing oranges with other vitamin C-rich foods such as bell peppers, strawberries, kiwi, broccoli, and Brussels sprouts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Oranges for immune support and cold-fighting benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin C is one of the most important nutrients for immunity. It helps protect cells from free-radical damage, supports the production of immune cells, and contributes to quicker recovery from everyday infections. While vitamin C cannot prevent the common cold, studies suggest that regular intake may reduce the duration and severity of cold symptoms. According to a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bmcpublichealth.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s12889-023-17229-8?" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;2023 meta‑analysis published in BMC Public Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, vitamin C supplementation (≥ 1 g/day) reduced the severity of common cold symptoms by 15% compared to placebo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is where oranges come in. Eating them frequently, along with a variety of fruits and vegetables, helps you maintain adequate vitamin C levels year-round. Their antioxidant compounds also support immune defences, helping the body respond more effectively to viruses and other stressors. Even though supplements are widely available, whole oranges offer additional benefits, including fibre, hydration, and plant compounds that work together to protect overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Vitamin C content in oranges and daily needs&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A single navel orange contains roughly 83 mg of vitamin C, making it one of the richest and most convenient dietary sources. Because vitamin C isn’t stored in the body, daily intake is essential to prevent deficiency and keep immune and skin health in balance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recommended daily amounts include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;75 mg for adult women&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;90 mg for adult men&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;85 mg for pregnant women&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;120 mg for people who are breastfeeding&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who smoke or are regularly exposed to secondhand smoke need 35 mg more vitamin C per day than non-smokers because smoking increases oxidative stress and reduces vitamin C levels in the body. Most people can meet their daily needs through food alone, and including one orange a day is an easy way to cover a large portion of those requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Eating oranges with iron-rich foods for better nutrient absorption&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most beneficial times to eat oranges is during or after an iron-rich meal. Vitamin C significantly boosts the absorption of non-heme iron, the type found in plant foods such as legumes, leafy greens, nuts, seeds, and whole grains. This is particularly helpful for vegetarians, vegans, and anyone with low iron levels, as improved absorption supports healthy energy, red blood cell production, and immune function. Adding oranges to your meals is easy: enjoy a few slices after a spinach salad, squeeze fresh citrus over lentil dishes, or pair a small glass of orange juice with an iron-rich breakfast to maximise iron uptake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin C is highly sensitive to heat, light, and prolonged storage, so how you handle and store oranges can significantly affect their nutrient content. To retain the maximum vitamin C, it’s best to eat oranges fresh and raw. Keep them out of direct sunlight, store them in a cool, dry place or in the refrigerator, and consume them soon after purchase rather than letting them sit for long periods. Avoid cooking, boiling, or heating oranges, as high temperatures can destroy much of their vitamin C. Enjoy them whole, juiced, or added to salads and snacks to get the most nutritional benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for general informational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the guidance of a qualified healthcare provider regarding any medical condition or lifestyle change.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also Read: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/what-is-the-right-time-to-eat-yoghurt-for-gut-health-probiotics-digestion-and-stronger-bones/articleshow/125489231.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;What is the right time to eat yoghurt for gut health, probiotics, digestion, and stronger bones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-AFBVV95cUxPYjlfWmcxb21WcG5NOXpJRDNxS2ZienVtMWhndTQ5bVdLdTdlbW9LTV9mUnpOSXB2RUVPQlRtSC00bm91dGtOUzVUZnczWFpCUzA1Y1F5R250ZlRtMkRLTTZJNWpxa3dCRWJrb1hpbWljVDZZWXk2dmx4Q2wyWjVQWm83bEpONXp2WkhkRTdoSk02VWpjckFZRl8zWGFpN0dWUG01Wm9ucy1wZm1MQVp3MklVUnBGUlVDTzRHMjhfbmY5MDdMT1RiYmxzcHZ5SHkzMHJBcTY2c2NESDI5OERzenI5cVIxaEVxUnBNUDJ3aFZFdTQ1RE05btIB_gFBVV95cUxQTTJvbHNKTHkwNTM1RG41eTBhU0V5dUJDWVhJNEM0dTVObVAydmVGZjhPM2VqU2VVbDdzU1JlRHNRbW9uTTZxdWFIbFNDbVE1YldFSkNIbktIcVI5T0tCWkJpV2Z3VEVua0xJREtwTG1HbzFWNTE2Zm1RR1J1bjZ1S3R0TjNxNTM5cG5EaF9xRy1NNTJjWjdXenRNbl9YdW9rVHk2UldtMXlzT1loRHdDdTE1MFNMTmk0Q3NnNWctbFh3d3RNZzdkRGdRQmk2eGpQOGdQLWNnTnJzbFJvSnpnODBGSlJMd3EzRDh0Wnk1WkZWRGxqcFhEbzJiWUhhUQ</guid></item><item><title>长寿专家建议的5个老化技巧：吃瘦蛋白质，与亲人共度时光等等|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/longevity-expert-suggests-5-tips-to-age-well-eat-lean-proteins-spend-time-with-loved-ones-and-more-101763896590776.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/longevity-expert-suggests-5-tips-to-age-well-eat-lean-proteins-spend-time-with-loved-ones-and-more-101763896590776.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Talks of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/longevity-doctor-shares-3-hacks-for-deeper-restorative-sleep-cool-your-room-to-101763893279200.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="longevity"&gt;longevity&lt;/a&gt; keep popping every now and then, especially when a centenarian makes headlines and everyone's looking for scoops on their long life's secrets. The curiosity to add years to life is not a novel concept; it has been around for a long time. Often, many wonder if there's a formula or secret pill. But the actual truth is way simpler than you think.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/23/550x309/boiled_egg_1752727803691_1763896963472.jpg" alt="Longevity expert recommends adding lean protein, like eggs to your diet.(Picture credit: Shutterstock)" title="Longevity expert recommends adding lean protein, like eggs to your diet.(Picture credit: Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/23/550x309/boiled_egg_1752727803691_1763896963472.jpg" alt="Longevity expert recommends adding lean protein, like eggs to your diet.(Picture credit: Shutterstock)" title="Longevity expert recommends adding lean protein, like eggs to your diet.(Picture credit: Shutterstock)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Longevity expert recommends adding lean protein, like eggs to your diet.(Picture credit: Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ALSO READ: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/100yearold-japanese-chef-from-jiro-dreams-of-sushi-documentary-shares-his-secret-to-long-life-101761653714078.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="100-year-old Japanese chef from Jiro Dreams of Sushi documentary shares his secret to long life: 'best medicine is...'"&gt;100-year-old Japanese chef from Jiro Dreams of Sushi documentary shares his secret to long life: 'best medicine is...'&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Ht Lifestyle connected to Dr Farman Ali, longevity expert and specialist surgeon at Tata Main Hospital, to learn more about longevity. For the surgeon, the meaning of longevity is different.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Longevity is not about immortality; it is about impact. It is never about adding years to life, but instead, it’s all about adding life to years," he said. He identified a very big distinction that many people may confuse. Longevity is about the quality of life, not quantity. It is not about how long you live, but how well you live your life. You could live to be an octogenarian and beyond, and yet struggle with multiple chronic illnesses with severe mobility issues. This reduces the quality of your life. True longevity includes independence, vitality, and &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/aiimstrained-gastroenterologist-reveals-5-food-combinations-for-good-health-eat-chia-seed-with-101763651754740.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="good health"&gt;good health&lt;/a&gt; in the golden years of your life.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But what's true longevity? &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;It is not exactly measured by the number of birthdays you celebrate, but whether you can keep your resilience and good health intact as you age.&lt;/span&gt; You could be in your 60s, strength training, eating healthy, travelling around, beginning new hobbies, and enjoying life without any exhaustion.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Farman revealed that longevity depends on multiple factors. He said, “Longevity depends on genetic, environmental, and, most of all, daily life habits.” &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;In his practice and across the broader wellness industry, he has observed how even the smallest and consistent choices can have a huge impact on the body over time.&lt;/span&gt; This is why you need to pay attention to your lifestyle habits as they impact your long-term health substantially.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Here are the 5 habits Dr Farman shared that help you live longer and healthier:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;1. Focus on quality sleep:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/20/550x309/sleeping_without_a_pillow_1763638378956_1763638386349.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Make sure you sleep well everyday!(Adobe Stock)" title="Make sure you sleep well everyday!(Adobe Stock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Make sure you sleep well everyday!(Adobe Stock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;There's a reason why experts across the health and wellness industry keep recommending prioritising quality sleep, and for all the right reasons. Dr Farman also advised sleeping well for better ageing. From immediate benefits like waking up well-rested with sharper focus in the morning, to several long-term advantages, sleep unconditionally supports your well-being.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Farman, highlighting sleep as be body's natural repair system, explained, "Aim for 7-8 hours of rest, uninterruptedly. Poor sleep creates inflammation, weakens the immune system, and accelerates ageing.” You can protect your health across decades if you follow healthy sleeping habits.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;2. Eat mindfully and in moderation:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diet is one of the pillars of good health. You have probably heard of the saying, ‘You are what you eat.’ Yes, it is quite literal. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;What you put on your plate determines how you are going to age or if you suffer, but also whether you are likely to develop co-morbidities.&lt;/span&gt; While genes are one of the factors, diet too is instrumental.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Farman advised an appropriate diet, “A diet of vegetables (such as spinach and broccoli), fruits (such as berries and apples), whole grains (like oats and brown rice), and lean proteins (such as fish, eggs, or lentils) is one that is balanced, with limited intake of sugar, salt, and processed foods.&lt;/span&gt;”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Simultaneously, pay attention to how you eat, as the longevity expert insisted on eating slowly and stopping if you are feeling full so that your metabolism remains healthy.&lt;/span&gt; When you eat fast, you don't allow your body to register the fullness, till the time it extremely strains your digestive system.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;3. Stay physically active:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/08/24/550x309/athletes12_1756044811029_1756044811187.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Regular movements keep your mobility levels high. (Shutterstock)" title="Regular movements keep your mobility levels high. (Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Regular movements keep your mobility levels high. (Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;The longevity expert warned against a sedentary lifestyle, highlighting that when you move, your joints, heart, and mind stay healthy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;A combination of walking, stretching, and light strength training for at least 30 minutes daily can help improve one's circulation, mood, and overall longevity,” he recommended, emphasising that physical activity needs to be a part of daily routine.&lt;/span&gt; This means movement is non-negotiable. Years later, you are likely to retain independence and mobility because you keep exercising every day.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;4. Manage stress positively:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lifestyles are becoming more dizzying, running at breakneck, almost hypersonic speed, from looming deadlines to back-to-back meetings. Your mind keeps buzzing, always teetering on the edge. Dr Farman reminded that stress management is crucial, and one needs to ensure they adopt mindfulness techniques to ease stress responses. The reason? &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;He shared that chronic stress releases hormones that accelerate the process of ageing, which is why stress management is one of the fundamentals if you wish to age healthily.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He recommended some techniques to manage daily stress, “Practice mindfulness, deep breathing, or meditation daily to create calm within. Even 10 minutes of quiet reflection can be soothing for your nervous system and help you improve your mental clarity.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;5. Build meaningful connections:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/22/original/hangouts_1763805013280.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Be in touch with your friends and hang out often to reduce stress. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Be in touch with your friends and hang out often to reduce stress. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Be in touch with your friends and hang out often to reduce stress. (Picture credit: Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;Lastly, focus on building social connections. Dr Farman insisted that it's one of the most prominent factors that determine how long one will live.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Spend time with your family and friends, nurture the relationships that get you through life, and find meaning in your community or work,” he advised.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So how often should you socialise? He suggested, “Ideally, aim to socialise for at least 5–6 hours per week, whether through calls, gatherings, or shared activities.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;People who maintain social connections are likely to live healthier lives. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;So if you tend to ghost, avoid calls, cancel plans, or take 2-3 business days to reply back to your friends, it's high time you reconsider this habit.&lt;/span&gt; Try to regularly be in touch with friends and family, whether through physical meet-ups or calls.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 01:21:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-wFBVV95cUxQSFlKSW9HRHBtNVRITnBrcW5Db1g4SjBRR0pjTkhzcDgwWk5keERfQU0tLWhMLXZjcmhqOTduZ0dfRko3cWlFRjRwbk80SHF2Y1lCYk1rZUJER0xEeTg5VEhsaVNGR1ljcDh1OFFuZGRPWEpyeWFGNWZfeHA5S1NPc1JvS0JLR3NpcDZHXy1oQk13VVRMRks3Rk1wMEJYUDN3WXY0anVtYzNvUlppYndreHJrLWxJdjNQWEJnS25lSmJvSlVZWURDTEdCd3NsbzRQTl9TM1hySnlBdnc3dk9jSmo3NDE3cjFFQnVBZW15Y1kzR1pSenRubUlwTdIBgAJBVV95cUxOcmp2MjY1U0hQUjVWUTFnUG1tekN0di1oQjFNNXNMYUNCZHJsa3QweEJLcHphWGlLeVVHOG1VaG8yWFdYWGdPRTFLU1d5RXJrWkZCQTQtNHRrQ1l4b05GWTZMekVYRXNTM1lvOFFHSE9rcGZpY1pHLU5SQmtkaVZQMExiZXZ6aUoyMTFzZDZjMEZLQ1YzYXA2d2JGbVJWaFBDRHhqMGdLQXlndHdCMGNERXR5YnFfbHBaMWc2YmZ0MFRlZHh3SWZzMDN4dl9pRlJ1NDBsS2FnaG5NVTZ3N2lBUlNPUGxlQklnVTJPVll0RERBMmlVbEl3eW85OXA2czla</guid></item><item><title>美国报道全球首例H5N5禽流感死亡病例- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/worlds-first-death-from-h5n5-bird-flu-strain-reported-in-us</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A resident of Washington state has died after contracting a rare strain of bird  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="182743" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt; previously only reported in animals, &lt;a href="https://doh.wa.gov/newsroom/grays-harbor-county-resident-dies-complications-avian-influenza"&gt;state health officials said&lt;/a&gt; – the second human fatality linked to the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="182743" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;virus&lt;/a&gt; in the United States this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The patient was only identified as "an older adult with underlying health conditions" and had been hospitalized since early this month, the Washington state Department of Health &lt;a href="https://doh.wa.gov/newsroom/grays-harbor-county-resident-dies-complications-avian-influenza"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tests conducted by the University of Washington confirmed the patient was suffering from H5N5 avian  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="182743" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;influenza&lt;/a&gt;, the department &lt;a href="https://doh.wa.gov/newsroom/grays-harbor-county-resident-dies-complications-avian-influenza"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; in a statement, calling it "the first recorded infection with this variant in a person globally."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/us-records-its-first-death-from-bird-flu-in-tragic-end-to-louisiana-case"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;US Records Its First Death From Bird Flu in Tragic End to Louisiana Case&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The result was confirmed by the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The risk to the public remains low. No other people involved have tested positive for avian influenza," it &lt;a href="https://doh.wa.gov/newsroom/grays-harbor-county-resident-dies-complications-avian-influenza"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;. "There is no evidence of transmission of this virus between people."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_148481" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-148481" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/chickens_flock_outside_642.jpg" alt="chickens outside" class="wp-image-148481 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/chickens_flock_outside_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/chickens_flock_outside_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-148481" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;A mix of domestic birds may be the source of the exposure. (&lt;a href="https://pixabay.com/photos/chicken-flock-of-chickens-poultry-3949199/"&gt;RitaE/Pixabay&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The patient has "a backyard flock of mixed domestic birds," and officials believe this was the source of exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/bird-flu/situation-summary/index.html"&gt;The CDC has recorded&lt;/a&gt; more than 70 human cases of bird flu this year. A person died after contracting H5N1 in Louisiana in January.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-181305" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-600x315.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-does-the-world-health-organisation-do" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73079" data-postid="182743" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt; has recorded more than 1,000 bird flu cases in humans since 2003 in 25 countries – a figure that includes all strains of the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;© &lt;a href="terms-and-conditions"&gt;Agence France-Presse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 23:55:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxNaWdYVFFURTEtWFlKVkIwTHU0U3VjQ3pVSThSanF2bVUyWTNVcG1DNUktMk51bjljU2lGUFQtZnNjQ2RCZDBIQndFZXVOWUk0OTUyQTNuSmFvNTRLV2s2LVo2UHVoTGMzZ0FobTNJWExSY3lWcWIzc2J0WjdIMG8zcUJEbXg0R1dDVGFCUFJCQVhRdw</guid></item><item><title>FDA删除“黑匣子”警告后对更年期激素治疗的了解- PBS</title><link>https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/what-to-know-about-menopause-hormone-therapy-after-fda-removed-black-box-warnings</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-text"&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.politifact.com/article/2025/nov/19/fda-black-box-warning-menopause-hormone-therapy/"&gt;Politifact&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What does it mean when a warning label is removed from a medication after two decades?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Nov. 10, the U.S. Food and Drug Administration said it will ask companies to remove most “black box” safety warnings — used on medications to warn patients of serious health risks —  from hormone drugs commonly used to treat menopause symptoms. The change comes after years of advocacy from &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/nejmp1514242"&gt;gynecologists&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/02/01/magazine/menopause-hot-flashes-hormone-therapy.html"&gt;patients&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.acog.org/news/news-releases/2025/11/acog-president-says-label-change-on-estrogen-will-increase-access-to-hormone-therapy"&gt;professional medical organizations&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The FDA began requiring the &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03687-0#ref-CR1" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;warnings&lt;/a&gt; in 2003 after results from a large study raised concerns the medications could increase the risk of breast cancer, stroke and heart attack. &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/nejmp1514242" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Patients became hesitant&lt;/a&gt; to take the medications, and &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/11/10/health/hormone-therapy-menopause-fda-warning-wellness" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;prescriptions decreased&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/show/how-a-decades-old-study-gave-hormone-therapy-for-menopause-a-bad-reputation"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WATCH:&lt;/strong&gt; How a decades-old study gave hormone therapy for menopause a bad reputation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the science wasn’t so clear cut. The study that drove the change included mostly women older than 60, and hormone formulations and delivery methods different from what’s often used today. More recent scientific research has shown the medications to be much safer than previously believed, especially for women under 60. Some types of hormone therapy slightly increase a woman’s risk for certain health conditions, but the increased risk is small.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We spoke with four OB/GYNs who specialize in menopause management to find out what you need to know before your next doctor’s appointment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What are the types of menopause hormone therapies?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Menopause hormone therapy, sometimes called hormone replacement therapy or HRT, refers to medications prescribed to treat menopause symptoms, including hot flashes, night sweats, mood swings and vaginal dryness. They work by replenishing hormones, such as estrogen and progesterone, that naturally diminish during the transition to menopause.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The medications take several forms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.med.umich.edu/1libr/urology/EstrogenVaginalCream.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Local estrogen therapy&lt;/a&gt; comes in creams, rings and tablets. These treatments are called “local” because their impact is limited to the area where they are applied, such as the vagina. These therapies address symptoms including vaginal dryness, itching, urinary tract infections and the sudden urge to urinate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With local therapies, the hormones are absorbed into the bloodstream only in trace amounts, making them a low-risk option. However, it also means they can’t treat broader symptoms, such as hot flashes or mood swings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/treatments/15245-hormone-therapy-for-menopause-symptoms" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Systemic hormone therapy&lt;/a&gt;, on the other hand, is designed to circulate the hormones throughout the bloodstream. It offers whole-body benefits but also carries more risk as a result. These therapies are administered orally or absorbed through the skin via patches, sprays or gels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Systemic therapies include estrogen-only therapy, progesterone-only therapy or a combination of estrogen and progesterone. Women who have had their uterus removed only need to take estrogen. Women who still have their uterus must also take progesterone, often in combination with estrogen, to  protect against endometrial cancer. The FDA said black-box warnings for &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/news-events/press-announcements/hhs-advances-womens-health-removes-misleading-fda-warnings-hormone-replacement-therapy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;endometrial cancer&lt;/a&gt; will remain on estrogen-only systemic medications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Different versions of estrogen and progesterone carry different risks and benefits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The treatments are highly individualized,” Dr. Marcy Nagpal, an OB/GYN at the Medical University of South Carolina, said in an email to PolitiFact. Talking with your doctor is the best way to know which therapy might be right for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Which patients are the best candidates for these meds?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Women with menopausal symptoms who are under 60, or women who had their last menstrual period within the last 10 years, doctors told us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But others can be candidates, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“At this time, it’s reasonable for anyone who feels that they are experiencing symptoms related to menopause to consider evaluation and treatment options,” Nagpal said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don’t have symptoms, you do not need to take menopausal hormone therapy, said Dr. Jennifer Howell, a Duke University OB/GYN. It’s “not generally recommended for health promotion.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some people might be less suited for systemic therapies. Among them: Women who have or had breast cancer; who suffered a heart attack or stroke; who have had blood clots in their legs, lungs or brain; or who have active liver or gallbladder disease. Alternative medications and non-hormonal options to manage the menopause symptoms also are available, doctors said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What are the benefits?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doctors we talked to overwhelmingly pointed to symptom relief.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hot flashes and night sweats stop, sleep improves, mood is stabilized, joint pain often improves, and vaginal dryness and pain with vaginal penetration resolves,” said Dr. Karen Adams, OB/GYN and director of the menopause program at Stanford Medicine. She said recurrent urinary tract infections and frequent urination can stop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Nanette Santoro, an OB/GYN and professor at the University of Colorado, said, “Depending on just how annoying and disruptive those symptoms are, (the medications) can be a godsend.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While taken, systemic therapy can also prevent the &lt;a href="https://theros.org.uk/information-and-support/osteoporosis/treatment/hormone-replacement-therapy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;rapid loss of bone density&lt;/a&gt; that typically accompanies menopause.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Women can lose up to 20% of bone mass in the first five years after their final period,” said Adams. Stronger bones can reduce the risk of fracture and osteoporosis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But contrary to recent claims, data on whether hormone therapy can prevent heart attacks or dementia are not conclusive, Howell and Santoro said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/rtvhshHADM0?si=_F81f75DOjsIaHaL&amp;amp;t=87" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;FDA announcement&lt;/a&gt; about the removal of black box warnings, assertions made about significantly improved cardiovascular health and lower Alzheimer’s risk are not supported by evidence, Adams said. “We absolutely do not have that data.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Likewise, the statement that these menopause therapies are life-extending “goes very far beyond the data and is in exactly no clinical guidelines,” Santoro said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What are the risks of menopause hormone therapy?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With few exceptions, most symptomatic women can use local low-dose estrogen without risk, Howell said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The local forms should never have had this labeling at all,” Adams said. “The black box was placed on all estrogen products without regard to whether they were local or systemic, and a correction of that was long overdue.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/show/fda-head-explains-decision-to-drop-black-box-warnings-from-menopause-hormone-treatment"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WATCH:&lt;/strong&gt; FDA head explains decision to drop ‘black box’ warnings from menopause hormone treatment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Systemic hormone therapies carry more risk and can be navigated with a more in-depth conversation with a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research shows that women who take a combination of estrogen and progesterone have an increased risk of breast cancer, but it’s “very small,” Howell said, and mainly pertains to prolonged use among older women.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This risk increases slowly and incrementally over time,” Santoro said, and applies to those who take hormones for longer periods, usually more than four to five years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The risk profile also depends on the type of hormones a patient takes. Newer formulas appear to be more neutral for breast cancer risk than the formulas used in the 2002 study that led to the warnings, Adams said. And some estrogen-only therapies have been found to reduce breast cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With some hormones, the risk varies depending on how they are taken. For example, some oral medications increase the risk for developing blood clots, but when the same medication is absorbed through the skin, it doesn’t appear to have that risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sorting out the risks and benefits for hormone therapy is a task for a patient and her doctor,” Santoro said, to determine the best type of hormones, how long to take them, and how to manage any risks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Will this change impact insurance coverage?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doctors said it’s unlikely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most generic hormone therapy treatments are covered by insurance, Howell said, but specialized formulations that can be more convenient, safe or less messy can be challenging to get covered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tips for discussing HRT with your doctor&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are approaching menopause, or already in the throes of it, here are some pointers about discussing hormone therapy with your doctor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, make sure you and your doctor are compatible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is a topic that can require a deep well of knowledge,” Nagpal said. “It’s reasonable to ask your doctor if they are comfortable with menopause medicine and, if not, to recommend someone who is.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Menopause Society, a nonprofit for healthcare professionals focused on improving menopause care, offers a search function to find &lt;a href="https://portal.menopause.org/NAMS/NAMS/Directory/Menopause-Practitioner.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;certified providers&lt;/a&gt; in your area who have passed a test about menopausal management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When scheduling, consider making an appointment specifically to address treatment options, rather than trying to combine the discussion with other concerns, Nagpal said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the day of your appointment, Santoro recommended bringing a list of your symptoms, ordered by which you would most like addressed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not always possible to take care of everything with hormones alone, and knowing the bothersomeness is very helpful to me as the doctor, so I make my best recommendation,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Knowing your own health history — current medications, past health events, how long since your last period — and your family health history can also help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nagpal advises keeping an open mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Therapies that are appropriate for one person may not be indicated or appropriate for someone else,” she said. Getting the right dose and regimen might take some trial and error, doctors said. So don’t be alarmed if it takes a few visits and changes to get the most appropriate treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

                                            &lt;div class="inline-invite inline-invite-type__funding inline-invite-style__default"&gt;
        
                    &lt;div class="inline-invite-funding__box"&gt;
                &lt;figure class="invite__logo"&gt;
                    &lt;svg class="svg"&gt;&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#pbs-newshour-horiz-refresh"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
                &lt;/figure&gt;
                &lt;p class="invite_heading"&gt;
                    A free press is a cornerstone of a healthy democracy. 
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p class="invite_body"&gt;
                    Support trusted journalism and civil dialogue. 
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://give.newshour.org/page/88646/donate/1?ea.tracking.id=pbs_news_sept_2025_article&amp;amp;supporter.appealCode=N2509AW1000100" class="donation-link ga-click-funding ga-click-ender-funding"&gt;
                    &lt;button class="donate-button"&gt;Donate now&lt;/button&gt;
                    &lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="#000000" class="bi bi-arrow-right-short" version="1.1" id="svg1" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:svg="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;
                    &lt;defs id="defs1"&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;
                    &lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" d="M4 8a.5.5 0 0 1 .5-.5h5.793L8.146 5.354a.5.5 0 1 1 .708-.708l3 3a.5.5 0 0 1 0 .708l-3 3a.5.5 0 0 1-.708-.708L10.293 8.5H4.5A.5.5 0 0 1 4 8z" id="path1"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
                    &lt;/svg&gt;
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;


                                    &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PBS</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 23:50:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxPRVRrdmlwM3ZzUnJMdk9mOWJoSS1VRWlqRXBZZHhKbkd5X2hFWjVQdklNNjRVN2NPcjVXUzlJaHRFUm8zU3FCc0Y1enhhMzdBWTJ6eGdlZFFhVnJCSUtyU3pjcFFGcV9fNUVpRVdJb3BXdTRfcXVzZWcxcE1BS0NqR3VCSFFwNENubjJDdnR6Q3JGOXdybms5MlNUSXRhaGNRN3lSTFVLdHFUalRMUzJNV1ZkWUdOM29V</guid></item><item><title>根据专家的说法，红茶支持健康的6种令人惊讶的方式-超越咖啡因踢-真正简单</title><link>https://www.realsimple.com/health-benefits-of-black-tea-11854556</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="realsimple-sc-page_1-0" class="comp realsimple-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--summary realsimple-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Black tea's caffeine and L-theanine content can improve focus, alertness, and mental clarity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The range of polyphenols in black tea supports immune, heart, metabolic, and gut health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Despite containing some caffeine, black tea can also support optimal hydration.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Of all the &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/types-of-tea-7152305" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;tea varieties&lt;/a&gt; out there (and there are a lot), black tea is among the most popular. If not enjoyed as-is, this tea is often the base for popular blends like chai, Earl Grey, English breakfast, and more.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Black tea is a type of tea that originated in China and is made from the Camellia sinensis plant—the same plant from which white, green, and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/oolong-tea-benefits-8765855" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;oolong tea&lt;/a&gt; are made,” says &lt;a href="https://wellnourishedmamas.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Jamie Adams&lt;/a&gt;, MS, RDN, RPYT, women’s health dietitian and founder of Mamaste Nutrition. What sets black tea apart from these other Camellia varieties is the way it’s made—through a process called oxidation.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “The oxidation process involves exposing the tea leaves to air, allowing enzymes to transform their natural compounds, which deepens its flavor and color,” shares Samina Kalloo, RDN, CDN, registered dietitian, nutrition counselor and founder of Samina Kalloo Nutrition.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; But aside from black tea’s flavor and versatility, this popular caffeinated beverage actually boasts quite a few health benefits. Read on to discover six of the most impressive ways black tea boosts overall health.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-supports-immunity"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Supports Immunity &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The plant compounds found in black tea exhibit antioxidant properties, which can &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/immunity-boosting-teas-8760555" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;boost immune health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “Antioxidants work by removing free radicals in the body and combating cell damage, both of which may help &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/anti-inflammatory-tea" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;reduce inflammation&lt;/a&gt; and risk of chronic disease,” says Adams. “These powerful antioxidants are formed during the oxidation process,” adds Kalloo. In fact, a 2025 study found that consuming a greater variety of flavonoid rich foods, including black tea, may reduce all-cause mortality and the risk of cancer and other chronic diseases by anywhere from 6% to 20%.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-improves-mental-focus-and-alertness"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Improves Mental Focus and Alertness &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Black tea is often turned to first thing in the morning for a caffeine boost to start the day. And while many people are aware of black tea’s caffeine content, they may not know that it also contains an amino acid called L-theanine. “Both caffeine and L-theanine may improve alertness and cognitive performance,” explains Adams. Recent research echoes this sentiment, highlighting how this specific nutrient combination aids in mental clarity.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-boosts-heart-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Boosts Heart Health &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The polyphenols in black tea are even beneficial for those with heart health concerns—or looking to steer clear of them. “Just two cups a day can provide 400 to 600 milligrams of flavan-3-ols, the recommended daily intake to support heart health,” says Kalloo.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; These plant compounds support heart health through encouraging both &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/healthy-cholesterol-foods-7567696" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;healthy cholesterol levels&lt;/a&gt; and blood pressure regulation. “A meta-analysis of randomized controlled trials found that black tea supplementation significantly reduced both systolic and diastolic blood pressure compared to control treatments,” explains Adams.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-regulates-blood-sugar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Regulates Blood Sugar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If blood sugar regulation or type 2 diabetes prevention are a top priority for you, black tea can also play a supporting role. “Some research suggests that black tea may offer several benefits for blood sugar regulation,” offers Adams, including this randomized control trial.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “Regular black tea consumption has also been linked to a lower risk for type 2 diabetes,” adds Kalloo.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-supports-gut-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Supports Gut Health &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Drinking black tea may encourage a healthier gut, too! For example, a 2023 study found that black tea consumption is tied to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/drinks-for-gut-health-8762795" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;improved gut microbiome flora&lt;/a&gt;, supporting digestive health, as well as all the other benefits associated with a thriving microbiome, including immune and brain health.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-contributes-to-hydration"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Contributes to Hydration &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Surprisingly, black tea can actually contribute to your &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/how-much-water-to-drink-day" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;daily hydration needs&lt;/a&gt;. “Both caffeinated and decaffeinated black tea can absolutely count toward your daily fluid intake. When consumed in moderate amounts, caffeinated beverages like tea are &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/hydrating-drinks-11745806" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;as hydrating as water&lt;/a&gt;. The fluid you get from tea typically outweighs any mild diuretic effect from the caffeine,” explains Kalloo.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; That said, it’s crucial to not go overboard with black tea in pursuit of hitting your fluid goals. “It's important to consume it in moderation, as &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/shopping-storing/beverages/how-much-caffeine-per-day" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;excessive intake of caffeine&lt;/a&gt; can lead to side effects such as insomnia or increased heart rate,” says Adams—though these effects only occur with excessive black tea consumption. “Caffeinated tea contains approximately 50 milligrams of caffeine per cup, and evidence shows no effect on hydration with intakes of up to 400 milligrams of caffeine per day or the equivalent of eight cups of tea,” explains Kalloo.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Real Simple</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 22:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE5uYXN5alNYelpfN3BqNzlWZWpvYVhwQUxzd2VMcWhtNG50MFQ4cHhXR19QMmxicmNCZmNvek1JWDV1RzRYYS1veHEyRkJWb3NQUWNTSnFFRnY0SXJpb3RQdkIzcGl3YUstNFFBaEdtYU8yUQ</guid></item><item><title>在99%的心脏病发作和中风之前出现四个常见因素- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/four-common-risk-factors-appear-before-99-percent-of-heart-attacks-and-strokes/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A large analysis of health records from South Korea and the United States reports that 99 percent of heart attacks and &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/stroke-risk-is-elevated-by-air-pollution-and-traffic-noise"&gt;strokes&lt;/a&gt; were preceded by at least one common risk. The main signal held across ages and in both countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those risks are high blood pressure, high cholesterol, high blood sugar, and tobacco use. These conditions fall under cardiovascular disease, illnesses that involve the heart and blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-studying-heart-health-risks"&gt;Studying heart health risks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The work was led by Hokyou Lee, MD, PhD, at Yonsei University College of Medicine in Seoul (&lt;a href="https://medicine.snu.ac.kr/en/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;SNU&lt;/a&gt;). His research focuses on cardiovascular risk and prevention in populations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers tracked two cohorts, one drawn from a national insurance database in Korea and one from a diverse research cohort in the United States. Together, the records spanned more than 9 million adults and many first cardiac or neurologic events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among people who eventually had a first event, the Korean database counted 601,025 outcomes while the U.S. cohort recorded 1,188. The team then checked whether any of the four risks appeared at any clinic visit before the event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They did not require a formal diagnosis to count risk, which better reflects everyday care. Many people carry numbers that are not ideal for years before disease appears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-four-heart-risk-factors"&gt;The four heart risk factors&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study counted hypertension, chronically high &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-identify-minimum-amount-of-physical-activity-needed-to-prevent-high-blood-pressure"&gt;blood pressure&lt;/a&gt; that strains the heart and blood vessels, as systolic 120 mm Hg or diastolic 80 mm Hg. It also counted people taking blood pressure medicine as having this risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cholesterol was counted as total cholesterol at or above 200 milligrams per deciliter or use of a lipid lowering drug. The team also tracked fasting glucose, blood sugar measured after not eating for at least 8 hours, at 100 milligrams per deciliter or higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Past or current &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/does-smoking-increase-blood-pressure-risk-urine-tests-reveal-the-answer/"&gt;tobacco use&lt;/a&gt; qualified as the fourth risk. Elevated blood pressure showed up most often before events, while smoking appeared least often.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors often focus on LDL cholesterol, the particle that most strongly drives plaque buildup in arteries. Lowering LDL cholesterol reduces future heart attack risk in a stepwise fashion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-when-non-optimal-is-dangerous"&gt;When non-optimal is dangerous&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The thresholds were intentionally modest to catch risk early. This approach reflects primordial prevention, which focuses on stopping risk factors from taking root long before they can trigger disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Damage to arteries builds slowly when blood pressure, glucose, or lipids sit above ideal levels. The body handles small shifts for a while, but steady exposure over years increases strain and raises the chances of a serious event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people move through life with numbers that are not alarming yet still fall outside the safest range. Those small gaps create pressure that grows with time and eventually weakens the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/whole-milk-or-low-fat-milk-study-shows-which-is-better-for-heart-health/"&gt;heart&lt;/a&gt; and blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Routine checkups and labs matter because they reveal these early shifts. Correcting issues while they are still mild can change long term outcomes and prevent a future emergency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-women-under-60-are-not-exempt"&gt;Women under 60 are not exempt&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In women younger than 60, heart failure and stroke still had more than 95 percent of events preceded by at least one nonoptimal risk. That means early prevention remains relevant even in the lowest risk female age group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This finding undercuts the belief that midlife events often strike without warning in otherwise healthy women. It highlights the value of early blood pressure, cholesterol, and glucose management across adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-gap-between-risk-and-care"&gt;Gap between risk and care&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;An accompanying &lt;a href="https://www.jacc.org/doi/10.1016/j.jacc.2025.08.030" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; noted that people typically had several clinic visits before their events, which meant there were many chances to check and manage their health risks. Those visits represented opportunities to test, treat, and follow through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood pressure control, cholesterol lowering, smoking cessation, and glucose management are all within reach today. Therapeutic combinations and steady lifestyle changes produce the largest gains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardiovascular &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/heart-disease-remains-the-leading-cause-of-death-worldwide/"&gt;disease remains&lt;/a&gt; the top &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/-/media/PHD-Files-2/Science-News/2/2025-Heart-and-Stroke-Stat-Update/2025-Statistics-At-A-Glance.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;cause&lt;/a&gt; of death in the United States, with 941,652 deaths in 2022, according to the American Heart Association (&lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/why-give?s_src=26D511AEMG&amp;amp;s_subsrc=fy26_sem_google&amp;amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;amp;utm_campaign=dr_fy26_evergreen_brand&amp;amp;utm_source=google&amp;amp;utm_content=161056132793&amp;amp;utm_term=the%20american%20heart%20association&amp;amp;gad_source=1&amp;amp;gad_campaignid=19652355320&amp;amp;gbraid=0AAAAADfYbP7YGJAly6Ap4vQ8zC7aVFx6D&amp;amp;gclid=Cj0KCQiA5uDIBhDAARIsAOxj0CGwNqfgTlJypy2RTwQr3KiYvhEMXyVdtsXk0YLoIn4bC6tVWQyCAdAaAjfgEALw_wcB" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;AHA&lt;/a&gt;). The scale of suffering underlines why early detection and treatment of these four risks is urgent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new results do not claim that every event can be prevented. They do indicate that stronger control of four common risks could avert large numbers of tragedies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-recognizing-heart-health-risks"&gt;Recognizing heart health risks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was an observational study, research that follows people without assigning treatments, so it reveals patterns but cannot prove cause. It still offers clear direction on where prevention should focus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cohorts came from different settings and cultures, and visits were spaced over years. Even with those differences, the central signal stayed consistent across groups and outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future work will test ways to reach people earlier and keep numbers controlled over time. Primary care access, community programs, and easy to use medicines will all play key parts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.jacc.org/doi/10.1016/j.jacc.2025.07.014" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Journal of the American College of Cardiology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 20:42:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxOb0ZFOUZLa056ZDNZeXMtZjlZT0pzZnh5TUh0bHJ1MWJaZXRsbjlOWlg3YlVDSGRET05tenQtbUxzYm1aY1VCUmhzOVp1VzZibWlHeDBWVU11NUlPSlZ6eHFTY0pSclBIMy1rVm9kZG9ueUhYUU5TNWNaY3ZJRlBXOGd2QWRHR2tQSU5FZWZkNW5aV0lGX2RlMGlxY01OYzBRM3NoSW9yeU1mQQ</guid></item><item><title>根管治疗降低心脏病和糖尿病风险-好消息网络</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/root-canal-treatment-reduces-heart-disease-and-diabetes-risk/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_225889" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-225889" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-225889" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Dentist-dental-teeth-surgery-by-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-l7UUq4ls9LM-unsplash.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Dentist-dental-teeth-surgery-by-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-l7UUq4ls9LM-unsplash.jpg 1400w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Dentist-dental-teeth-surgery-by-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-l7UUq4ls9LM-unsplash-326x176.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Dentist-dental-teeth-surgery-by-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-l7UUq4ls9LM-unsplash-1024x552.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Dentist-dental-teeth-surgery-by-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-l7UUq4ls9LM-unsplash-768x414.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Dentist-dental-teeth-surgery-by-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-l7UUq4ls9LM-unsplash-696x375.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Dentist-dental-teeth-surgery-by-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-l7UUq4ls9LM-unsplash-1068x576.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Dentist-dental-teeth-surgery-by-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-l7UUq4ls9LM-unsplash-779x420.jpg 779w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Dentist-dental-teeth-surgery-by-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-l7UUq4ls9LM-unsplash-530x286.jpg 530w" sizes="(max-width: 1400px) 100vw, 1400px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-225889" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Credit: Getty Images for Unsplash+&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Successful root canal treatment can reduce inflammation linked to heart disease, according to new research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The much dreaded dental surgery can also improve levels of blood sugar and cholesterol, say scientists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the first of its kind clinical study, King’s College London researchers tracked changes in blood chemistry following root canal treatment for a common dental infection, called apical periodontitis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The infection can cause bacteria to enter the bloodstream and increase inflammation, associated with risks to cardiac health and reduced ability to control blood sugar levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the link between the infection and wider health impacts, no one has investigated the association between successful root canal treatment and the benefits to heart and metabolic health until now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings,&lt;a href="https://translational-medicine.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s12967-025-07110-0" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; published in the&lt;/a&gt; Journal of Translational Medicine, showed that successful root canal treatment was associated with improved glucose metabolism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blood sugar levels dropped “significantly” over two years after treatment, a key factor in preventing diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The treatment also resulted in better lipid profiles, short-term improvements in blood cholesterol and fatty acid levels, which are closely linked to heart health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings also showed that the treatment saw key markers of inflammation, often linked to cardiovascular risk and other chronic conditions—decreased over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GREAT TIP:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a title="Be Sure and Floss! Researchers Say Good Dental Health ‘Substantially’ Decreases Risk of Alzheimer’s" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/good-dental-health-substantially-decreases-alzheimers-risk/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Be Sure and Floss! Researchers Say Good Dental Health ‘Substantially’ Decreases Risk of Alzheimer’s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_225874" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-225874" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-225874" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/chart-of-root-canal-tooth-care-benefits-SWNS.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-225874" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Chart via SWNS news&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bacteria from infected teeth were associated with changes in the body’s overall metabolism, according to the findings. The research team explained that root canal infections can cause bacteria to enter the blood, leading to inflammation, heart disease and diabetes risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But successful treatment reduced those risks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study followed the health of 65 patients in England over two years after root canal treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientists analyzed molecules in the blood of patients to reveal how the body processes sugar, fat, other key substances, and responds to disease and treatment. They used a technique known as nuclear magnetic resonance (NMR) spectroscopy, used to analyze proteins in the body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DYNAMITE DENTAL NEWS&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;
• &lt;a title="New Gel Regrows Dental Enamel–Which Humans Cannot Do–and Could Revolutionize Tooth Care" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/new-gel-regrows-dental-enamel-which-humans-cannot-do-and-could-revolutionize-tooth-care/" rel="bookmark"&gt;New Gel Regrows Dental Enamel–Which Humans Cannot Do–and Could Revolutionize Tooth Care&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
• &lt;a title="Wisdom Teeth Contain Unique Stem Cell That Can Form Cartilage, Neurons, and Heart Tissue" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wisdom-teeth-contain-unique-stem-cell-that-can-form-cartilage-neurons-and-heart-tissue/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Wisdom Teeth Contain Unique Stem Cell That Can Form Cartilage, Neurons, and Heart Tissue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings suggest that monitoring blood metabolic markers—such as glucose, fats known as triglycerides, and the protein tryptophan—could help assess recovery and risk after dental treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Our findings show that root canal treatment doesn’t just improve oral health – it may also help reduce the risk of serious health conditions like diabetes and heart disease,” &lt;a href="https://www.kcl.ac.uk/news/root-canal-treatment-reduces-heart-disease-and-diabetes-risk" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;said lead Author&lt;/a&gt; Dr. Sadia Niazi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s a powerful reminder that oral (tooth) health is deeply connected to overall health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Long-standing root canal infections can allow bacteria to enter the bloodstream, trigger inflammation, and increase blood glucose and fats levels – raising the risk of serious health issues like heart disease and diabetes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While more research is needed to confirm the effects in larger populations, she says the study opens “exciting new doors” for understanding how oral care can support general health and well-being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It is vital that dental professionals recognise the wider impact of these root canal infections and advocate for early diagnosis and treatment,” added Dr. Niazi, a senior clinical lecturer in endodontics at King’s College London.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WILD, BUT TRUE:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a title="Tooth Is Implanted in 34-year-old’s Eye to Restore His Vision After Two Decades" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/tooth-is-implanted-in-34-year-olds-eye-to-restore-his-vision-after-two-decades/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Tooth Is Implanted in 34-year-old’s Eye to Restore His Vision After Two Decades&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We also need to move towards integrated care, where dentists and general practitioners work together to monitor the risks through these blood markers and protect overall health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s time to move beyond the tooth and embrace a truly holistic approach to dental care.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SHARE THIS ON SOCIAL MEDIA With Those Who’ve Been Delaying Dental Work…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 20:00:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxNZndJVXNrVndCelE1X19sZ3lVX2Z5QWdHZ3BhdjdzSVdfQUtyaHk5U25GcGcxd3ZNTGQ2d1RUMjY2eGI1OFFmOTdRbWJFbzRxMjNIT1ZMNnZNNV9EU3hXWjFiaHhrUWhJRDFpbURwVzc2M0pjZFNxWDlnU1FwM0dERmJDOFJzQVFtMDB1SWtiaTg2Q19sTEYzZg</guid></item><item><title>正如顶级心脏病专家透露的那样， 5个简单的方法来阻止糖尿病-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/5-simple-hacks-to-keep-diabetes-at-bay-as-revealed-by-top-cardiologist/articleshow/125248102.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diabetes is a chronic condition that affects millions across the world. When one is diabetic, the body either is unable to produce insulin, or has trouble processing it in the right manner. Diabetes can be genetic, but is also largely based on lifestyle factors such as obesity, poor diet, High Blood Pressure etc,. The good news is that even if diabetes runs in your family, and you are not a diabetic yet, there are certain things you can do to mitigate that risk. Dr Evan Levine, board certified cardiologist, lists out 5 lifestyle changes you can bring about, to keep Diabetes at bay. Remember, prevention is always better than cure!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Lose weight&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even a modest dip in weight, can make a dent in your chance of developing diabetes. The Diabetes Prevention Program found that shedding 5–7 % of total body weight, cut diabetes &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC1762038/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;risk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; by 60 % over three years. Losing those kgs improves insulin sensitivity, and brings blood‑sugar levels down, two of the biggest markers behind diabetes. Experts advise aiming for a healthy weight loss through modest tweaks through diet and activity, to achieve the best results. Maintaining an ideal weight not only wards off diabetes; it also curtails the likelihood of heart disease, joint ailments, and a host of other health complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Exercise most days of the week&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Physical activity nudges your body into using insulin, which helps lower blood sugar, and cuts the risk of developing diabetes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American Diabetes Association recommends clocking 150 minutes each week of moderate‑intensity exercise-think brisk walking, cycling or swimming. Beyond supporting weight loss, regular movement gives the heart a boost as well. Research indicates that individuals who hit these activity targets, enjoy a 44 %‑70 % reduction in diabetes risk, even when the scale doesn’t move much at first. Staying active also keeps stress in control, and promotes more restorative sleep-both essential pieces for keeping diabetes at way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Cut out sugary drinks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sugary drinks-sodas, fruit juices, and energy drinks, send blood sugar soaring quickly, and often adds the kgs. Removing them from the diet pulls down your diabetes risk by slashing calories, and smoothing out those glucose spikes. Switching to water, plain tea or black coffee, gives the body a sort of protection against diabetes. Research backs the link between cutting out sugary beverages, and a reduced incidence of diabetes. Keeping an eye on hidden sugars tucked into processed foods and sweets, further aids blood‑sugar management, and supports a healthy weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Fiber rich food over carbs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swapping out carbs-bread, pasta and sugary snacks-for fiber‑packed whole grains, fresh fruit and vegetables tends to smooth blood‑sugar fluctuations. The extra fiber acts like a brake on digestion, slowing the entry of sugar into the bloodstream. A growing body of research links high‑fiber eating patterns to a risk of diabetes, and to a healthier metabolic profile. Whole‑food choices also make it easier to maintain a steady weight while nurturing a healthy gut microbiome. Moreover, opting for low‑glycemic‑index foods, which raise blood sugar gradually than in a surge, adds a layer of protection against diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Keep stress in control&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When stress lingers, it floods the body with cortisol, and other hormones that nudge blood sugar upward, and blunt insulin’s effectiveness. Tackling that pressure with habits such as meditation, yoga, deep‑breathing exercises or simply picking a hobby, can smooth out glucose swings, and shrink the odds of developing diabetes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC1762038/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; now shows that stress‑reduction programs, not only improve metabolic markers, but also slash the likelihood of diabetes. Layering those calming practices with good sleep, further sharpens insulin sensitivity and underpins overall well‑being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Tiny adjustments can end up having an effect&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;What makes these diabetes‑prevention hacks by Dr Levine so helpful, is their sheer simplicity and effectiveness. Even modest weight loss, swapping sodas for water, fitting a short walk into your day, piling your plate with fiber‑dense foods, and carving out a few minutes to unwind, can slash your diabetes risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7wFBVV95cUxPeUFZVS1zTFJJTHIwZ05kVUFXVk1wWXR0bEFoTjFVbVM2VjE2TGhlald2cEZ0bXZsejg1Ty10bmYwdld2X0JKYnFLeUZjbUE1cTdZOHl6al9FZW1xUEJibHI1Zk5PbVNuZGt2SGN5aVRXa08yNllvUmx2cm1kZGd3S1hxc0VnU1Bic3JaQzRFWWlVZ0FvZm1lcWVQN0gwOXF5SkNqVl9mSFdUOVBFNUV2S09FN3ZlZnpOV3p0eFBkcHNGNWM1TGI1SUpHaXpHMUZ1Y3c5M1BnZ3plcW9Ib3djSEV3Xy12UE9Femtqd1JlRQ</guid></item><item><title>多名学生在瓦萨奇高中（ KUTV ）接触麻疹后被诊断出患有麻疹</title><link>https://kutv.com/news/local/multiple-high-schoolers-diagnosed-with-measles-after-exposure-at-wasatch-county-school</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;HEBER CITY, Utah (KUTV) — &lt;/span&gt;At least five high schoolers in Wasatch County were infected with measles after being exposed during school hours and at the school play in mid-November.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials confirmed Saturday that five people had recently contracted measles in Wasatch County, all of whom are students at Wasatch High School.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jonelle Fitzgerald, director of the Wasatch County Health Department, said that while the students attend the same school, they do not believe the cases are connected. Because of this, they believe there may be other cases that "pop up in the community," with two additional patients currently awaiting test results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We did have a wastewater test indicate the presence of measles in the community on November 6th, and with cases existing in other parts of the state, we weren’t surprised to see cases here,” Fitzgerald said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials said they are taking "immediate action" to investigate the spread and work to limit further exposures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;MORE | Measles:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lana North, WCHD public information officer, said it's important to be aware of measles in the community, especially during this holiday season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"With Thanksgiving and family gatherings around the corner, please be aware that measles is around," North said. "Keep your friends and family healthy by staying home if you’re sick."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles symptoms present within one to three weeks after exposure, and as most of the exposures were determined to be between Nov. 14 and 17, there is still time for others who were exposed to show symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some symptoms include high fever, cough, runny nose, red or watery eyes, and a rash that begins on the face and spreads down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you notice symptoms, officials ask that you call doctors or clinics before arriving at a facility to prevent infecting others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We encourage all Wasatch County residents and families to get both doses of the MMR vaccine, as it is 97% effective in preventing illness,” said Brenda Scobee, WCHD immunizer coordinator.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Out of the five people confirmed to be infected and the two others awaiting test results, two were vaccinated against the virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are the first confirmed cases of measles in Wasatch County this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KUTV</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 18:23:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxQbTJMYjk1MkZQNUF0Q25teUJIZUwxaVVZVTQteDBJOE9wOUQ5VXVGNmtKNDdKNnNCN3ZQNDFDQTlBVWs4aTloY1hnUkQ1RVQzOUhFVTlnS2RweEF1WmM1WkJRZkRPaHRGbHpoc1BSSUNBcGJvbE1HX24zNk5BQ3BNUXppY25Za2duY2M3YnpwWGs0YXV3YzIzQjhZajZkcHF6b0J4ZjdaZmp5MlduemZsVVlDcUk</guid></item><item><title>警告！您的头发颜色可能导致多器官衰竭；了解PPD风险、过敏和安全替代方案-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/warning-your-hair-colour-can-cause-multi-organ-failure-understand-ppd-risks-allergies-and-safe-alternatives/articleshow/125515624.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Permanent hair dyes are a popular choice for achieving bright, long-lasting hair colour. Many of these products contain a chemical called p-phenylenediamine, commonly known as PPD. This ingredient is essential for keeping hair shades vibrant and resistant to fading. However, experts warn that PPD may pose serious health risks. Regular exposure can lead to skin reactions such as redness, itching, swelling, and blistering. Some individuals may experience allergic responses, particularly those with pre-existing skin conditions. In rare cases, PPD can even cause life-threatening poisoning if ingested. Awareness of these risks is crucial for anyone who colours their hair frequently, allowing safer choices and preventive measures like patch testing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding PPD and why is it used in hair dye&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;P-phenylenediamine is an aromatic amine that allows permanent hair dyes to retain their colour over time. It reacts with other ingredients to create pigments that penetrate the hair shaft, producing long-lasting shades. Without PPD, hair colour would fade quickly and appear dull. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite its cosmetic benefits, PPD has been associated with several health risks. Repeated exposure can sensitise the immune system, leading to allergic reactions and skin inflammation. This dual nature makes it a controversial ingredient in hair care products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Skin reactions and potential cancer risks from &lt;keyword id="30917361" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="PPD-in-hair-dye" source="keywords"&gt;PPD in hair dye&lt;/keyword&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even small amounts of PPD absorbed through the scalp can trigger a range of skin issues. The most common reaction is contact dermatitis, which manifests as redness, itching, swelling, and in some cases, blistering. These symptoms typically appear 48 to 72 hours after hair dye application.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with pre-existing skin conditions such as eczema, psoriasis, or scalp irritation are more likely to experience adverse reactions. Studies suggest that while 1.5 percent of the general population may react to PPD, the number rises to approximately 6 percent for individuals already prone to dermatitis. There have been questions about the potential link between hair dye chemicals and cancer. The &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://publications.iarc.who.int/75" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;International Agency for Research on Cancer &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;(IARC) has classified occupational exposure to hair dyes as “probably carcinogenic.” However, research on personal use of hair dye shows mixed results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 36-year study published in 2020 found no strong overall connection between regular hair dye use and most cancers. It did indicate potential associations with specific types, such as basal cell carcinoma and estrogen receptor-negative breast cancer. Experts emphasise that these findings are not definitive and require further study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;PPD poisoning risks and the importance of careful handling&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although cosmetic use of PPD is generally safe, accidental ingestion of the chemical can be extremely dangerous. Oral exposure can cause rapid multi-organ failure, with early signs including sudden swelling of the neck and airways, known as angioneurotic oedema. Even with prompt medical intervention, severe PPD poisoning carries a mortality rate of around 14.5 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This highlights that while PPD is safe in controlled cosmetic use, awareness and careful handling are crucial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Safer hair dye alternatives and testing for PPD sensitivity&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Growing concern about PPD has led to the development of PPD-free hair dyes. One common alternative is p-toluenediamine sulfate (PTDS). However, research indicates that approximately half of individuals allergic to PPD may also react to PTDS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The safest approach includes performing a patch test 48 hours before using any hair dye, wearing protective gloves during application, and educating consumers about potential sensitivities. Professional hairdressers should also follow strict safety protocols to minimise exposure. Identifying a sensitivity to PPD can prevent severe reactions. Allergy clinics can provide professional testing, or a patch test at home can indicate whether a person may react to the chemical. The patch test involves applying a small amount of hair dye to a small patch of skin and monitoring for redness, swelling, or irritation over 48 hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAJBVV95cUxQai1obVRjNkVaQW5vcC1nQUw5cUNLZVZ4a093NUpNa1BoaDVWeGhNTXVzQnM3Y3NKNFRYQTFJSmNGRUxjaWxJZE92bTNILVZ2aDFuTm9TMkRvazI1T0poT0NrMl9xR0FaTGVTU0hIcFZWNnY2TUJIWTJ6cHZSbzVnbjBXYUx2dlZoczRYOUNSbHFzb3pMdHEwNV9ocXBKS1g0TFllZGYxS2RBQzZHd1ZXemhPanJ3UVJyRXFNVVoxTzRrWW16Y3NWUGN0OXhCNFpKcF9McmpYLXRUNGpncEZzN2k0Zi1laTZaSDc3QU50UGFIZ0JwX0xzN1RZUlRiWDBiMzFVWllFS1V1ZEh6RVZ0b0hNeUE3TzFXTzJYdG5lV3pRM295SWxVTEdoLUtaMlBK0gG2AkFVX3lxTE9nSWRYVGxoVDA0UEF5TkZDSUpFVy0xWWlQcUoxS2JOTmRVdDZKNEh0Zk1iSzlaZzhlSEN0TmdvVF9VZDdzbC1QNWZfSEg5OHRPbS14MzNidTZtaXBqUTBnZ0pOZHJNdlcwT28wZ214VFdGZi0zZUtfMVJBQ2pZaG9TMjJiWUtSMk5iUUFmZGl1dWFfenhYLXVGSnU3TVlVT0d6WUxCMzE5X09jNEN5eXlXSC1ydnBuaXc4NXpiU1k2Nm1DeG5hM3ZzVmRvY3g1MXNPZm9WZDlrLXhkcUZpaWZOa3BnaTZuV3d4a0tkeGJvaXNFRHc1SDRDNDltSkRtbU54alFfbkIyWkVEbXZyVkxKMTZXUzNNYTBTblpxSjJPanJFcGR1Y25tUDJiVlZOLUU0QmNNaFE</guid></item><item><title>支持疫苗的Cassidy拒绝反对RFK Jr. - Politico</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2025/11/23/bill-cassidy-refuses-to-speak-against-rfk-jr-00666410</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Politico</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:04:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNVEF6SURQTmVudzhkWk9JdExsNjBfM3AtUDFvRENkZ1ZRZW9MR2VyMkFfTGxGRExZdkV6QW1SMEZ5ZklHRENERHI1T0swWk8zQmJGMUxRNDU0NFJmSHhuSE9CYWVDQ3RSTWZWSFpSRll5R1NWS240Sm5nUHJYcU5KZ2dkaXpFUENDRUVHT1F4cnUwamdERmlnNUp3</guid></item><item><title>医生解释了为什么10000步无法挽回10个小时的坐姿： “你可以达到目标，但……” |热门话题-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/trending/doctor-explains-why-10-000-steps-cant-undo-10-hours-of-sitting-you-can-hit-step-goal-but-101763914063116.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/trending/doctor-explains-why-10-000-steps-cant-undo-10-hours-of-sitting-you-can-hit-step-goal-but-101763914063116.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;A doctor’s Instagram post about the hidden dangers of prolonged sitting is gaining attention online after he explained why even 10,000 steps a day cannot undo the damage caused by 10 hours of immobility.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/23/550x309/photo-1515378791036-0648a3ef77b2_1763914314328_1763914324755.jpg" alt="The doctor said that the damage begins long before people lace up their shoes for an evening walk. (Unsplash/Representative image)" title="The doctor said that the damage begins long before people lace up their shoes for an evening walk. (Unsplash/Representative image)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/23/550x309/photo-1515378791036-0648a3ef77b2_1763914314328_1763914324755.jpg" alt="The doctor said that the damage begins long before people lace up their shoes for an evening walk. (Unsplash/Representative image)" title="The doctor said that the damage begins long before people lace up their shoes for an evening walk. (Unsplash/Representative image)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;The doctor said that the damage begins long before people lace up their shoes for an evening walk. (Unsplash/Representative image)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Taking to Instagram, Dr Sumit Kapadia, who, according to his bio, is a vascular surgeon and varicose vein specialist, wrote that most people assume that hitting their step goal in the evening cancels out a sedentary workday, but he explained that the body doesn’t work that way. Dr Kapadia said that even if someone achieves their daily 10,000 steps, spending the entire day desk-bound from 9 am to 7 pm still harms circulation.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“This is something I tell my patients almost every day. You can hit your step goal in the evening…but if you’ve been desk-bound from 9 AM to 7 PM, your veins have already taken the damage,” he wrote in the caption of his Instagram post.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Dr Kapadia explained that vein health depends less on the total distance walked and more on how often a person moves throughout the day. “Circulation doesn’t depend on how much you walk. It depends on how often you move,” he said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to the doctor, prolonged sitting leads to blood stagnation, weakening of vein valves, swelling, and a higher risk of varicose veins and even blood clots. The damage, he said, begins long before people lace up their shoes for an evening walk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Even a healthy step count cannot reverse 10 hours of immobility,” he said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Kapadia urged people to break long sedentary stretches by standing up every hour, stretching, walking briefly and engaging the calf muscles, which he described as the body’s “peripheral heart” due to their key role in supporting blood flow.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Tiny breaks. Huge difference. Your veins don’t need marathons. They need movement,” he concluded.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Social media reactions&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reacting to the post, one user wrote, “I think I’m already facing the consequences.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“On average, how long should you be sitting and standing per day to achieve the best health?” asked another.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“I was sitting for almost 10-11 hours and my side hips, lower back pains alot also i cant walk and stand for longer time. thankfully i have left the job,” shared a third user, urging others to prioritise health before it's too late.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:23:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4wFBVV95cUxPcHFfSkNjdDhGOGN0aWJmWnc0bHNtT2pOcXdvSjBFd3QxQ2RwOFlJVWlPNW13bUpfUTlUMU94aVRSUWZTTjUzUVNDOUFNVl9WdWMzdl9IQ3hGal9LY2pZTVluY0hRY2ZxWWFBZkZqYmMxWHJiLXJJT2diUTh0VHlyYlNveEpEakJ5ZmM5emc4NWRkWUJoc041TXpZRWZPRUE0cHdVbTJodU4tRE1SMGlMWnk2RS0xNEV1elRSLVZ1UEY4b3BDZ1dSVGV0T0l3UUZTZndJQ0JSMmkxdVBBQ25NaFo5Y9IB6AFBVV95cUxPc0JpZG5MMTZ4SjRYMkhyc1Zaa08zcGs0Tl8yZFFIS3lYbGtRRmIwTTdKZlhXTWdyazA3ZU5QZy1rcmRzVU5UYnk5SnFkTEZEWC1McThLVWhnYXZfQWtMX3RCVlM1YmxhMWRsWUNtSWU4WVd4SmxWdUNmY0pzVGRWYzBYOW5YcjRCWnl2Zk5CQlh2dS01MUQzYnB2RWpqT3hwYlJvbDRuRFNxdklXbjVzLTA2U2R5RkRLQTE2Y2ZNLTFvcU1TY0UwWlZGdkFoQm1Rb29DMkJfY2oxTFRlWFR6QXVrUkUyd3Zi</guid></item><item><title>随着传染性EHV-1疫情加速爆发，德克萨斯州的马匹死亡- MySA</title><link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/local/article/ehv-outbreak-horses-texas-21203524.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>MySA</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:26:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOOEtZMkdkTXlVdnFJdUdBV1pRaTJXRGJzUkktLUtzU0JXRzlHMjVFSkhzNXdsWkhBMmhaRHkzdnN4dFZrMXVEbFBGS09CSk05aWZOYWtXcGI4OS1vVHRKaWpfSzNYc2ZkbzJEV3l0WElnREdtOHVZN3RFSGdJZUx4X2I5d1dZTnc3V0hnMHU2TQ</guid></item><item><title>为什么自身免疫性疾病在50岁后急剧上升-华尔街日报</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/health/wellness/autoimmune-diseases-increase-age-41733014</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Wall Street Journal</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxPdjR6T1ItbnpYY1JQNFozd0hmUjh4TzVOR0ltd0cyTTVCVVNwOElXUVIyUXA2TlVhWlpvcDlpZjRMOXhOZjFmZjc2NDI2RVFiT1ZBeDdlWmVnemtNbXl0c3BNRWRkRmozVEVnSm1EY0ViTjZWQTZqQlVKdzVJa3NTM1VKcw</guid></item><item><title>更好的睡眠对心脏健康：饭后立即步行15分钟的五大好处-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/better-sleep-to-heart-health-top-5-benefits-of-walking-for-15-minutes-right-after-meals/photostory/125518685.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most powerful benefits of a 15‑minute walk after eating is its ability to blunt the post-meal glucose spike. Research shows that even brief, moderate-intensity walking shortly after a meal can significantly reduce blood sugar peaks.&lt;br&gt;An American Diabetes Association &lt;a href="https://diabetesjournals.org/care/article/36/10/3262/30770/Three-15-min-Bouts-of-Moderate-Postmeal-Walking"&gt;study &lt;/a&gt;conducted on older adults at risk of impaired glucose tolerance found that 15 minutes of walking, done 30 minutes after each meal, was just as effective in improving 24-hour glycemic control as a single 45‑minute walk. &lt;br&gt;These findings suggest that the timing plays a key role, i.e., walking soon after eating makes the muscles take up more glucose for energy, helping reduce the sugar circulating in your blood. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAJBVV95cUxOcTNkMWlBMm1xOVdjRG9Nd3dhTU90SnRnNkNkQXhmY2NHR2wzX05YQlMyM3gyX3dRYzlQMFJ3VHBEX0oxU3kzS1BNTVJ3bGcwWmo1QnNpakxTZDFMS1FoMEVZUDhoT0hRTEhKcXJ4YV80MkRsRlZDc2RuT3JMelY5UGxqT1JtbWhrNWxUYWI1SG1kaXMzdzQ5VUdOcGlQeEFjVmh3cG9GcklRRHYtWjRBMEEtUWJjajNyd1YtNDhPOXNETFNsREE1c2s2SDVYQ3lBYzdmVmFJNzhOcXkyZzJGeVdBS2lHbmJrQ1VwOEhYUWZzLTdLMWs2aXBocWdXYzhkSEowX001MFpGdzFPdVlrVWdqRTHSAZwCQVVfeXFMUGNHQzJOYUdYbEdYczVJMFhXcUl3TjJOSVctVk5XYUROd0NFZzR4Zmx2U1BFSWEwNHROakduQmdLWV92RzFDWlBaS3FnR0VTZGc0Q0FOaVh3M3dra0doWDNtVlNsenVjdzVYZEU0XzUzNWFyc1VNdWxYbnNQU0tnVmpoNnViQmlIUlYzSTJSSFBYS0dTVExxdWlXZlZRTkVTcGF1SXJ4LXV5cVM3c0lPWG1vZzBndWlKNG82RGlSQ19aYjhyNnBLNV9reWkzZ21mLVRGV2dDUkZ3LS13cDJ0OUpGdFlabG5fVlhQbkhCSFhtc005WWJObFRQSEs5NkV3NnIwV0NySFU2RElEcFYyd21Ud3VpNG1VdXZBNF8</guid></item><item><title>增强一种蛋白质有助于大脑保护自己免受阿尔茨海默氏症的侵害- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/11/251123085550.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Researchers at Baylor College of Medicine have identified a natural process in the brain that can remove existing amyloid plaques in mouse models of Alzheimer's disease while also helping preserve memory and thinking ability. This process relies on astrocytes, star shaped support cells, which can be guided to clear out the toxic plaque buildup commonly seen in Alzheimer's. When the team increased the amount of Sox9, a protein that influences many astrocyte functions during aging, the cells became more effective at removing amyloid deposits. The findings, reported in &lt;em&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;, suggest that strengthening astrocyte activity could one day help slow cognitive decline linked to neurodegenerative disorders.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Astrocytes perform diverse tasks that are essential for normal brain function, including facilitating brain communications and memory storage. As the brain ages, astrocytes show profound functional alterations; however, the role these alterations play in aging and neurodegeneration is not yet understood," said first author Dr. Dong-Joo Choi, who conducted this work while at the Center for Cell and Gene Therapy and the Department of Neurosurgery at Baylor. Choi is now an assistant professor at the Center for Neuroimmunology and Glial Biology, Institute of Molecular Medicine at the University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focusing on Sox9 as a Key Regulator&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this project, the investigators set out to understand how astrocytes change with age and how those changes relate to Alzheimer's disease. Their attention centered on Sox9, a protein that influences a wide network of genes involved in astrocyte aging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We manipulated the expression of the Sox9 gene to assess its role in maintaining astrocyte function in the aging brain and in Alzheimer's disease models," explained corresponding author Dr. Benjamin Deneen, professor and Dr. Russell J. and Marian K. Blattner Chair in the Department of Neurosurgery, director of the Center for Cancer Neuroscience, member of the Dan L Duncan Comprehensive Cancer Center at Baylor and principal investigator at the Jan and Dan Duncan Neurological Research Institute at Texas Children's Hospital.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Testing the Approach in Symptomatic Alzheimer's Models&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"An important point of our experimental design is that we worked with mouse models of Alzheimer's disease that had already developed cognitive impairment, such as memory deficits, and had amyloid plaques in the brain," Choi said. "We believe these models are more relevant to what we see in many patients with Alzheimer's disease symptoms than other models in which these types of experiments are conducted before the plaques form."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In these models, the researchers either increased or removed Sox9 and then monitored each mouse's cognitive performance for six months. During this period, the animals were tested on their ability to recognize familiar objects and locations. After the behavioral studies were completed, the team examined the brains to measure plaque accumulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Higher Sox9 Levels Improve Plaque Removal and Memory&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results showed a clear difference. Lowering Sox9 led to faster plaque buildup, reduced structural complexity in astrocytes and diminished plaque clearing. Raising Sox9 had the opposite effect, increasing the cells' activity, supporting plaque removal and preserving cognitive performance. The protective benefits suggested that strong astrocyte engagement may help slow the cognitive decline associated with neurodegenerative disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We found that increasing Sox9 expression triggered astrocytes to ingest more amyloid plaques, clearing them from the brain like a vacuum cleaner," Deneen said. "Most current treatments focus on neurons or try to prevent the formation of amyloid plaques. This study suggests that enhancing astrocytes' natural ability to clean up could be just as important."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Future Potential and Ongoing Research Needs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choi, Deneen and their colleagues note that additional research is needed to understand how Sox9 behaves in the human brain across time. Still, these results point toward the possibility of developing therapies that harness astrocytes' natural cleaning abilities to combat neurodegenerative disorders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sanjana Murali, Wookbong Kwon, Junsung Woo, Eun-Ah Christine Song, Yeunjung Ko, Debo Sardar, Brittney Lozzi, Yi-Ting Cheng, Michael R. Williamson, Teng-Wei Huang, Kaitlyn Sanchez and Joanna Jankowsky, all at Baylor College of Medicine, also contributed to this work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This research was supported by National Institutes of Health grants (R35-NS132230, R01-AG071687, R01-CA284455, K01-AG083128, R56-MH133822). Additional funding came from the David and Eula Wintermann Foundation, the Eunice Kennedy Shriver National Institute of Child Health &amp;amp; Human Development of the National Institutes of Health under Award Number P50HD103555 and from shared resources provided by Houston Methodist and Baylor College of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 14:25:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBKM0VfTFpzczZxalQwSVlCTWxYUEZoVXk0X3hEXzY3S2xNdVlLeDB2anlXUnhCMVdETHlWSExFTFVheFdaYnowMUpzNmpmYmxYWUlzWU1GS05fTURNNDF0enVjeXRBNWJyNFhRQXoxVQ</guid></item><item><title>研究人员强调了与慢性大麻使用相关的新诊断- WHIO TV</title><link>https://www.whio.com/news/local/researchers-highlight-new-diagnosis-tied-chronic-cannabis-use/IDI4RA75GJD3RPM53KDALAJLZE/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="default__ArticleBody-sc-tl066j-1 jPcFTl article-body-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;WASHINGTON — Researchers say a condition that has been connected to chronic cannabis use has been recognized as a formal diagnosis, according to our sister station &lt;a href="https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/uw-study-researchers-highlight-new-diagnosis-tied-chronic-cannabis-use/LUPADHUMVVHYHIIC4GBTERQ7SI/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/uw-study-researchers-highlight-new-diagnosis-tied-chronic-cannabis-use/LUPADHUMVVHYHIIC4GBTERQ7SI/"&gt;KIRO-7&lt;/a&gt; TV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[DOWNLOAD: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.whio.com/mobile-apps/" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.whio.com/mobile-apps/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free WHIO-TV News app for alerts as news breaks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Cannabis hyperemesis syndrome is a condition tied to long-term cannabis use that can cause severe stomach pain, vomiting, and nausea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;The World Health Organization added an official diagnosis code for the syndrome to its medical classification manual on October 1, according to &lt;a href="https://newsroom.uw.edu/blog/disabling-cannabis-condition-gets-formal-clinical-identity" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://newsroom.uw.edu/blog/disabling-cannabis-condition-gets-formal-clinical-identity"&gt;the University of Washington&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more" class="taboola-read-more"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;TRENDING STORIES:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;That update now gives doctors a clear way to diagnose the condition — something beneficial for addiction researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;It also lets providers spot the condition more easily by reviewing a patient’s medical history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;“It helps us count and monitor these cases,” Beatriz Carlini, a research associate professor at the University of Washington School of Medicine, said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more-8" class="taboola-read-more-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Many doctors aren’t familiar with the syndrome because it’s still relatively new. They’re not entirely sure why it affects some cannabis users and not others, &lt;a href="https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/uw-study-researchers-highlight-new-diagnosis-tied-chronic-cannabis-use/LUPADHUMVVHYHIIC4GBTERQ7SI/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/uw-study-researchers-highlight-new-diagnosis-tied-chronic-cannabis-use/LUPADHUMVVHYHIIC4GBTERQ7SI/"&gt;KIRO-7&lt;/a&gt; reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;For treatment, doctors have found that home remedies, such as hot showers, alleviate symptoms when other treatments are ineffective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Medications like Haldol and over-the-counter options such as capsaicin cream can help ease symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[SIGN UP: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://membercenter.whio.com/newsletters" target="_self" rel="" title="https://membercenter.whio.com/newsletters"&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHIO-TV Daily Headlines Newsletter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph body-copyright"&gt;©2025 Cox Media Group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WHIO TV</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 14:20:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxPcHcwLW1iTnJNZXFDLUdyWjVUT0NuRmdyd1p6RFhxT29qajZJZlBZekpJeTZoVnhkR0szUUplOF9kUEFiaTQwVW1aNWpwem1VNk80XzR3a3NqRDBDM3l2ZVFyQkVucWRwejVxSWJUR29rN3dHMWpNLTFzYkh1TEU2bnVQSnpFU1RwLUI1RHdMcHJ2OWRseWp1dVRMUGZGQ3doZ3pCLVE4Z0REbS1iQWt3SkhlbWxjanIzZTRIYWVn0gHSAUFVX3lxTE5RWUVvT1ExUUVsOXhKQk53SUEwWG8wamppYmo5ZDVVT1ZETk1Qbzh0LTBjdFZCYkU3LUlSaTZLT2NPUlNqZTl1ZzU1RjF4SGZ1bER1aVc2Z2thV2V1QjRXZTUzLVB0N3gxSGd6YlFaQ0xmLTN5cUNKVEg3XzJwRHZUS1VDZ0RXUThWNndobnZYSzJ0QVNBZkVOdWd1M20yNFl0amlrOGNVZy1ZZTNxeXhsVlVuQ3Q5bHFZaVV3dUgwV2hSSXJaenlORkdNNGJvdnBSQQ</guid></item></channel></rss>