<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>人民药店：我认为服用他汀类药物会影响我的认知功能。这有什么道理吗？ - OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/advice/2026/01/peoples-pharmacy-i-think-taking-statins-effected-my-cognitive-function-is-there-any-truth-to-that.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BWVOY24CQBDELDXQ6NXPISPPEE"&gt;Q. My doctor prescribed rosuvastatin for high cholesterol. After taking it for six to nine months, I noticed that my cognitive function had slipped. I would not be able to find the word I was looking for. My family also noticed this cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XRXZNHEK3VFCXHMENCJ3KZEFSU"&gt;I stopped the rosuvastatin and, in a fairly short period of time, my full cognitive function returned. I do engineering-type design work, and it is critical that I have full mental capacity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="D2ED4QO2EBF7HHDJUYHYB5FHXM"&gt;A. Health professionals have been arguing about statin side effects for years, especially when it comes to cognitive impairment. Many discount this complaint, but other readers have reported problems like the ones you describe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="L2BGBFTUBVAKHG7HPRZJ32D6JQ"&gt;The official prescribing information for rosuvastatin (Crestor) includes the following: “... rare postmarketing reports of cognitive impairment (e.g., memory loss, forgetfulness, amnesia, memory impairment, and confusion) associated with the use of all statins.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7ND4BJT64JB2ZAI5OEYUAHV6TA"&gt;An article in the journal Medicine (Sept. 5, 2025) asked the question: “Are lipid-lowering drugs harmful to cognitive performance?” The authors’ answer: “This study suggests that statins and ezetimibe [Zetia] may have adverse effects on cognition, while PCSK9 inhibitors [Praluent, Repatha] and fibrates appear to have no such effect, which may help clinicians make more informed prescription decisions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NHRIVE3L7FEA5CEFBIHEZNEYNA"&gt;To help you and your doctor determine other ways to lower your risk of heart disease, you may wish to review our “eGuide to Cholesterol Control &amp;amp; Heart Health.” This online resource may be found under the Health eGuides tab at www.PeoplesPharmacy.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AW27S6DSHFCL3LRTWJSJCAN7NU"&gt;* * *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JV6MCHOH2VEWXPLJQLBNMTAT4M"&gt;&lt;i&gt;In their column, Joe and Teresa Graedon answer letters from readers. Write to them in care of King Features, 628 Virginia Drive, Orlando, FL 32803, or email them via their website: www.PeoplesPharmacy.com. Their newest book is “Top Screwups Doctors Make and How to Avoid Them.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3AFBVV95cUxOV21OcVljY2pSdWVFcDM5X2E5TEViWmVCcTQ5V0Z6cnRTOERydHQyZHhJY1hLNzAxWjNTTmNTRmUzLXluNjZiYVJNOGtaaWNRbWFPVG9ZNEtvc0gxNkI4NTFIRGJvajc0QnRqMDRGWG5FVE5rdGZWOTdoTTQ1U21jek9qWkFtZVFWMEFJZDA2cnk1LUE0X2c3dXdKVVpmTjN6RUdWaXhDWjFaNkFnQTBtVTFqNk5wbEZvN253eGpDM1dyX1B4d2hYSjVNeG1WMWo3NUJicUhkV0p5a0lz0gHwAUFVX3lxTE9KS3pJM0w1MlJ4UjU0dWJtcnp5dGhORzRnV0RWcVp4bnAyRXZvMVRPUERDZmNBN1Q0d3A0d1RCZVoyek9KcVcwVDNyOTBOSFFTUDdEWTdRMGkxQ2J6bVhsR1dIeXB3VDhKTjdNN0E5VV9SeFVjQ1I5N1NLWHpEMXVHQUd3cm1KQUVxSXlTTk5NTXUtQWhpRktLOWN0Tmg4UVkzOE1OMGJNOGxxVy11VGE4aS1objJKNkJySjJYaXZSWHJ0Z0tzSEZvMzJncmhrT2ducWZhNEx2VGpSbHNpMVM0OU5CR2hCSTY4Y3ZzUFAyZw</guid></item><item><title>加拿大官员表示，美国医疗机构不再依赖准确的信息--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2026/jan/04/canada-us-health-institutions-information</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Canadian officials and public health experts are warning that US health and science institutions can no longer be depended upon for accurate information, particularly when it comes to &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/vaccines" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;vaccinations&lt;/a&gt;, amid fears that misinformation from the &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/trump-administration" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Trump administration&lt;/a&gt; could further erode Canadians’ confidence in healthcare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“I can’t imagine a world in which this misinformation doesn’t creep into Canadians’ consciousness and leads to doubt,” said Dawn Bowdish, an immunologist and professor at McMaster University in Ontario.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Those fears have emerged as the US health secretary, &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/robert-f-kennedy-jr" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Robert F Kennedy Jr&lt;/a&gt;, has forwarded an anti-vaccine agenda. In December, a panel appointed by Kennedy voted to remove a longstanding recommendation by the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) that all newborns be vaccinated against hepatitis B.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The CDC also &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/nov/21/rfk-jr-cdc-vaccine-autism" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;updated its website in November&lt;/a&gt; at the instruction of Kennedy to claim that “studies have not ruled out the possibility that infant vaccines cause autism”, which top public health experts have decried as false.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The agency’s move toward misinformation and away from public health leadership makes it more difficult to combat distrust in vaccinations in &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/canada" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Canada&lt;/a&gt;, says Bowdish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In December, Canada’s health minister, Marjorie Michel, warned that US health and science institutions can no longer be depended upon for accurate information. In an interview with the Canadian Press, she said: “I cannot trust them as a reliable partner, no.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Michel also told CBC News that “some” Canadians could be influenced by Kennedy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The minister’s comments come at the conclusion of a disastrous year for measles in Canada, as the country was &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/nov/11/canada-loses-measles-free-elimination-status" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;stripped of its measles elimination status in November&lt;/a&gt; after more than 5,000 cases were reported across the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="e3fd6897-0f0b-4633-a86b-22dbcabd5e6c" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":8,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"A huge outbreak has made Ontario the measles centre of the western hemisphere","elementId":"e3fd6897-0f0b-4633-a86b-22dbcabd5e6c","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/jun/06/measles-outbreak-ontario-canada"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Physicians pointed to drops in childhood vaccination rates, limited access to family doctors and surging misinformation in the aftermath of the coronavirus pandemic as &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/jun/06/measles-outbreak-ontario-canada" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;just some of the factors&lt;/a&gt; fuelling the spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Meta’s ban on &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2023/aug/04/canada-meta-news-ban-facebook-fake" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the sharing of news&lt;/a&gt; in Canada, due to an ongoing dispute over legislation between the tech company and the government, also impedes reliable public health messaging, said Bowdish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In 2021, Canada published the results from a national survey on childhood immunisation and found 2.1% of two-year-olds had not received any vaccinations, an increase from 1.7% in 2019. Parents cited safety concerns or beliefs that vaccines did not work as their reasons for refusal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Bowdish said in 2021 that these reasons often were connected to not having a family doctor and were related to access rather than skepticism. But in the last four years she suspects misinformation has surged, and new data is not available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A December &lt;a href="https://documents.leger360.com/hubfs/Vaccines%20Hesitancy%20Dec.%202025/LegerHealthcare_VaccineHesitancy_2025%20Final.pdf" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;poll on vaccination hesitancy&lt;/a&gt; by research firm Leger Healthcare found that while most Canadians (74%) have confidence in vaccines, hesitancy has increased primarily due to fears around safety driven by social media and government mistrust.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The survey also found that 17% of those who expressed a lack of confidence in vaccines say they get their information from US government websites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"index":15,"listId":6042,"identityName":"the-stakes-us-election-edition","description":"A deep dive into the policies, controversies and oddities surrounding the Trump administration","name":"This Week in Trumpland","frequency":"At least once a week","successDescription":"You are subscribed","theme":"news","idApiUrl":"https://idapi.theguardian.com"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Kumanan Wilson, a doctor and professor of medicine at the University of Ottawa, said Canada can combat concerns about changes at the CDC by cooperating with other public health systems worldwide and taking the helm on developing health surveillance while US institutions languish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“If we build this system, it’s not only going to be great for Canada. We can provide really valuable information to the world,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But Michel Grignon, a professor and health economist at McMaster University, warned that increased mistrust in vaccinations in Canada is the country’s own doing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;He said the federal government instead needs to look at the homegrown causes of vaccine distrust, rather than focusing too much on the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;As Canada’s social safety nets have eroded over many decades, the pandemic was a further catalyst that disrupted social cohesion, pushing people to the margins of society and sowing distrust in government, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Grignon pointed to the &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/feb/07/ottawa-declares-state-of-emergency-as-canada-trucker-protest-paralyses-city" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;2022 trucker protests&lt;/a&gt; against Covid restrictions as a manifestation of the collapse of trust.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We are the source of our own problem, and our vaccine hesitancy has not much to do with the US. It has to do with us,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 13:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxPdVlieC1GR1dHdUowTVJiMjdNZWdtRHFxUURDTkpEQllGQVJ2YVVNWTE3LU5ITTBnOWFnMUZyRFo1WC0xOXRoblh2aTFIVlphOENaeVUybUE0bWhZbHBGMEp4Y0RDTFBFVzZPbUNFQUx5MHppWDlLbXVoQV9kOEpZRnB0YjlMNEs3MXZVN2VGZ3A</guid></item><item><title>如果您以这个姿势睡觉，医生会说您需要立即停止- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/t-rex-sleep-position-arms-goog_l_69405dcbe4b0fa125e7f4dd9</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It’s the same every morning. That tingling creeps into your fingers. And your shoulders? Stiff as always. You stretch out your arms and roll your shoulders until the feeling comes back. You get up, shake it off. Probably nothing, you tell yourself. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Just slept weird, right? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Maybe not. The way you sleep might be the real problem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Many people don’t even realize it’s happening. They fall asleep with their arms relaxed, but by 3 a.m., they’ve curled in tight. Sleeping with arms bent, curled close to your chest, has been dubbed the “T. rex position” on social media. And while doctors don’t call it that, they do warn that doing it night after night can turn those temporary pins and needles into lasting nerve damage.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When you sleep with your arms bent and tucked in, you can press on the nerves in your elbows or wrists,” &lt;a href="https://sleepopolis.com/experts/dr-raj-dasgupta/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Raj Dasgupta," data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69405dcbe4b0fa125e7f4dd9" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://sleepopolis.com/experts/dr-raj-dasgupta/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;Dr. Raj Dasgupta,&lt;/a&gt; a sleep medicine specialist and chief medical adviser for Sleepopolis, told HuffPost. “This can slow blood flow and make your arms feel numb or tingly. If you do it often, it can also strain your shoulders and make them stiff or sore.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://noceviva.com/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Matthew Bennett, " data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69405dcbe4b0fa125e7f4dd9" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://noceviva.com/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr. Matthew Bennett, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;a board-certified orthopedic surgeon, some people also develop similar nerve irritation at the wrist, much like what happens with carpal tunnel syndrome. Keeping your elbow bent all night builds pressure where nerves pass through narrow spaces. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Turns out, it’s surprisingly common — and it can steadily get worse over time. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Warning Signs Doctors Want You To Notice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.gulfphysio.com/author/kieran-sheridan/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Kieran Sheridan" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69405dcbe4b0fa125e7f4dd9" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.gulfphysio.com/author/kieran-sheridan/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kieran Sheridan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a physiotherapist and founder of GulfPhysio, sees complaints regularly in his practice. Patients often describe a “dead arm” feeling or needing to shake out their hands in the morning. “This is your body telling you your nervous system isn’t happy,” he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dasgupta also emphasized this. “If your arms or hands go numb every night, stay numb for a while after waking up, or start to feel weak during the day, it’s time to see a doctor.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Warning signs include shooting pain down your arm, trouble gripping things or even dropping your phone more often. Don’t mistake these for annoying symptoms or clumsiness. It’s your body telling you the damage is getting worse.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bennett said anyone who notices these symptoms becoming more frequent should get checked. “Most cases are manageable and respond well to early, conservative treatment,” he said. Skip treatment, and that’s when trouble starts. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“It’s usually temporary and goes away once you change your sleeping position,” Dasgupta noted. “But if the pressure keeps happening for a long time, weeks or months, it can cause lasting nerve damage.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;If you wake up with some numbness in your hands, wrists or arms, it could be due to the "T. rex" sleep position.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Your Body Locks Into This Position At Night&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Curling up feels comforting. It’s instinctive, like pulling a blanket tighter when you’re cold. However, there’s usually more behind it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The body slips into self-protection even when there’s no threat. When the nervous system is on high alert from chronic pain, stress, poor sleep or trauma, Bennett said, “we may subconsciously adopt postures that feel safer and less exposed.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We automatically search for safety during sleep. And for some people, that search runs deeper than others. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://juditmerayopsicologa.es/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Judit Merayo Barredo" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69405dcbe4b0fa125e7f4dd9" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://juditmerayopsicologa.es/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Judit Merayo Barredo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; a clinical psychologist, said she had a patient who came to therapy experiencing chronic insomnia and persistent fatigue. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Every night, her patient would wake up tightly curled, arms pressed to her chest, shoulders hunched in that T. rex position. “She often woke with muscle tension, a clenched jaw, and a feeling of emotional heaviness,” Barredo said, “despite sleeping for hours.” It turns out, Barredo’s client was dealing with heavy anxiety and expressing it in her sleep.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The first goal Barredo set for her patient was calming down her nervous system at night. They tried guided body scans before bed, pre-sleep journaling to get the stress out and also changing her sleep setup. The patient added extra pillows, softened the lights and built a routine she could actually stick to. Barredo said the “shift in her sleep position was one of the first signs that her body was learning to feel safe again.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Of course, not everyone sleeping in the T. rex position suffers from chronic anxiety. Everyday stress, trauma, poor sleep and regular tension can trigger the same response.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple Ways To Retrain Your Body To Sleep Differently&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The problem is willpower doesn’t work during sleep. You can’t tell yourself to stop curling up in the middle of the night. So the aim is to make it physically harder to curl up using barriers and supports.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bennett recommended something surprisingly simple: wrap a hand towel around your elbow and secure it loosely with an elastic bandage. This creates a soft barrier that makes deep bending uncomfortable without waking you up. If you have wrist pain, a wrist brace at night also helps.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;For side sleepers, Sheridan suggests a couple of approaches:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Place a small pillow or folded towel between your arms and chest to prevent that full curl.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hug a body pillow to keep your arms neutral while giving you something to hold.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you sleep on your back, rest your arms by your side or on a pillow near the hips. Your arms should stay straight or just slightly bent. Don’t tuck them under your body or pillow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Keeping the arms open allows for better circulation, less nerve compression, and faster muscle recovery,” Sheridan explained.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Since this position often reflects a nervous system on high alert, Bennett suggested calming techniques before bed, like breath work or gentle stretching. “The goal isn’t rigid posture correction,” he said. “It’s offering the body more supportive options for rest and recovery.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you wake up with numb hands, stiff shoulders, or pins and needles in your arm, you don’t need a total sleep overhaul, just a few small tweaks. Tonight’s the night to make a change. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The T. rex couldn’t change its position ― b&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;ut you can.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 12:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxONHdISXdIanlJSGs0VTNqdkg5c1NuQnNYQjZvRWpidHhYZHBvem4zUnVwLTYzMTZmY1oteHFyYkNuUDlxWEpTVl9XZXhqNWZrTjhHODMwTFZyLWZTZFd0WGhVSy1WZGVRMDg4SkhjZDcwRHplUGJNb1hzZk91TXhBWTRHa0t4UlY3dlBTN1RnVS1JQdIBlwFBVV95cUxQb1U1TU1ZZ2YwNWJwQ0ttUUFSbGFoZGs2MDVPR1VucHAtLVFLYTFJZHNTZkN6RjNaZG1uYW00QmF1WFZoOUZpMGF2djZfOXFEMXFGMVR6OVAwcC1Lbk9DMzVOYmJKUFhrRGRUQjd1VmctRjhlODZTTVVWOElOMmRSYWwybk5GanV6VEJkUGZLcEt6M21PbThN</guid></item><item><title>严重的事情正在发生在脱离GLP-1s的人身上-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/glp1-weight-gain</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="article-featured-image-figure"&gt;
			
			
	&lt;p class="article-featured-image-caption-container"&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="article-featured-image-caption"&gt;
			Getty Images / Jon Challicom 		&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/figure&gt;
	
	
	
	
	
	&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;Many people who successfully lost weight on Ozempic and other &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/treatments/13901-glp-1-agonists" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;GLP-1 agonist drugs&lt;/a&gt; are having trouble weaning themselves off the injectables, &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cn98pdpyjz5o" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;according to the &lt;em&gt;BBC&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; because the hunger for food comes roaring back with a vengeance — and hence the pounds start creeping up again, hinting that patients are likely to develop life-long dependencies on the substances.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“For the first 38 years of my life, I was overweight — now I’m six stone (38kg) [83 pounds] lighter,” Tanya Hall, a Wegovy user who can’t get off the drug, told the news organization. “Therefore, there’s part of me that feels like there’s an addiction to keep it going because it makes me feel the way that I feel, it makes me feel in control.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;This is borne out by &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-says-stopping-obesity-drug-may-cause-full-weight-regain-5-years-2023-03-30/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; that found patients who stop using these medications often gain much of their weight back. That’s why you have celebrities like Oprah, who &lt;a href="https://people.com/oprah-reveals-she-stopped-using-glp1s-for-12-months-and-shares-exactly-what-happened-exclusive-11877163" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;told &lt;em&gt;People Magazine&lt;/em&gt; last month&lt;/a&gt; that she plans to stay on it indefinitely. The implication: many users will have to treat their obesity as a chronic condition and will need to stay on these drugs for the rest of their lives.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“It’s going to be a lifetime thing,” Oprah said. “I’m on high blood pressure medication, and if I go off the high blood pressure medication, my blood pressure is going to go up. The same thing is true now, I realize, with these medications. I’ve proven to myself I need it.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;For patients who do get off the drugs, they tend to gain two thirds of their lost weight back, &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-says-stopping-obesity-drug-may-cause-full-weight-regain-5-years-2023-03-30/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;according to research&lt;/a&gt; by Ozempic maker Novo Nordisk. Physician Hussain Al-Zubaidi told the &lt;em&gt;BBC &lt;/em&gt;that he’s seen patients gain 60 to 80 percent back of the weight they lost.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;It might seem hopeless task, but all is not lost, according to Al-Zubaidi. He said patients should have an “exit strategy” in which they have made healthier lifestyle changes while on the injectables; the lifestyle changes can sustain the weight loss once they are completely off the drugs.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;That’s what happened to Ellen Ogley, who told the &lt;em&gt;BBC &lt;/em&gt;that she lost 48.5 pounds while on Eli Lily’s GLP-1 drug Mounjaro. While on the medication, she established healthier eating habits and incorporated excerise into her routine. Even off the drugs for some time, she’s been able to maintain her weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“I want people to know that life after Mounjaro can be sustainable as well,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on Ozempic:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://futurism.com/health-medicine/retatrutide-ozempic-gray-black-market"&gt;People Jabbing Themselves With Black Market “GLP-3” Drugs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiY0FVX3lxTE9TNlpXa29RVjF2QkQ0cUJhb2FCdW1YLThvRE1qRG8xU3AwU2gwaVhhR1ctTng4WjJiX01Kc2Ffcy1MazU1TUVIOTRmWmJIOEh0UmRMS2ozN00zbDFkTUttQWFwdw</guid></item><item><title>在一种新变种的推动下，流感正在迅速崛起。以下是须知事项-《洛杉矶时报》</title><link>https://www.latimes.com/science/story/2026-01-04/flu-is-rising-rapidly-driven-by-new-variant-heres-what-to-know</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-element="story-body" class="ct-rich-text-children font-cms-font-brand-text font-normal text-lg leading-7.75 [&amp;amp;_&amp;gt;p]:text-cms-story-body-color-text clearfix mb-10 md:max-w-170 md:mx-auto" data-dateline data-subscriber-content&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;WASHINGTON — &lt;/span&gt;Flu is rising rapidly across the U.S., driven by a new variant of the virus — and cases are expected to keep growing as holiday travel plays out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That variant, known as “subclade K,” led to early outbreaks in the United Kingdom, Japan and Canada. On Tuesday, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported high or very high levels of illness in more than half of the states. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC estimated there have been at least 7.5 million illnesses in the U.S., 81,000 hospitalizations and 3,100 deaths from flu so far this season. That includes at least eight child deaths, and is based on data as of Dec. 20, prior to major holiday gatherings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some states are particularly hard-hit. New York’s health department said the week ending Dec. 20 marked the most flu cases the state had recorded in a single week since 2004: 71,000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s far too soon to know if this flu season will be as severe as last winter’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it’s not too late to get a flu shot, which health experts say can still prevent severe illness even if someone gets infected. While this year’s vaccine isn’t a perfect match to the subclade K strain, &lt;a class="link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12639273/" target="_blank"&gt;a preliminary analysis from the UK&lt;/a&gt; found it offered at least partial protection, lowering people’s risk of hospitalization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the CDC, only about 42% of adults and children have gotten a flu vaccination so far this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-is-subclade-k-flu" class="subhead"&gt;What is subclade K flu?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flu virus is a shape-shifter, constantly mutating, and it comes in multiple forms. There are two subtypes of Type A flu, and subclade K is a mutated version of one of them, named H3N2. That H3N2 strain is always harsh, especially for older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subclade K’s mutations aren’t enough of a change to be considered an entirely new kind of flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But they’re different enough to evade some of the protection from this year’s vaccine, said Andrew Pekosz, a virus expert at Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="will-subclade-k-make-people-sicker" class="subhead"&gt;Will subclade K make people sicker?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC said it’s too soon to know how severe this season will be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flu seasons dominated by any version of H3N2 tend to be bad, with more infections overall and more people becoming seriously ill. But Hopkins’ Pekosz cautioned it will take time to tease apart whether this subclade K version simply spreads more easily or also is more dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That question aside, the CDC notes there are some prescription medicines to treat flu — usually recommended for people at high risk of complications. But they generally need to be started a day or two after symptoms begin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="who-needs-a-flu-vaccine" class="subhead"&gt;Who needs a flu vaccine?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC and major medical societies all recommend a flu vaccine for just about everyone age 6 months and older. Despite lots of recent misinformation and confusion about vaccines, the flu recommendations haven’t changed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flu is particularly dangerous for people 65 and older, pregnant women, young children and people of any age who have chronic health problems, including asthma, diabetes, heart disease and weak immune systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The vaccines are brewed to protect against three influenza strains. Despite concern over that new H3N2 variant, they appear to be a good match against H1N1 and Type B flu that may also circulate this year, Pekosz said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are shots for all ages, as well as the nasal spray FluMist for ages 2 to 49. For the first time this year, some people may be eligible to vaccinate themselves with FluMist at home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Neergaard writes for the Associated Press. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Los Angeles Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxQMTh2V2h4bC1YeEZ1QVRWRjl5V183RkdlWmt2cHoxMmFURy14MGd3azZ6SUdmcU9oTEtSQ1ZNSW4wSmhSNFdoOTdDX21XZW5rTUdCeVhkMFIyVGJKbFNFR2N0TFZtT2ctMEhtaWprenpwTXVsaU1BU09kM1QxTzMyaERqVjdYVl9VeWVKLXFlajFqYUdjRmRNa0ZvUFVCVE1RSjFrYnFXUDgxc05NMzR5Qw</guid></item><item><title>发生在脱离GLP-1s的人身上的严峻事件-雅虎新西兰新闻</title><link>https://nz.news.yahoo.com/something-grim-happening-people-off-110000759.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Many people who successfully lost weight on Ozempic and other &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/treatments/13901-glp-1-agonists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:GLP-1 agonist drugs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;GLP-1 agonist drugs&lt;/a&gt; are having trouble weaning themselves off the injectables, &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cn98pdpyjz5o" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:according to the BBC;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;according to the &lt;em&gt;BBC&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; because the hunger for food comes roaring back with a vengeance — and hence the pounds start creeping up again, hinting that patients are likely to develop life-long dependencies on the substances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“For the first 38 years of my life, I was overweight — now I’m six stone (38kg) [83 pounds] lighter,” Tanya Hall, a Wegovy user who can’t get off the drug, told the news organization. “Therefore, there’s part of me that feels like there’s an addiction to keep it going because it makes me feel the way that I feel, it makes me feel in control.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This is borne out by &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-says-stopping-obesity-drug-may-cause-full-weight-regain-5-years-2023-03-30/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:research;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; that found patients who stop using these medications often gain much of their weight back. That’s why you have celebrities like Oprah, who &lt;a href="https://people.com/oprah-reveals-she-stopped-using-glp1s-for-12-months-and-shares-exactly-what-happened-exclusive-11877163" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:told People Magazine last month;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;told &lt;em&gt;People Magazine&lt;/em&gt; last month&lt;/a&gt; that she plans to stay on it indefinitely. The implication: many users will have to treat their obesity as a chronic condition and will need to stay on these drugs for the rest of their lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“It’s going to be a lifetime thing,” Oprah said. “I’m on high blood pressure medication, and if I go off the high blood pressure medication, my blood pressure is going to go up. The same thing is true now, I realize, with these medications. I’ve proven to myself I need it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;For patients who do get off the drugs, they tend to gain two thirds of their lost weight back, &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-nordisk-says-stopping-obesity-drug-may-cause-full-weight-regain-5-years-2023-03-30/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:according to research;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;according to research&lt;/a&gt; by Ozempic maker Novo Nordisk. Physician Hussain Al-Zubaidi told the &lt;em&gt;BBC &lt;/em&gt;that he’s seen patients gain 60 to 80 percent back of the weight they lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It might seem hopeless task, but all is not lost, according to Al-Zubaidi. He said patients should have an “exit strategy” in which they have made healthier lifestyle changes while on the injectables; the lifestyle changes can sustain the weight loss once they are completely off the drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;That’s what happened to Ellen Ogley, who told the &lt;em&gt;BBC &lt;/em&gt;that she lost 48.5 pounds while on Eli Lily’s GLP-1 drug Mounjaro. While on the medication, she established healthier eating habits and incorporated excerise into her routine. Even off the drugs for some time, she’s been able to maintain her weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“I want people to know that life after Mounjaro can be sustainable as well,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on Ozempic:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/people-jabbing-themselves-black-market-130000262.html" data-ylk="slk:People Jabbing Themselves With Black Market “GLP-3” Drugs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;People Jabbing Themselves With Black Market “GLP-3” Drugs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News New Zealand</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxPYzdmek9BeU84Zm1pbXBGdUZYRVN4bEd6cVNnMGpEYVM3Tk5aUlRyVVhRWTU1MVY5aHNfTWJaNThMTU4xMldtSHJ1QlJUaGlkdHpjOHBOeWN6TVIxbklJelBDUVdCdUVvUTdnUk9hQjJ6ZFZ4YmxoUXZ2MUpubzhYR0tn</guid></item><item><title>专家警告：康涅狄格州已发现新的“超级可怕”真菌- CT Insider</title><link>https://www.ctinsider.com/connecticut/article/ct-candida-auris-spread-fungus-symptoms-pandemic-21267814.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>CT Insider</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 10:04:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxQdElxUklQVlM0WjU4aUhkVnpfbllkN0ZjQ0FUaXJVRy1Yc1VPUUJQQ0p2R0preFZrRC0zQXdYOHl0VjJxWm9rVVJjampISjF4eEVGTWdwd21jUzF4ajFibURFdWxkaGx4d3FJUHlsMVNuVGw5cGJOSjd4dDVvb2d6WnZQMF9mWURldUdYUURTNkExNC0zckozNTNCZGVUQm81N2pfaWRLeGhPYkk</guid></item><item><title>随着CT恢复牡蛎，研究发现痕量的芬太尼、氯胺酮会破坏它们的生存- CT Insider</title><link>https://www.ctinsider.com/connecticut/article/oyster-larvae-drug-traces-study-long-island-sound-21256672.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>CT Insider</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 10:04:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxNR00wZXpUQklfRFdqbEUycVNob2FITURqUFY0eTd2RlhoaXFfcm91LTBBdUdFeVNrZy1HOE9KMGlmSkNvNVVUNm5abGVRUHlOU1NCTm5mMDNLZTVDLW1xTVRHQnRHTy1DM25rVzI1ZTJ2Q3hyaEptbGFqMVc0OFZuNGdzRkhadVB3TmRKa2ZRckZKcHZJZ2N2WS0tQm1tNThkVnRnMXdndFBnMTA1</guid></item><item><title>当Twinkle Khanna打开黄褐斑时，称之为“bin bulaya mehman” ：这是我们在印度时报上所知道的</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/when-twinkle-khanna-opened-up-on-melasma-calling-it-a-bin-bulaya-mehman-heres-what-we-know-on-the-condition/articleshow/126332617.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2023, former actor turned author &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/topic/twinkle-khanna" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Twinkle Khanna&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, revealed her experience with melasma, calling it an "uninvited guest" that appeared during her second pregnancy. Talking about it on her Tweak video, the now 52-year-old said that she developed melasma after her family trip, and instead of souvenirs, she came back with a melasma flare‑up, describing it as a “bin bulaya mehman” (an uninvited guest). She made a joke about how she now feels compelled to tell every pregnant woman she meets to use tranexamic acid, niacinamide and sunscreen, because these products help prevent this difficult skin discoloration. Her open discussion has enabled numerous women to recognize that melasma affects many people without causing harm, while it creates emotional challenges, which require appropriate medical treatment. Let's learn more...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What is melasma&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Melasma is a common skin condition where patches of skin become darker than the surrounding area, usually on the face. The medical term for this condition is chloasma, because it appears mostly during pregnancy, but it also affects women who use birth control pills, hormone therapy and also men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Twinkle Khanna Opens Up On Menopause: 'I Squat, I Lunge, I Do Pelvic-Floor Exercises'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this condition, the dark skin areas show brown or gray‑brown colors, which appear on the cheeks, forehead, nose bridge, upper lip and chin areas. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The condition of melasma does not cause any pain, does not itch, is neither contagious or cancerous, so it only affects appearance. The condition which affects facial skin causes people to lose their self-assurance, because they become embarrassed by their physical appearance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What causes melasma&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The skin condition Melasma develops when melanocytes which produce skin pigment, become hyperactive to create excessive melanin production. Experts don’t know exactly why this happens in every case, but several triggers are known:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sun exposure-The sun's UV rays function as the primary factor which causes melasma to develop, and sunlight exposure leads to worsening of melasma symptoms and treatment relapse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hormonal shifts which occur during pregnancy and when using birth control pills and hormone replacement therapy, lead to melasma development because they modify body hormone production.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who have family members with melasma, face an increased risk of developing this condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The skin becomes more sensitive when using particular medications together with certain skincare products. The skin becomes more sensitive when using particular medications, together with certain skincare products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stress and thyroid problems-Stress and thyroid disorders seem to affect certain individuals who develop these conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Melasma is much more common in women, especially those with medium to dark skin tones (Fitzpatrick skin types III–V), but men can also get it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Melasma proves difficult to treat because of its specific characteristics&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8511390/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Melasma&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; is known to be stubborn and often comes back, even after successful treatment. The triggers which include sun exposure and hormonal changes, make it difficult to prevent them from happening. People who try different skin treatments including creams, peels and lasers will experience their dark skin patches return, because they do not protect their skin from sunlight, and their hormone levels continue to shift.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The skin becomes irritated during certain treatments which lead to worsening pigmentation symptoms, particularly when patients have darker skin tones, so they should follow a gradual treatment plan under dermatological supervision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Common treatments for melasma&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The treatment of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31802394/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;melasma&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; requires patients to use topical creams, while practicing sun protection and undergoing medical procedures depending on their skin condition severity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Topical creams (applied on skin)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are the first line of treatment and are used daily:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="72"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hydroquinone (HQ) functions as a skin-lightening agent which decreases melanin production during treatment periods that usually last several months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Triple combination cream-The combination of hydroquinone with hydrocortisone steroid and tretinoin retinoid, makes this treatment one of the most effective solutions for melasma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="77"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Niacinamide (vitamin B3) serves two purposes by decreasing skin discoloration and strengthening the skin barrier, while being suitable for extended use because it has a mild effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The treatment of dark spots includes Kojic acid, azelaic acid, arbutin and vitamin C as alternative lightening agents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="82"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;2. Oral tranexamic acid (oTA)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="84"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twinkle Khanna mentioned tranexamic acid, which is a medicine that can be taken by mouth to reduce melasma. Research indicates that oral tranexamic acid serves as a protected supplementary treatment which doctors can use to treat melasma patients, who fail to respond to topical creams. However, it should only be taken under a doctor’s supervision, because it can affect blood clotting in some people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="87"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;3. Procedures (done by a dermatologist)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="89"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A dermatologist will recommend treatment options for stubborn melasma cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="91"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The treatment of chemical peels involves applying mild acids such as glycolic acid, salicylic acid and TCA, to remove skin surface layers which helps decrease skin pigmentation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="93"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The treatment of laser and light technology includes Q-switched lasers, intense pulsed light (IPL) and fractional lasers, but these methods increase the chances of developing skin irritation and making pigmentation conditions worse, particularly for patients with Indian and South Asian skin types.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="96"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The treatment of microneedling with microdermabrasion enables skin creams to reach deeper skin layers, while simultaneously enhancing skin texture and reducing pigmentation problems, during the procedure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="98"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;The most important step: Sun protection&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="100"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twinkle Khanna correctly advises people to use sunscreen because sun protection stands as the primary method to control melasma. The sun's ultraviolet rays activate melasma and lead to its worsening condition, which occurs both under sunny conditions and through window glass and on cloudy days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="103"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="105"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Experts recommend:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="108"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;People should apply broad-spectrum sunscreen with SPF 30 or higher to their skin throughout each day, regardless of their location inside or outside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="110"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;They also need to reapply sunscreen every 2–3 hours when they are outside, and when the body starts sweating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="112"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;They should protect themselves from the sun by using wide-brimmed hats and sunglasses while staying in shaded areas during peak sun hours between 10 a.m. and 4 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="116"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best creams and procedures fail to prevent melasma from returning because they do not provide enough protection against sunlight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="118"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Lifestyle and emotional side&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="120"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twinkle also shared an important message about self‑care. “Everyone expects us to be Mother India and focus all our energies on the child. Let me tell you — the child will grow up, go to college, and you will still be living with melasma. So give yourself permission to take care of yourself and your skin”. This resonates with many women who feel guilty for spending time and money on their own skin and well‑being," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="124"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The treatment of melasma requires more than topical creams and laser therapy because it involves additional aspects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="126"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The process requires patients to wait because it needs multiple weeks or months to generate results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="128"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Avoiding harsh scrubs and home remedies that can irritate the skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="130"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The management of stress, together with proper sleep practices, will benefit your skin health in general.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="133"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;People should consult dermatologists instead of using powerful skin products which could harm their skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="135"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;When to see a dermatologist&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="137"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Melasma is not dangerous, but it’s best to see a dermatologist if:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="139"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dark patches appear suddenly or change in shape/colour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="141"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The over-the-counter creams have not provided any relief during the past several months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="143"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A dermatologist will verify that the condition is melasma while ruling out other pigmentation disorders, and will create a protected treatment approach and track any potential adverse reactions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="145"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is informational only and not a substitute for medical advice&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="147"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="150"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="153"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 08:07:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAJBVV95cUxQSzFIbGJzQ1hNZUxwcDZmQ2w2aVR6NU9sNmx2LXVEUjVCbHllUmFwZm5zcTNWbW5IRmVmWVJIM0tzVFlqNkxTX3Vvbk4wWUptUmhGOGFGTGxhWEJFazZab3pSajdVa0pBdHlDaU4yaGNDMFpCeDl2RzNxRjJkZVlzMGhpempXUWp3QUVLUGpCeVpOV2hxWUxqYlJNb01nQnVWN0hZTXlpSmJLX1VpUTI1WEVWQTN5SkNfX3lwSExnbkFhMDZhb1QtcUJpQmJaWTRpTTBtVktIZFdJaVZubzhINXNGVVNrNzkwUW9iQ21rQWVFb08tdWo3SVRGeFpZLU1WcDlXekwtOE9tdWk1SFd6UG0zR0JPSERUczVaYVdzdXFQdzJqR2J4YTBFeklVTU1N</guid></item><item><title>研究发现， 2型糖尿病会改变人体心脏- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2026/01/260103155034.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Researchers at the University of Sydney have uncovered new evidence showing that type 2 diabetes directly changes the heart's structure and how it produces energy. These findings help explain why people living with diabetes face a much higher risk of developing heart failure.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study, published in &lt;em&gt;EMBO Molecular Medicine&lt;/em&gt;, was led by Dr. Benjamin Hunter and Associate Professor Sean Lal from the School of Medical Sciences. The team examined donated human heart tissue from patients receiving heart transplants in Sydney, comparing it with tissue from healthy donors. Their analysis revealed that diabetes drives specific molecular changes inside heart cells and alters the physical makeup of heart muscle. These effects were most pronounced in patients with ischemia cardiomyopathy, which is the leading cause of heart failure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We've long seen a correlation between heart disease and type 2 diabetes," said Dr. Hunter, "but this is the first research to jointly look at diabetes and ischemia heart disease and uncover a unique molecular profile in people with both conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Our findings show that diabetes alters how the heart produces energy, maintains its structure under stress, and contracts to pump blood. Using advanced microscopy techniques, we were able to see direct changes to the heart muscle as a result of this, in the form of a build-up of fibrous tissue."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heart disease remains the leading cause of death in Australia, and more than 1.2 million Australians are living with type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Associate Professor Lal said: "Our research links heart disease and diabetes in ways that have never been demonstrated in humans, offering new insights into potential treatment strategies that could one day benefit millions of people in Australia and globally."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking Inside Diseased Human Hearts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To better understand how diabetes affects the heart, the researchers studied heart tissue from both transplant recipients and healthy individuals. This direct examination allowed them to see how diabetes influences heart biology in real human patients rather than relying solely on animal models.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results showed that diabetes is more than a co-morbidity for heart disease. It actively accelerates heart failure by interfering with essential biological processes and reshaping heart muscle at the microscopic level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The metabolic effect of diabetes in the heart is not fully understood in humans," said Dr. Hunter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Diabetes Disrupts the Heart's Energy Supply&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In healthy hearts, energy is mainly generated from fats, with glucose and ketones also contributing. Previous research has shown that glucose use increases during heart failure. However, diabetes interferes with this process by reducing how sensitive heart cells are to insulin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Under healthy conditions, the heart primarily uses fats but also glucose and ketones as fuel for energy. It has previously been described that glucose uptake is increased in heart failure, however, diabetes reduces the insulin sensitivity of glucose transporters -- proteins that move glucose in and out of cells -- in heart muscle cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We observed that diabetes worsens the molecular characteristics of heart failure in patients with advanced heart disease and increases the stress on mitochondria -- the powerhouse of the cell which produces energy."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Structural Damage and Fibrosis in the Heart Muscle&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond energy production, the researchers found that diabetes affects the proteins responsible for heart muscle contraction and calcium regulation. In patients with both diabetes and ischemic heart disease, these proteins were produced at lower levels. At the same time, excess fibrous tissue accumulated within the heart, making the muscle stiffer and less able to pump blood efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"RNA sequencing confirmed that many of these protein changes were also reflected at the gene transcription level, particularly in pathways related to energy metabolism and tissue structure, which reinforces our other observations," said Dr. Hunter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"And once we had these clues at the molecular level, we were able to confirm these structural changes using confocal microscopy."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Implications for Future Treatment and Care&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Associate Professor Lal said identifying mitochondrial dysfunction and fibrosis-related pathways opens the door to new treatment approaches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Now that we've linked diabetes and heart disease at the molecular level and observed how it changes energy production in the heart while also changing its structure, we can begin to explore new treatment avenues," he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Our findings could also be used to inform diagnosis criteria and disease management strategies across cardiology and endocrinology, improving care for millions of patients."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 05:35:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFB3eW1hb2x6ckF4cUx1WjZjel93SkpzR2d0SVFVQVBnX253QXZva0Q1dUI1dmRzRGNnbG9oTmd5aUxNRUlvOEJhUnpkM1Y4cnR3dkhyOHNZcVZGcFBpcHVjY3dhOVVSZlY4Rmp5MkgyYw</guid></item><item><title>Kareena Kapoor的营养学家Rujuta Diwekar分享了“来自印度不同地区的冬季食物” ： Bajra bhakri到cholai |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/kareena-kapoor-nutritionist-rujuta-diwekar-shares-winter-foods-from-different-parts-of-india-bajra-bhakri-to-cholai-101767501386022.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/kareena-kapoor-nutritionist-rujuta-diwekar-shares-winter-foods-from-different-parts-of-india-bajra-bhakri-to-cholai-101767501386022.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;The cold winter months can affect everything from digestion and metabolism to energy levels and immunity. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;While layering up and sipping hot drinks may offer immediate relief from the chill, what you eat plays an equally important role in keeping the body warm and resilient.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2026/01/04/550x309/rujuta_diwekar_kareena_kapoor_1748772120748_1767501625168.jpg" alt="Celebrity nutritionist Rujuta Diwekar discusses foods and attitude for winter wellness. (Instagram)" title="Celebrity nutritionist Rujuta Diwekar discusses foods and attitude for winter wellness. (Instagram)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2026/01/04/550x309/rujuta_diwekar_kareena_kapoor_1748772120748_1767501625168.jpg" alt="Celebrity nutritionist Rujuta Diwekar discusses foods and attitude for winter wellness. (Instagram)" title="Celebrity nutritionist Rujuta Diwekar discusses foods and attitude for winter wellness. (Instagram)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Celebrity nutritionist Rujuta Diwekar discusses foods and attitude for winter wellness. (Instagram)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Celebrity nutritionist &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/rujuta-diwekar" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Rujuta Diwekar,"&gt;Rujuta Diwekar,&lt;/a&gt; who has worked with stars like Kareena Kapoor, shared in her January 3 Instagram post Indian foods that naturally help keep the body warm during colder months.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;What foods help keep the body warm in winter&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sharing examples from regional winter diets, Rujuta highlighted how everyday foods consumed across different parts of India naturally help the body stay warm. “Bajra bhakri with loni, which is basically white butter, arshi chai chutney, which is &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/flaxseed-gel-the-viral-diy-hack-for-glass-hair-101766145172897.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="flaxseed"&gt;flaxseed&lt;/a&gt; chutney, and everything that is eaten here, like mandua ka roti, kulith ka paratha, and gehat ki dal, all of these things keep you warm,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;She also pointed out that winter meals often include a balance of grains, lentils, and vegetables. “There is also one green sabzi that is eaten here, cholai,” Rujuta added, underlining how seasonal greens play a key role in winter nutrition.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Why attitude matter as much as food in winter&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond food, &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/celebrity-nutritionist-rujuta-diwekar-shares-3-small-lifestyle-habits-that-can-make-a-big-impact-on-your-health-101762343698563.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Rujuta shared a simple life"&gt;Rujuta shared a simple life&lt;/a&gt; lesson she once learned from an elderly person, highlighting the role of mindset in dealing with winter. Recalling the anecdote, she said, “I learned a very nice kahawat (proverb) from an old wise person. His grandchild was complaining, ‘Dadaji, mujhe bohot thand lag rahi hai’ (Grandfather, I’m feeling very cold).”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to Rujuta, the grandfather’s response carried a deeper meaning. “The grandfather told him, ‘Tum thand ko pakdo’ (Catch the cold),” she said. “So the child stood with his chest open, and the cold went away.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Drawing from the story, Rujuta emphasised that resilience and attitude matter just as much as diet. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;“I think in North India, there is very good jugaad for everything (a smart, practical solution for everything),” she said, adding, “You don’t just need food, you also need the attitude.&lt;/span&gt;”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 04:52:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgJBVV95cUxQanM5dWxNa0w5dnZsZWQyUjVwNXZrS0JFUEhyYTZtcVpwQ1gwZllrMTlfbFo3ZUE4XzNDUlpzdmZfV2dnMEtSMG9MSXZSRER3ZVktRG5NRFR6T2l4eUoxVDBOd1BhRkhXQzBMUVoxVG93dU9WVkc0aVE5VEl0TzZRa2ZEdURndllQUmxFVVVkN0N2R2d0enVDV0hMUGlnd19hRmJsdURIZ0F6RjNxaTFqdVNma0JxOXpycUxVNkNuUHBLOTRlZUNZZGZhU3N1Q2ZpaXNKRTZjRTBLbjhjcS04eW9CUTZzSFNTSWliSTJWUFQzQ2x3MUlZU05GUmhycVRiRDZlYl9VWFpidGRlVU1uMnBR0gGXAkFVX3lxTE4tNTl1alBaTnNEQ1ZFbGJnNzkxNU0yTm14NFNseHlpaktuSFZfUWtlcElMbHBLcjZBUzR0SFRwejZUR2ZfQ3BqWnZEVkUxZFVFU3Y2dnloRk1TbkNscnp2ZW1xTFFPUDB6OHVMY0xaZmZJWVdkSWY5YjA4OXZzaENPZFRzWjgydzZxbWhHMFpuaE1rbURDOE1zUm5zR21KWE81b3dHZVNvTFJvUk42bHpQZndIYkMxRW1LLV9McGtUcnJOYU9rb0dnNkdybmhRY1pPUzl5eXl6ZkNkMHdmalE1QndIMGN2eEEtTHFpMVhoR0JWX2VqNHJybGNSc0ZGN0VpWDZXa1REeE1VejEzdEt6Q05RWTRrSQ</guid></item><item><title>研究人员警告说，随着耐药性的增长，致命的“超级细菌”正在美国蔓延- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/news/deadly-superbug-spreading-across-us-232325547.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A deadly, drug-resistant fungus already spreading rapidly through U.S. hospitals is becoming even more threatening worldwide, though there may be hope for new treatments, according to a new scientific review.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Candida auris (C. auris), often described as a &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/infectious-disease/superbugs" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:"superbug fungus,";elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;"superbug fungus,"&lt;/a&gt; is spreading globally and increasingly resisting human immune systems, Hackensack Meridian Center for Discovery and Innovation (CDI) researchers said in a review published in early December.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings reinforce prior CDC warnings that have labeled C. auris an "urgent antimicrobial threat" — the first fungal pathogen to receive that designation — as U.S. cases have surged, particularly in hospitals and long-term care centers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/dangerous-spike-superbug-infections-surges-across-us-experts-share-cautions" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dangerous Spike In Superbug Infections Surges Across Us As Experts Share Cautions;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dangerous Spike In Superbug Infections Surges Across Us As Experts Share Cautions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approximately 7,000 cases were identified across dozens of U.S. states in 2025, &lt;a href="https://stacks.cdc.gov/view/cdc/251234" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:according to the CDC,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;according to the CDC,&lt;/a&gt; and it has reportedly been identified in at least 60 countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Candida auris is a drug-resistant fungus spreading in hospitals worldwide.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The review, published in Microbiology and Molecular Biology Reviews, helps explain why the pathogen is so difficult to contain and warns that outdated diagnostics and limited treatments lag behind. It was conducted by Dr. Neeraj Chauhan of the Hackensack Meridian CDI in New Jersey, Dr. Anuradha Chowdhary of the University of Delhi’s Medical Mycology Unit and Dr. Michail Lionakis, chief of the clinical mycology program at the National Institutes of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS/mvaj7wvj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read On The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Read On The Fox News App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their findings stress the need to develop "novel antifungal agents with broad-spectrum activity against human fungal pathogens, to improve diagnostic tests and to develop immune- and vaccine-based adjunct modalities for the treatment of high-risk patients," the researchers said &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-candida-auris-globally-drug-resistance.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:in a statement.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;in a statement.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/growing-antibiotic-crisis-could-turn-bacterial-infections-deadly-experts-warn" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Growing Antibiotic Crisis Could Turn Bacterial Infections Deadly, Experts Warn;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Growing Antibiotic Crisis Could Turn Bacterial Infections Deadly, Experts Warn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In addition, future efforts should focus on raising awareness about &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/infectious-disease" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:fungal disease;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;fungal disease&lt;/a&gt; through developing better surveillance mechanisms, especially in resource-poor countries," they added. "All these developments should help improve the outcomes and prognosis of patients afflicted by opportunistic fungal infections."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Candida auris can survive on skin and hospital surfaces, allowing it to spread easily.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;First identified in 2009 from a patient's ear sample in Japan, C. auris has since spread to dozens of countries, including the U.S., where outbreaks have forced some hospital intensive care units to shut down, according to the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fungus poses the greatest risk to people who are already critically ill, particularly those on ventilators or with weakened immune systems. Once infected, about half of patients may die, according to some estimates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/flu-state-where-seasons-highly-contagious-variant-spreading-most" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Flu By State: Where This Season’s Highly Contagious Variant Is Spreading The Most;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flu By State: Where This Season’s Highly Contagious Variant Is Spreading The Most&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike many other fungi, C. auris can survive on human skin and cling to hospital surfaces and medical equipment, allowing it to spread easily in healthcare settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is resistant to multiple antifungal drugs, and it tends to spread in hospital settings, including on equipment being used on immunocompromised and semi-immunocompromised patients, such as ventilators and catheters," Dr. Marc Siegel, Fox News senior medical analyst and clinical professor of medicine at NYU Langone, &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/dangerous-fungus-spreading-us-hospitals-rapidly-increased" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:previously told Fox News Digital.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;previously told Fox News Digital.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Scientists say the unique cell wall structure of C. auris makes it harder to kill.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is also frequently misdiagnosed, delaying treatment and infection control measures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Sign Up For Our Lifestyle Newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here To Sign Up For Our Lifestyle Newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Unfortunately, symptoms such as fever, chills and aches may be ubiquitous, and it can be mistaken for other infections," Siegel said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In September, he said intense research was ongoing to develop new treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only four major classes of antifungal drugs are currently available, and C. auris has already shown resistance to many of them. While three new antifungal drugs have been approved or are in late-stage trials, researchers warn that drug development has struggled to keep pace with the fungus’s evolution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here For More Lifestyle Stories;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here For More Lifestyle Stories&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the sobering findings, there is still room for cautious optimism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;The fungus can cling to skin and hospital surfaces, aiding its spread.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/medical-research" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:separate research;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;separate research&lt;/a&gt; published in December, scientists at the University of Exeter in England discovered a potential weakness in C. auris while studying the fungus in a living-host model.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team found that, during infection, the fungus activates specific genes to scavenge iron, a nutrient it needs to survive, according to their paper, published in the Nature portfolio journal Communications Biology in December.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS?pid=AppArticleLink&amp;amp;af_dp=foxnewsaf%3A%2F%2F&amp;amp;af_web_dp=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.foxnews.com%2Fapps-products" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Download The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here To Download The Fox News App&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because iron is essential for the pathogen, researchers believe drugs that block this process could eventually stop infections or even allow existing medications to be repurposed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We think our research may have revealed an Achilles’ heel in this lethal pathogen during active infection," Dr. Hugh Gifford, a clinical lecturer at the University of Exeter and co-author of the study, said &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251223043934.htm" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:in a statement.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;in a statement.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;New research is underway to develop better treatments and diagnostics for C. auris.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;As researchers race to better understand the fungus, officials warn that strict infection control, rapid detection and continued investment in new treatments remain critical.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/lifestyle/quizzes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Test Yourself With Our Latest Lifestyle Quiz;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Test Yourself With Our Latest Lifestyle Quiz&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health experts emphasize that C. auris is not a threat to &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:healthy people.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;healthy people.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fox News Digital has reached out to the CDI researchers and additional experts for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fox News Digital's Angelica Stabile contributed reporting.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Original article source:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/deadly-superbug-spreading-across-us-drug-resistance-grows-researchers-warn" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Deadly 'superbug' is spreading across US as drug resistance grows, researchers warn;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Deadly 'superbug' is spreading across US as drug resistance grows, researchers warn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 02:46:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQUWg2QVprclJmU0lGUFdyeEU3em9GREg3M0pZOTZVNXZrNEx6c1AwQjRmU2FCN1Iyc1dsM1E5d1F3QVhmalA3S0N2dUI5NVFacjc5ZWhXX19nVW45TU52SGxjVXkzZHZtOVM3YjRkLVp5c2ZSTU1JX2p1enNQVUJBTA</guid></item><item><title>隐藏的压力信号让老鼠渴望大麻- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/a-hidden-stress-signal-makes-rats-crave-cannabis/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 02:18:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTFBNMzd5MkdJUGRnVVRnanF2ODQ1eXdneUFvSXlId0NXOVV4dlNYTDE0Y2IxQm5mUkl3TldvLUhlYzVFbzFwMDlmM2pKR0dnblhNNkZ2bk9EVWpFZnhpZG1TQlhZMDMwNVA4UWZxano0WFlua2xsTFJyVkVuRmdNWFk</guid></item><item><title>科学家找到帮助大脑从阿尔茨海默氏症中恢复过来的方法- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/scientists-found-a-way-to-help-the-brain-bounce-back-from-alzheimers/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 01:43:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPY0dmejhEcUUxcmFnLXB4a1hoSHZYRFQ1bFI1RmVLcFZIT0dOdzdTY3NGTzV4MnM1S0tYT2otWXF6TkZwTnZoN2Jmd1RsUDlSeHlKb3pZMXBvRlpiVV9vU25tMVlTaG1ueEtvRmg2WWtTWnNwVEhSN0Y4SG90SjVpemZ3LUVCQm4xakMxeThvaWJLU0Y2RWRKOWNB</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法，如果您正在尝试减肥，您不应该服用的4种补充剂- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/supplements-to-avoid-for-weight-loss-11875734</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some supplements for weight loss are unregulated, may be harmful and are not recommended.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do not take green coffee bean extract, Garcinia cambogia, raspberry ketone or caffeine.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work toward an energy deficit for weight loss with a healthy diet and daily exercise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Losing weight is challenging, and many people turn to weight-loss supplements to help achieve their goals. Unfortunately, many supplements marketed for weight loss don’t do what they promise—and may even work against your goals. Not only are supplements expensive, but they are also unregulated, so you don’t always know what you’re getting. The best way to lose weight is to focus on a food-first approach, which means eating plenty of nutrient-dense foods and maintaining a slight &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7922773/best-way-to-lose-weight-and-keep-it-off-according-to-experts/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;calorie deficit&lt;/a&gt; over time. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In this article, we get into some popular weight-loss supplements and why nutrition professionals don't recommend them, plus helpful tips for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7893676/how-to-lose-weight-when-you-dont-know-where-to-start-according-to-a-dietitian/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;healthy, sustainable weight loss&lt;/a&gt;. Knowing what to watch out for can help you make informed choices and prioritize strategies that actually support your health and weight-loss journey.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-green-coffee-bean-extract"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Green Coffee Bean Extract &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’ve searched for supplements aiding weight loss, you’ve likely come across green coffee bean extract. Quite simply, this supplement is derived from the coffee plant’s seeds, which are green before roasting. “[Green coffee bean extract] has chlorogenic acid, a coffee compound that can supposedly decrease fat absorption and speed up metabolism,” says &lt;a href="https://foodsense.net/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Danielle VenHuizen, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;. She adds that these claims are mostly unwarranted. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Only a few human trials have examined the effectiveness of green coffee bean extract on weight loss. These trials had poor study design and showed mixed results.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; While one study found that green coffee extract may help reduce weight and body mass index, there wasn’t a significant effect on body fat percentage, meaning that the mass lost could come from water or muscle.&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Body mass index (BMI) is a flawed measure that’s often used in healthcare to determine a person’s body weight category, and therefore, chronic disease risk. However, it has limitations and does not account for individual factors that influence one’s health status, such as body composition, ethnicity, race, sex and age. This is why it shouldn’t be used as a comprehensive measure of someone’s health and can be a source of body size stigma and bias.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Additionally, in my clinical experience, I have yet to meet a client who has lost weight by using green coffee bean extract,” says VenHuizen. Lastly, there isn’t much information on the safety of green coffee bean extract, so buyers beware. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-garcinia-cambogia"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Garcinia Cambogia &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Garcinia cambogia is a fruit with ​​hydroxycitric acid (HCA), a compound thought to reduce fat production in the body and suppress appetite. “Studies seem to indicate that some of these claims might be true, but unfortunately, the benefits are modest, and the research is conflicting,” says VenHuizen. One study&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;states that there are only a small number of studies on Garcinia cambogia, and the methodology is poor, meaning that these results shouldn’t be trusted.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Even more alarming, “several studies have reported liver issues with long-term use of this supplement,” says VenHuizen.&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This is another pretty convincing reason to avoid adding this supplement to your weight-loss regimen. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-raspberry-ketone"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Raspberry Ketone &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Raspberry ketone is a compound found in the raspberry fruit. Small test-tube and animal studies suggest it may suppress the buildup of fat in the body, but the results are extremely limited. There has only been one human study on the effects of raspberry ketone on weight loss.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The participants took the supplement for eight weeks while also following a calorie-restricted diet. The raspberry ketone supplement was combined with caffeine, bitter orange, ginger, garlic, cayenne, L-theanine, pepper extract, B vitamins and chromium. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The 45 participants who finished the study lost weight, but it’s impossible to know if it was due to the raspberry ketone blend or the calorie deficit. In short, there isn’t enough evidence to support raspberry ketone for weight loss, so save your money. Instead, we recommend snacking on some raspberries, which have &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7835832/health-benefits-of-raspberries/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;several health benefits&lt;/a&gt;, including filling fiber and inflammation-fighting anthocyanins.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-caffeine"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Caffeine &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The most recognizable supplement on this list, caffeine is a compound that stimulates the nervous system. It’s naturally present in tea, coffee and chocolate, as well as in herbal supplements like guarana. Caffeine increases thermogenesis, the body’s natural production of heat. During this process, the body burns extra calories. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Research suggests caffeine can help with weight loss, but a large dose is necessary to create a response. One study concluded that more than 3 milligrams of caffeine per kilogram of body weight is necessary to stimulate the breakdown of fat.&lt;span data-cite="5" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; For a 150-pound person, that’s 200 mg of caffeine, or two cups of coffee. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It is recommended to cap caffeine consumption 400 mg daily for safety, but everyone has a different tolerance level.&lt;span data-cite="6" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8009784/how-much-caffeine-is-too-much/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;People sensitive to caffeine may experience symptoms&lt;/a&gt; like nervousness, jitters, heart racing and headaches, among others. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Although caffeine may increase fat loss, it’s not the best way to lose weight, especially because supplements with caffeine may contain more than that, plus other stimulants. That said, caffeine from natural sources like coffee is the safest way to consume caffeine. So, feel free to include a cup of coffee or tea in your day for an energy boost, but don’t expect it to affect your weight too much. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-tips-for-healthy-weight-loss"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Tips for Healthy Weight Loss  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Although they may not be quick or flashy, the most effective tools for losing weight are good old-fashioned healthy eating and exercise. VenHuizen recommends increasing &lt;a class="pseudoStyle" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8068570/best-high-fiber-fruits-for-weight-loss-according-to-gastroenterologist/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;fiber-rich fruits&lt;/a&gt; and vegetables and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/the-best-healthy-fats-for-weight-loss-8417296" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;healthy fats&lt;/a&gt; in the diet. “These foods naturally increase satiety and provide anti-inflammatory benefits that may aid in weight loss,” says VenHuizen. “And unlike supplements, studies on fruit and vegetable intake show that these foods improve weight-loss efforts,” she adds. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In addition, “Trying to stay moderately active throughout the day, especially for people who work sedentary desk jobs, can help with weight loss,” says &lt;a href="https://dietitianmadeleine.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Madeleine Putzi, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;. She recommends getting up and walking around once per hour to increase your total amount of steps for the day, which is an easy and non-taxing way to increase your daily calorie burn. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Putzi also suggests investing in a standing desk and/or a walking pad if possible. “If you walk for 10 minutes at 3 miles per hour, you will hit around 1,000 steps. Do that every hour, and that's an easy 8,000 steps by the end of your workday,” says Putzi.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Weight-loss supplements are usually not worth the expensive price tag. If a supplement promises to “magically burn fat or flatten your belly,” chances are it’s not the miracle that’s promised on the bottle. A food and exercise approach to weight loss is the most effective way to reach your weight-loss goals in a sustainable way.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE5UYUFDSkt3TURINDE5TUJxQUVfa004TEx1d096RDJBQ044amNvZXF0Ymk4d0hlazlicXk4aE5YYkdZbTdSU2FKQ0JEUEtUVjk5VDVsbnVkd0cxc1FrU0tYNnBkcnBISVYyd2FPZG93WHZkcjlHWWVTN2hpTzk</guid></item><item><title>最常见的糖尿病治疗方法之一可能是使疾病恶化，研究警告-SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/one-of-the-most-common-diabetes-treatments-may-be-making-the-disease-worse-study-warns/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 01:08:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxNc2lZQ1EzNEhZZkctZmc4Z2NZX20xWEhYcE9JNjEzcXhmaXNYTkc4Zk9nY0ZoRUJYMUNfdkxUUmFpeXl6QmlSRGYyTmhUdnVlS1JiN1ZIcFFaWFRqQ1ZlcEJhWW9ULTlrOEt0RElTX0p5TzcxaklqZnI4bVNONXc0SWJPSW83Q0NHMmRzNXRKSEZKazFSb1JsZlJ1ZlJmS1RJUklrY1VWUk9SZHZvZnZjX05n</guid></item><item><title>研究人员在将父亲和孩子之间新出现的健康问题联系起来后做出了令人不安的发现： “计划生孩子的男性应该考虑……” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/researchers-troubling-discovery-linking-emerging-231500710.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Microplastics are an emerging environmental and health risk increasingly linked to adverse outcomes in wildlife and people alike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A study pending publication in the &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/jes/advance-article/doi/10.1210/jendso/bvaf214/8383852" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Journal of the Endocrine Society;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Journal of the Endocrine Society&lt;/a&gt; recently found evidence that their impact might be passed down to future generations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Microplastics (MPs) are small plastic particles emerging as significant environmental pollutants,  and humans are ubiquitously exposed to microplastics," its abstract began.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As the researchers noted, exposure to microplastics has been linked to chronic health conditions, and previous research identified microplastic particles in human reproductive tissue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the abstract, the authors explained that parents' exposure to environmental contaminants has been shown to "increase the risk of cardiometabolic disease" in their children, but parental exposure to microplastics as a distinct pollutant had "not been studied."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Researchers exposed male mice to microplastics to assess whether &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/how-good-is-your-cardiometabolic-health-and-what-is-that-anyway-202208182803" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:cardiometabolic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;cardiometabolic&lt;/a&gt; diseases — such as Type 2 diabetes, insulin resistance, and obesity — would occur more frequently in their offspring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Using a novel sequencing method, the authors were surprised to find that female offspring of male mice exposed to microplastics exhibited "exacerbated insulin resistance" compared with their male counterparts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ultimately, they concluded that "parental microplastic exposure may have intergenerational adverse impact on offspring metabolic health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why is this study concerning?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As the authors emphasized, microplastics truly are everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Plastic can take centuries to break down, and each year, more of it is manufactured, increasing our exposure to these dangerous plastic particles. Microplastics have been found not just in water, soil, and air, but also in Earth's least-traversed places.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Researchers have identified microplastics in human reproductive tissues, but they've also been found throughout the human body, including our brain tissue, organs, and blood. Due to their pervasiveness, microplastics are impossible to avoid entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Studies linking microplastics to adverse outcomes are worryingly numerous, with new findings emerging routinely, indicating an ever-escalating environmental and health crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Research tends to focus on direct, immediate effects, but this study highlighted the potential for microplastics to harm future generations without direct exposure. Lead author Changcheng Zhou explained why that was particularly worrisome, according to the University of California, Riverside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"These findings from a mouse study likely have implications for humans. Men planning to have children should consider reducing their exposure to harmful substances like microplastics to protect both their health and that of their future children," Zhou &lt;a href="https://news.ucr.edu/articles/2025/12/23/fathers-microplastic-exposure-tied-their-childrens-metabolic-problems" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:advised;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;advised&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's being done about microplastics?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Although microplastics are environmentally pervasive, that doesn't mean there aren't ways to minimize direct exposure, as Zhou recommended prospective parents do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.ucr.edu/articles/2025/12/23/fathers-microplastic-exposure-tied-their-childrens-metabolic-problems" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Using less plastic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Using less plastic&lt;/a&gt; and replacing your most-used plastic items with &lt;a href="http://guide.thecooldown.com/actions/choose-plastic-free-options-for-everyday-products" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:plastic-free alternatives;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;plastic-free alternatives&lt;/a&gt; can significantly reduce your exposure to microplastics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Get TCD's &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/newsletter/?utm_source=rec5IK1GWc7WrmVhU" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletters;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletters&lt;/a&gt; for easy tips to save more, waste less, and make smarter choices — and earn up to $5,000 toward clean upgrades in TCD's exclusive &lt;a href="https://links.thecooldown.com/rewards-club" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Rewards Club;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Rewards Club&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxNVFdyd3h5OVpFNVRvaE1LdG9aR2s2cHJmNWw0c3l6ZWV0Uk5mQS1OdUdnWVJLWWpvbTJjY3lJdTVOMElSSEc4TEtCTElxckFFN1N6dkpqTmlueFFTUTQ3bjVaMmRlR1pSd2F3T0RVTHBGV0xaY0p0S3JrSVg3RWRZYUsyRjBoaExoOE8taENIYkZtOWpNNUgyUVJZLWlQS2dB</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现人体组织中隐藏的纤维网络- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/scientists-uncover-hidden-fiber-networks-inside-human-tissues/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 21:51:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxNUld2VUFkcjY4OUJYdmlMRUg5V2FNOG5zRHdHWVpFN3loX21NeTd0TTRpU1JWV1JDYXY5Nkw1Ty1mTXR1MkhNcWJtMmpDNEpQM05CZjVlbTZNbTNTbnhsc2ZtV3NXSktWWmRpSGhYZ1pWX2tUOUdhb2tJNjhLblE0QVhsdThlZ1J5cjdKYnMtSGY</guid></item><item><title>黑金：调节血糖和血压的富含维生素的水果- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/black-gold-vitamin-packed-fruit-aronia-regulates-blood-sugar-pressure/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Berries from the genus &lt;em&gt;Aronia&lt;/em&gt;, often called black chokeberry, are native to North America and have gained attention for their high content of polyphenolic compounds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These natural chemicals have been associated with benefits that go beyond ordinary nutrition, such as antioxidant effects that may help calm the body’s inflammatory processes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People have started asking about aronia’s place in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/meal-timing-has-a-major-influence-on-our-health/"&gt;everyday meals&lt;/a&gt;, hoping to see if a simple fruit could support healthy lifestyles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists recently examined whether aronia juice might protect against diet-induced challenges linked to the gut microbiome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This project was led by &lt;a href="https://www.montana.edu/news/22109/stephanie-wilson-one-of-first-three-students-to-complete-montana-state-s-individual-interdisciplinary-ph-d-program"&gt;Dr. Stephanie M. G. Wilson&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href="https://www.montana.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Montana State University&lt;/a&gt;. Research in this area has looked at how bacteria in the digestive system respond when aronia berries are introduced, particularly in situations where unhealthy eating patterns could raise inflammation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early investigations point to intriguing changes in microbes, and hinting that this berry might shift certain bacterial communities and reduce the strain triggered by high-fat diets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-science-behind-aronia-berries"&gt;Science behind aronia berries&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team used a mouse model with transplanted human gut microbiomes that came from donors with different inflammation levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Aronia supplementation provided robust protection,” noted Dr. Wilson when reviewing the results at the end of the study. Scientists saw increases in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/gut-bacteria-have-very-clever-ways-of-supporting-human-health/"&gt;Eggerthellaceae&lt;/a&gt;, a family of bacteria that can process polyphenols. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some data also linked &lt;a href="https://extension.umn.edu/trees-and-shrubs/black-chokeberry" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;black chokeberry&lt;/a&gt; intake with changes in metabolites related to improved gut barriers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These shifts suggest that eating or drinking aronia-based products might assist in keeping the digestive system more balanced during periods of dietary stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-personalizing-nutrition"&gt;Personalizing nutrition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inflammation can arise when people eat high-fat or sugary foods for long stretches. Researchers point out that a person’s unique microbiome might determine how well they adapt to certain dietary habits. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aronia’s &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/1420-3049/27/22/7823"&gt;benefits&lt;/a&gt; may vary from one person to another, depending on individual gut ecology and background health status. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those who carry a set of gut bacteria already geared toward lower inflammation, the advantages from adding aronia might be more visible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This concept underscores how science is moving toward personalized nutrition, where different bodies respond to the same foods in slightly different ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-aronia-berries-help"&gt;How aronia berries help&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other published works indicate that aronia is not just a source of antioxidants; it may also be linked with healthier glucose levels and heart function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The presence of anthocyanins and other phenolic substances could explain how this fruit influences complex pathways connected to metabolism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Traditional uses of aronia include juices, jams, and powders, but emerging science is urging a closer look at its larger dietary potential. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While some folks already consume aronia to freshen up their breakfast or snack routines, others remain unaware of its possible contributions to gut stability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-unraveling-unexpected-twists"&gt;Unraveling unexpected twists&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some findings highlight the importance of gut diversity when it comes to inflammation. Researchers observed that mice with microbiomes from donors who had lower inflammation were more resilient during the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/high-fat-diets-cause-high-anxiety-through-changes-in-gut-bacteria/"&gt;high-fat diet&lt;/a&gt; challenge. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aronia seemed to shield this group even further. This suggests that, while aronia might help most individuals, those who have specific microbial imbalances might notice the biggest improvements. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On a broader level, it points to how small dietary changes, like adding a berry drink, can create ripple effects that protect overall wellness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-applications-on-the-horizon"&gt;Applications on the horizon&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aronia’s tart flavor might not suit everyone right away. In grocery stores, it often appears in juice blends, concentrates, or dried forms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because it’s easy to mix with other fruits, people can add it to smoothies or desserts without changing their routines too drastically. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research continues to evaluate how much aronia consumption is ideal for humans, since the dose can vary widely. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some clinical trials, individuals experienced potential &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/tackling-fat-with-food-tropical-plant-in-china-has-anti-obesity-properties/"&gt;anti-obesity benefits&lt;/a&gt;, in addition to improvements in the body’s natural defenses. These early observations pave the way for deeper investigations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aronia may carry special ingredients that bolster the gut’s ability to cope with stress, especially during nutritional challenges. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investigators are looking to see if these insights might lead to new strategies for lowering inflammation in the long term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This berry isn’t a magic bullet, and results will differ from person to person. Its potential, though, goes beyond just delivering antioxidants: it may connect with gut microbes in ways that support healthy balance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fresh interest in aronia keeps growing, and the findings so far hint at a fruitful path for future study.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/nutrition/articles/10.3389/fnut.2023.1244692" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Frontiers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 21:36:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxPclV4SkduQ0N6X0hYRXlOaHJ2VHRVMnFEYlBMbDFtRDJWaU9uY0wzeTFPZ1doWURndVlXTVJ2YXZtc09yVDJlWjhGVHJiTndlVkpnWWdya0RUdGtpbVZlZDcyTlhJbnZfeERXUEdOOW5RZElTREFuTkRpZHFCTkdvbGJFZWVPMjdmRTdjdzBsQXFjeXZPVFhPYWxmQURodw</guid></item><item><title>在留下遗产的过程中，科罗拉多斯普林斯强大的夫妇聊天前列腺癌-科罗拉多斯普林斯公报</title><link>https://gazette.com/2026/01/03/in-leaving-a-legacy-colorado-springs-powerhouse-couple-chat-up-prostate-cancer/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="post-content-container" class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow"&gt;
                                                                                        
&lt;p&gt;“Cool hair.”  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Everywhere Leo and Brandy Nunes go, they hear such a comment.  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Leo’s response to the interest and curiosity from the couple’s bright blue locks is usually, “Thanks. It’s for prostate cancer.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;People will then often ask who has prostate cancer that they know. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;When Leo responds, “I do,” many are surprised, he says. “They think it’s a grandpa disease.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But that’s mistake No. 1, the Nuneses tell anyone who’ll listen. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Since Leo was diagnosed three years ago while in his 40s, the couple have been clanging a loud warning bell about the deadly but somewhat hush-hush disease that can appear in younger men as well as aging seniors. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And they’ve succeeded in getting people to pay attention and support the cause.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“People wonder who are the weird guys with the blue hair,” Leo says. “But it works.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The married couple, who have been together for 25 years, initially dyed their hair blue after Leo’s diagnosis in 2022, to mark September’s national recognition as Prostate Cancer Awareness Month. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;They’ve been blue-headed ever since because they discovered their look — which for Leo also includes blue clothing, socks, shoes and accessories — is a great conversation-starter.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Leo and Brandy recently had a lengthy talk with a TSA agent at the airport, who has had several men in his family affected by prostate cancer. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And a recent trip to Costco yielded an exchange with someone at the store whose dad had prostate cancer. They’re not shy about telling people who are at risk how to get tested, what direct support is available and anything else.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I thought if I were to have a chance of making an impact, I could go blue and be public about prostate cancer, or I could be private about it and not make a difference,” Leo says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Despite the numbers — a man is diagnosed with prostate cancer every two minutes and a man dies from it every 15 minutes in the U.S. — and that it’s the second most diagnosed cancer in men next to skin cancer and the second leading cancer death in men — prostate cancer is just not openly discussed or supported in the same way that breast cancer is, Leo and Brandy point out.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“People don’t like talking about stuff below the waist,” Leo says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Which is unfortunate, the Nuneses say, because the survival rate is high — 99% — if it’s detected early and hasn’t spread. The odds decrease from there. The five-year survival rate for the stage that former President Joe Biden has is 38%, for example.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“This needs to be something that’s constantly in front of people,” Leo says. “For me, prostate cancer awareness is every day.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Medically, improvements in detection and treatment have made this type of cancer more palatable and less scary, Leo attests. For example, presence can be detected through a blood test rather than the old rectal exam that’s often the butt of a joke.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And the condition does not necessarily mean the prostate must be removed, which can affect sexual performance and lead to incontinence. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In May, Leo had his third treatment of laser ablation with real-time imaging that targets cancer-ridden cells and leaves healthy cells alone.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The downtime is minimal and has resulted in optimistic outcomes, Leo says. Surgery is still in the cards for some cases, he says, but it’s not automatic.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This year, the Nuneses secured proclamations for September to be recognized by local and state elected officials for prostate cancer awareness.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;They’ve also advocated in Washington, D.C., for more funding for free testing for low-income men and more programs for all.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Prostate cancer should not be anything there’s stigma around or barriers,” Leo says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The powerhouse health insurance brokers who own Nunes Partners are still riding the high of hosting a wildly successful No Cancer November Casino Night fundraiser held at COS City Hub event center to support cancer research, treatment and support.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Leo and Brandy set a goal of raising $20,000 this year, but pulled in $28,000 from 135 attendees and 19 business sponsors. That’s more than double from last year’s gala, which raised $10,000.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Two charities split the proceeds: the local Sue’s Gift that assists women diagnosed with gynecological cancers, and the national ZERO Prostate Cancer, which has online support groups and other help for men navigating the illness.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There’s no local organization that focuses on prostate cancer, so the Nuneses have decided it’s their philanthropic fate to build momentum for the cause.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;They’ve started the Nunes Foundation with prostate cancer as the first of three pillars of health and human welfare, along with the environment and animals.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Over the past three years, they’ve raised more than $45,000 for cancer-busting organizations that provide early detection programs, financial assistance and critical resources for patients.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“We don’t have kids; we tried to have a family, but it just didn’t work out,” Brandy says. “This is the legacy we’re going to leave.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Cancer makes you go crazy a little bit,” says Leo, who has taken on a do-or-die attitude and lately has done several “crazy things” beyond dying his hair.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Admittedly non-athletic and definitely not a runner, Leo completed a half-marathon with little preparation but sheer determination to see how far he could push his body.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;He’s since participated in other physical challenges to raise more money for ZERO Prostate Cancer, including running the Manitou Springs Incline for 30 consecutive days, which garnered $15,000 in donations. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;He also climbed Mount Kilimanjaro with a group of 17 hikers from ZERO Prostate Cancer. His effort added nearly $9,000 in contributions, and he was the only prostate cancer survivor from Colorado to complete the ascent. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Another high-altitude climb is in sight for June in the Andes mountains, and 2027 looks like it’ll be Mount Everest.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It’s nuts,” Brandy says, with a smile. She doesn’t accompany Leo on his quests to conquer mountains but does her best to stand by her man in his newfound passion.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“He’s like in this mindset that he’s going to do something, and he does,” Brandy says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I feel like if I can do extreme challenges, I can take out cancer,” Leo says. “It gives you the strength to know there’s a lot of harder things than pushing through disease.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Perhaps somewhat strangely, but also with total clarity, cancer has opened doors the couple never imagined.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“People feel there’s nothing to live for and there’s no hope if you have cancer,” Brandy said. “For us, it’s been the thing that lights the fuel in the fire and sparks change.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;They think it’s better than living in silence.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                            
    &lt;span class="article-social-share-icons"&gt;
        &lt;a class="article-social-share-icon" href="https://www.facebook.com/sharer/sharer.php?u=https://gazette.com/2026/01/03/in-leaving-a-legacy-colorado-springs-powerhouse-couple-chat-up-prostate-cancer/" title="Share on Facebook"&gt;
            &lt;span class="dashicons dashicons-facebook-alt"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;

        &lt;a class="article-social-share-icon" href="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?url=https://gazette.com/2026/01/03/in-leaving-a-legacy-colorado-springs-powerhouse-couple-chat-up-prostate-cancer/&amp;amp;text=In+leaving+a+legacy%2C+Colorado+Springs+powerhouse+couple+chat+up+prostate+cancer" title="Share on Twitter"&gt;
            &lt;span&gt;
                
            &lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;

        &lt;a class="article-social-share-icon" href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#e4db9791868e818790d9a78c81878fc1d6d48b9190c1d6d4908c8d97c1d6d48596908d878881c2868b809dd98c90909497decbcb83859e81909081ca878b89cbd6d4d6d2cbd4d5cbd4d7cb8d8ac9888185928d8a83c985c988818385879dc9878b888b9685808bc99794968d8a8397c9948b9381968c8b919781c9878b91948881c9878c8590c99194c994968b9790859081c987858a878196cb" title="Share via Email"&gt;
            &lt;span class="dashicons dashicons-email"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;

        &lt;a class="article-social-share-icon" href="" title="Print Page"&gt;
            &lt;span class="dashicons dashicons-printer"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;
        
        &lt;a class="article-social-share-icon" href="#" title="Copy Link"&gt;
            &lt;span class="dashicons dashicons-admin-page"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;
    
    &lt;/span&gt;

            
                                        &lt;/div&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Colorado Springs Gazette</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 21:33:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxQUFEwenNwTzkzVGNBQmlxMVRaelVyWHlvZzlINGFKUWtYckNwci1IOWw1WFZnT1B1NVV2SjJzVjhpMXBFRzNkMkNxeWRNdjZreG4zU1NNNDdLSWtHd3oxT2o3WjNkZ0xLUXk3eFFsaFFNNnRuU1V1UlFHd0J4M1VlQjl5aENrN2dNdWdkYnB3YjYwWm1uUDZtOUJycVFFTFVhMElwajFULWJSWXA2RWZB</guid></item><item><title>这种季节性35卡路里水果可以提高你的免疫力，改善你的皮肤—并帮助你的大脑健康-纽约邮报</title><link>https://nypost.com/2026/01/03/health/this-35-calorie-fruit-can-boost-your-immunity-skin-and-brain-health/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom"&gt;
							


&lt;p&gt;Want to stay healthy this cold and flu season — and look good doing it?&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There’s a budget-friendly fruit in season right now that’s bursting with nutrients, low in calories and might just be the secret weapon your immune system and skin need this winter.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;An added bonus: Your brain will also get a boost. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;By providing antioxidants and vitamin C, these fruits can brighten skin tone, improve texture and reduce wrinkles.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Rido – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Clementines, better known by their brand names Cuties or Halos, are like the smaller, sweeter cousins of the orange. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="connatix-outstream-video"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These tiny citrus fruits are easy to peel, usually seedless and hit peak season from October through January.  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But don’t let their small size fool you: &lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/168195/nutrients" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;One clementine&lt;/a&gt; clocks in at just 35 calories but delivers 36.1 mg of vitamin C — nearly 40% of what you need daily for optimal health. &lt;/p&gt;


	



&lt;p&gt;Vitamin C is essential nutrient, meaning your body can’t make it on its own so you need to get it from your diet. It’s a powerhouse for your immune system, helping to destroy infectious microbes while keeping your tissues safe from damage. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/23440782/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Research shows&lt;/a&gt; that getting enough vitamin C on a regular basis can help reduce the severity and duration of cold and flu symptoms. However, there is little evidence that popping vitamin C once you are already sick will speed recovery, so consistency matters when it comes to eating clementines.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;In the US, most clementines are grown in California and Florida.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Markus Mainka – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The perks don’t stop at immunity. Vitamin C is also crucial for &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/12/05/health/boost-collagen-in-your-skin-with-this-small-fruit-twice-a-day/"&gt;collagen&lt;/a&gt;, the protein that keeps your skin firm, plump and smooth. &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Maintaining adequate collagen levels can reduce fine lines, prevent sagging and even speed up wound healing. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Clementines are also packed with other antioxidants, like flavonoids, which can fight inflammation, calm redness and soothe skin conditions like acne or rosacea.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And with their high water content, these juicy snacks can help the skin stay hydrated, preventing dryness and flakiness.   &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But the goodness doesn’t end there. Clementines contain folate and thiamine, two B vitamins that are crucial for your body, supporting everything from cell development to a healthy metabolism.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And while a single clementine only has about 1 gram of fiber, snacking on a few throughout the day is an easy way to &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/05/30/health/what-is-fibermaxxing-dietitian-warns-about-viral-trend/"&gt;boost your intake&lt;/a&gt;, supporting digestion, gut health and weight management. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Like other citrus fruits, clementines are brain-friendly, too.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Clementines are nutrient-dense, helping promote brain function and healthy aging.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;WavebreakMediaMicro – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;They contain bioactive compounds such as polyphenols, which have anti-inflammatory and antioxidative properties that help protect the brain from damage.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Studies on animals have shown that supplementing the diet with citruis fruits improves deficits in learning and memory, particularly spacial memory, which helps us remember where we’ve put things and recognition memory, which is vital for facial and name recall,” Dr. David Vauzour, a senior research fellow at Norwich Medical School, &lt;a href="https://www.foodnavigator.com/Article/2021/03/03/The-role-of-citrus-in-brain-health-Citrus-bioactive-compounds-improve-general-cognition/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;told FoodNavigator&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Clementines are also a rich source of hesperidin, a bioflavonoid with antioxidant properties that may help reduce inflammation, improve blood flow in the brain and support overall brain cell health. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40694049/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Research suggests&lt;/a&gt; that getting hesperidin in your diet can help improve cognitive functions such as attention, learning and memory, as well as psychomotor skills like movement and coordination. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In fact, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40694049/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;studies show&lt;/a&gt; that eating citrus fruits like clementines daily could cut the risk of developing dementia in older adults by nearly 15%.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;They might even help your mood. Last year, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/03/09/health/eating-this-fruit-daily-can-lower-depression-risk-by-20-study/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;scientists found&lt;/a&gt; that people who ate a daily serving of citrus had about a 20% lower risk of being diagnosed with depression. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The effect seems to be specific to citrus,” Raaj Mehta, the lead study author, told &lt;a href="https://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2025/02/eating-citrus-may-lower-depression-risk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;The Harvard Gazette&lt;/a&gt;. “When we look at people’s total fruit or vegetable consumption, or at other individual fruits such as apples or bananas, we don’t see any relationship between intake and risk of depression.”&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;But before you grab a bag and start peeling, there’s something to keep in mind about clementines. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Some research has shown that clementines contain furanocoumarins, a compound also &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3589309/"&gt;found in grapefruit&lt;/a&gt; that can interfere with certain medications, including &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/27890698/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;cholesterol-lowering statins&lt;/a&gt;, and potentially cause complications.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To be safe, experts recommend checking with your doctor or pharmacist about possible drug interactions before adding large amounts of citrus fruit to your daily diet.&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;

												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOMzA3Z1pZYThFM1pPYUdhZjJQVEQ3dnRScHdHVENQRmZqZWtXR0pOeUxHaVRfYndUMUhydTdlZmc1OFBnbW8yQjVQUDJkVzRQSkFBZmlZVklpUjRNMFQtT0Vud2lGMVZ1WDJSTGhzZl9uNTdTYnlYUi1wZXVtODhiMnpEN3ZVZkF6TmhtbTV5d2paMjB0Z0ltdnFMM3lITkFVTmY5dEVnMEk</guid></item><item><title>我无法停止的高纤维、高蛋白晚餐- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/my-favorite-high-fiber-dinner-11875632</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Roasted Potato Tzatziki Bowls deliver comfort and flavor while packing 10g of fiber per serving.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Plant-based yet protein-rich, each bowl offers 17g of protein thanks to chickpeas and Greek-style yogurt.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Easy and satisfying, this 45-minute meal proves high-fiber dinners can be cozy and delicious.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When you hear “high-fiber meal,” chances are you’re thinking about salads, hearty soups or even bean skillets. These are great and all, but what if I told you that my favorite high-fiber diner is none of these things, and it doesn’t skimp on comfort?
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Meet the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/roasted-potato-tzatziki-bowls-11686979" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Roasted Potato Tzatziki Bowls&lt;/a&gt; that I swear by. Although they star roasted potatoes, the fresh and vibrant in this dish really shine any time of year. Besides the delicious mix of tangy and herby flavors, there’s so many things that I love about this dinner. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It’s hard to pick a place to start, but let’s talk about its surprising nutrition content. Thanks to the chickpeas, cucumbers, tomatoes and onions, these bowls are loaded with fiber, packing 10 grams per serving, which is 40% of the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-it-looks-like-to-eat-enough-fiber-11798470" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;recommended daily value for women&lt;/a&gt;. I’m acutely aware that most Americans &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/small-changes-that-helped-me-eat-more-fiber-11775341" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;do not get enough fiber&lt;/a&gt; in their eating pattern, so I’m always looking for ways to include the satisfying essential nutrient in my meal, as consuming more fiber can help reduce &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/287742/10-amazing-health-benefits-of-eating-more-fiber/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;the risk of type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; (which runs in my family).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Not only are they fibrous, but these bowls are also protein-rich, even while being a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/plant-based-protein-benefits-11712145" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;plant-based&lt;/a&gt; meal. Combining chickpeas and homemade tzatziki made with strained (Greek-style) yogurt, each bowl serves 17 grams of protein per serving. I love incorporating more plant-based proteins into my meals, and I usually always have a can of chickpeas in my pantry or a tub of yogurt in my refrigerator, making shopping for this dinner that much easier.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;
Speaking of easy, this recipe notes that it takes a total of 45 minutes to make, but the busy work is mostly just chopping veggies and mixing up the tzatziki. Once you have everything prepared, it’s easy: the base of the bowl is the tzatziki, then top with your chickpeas and veggies, add your roasted potatoes and drizzle the whole thing with some really good olive oil. Personally, I’ve been loving &lt;a href="https://canaanpalestine.com/products/rumi-olive-oil" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Canaan Palestine’s Rumi Olive Oil&lt;/a&gt; lately for its bold flavor, and it’s amazingly all-purpose, so I can use it for the potatoes as well as for the finish.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If I haven’t convinced you yet to make these tzatziki bowls, I don’t know what will. In fact, I just convinced myself to make them for dinner tonight. And I may even pair it with leftover Christmas cookies and New Year’s wine… it’s called balance!&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE81SVRFaDFQWWxrZDJMRkMxMjFzWTdTckF5QW0wZ3NQUzRhdXNrSFA2Y1BTZFVNZldnOWNad3haV0s5UExRVmltb2F6YnNnVkNNX2Vab1Foa3Zkb2tsclpWSzRRVURMaFpzYVVFUDhZTnBqVkE</guid></item><item><title>我以为我的宝宝只是得了流感。然后医生做出了可怕的发现-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15420457/ohio-toddler-liver-cancer-lifesaving-donation-warning-signs.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As the youngest of four, Crew Dearth knows how to keep up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The toddler from &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/ohio/index.html" id="mol-aee46600-e5c4-11f0-9b8d-bb554bac5122" class=""&gt;Ohio&lt;/a&gt; 'loves being a little brother' and is an expert in greeting his siblings at the bus stop and getting into absolutely everything at home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But in February, when he was just 11 months old, Crew slowed down after testing positive for influenza A, the most common form of the &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/flu/index.html" id="mol-aee02040-e5c4-11f0-9b8d-bb554bac5122"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The flu can be devastating for young children who have yet to build up their immune system. But after a couple of weeks, Crew's mother, Nicole Dearth, was shocked he hadn't yet bounced back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Something just seemed off,' Dearth told the Daily Mail. 'He was restless. He was cranky, and he is not a cranky baby - and he's not restless. It was just weird.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors at first suspected the infant had an ear infection and put him on antibiotics, but he still failed to improve. Several days later, Dearth noticed Crew's stomach seemed distended and swollen. 'I just knew it wasn't right,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Physicians at Cleveland Clinic immediately ordered an ultrasound and blood work, which revealed several masses practically swallowing Crew's liver and 'dangerously low' sodium levels, leaving him at risk of seizures, a coma and brain damage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;On March 17, Crew was diagnosed with stage four hepatoblastoma, a rare &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15103925/liver-cancer-fruit-guava-delaware.html"&gt;form of liver cancer&lt;/a&gt; that strikes just one in every one million children between the ages of one and three in the US. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Crew Dearth, pictured above, was just under one year old when he was diagnosed with stage four hepatoblastoma in March 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The disease grows slowly, with symptoms such as abdominal pain, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="/news/weight_loss/index.html" id="mol-851cc350-e504-11f0-bd3b-2b5f4405ab2d"&gt;weight loss&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and yellow skin or eyes not appearing until the cancer has spread, much like in Crew's case. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;'We knew something was wrong, but I wasn't expecting to hear cancer,' Dearth told the Daily Mail. 'I was stunned, shocked, like I couldn't believe it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;'He was fine. He was eating fine, playing fine, acting fine. Everything was fine until influenza hit, and that's when everything went downhill.' &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's unclear what causes hepatoblastoma, but low birth weight or preterm birth have been shown to raise the risk because the liver may not be fully developed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The disease, however, carries a good prognosis with an average five-year survival rate of 80 percent, though the rate can dwindle to 20 percent if the cancer spreads beyond the liver. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors immediately started Crew on chemotherapy but quickly realized a liver transplant would best help him avoid intense side effects like vomiting and dehydration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Crew, pictured above in the hospital, immediately underwent aggressive chemotherapy, but doctors quickly realized he would need a liver transplant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Several friends and family members were tested to be Crew's liver donor. His aunt, Taylor Dearth, ended up being a match. Crew is pictured in the hospital&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At just one year old, Crew became one of the 9,000 Americans awaiting a liver transplant, which makes it the most&lt;span&gt; sought after organ behind kidneys. Roughly five to 10 percent of these patients are children. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While most organs come from deceased donors, more and more patients with liver disease are seeking live donors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Living donors provide up to 70 percent of their liver to a recipient. Unlike other transplanted organs, the liver regenerates. In fact, it only takes about three months for both the donor and recipient livers to regrow to their full size and capacity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Living donors need to be the same blood type as the recipient, or they can be the universal donor blood type O negative. Donors also need to be free of any form of liver disease, be under 50 years old and have a relatively healthy lifestyle. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors tested 15 family members and friends of the Dearth family, and the first match they found was Crew's aunt, Taylor Dearth, a dietitian and mother of three daughters also living in Ohio. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I was the very first person the nurse called,' Taylor told the Daily Mail. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Taylor Dearth, Crew's aunt, is pictured above helping Crew ring the Bravery Bell at Cleveland Clinic, a sign that he had finished cancer treatment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Crew, pictured above with his family, now has no evidence of disease, but he will be closely followed for several years to make sure the cancer does not return&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Once she found out she was a match, she immediately stopped drinking alcohol and bolstered her already healthy diet with additional nutrients like antioxidants and B vitamins to keep her liver in prime shape. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dearth told the Daily Mail she was surprised when Cleveland Clinic told her Taylor was being evaluated as a potential donor and was 'super overwhelmed at first.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It's a big surgery for [Taylor], and she has three small kids,' Dearth said. 'I was like, "You're going to put your life at risk to save ours?" It's the most selfless thing that anyone could ever do for somebody.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I just felt so overwhelmed and just felt grateful for her, and I felt blessed that she wanted to do this for [Crew].'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Though liver donors can give 70 percent, young children like Crew can only receive about 15 to 20 percent due to their small size. Taylor's operation took about six hours, while Crew's took 15. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Taylor was able to give Crew (pictured above) about 20 percent of her liver, which regenerates in both the donor and recipient within about six months&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Crew is pictured above with his mother, Nicole Dearth, who said the family is looking forward to 'moving on' from cancer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Crew was in the hospital for 12 days, and Taylor stayed for about a week. After around three weeks, pain from the operation dissipated for Taylor and she was able to return to her regular activities. She will be evaluated for complications over the next two years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It's mind-blowing what living transplants can do,' Taylor said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Crew started chemotherapy again three weeks after the surgery to make sure the cancer was eliminated. His last round of chemotherapy was in September. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The toddler's latest scans show no evidence of disease, but hepatoblastoma still has a 20 percent chance of returning, even after a liver transplant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Crew now has weekly blood tests to check his liver enzymes and he is on medication to prevent his immune system from rejecting the transplanted liver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But four months after completing chemotherapy, Crew is 'thriving,' Taylor said. 'It's just amazing,' she added. 'You would not even know that he went through all of that. He's just so happy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;'It's so fulfilling to think that I had a healthy liver and that I could save Crew's life,' Taylor told the Daily Mail. Crew, now almost two years old, is pictured above&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It's so fulfilling to think that I had a healthy liver and that I could save Crew's life. I've always liked to help others, and I've always wanted to make a big impact on someone's life, and for it to be my nephew just makes it so much more meaningful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I had a chance to take his pain away and help in a way that I never imagined I would be able to help him.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Crew will be immunocompromised for the rest of his life due to the transplant, which makes him more likely to get sick. Even a common cold or the flu could land him in the hospital.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He also will not be able to go to daycare due to the risks of getting sick and will have to avoid contact sports when he gets older, as they may injure the liver. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Still, the family is looking forward to celebrating Crew's second birthday in March.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We're looking forward to moving on from this disease, just doing the normal things,' Dearth told the Daily Mail. 'I'm so ready to live as normal as we possibly can.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:01:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxNUGFDMVROTXZyR3VyVGZ6eFVLWVg0X3puS25WVnJKc1JEclJHNDR0ZlowVWMzV3NnTnNRd2Jianc0QlVsY0g0RDFpaFY4R01VQXFHTlpMWlFuN1BMQTRnM3FzelJpbG9RVi1IblI1SmtIaHp6aFkteVlSbjVtdlVlc1JiMThVTnBXc0h6WTlkeE4taFV6QkxFLXQtNWN3OGQwY2VLZkVwckZJaWN5ajhxYkx6c01pNFE</guid></item><item><title>我38岁了，比以往任何时候都热，终于用我的简单新方法压制了食物噪音……你不需要药物或饮食--《每日邮报》</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15396825/weight-loss-method-silence-food-noise-diet.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ask any millennial woman how much of their lives have been consumed by hating their body and, regardless of their size, I can promise you, it’s monopolized far too much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If the tabloids at the grocery store check outs taught me anything, even women with supermodel bodies can be taught to despise themselves based on their reflection or pants size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;That’s because &lt;a target="_self" class="class" href="/health/article-15392661/weight-loss-obesity-wegovy-zepbound-ozempic-bariatric-surgery.html"&gt;diet culture&lt;/a&gt; isn’t just a neutral set of health guidelines, it’s a sophisticated multi-billion-dollar system engineered to profit off people (especially women) feeling perpetually inadequate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Like so many with perfectionist tendencies, my descent into diet perfection started harmlessly enough. I, like many other girls with anxiety and &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/adhd/index.html" id="mol-acba5fa0-dc38-11f0-97f1-f583eb887e9d"&gt;ADHD&lt;/a&gt;, had suffered from digestive maladies my entire life, gifting me a catch-all condition diagnosis of IBS (Irritable Bowel Syndrome).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It took decades - and becoming a registered dietician - to finally free myself from the food noise that had controlled my erratic eating habits and get in the best shape of my life as I approach my 40s, &lt;a target="_self" class="class" href="/health/article-15378471/Doctor-reveals-exactly-protein-eating-avoid-Ozempic-face.html"&gt;without drugs&lt;/a&gt;, counting calories, or even restricting my favorite treats. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As a teenager, when my anxiety was managed, I generally felt just fine. But when I left my small town and moved to Toronto, the flares came on full force. I was ready to do whatever I had to do to feel better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I didn’t realize it then, but this is often the bait of wellness culture - the illusion of purity disguised as care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At the recommendation of a family friend, I visited a homeopathic naturopath who told me I had a mysterious sugar intolerance (dietitian fact check: that was fake news).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Women's magazines teach us that even those with supermodel bodies can be taught to despise themselves based on their reflection or pants size&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;After just a few months, the food noise petered out, the incessant cravings disappeared, and Abbey's sleep, digestion, energy and mood improved&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Naturally, the supposed cure was a full sugar detox. I took these instructions to heart, tossing out every sauce, dressing, snack or drink that featured an ingredient ending in ‘-ose’ (shorthand for various forms of the sweet stuff).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After a few weeks of strict abstinence, some of my IBS symptoms were feeling better and bonus! I lost some weight. The compliments poured in with praise for my ‘discipline,’ my ‘health,’ and my evidently more toned body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Naturally, my next thought was: ‘Well, if cutting out sugar gets me a round of applause, cutting out more bad things will get me a standing ovation.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I then set my sights on fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Very quickly, my once-balanced diet of colorful salads, turkey burgers, and chocolate-chip cookies morphed into something joyless, bland and stale. What began as an experiment to feel better had very quickly swelled into a gripping fear of anything deemed unhealthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And as my list of ‘safe foods’ shrunk, so too did my increasingly feeble frame, stealing friendships, hobbies, laughter, and my identity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It wasn’t yet a formal diagnosis, but I now know what I was suffering from in my late teens was an eating disorder called orthorexia - often considered an obsessive pursuit of dietary purity and healthfulness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In reality, I was less healthy than I’d ever been.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;That’s when the binges started. After dragging myself through months of dry kale and microwaved egg whites with sugar-free hot sauce, I would binge on all the foods I had restricted. Mountains of fries, pizza, pasta, cheesecake, donuts, and ice cream, all within a few hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With each week, the restrictions tightened, the binges swelled, and I plunged into a deeper state of depression and shame.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Eventually, as the validation I so desperately sought turned into whispers and words of concern, I knew something had to change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As part of my recovery, I worked with a registered dietitian who helped me slowly get my weight to a healthier place, while also challenging the food fears that had overtaken my life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One of the exercises I found most helpful was repeated exposure to my forbidden foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;When Abbey moved to Toronto, her anxiety flared and her eating grew more disordered&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;As part of her recovery, Abbey worked with a registered dietitian who helped her slowly get her weight to a healthier place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Abbey still enjoys her Lucky Charms, but eats them in a more healthy combo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When I was in the throes of my eating disorder, I had an obsession with sugary cereal. Lucky Charms, Cinnamon Toast Crunch, Frosted Flakes (oh my yum). If it was in my house on cheat day, I would polish off an entire box.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So I started to eat Frosted Flakes every day. To my surprise, nothing terrible happened. In contrast, something quite wonderful ensued. I stopped caring about it. Eating cereal every day knocked it off its pedestal, loosened its moral grip and neutralized the power it held over me for so long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I continued this exposure therapy with lots of forbidden foods that I had been binging on, and in many cases, I learned that I don’t even like them that much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In other cases, I discovered that I did still enjoy a previously forbidden food (pasta, bread, cheese - get at me!), but I just felt better when I ate them in moderation or alongside other nutritious foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This is when my &lt;a class="class" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/abbey-sharp-rd/the-hunger-crushing-combo-method/9781668654330/?lens=balance"&gt;Hunger Crushing Combo Method&lt;/a&gt; was born. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I found out for myself what is already backed up by science: that the simplest way to silence the food noise in our heads isn’t with drugs, calorie counting or the latest detox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Instead, by combining two or more of the Hunger Crushing Compounds - protein, fiber, and healthy fats - we can turn our favorite 'junk foods' into balanced meals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the process, we crush the physical hunger and emotional cravings that are keeping us from reaching our healthiest happiest weight and a joyful relationship with food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For example, despite all the exposure I gave myself with sugary cereal, I still love it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But when I removed the morality around it, I learned that eating a mountainous bowl of what we call ‘naked carbs’ in their birthday suit doesn’t always feel great. I might feel sluggish, I might feel a little backed up, and because naked carbs are rapidly digested and absorbed, I’d likely feel hungry again (and often a bit irritable thanks to the blood sugar crash) shortly after.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In contrast, foods rich in protein, fiber, and healthy fats are the perfect anchors for naked carbs because they stimulate satiety hormones, quiet food noise and hunger hormones, balance blood sugars (so no spikes or subsequent crashes), and provide your body with the nutrients it needs to support focus, digestion, sleep and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In my case, I learned that if I build a big ol’ bowl of Greek yogurt (protein), added a handful of berries (fiber), a couple spoonfuls of nuts (healthy fats), and then topped it off with colorful magically delicious ‘breakfast marshmallows,’ I achieved both physical satiety and emotional satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Using the Hunger Crushing Combo method, you can still eat naked carbs like toast, but combine them with protein, fiber and healthy fats&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;On family pizza night, load your slice up with grilled chicken, mixed vegetables and olives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If you love cookies, try serving them on a snack plate with pear (fiber), walnuts (healthy fats), and cheese (protein) to temper the blood sugar spike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;On family pizza night, load your slice up with grilled chicken, mixed vegetables and olives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And if you’re a breakfast bagel lover, build a sandwich with canned tuna, sliced veggies and greens, and smashed avocado.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After just a few months of adding Hunger Crushing Compounds to the naked carbs I loved, the food noise in my head petered out, the incessant cravings disappeared, my sleep, digestion, energy and mood improved, and I settled into my healthiest, happiest weight and body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And this isn’t just my unique response - we have so much research to support why a nourishing abundance mindset, instead of the restrictive mentality I was trapped in for so long, is the key to long-term behavior change. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When we’re no longer distracted by the impending doom of the next D-day, we have the mental capacity to listen to our bodies' true needs and wants, and space in our lives for acts of self care that actually fill our cup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Hunger Crushing Combo Method works because it’s not another restrictive diet that depends on your willpower to white-knuckle through discomfort. It works with your biology and psychology to help optimize your health, regardless of your goal, life stage, or preferences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For example, research suggests that combining foods rich in fiber, protein and healthy fats can help reduce blood sugar spikes by 30 to 50 per cent, can spontaneously (and effortlessly) help support excess fat loss and muscle growth, and can significantly reduce the long term risk of heart disease, cancers, type 2 diabetes and other chronic disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And it does all of this without restriction, deprivation or denial. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;No risk, all rewards. No scarcity, just abundance. No fear, just loads of delicious, nourishing food. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It’s simple science and a massive mindset shift. Welcome to a brand new world of fueling your body with confidence and joy. You’ll never look at a box of kids' cereal the same way again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;The Hunger Crushing Combo Method by Abbey Sharp is published by Balance, January 13&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:00:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxQSWZSUkdMSWFBYmJ0dWtXekZ0ZUxzUDB1T3BJTGRQM3ZPcjhBTl9DMEVTQ0pjRzJMeHkzYzY2cE9rZ2MtUHUyMkFUQXdRTDJvbEVQaWN6dUtaYVFPb2JEWF9WOUtYWEVBSjdYcHBNcGV2ZkpwS1kxVTBSWUxFOU5tZUh6S2sweW80cGZvXzdHQnBlblpQb3FiMGRHUkhCQmxp</guid></item><item><title>纽约报告一周内流感住院人数创历史新高-时代联盟</title><link>https://www.timesunion.com/health/article/new-york-record-high-flu-hospitalizations-21274192.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>Times Union</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 19:04:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPR2xYQ0w4TWZEc1kzWWhZdHVBeHBsOEFmcktDLWVRbmdDN19hSEk0RXFENXlhTE1EWTV6eTN6ZkljOXdLUHJVenBnTVlVTWRKdlEwVnMwb2d6RjcyTUdiazVXVno0ZlctLW44Mk0wMkIzTkpQR085cmNUS1FSQ1c0MHJiZ3hYZkJTWFNUYllkVXlBYXFweEJFajdHcjM</guid></item><item><title>在NC中发现的麻疹暴露- WRAL</title><link>https://www.wral.com/news/state/gaston-county-measles-north-carolina-january-2026/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;
					&lt;p id="font-resize" class="font-resize-container"&gt;
						&lt;button id="small-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa small-buttom-font-svg" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;button id="medium-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;button id="large-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;

					
						&lt;p&gt;A person carrying measles traveled through Gaston County while infectious, according to the North Carolina Department of Health and Human Services. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Health officials ask anyone who was at Constantine’s Restaurant in Gastonia after 8:30 p.m. on Dec. 26, 2025, to monitor for measles symptoms until Jan. 16.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
								
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;The individual also attended Christmas Town USA in McAdenville from 5:30 to 8 p.m. on Dec. 26, 2025. The individual did not visit any indoor locations, so the risk of transmission of measles to others who were attending at the same time is low.  &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Measles is a respiratory disease that can be spread by coughing and sneezing.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;As of Dec. 30, 2025, the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has reported 2,065 people from 44 states as confirmed measles cases this year.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Symptoms of measles include:&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;High fever (may spike to more than 104 degrees)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cough&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Runny nose&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Red, watery eyes (conjunctivitis)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiny white spots on the inner cheeks, gums and roof of the mouth (Koplik Spots) two to three days after symptoms begin&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A rash that is red, raised, blotchy; usually starts on face, spreads to trunk, arms and legs three to five days after symptoms begin&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
						
							
							
								&lt;p class="opscoad-Mobile_In_Content" data-unit="wral-v4/news/state/gaston-county-measles-north-carolina-january-2026"&gt;
								&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;p class="opscoad-article_in_read" data-unit="wral-v4/news/state/gaston-county-measles-north-carolina-january-2026/"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;In December, &lt;a href="https://www.wral.com/news/local/rdu-measles-exposure-dec-10-2025/"&gt;a traveler infected with measles came through Terminal 2&lt;/a&gt; of Raleigh-Durham International Airport.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
					
				&lt;/div&gt;


				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WRAL</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 19:01:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNRXRVNWJvbXBQUnRCM1FfNjJfOGpOWENlRVZPUDlHelNpbnVJRnZqa1EwaE1nTDRWNE5EWUwzeFIxcnZjVnJ1Z09yQmhtT25Ub1M2cDB5MUFvMlJfZ2NRV2phSm5JaV9tREN3ZmtRUmgxYUZWRklwZk1wVlp3R1hhdXprdzJSZzBjMUE</guid></item><item><title>继2018年以来最严重的季节之后，美国12月流感病例激增--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2026/jan/03/us-spike-influenza-december</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The United States has seen the number of influenza cases climb significantly in December, coming after the most severe flu season since 2018, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It’s not yet clear whether there will be an increase in the total number of people who get the flu this season – or whether more people just got it at once in December – but more than 3,100 people died from the virus in the US in the year ending August 2025, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-51.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;latest data&lt;/a&gt; from the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;As such, people who have not yet gotten a flu vaccine should still get one, according to &lt;a href="https://vivo.brown.edu/display/jnuzzo" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Jennifer Nuzzo&lt;/a&gt;, an epidemiologist at Brown University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Bottom line for people, if they haven’t gotten vaccinated against the flu, they should get vaccinated, particularly young kids and older adults,” Nuzzo said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The spike in cases comes after a 2024-2025 flu season that was the most severe since 2018, according to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/whats-new/2025-2026-influenza-activity.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the CDC&lt;/a&gt;. It also included 279 influenza-associated pediatric deaths, the highest reported to the agency during a seasonal influenza epidemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;This year, a new variant, subclade K, has emerged and the flu season started earlier than usual in Europe, with “&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/dec/17/new-flu-strain-sweeping-across-europe-is-putting-pressure-on-healthcare-says-who" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;high or very high influenza activity&lt;/a&gt;”, in December in the region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the United States, there had been an estimated 7.5m influenza cases and 81,000 hospitalizations by 20 December. That marked a 25% increase in cases over the previous week, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;a href="https://gis.cdc.gov/grasp/fluview/main.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Thirty-two states&lt;/a&gt; have seen a “high or very high” number of flu illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“A lot of people are getting the flu at the same time, which is always tough. That is actually tougher than a situation in which people get it and it’s spread out over a longer period,” Nuzzo said. “It could be a worse season, in part because more people are going to need care than hospitals can easily deliver.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Epidemiologists are also concerned that fewer people could opt to get the flu vaccine because the CDC, led by the health secretary, Robert F Kennedy Jr, canceled &lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/388/bmj.r389" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;its campaign&lt;/a&gt; encouraging people to get the shot. At the start of December, about 130m flu vaccines had been distributed in the US, 13m less than at the same point last year, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluvaxview/dashboard/vaccine-doses-distributed.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;according to the CDC&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s completely incredulous to me that after experiencing the worst flu season for kids on record that we could head into this flu season – with signs that it could be bad, based on the viruses circulating out there – with anything but a robust plan to encourage people to get vaccinated,” Nuzzo said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some US residents could also be concerned about how much protection the new round of vaccine shots offer against the latest variant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We have some reason to think that the protection may be lower, but I want to be careful by saying” that, Nuzzo said. “It may protect you less, but it’s likely still going to give you some important protection.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;People also might not be aware that they can pick up an at-home test from a pharmacy, Nuzzo said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“There are some people who might benefit from medication if they tested positive, but that medication needs to be given very soon after symptoms start,” Nuzzo said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 19:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQMDViMWVKYm1xc3FCalY1VVJ3cTF2NDRteHlJQWgwQl8zc3JMSWxGNTRVM09mSGZmYzZhdzl3MllTNDFRbG9FcGNhVjRrZTNnV0RkR1FaNVBoUnFPanl2TXBQUUlYekh6cDdkY2haUkpWMXVXZmpBRWxBNThUZVowdA</guid></item><item><title>服用维生素B12的最佳时间？ -健康：值得信赖且富有同理心的健康与保健信息</title><link>https://www.health.com/best-time-to-take-vitamin-b12-11873881</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Vitamin B12 is an essential nutrient that supports red blood cell production, nerve function, energy metabolism, and DNA synthesis. A supplement can help fill gaps when you’re not getting enough vitamin B12 from foods like eggs, oysters, and salmon, but experts say there’s no single best time to take it.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-when-to-take-vitamin-b12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Because &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.health.com/vitamin-b12-7252832" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;vitamin B12&lt;/a&gt; is water-soluble, meaning it dissolves in water, it’s often best taken on an empty stomach with water, said &lt;a href="https://meganmeyerphd.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Megan Meyer, PhD&lt;/a&gt;, a science communication consultant based in Durham, North Carolina. Some limited evidence also suggests vitamin B12 could reduce sleep, so taking it earlier in the day may be a good idea.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Still, there’s no universally ideal time to take vitamin B12, according to &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/talia-follador-rdn-ldn-52842883/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Talia Follador, RDN, LDN&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian nutritionist and founder of Follador Nutrition Services. “What matters most is being consistent and taking the proper dosage,” she said.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-factors-that-can-make-a-difference"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While the timing of vitamin B12 may not matter much, other factors can impact the efficacy of the supplement, said &lt;a href="https://www.corenutritionhw.com/about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Julie Pace, RDN&lt;/a&gt;, a functional dietitian nutritionist &amp;amp; founder of Core Nutrition Health &amp;amp; Wellness.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These include the form of the supplement, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.health.com/stomach-7644099" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;stomach acid levels&lt;/a&gt;, existing B12 status, and the body’s ability to produce a protein called intrinsic factor, which is essential for absorption. “Think of it as a ‘shuttle bus’ that carries B12 through your digestive system into your bloodstream,” Pace told &lt;em&gt;Health&lt;/em&gt;. “Without it, your body can't absorb B12 from food, regardless of how much you eat.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For people who have trouble absorbing B12, higher-dose supplements or even injections may be necessary, Follador said.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-who-may-benefit-from-vitamin-b12-supplements"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Meyer recommends &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.health.com/foods-with-the-most-vitamin-b12-11852167" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;getting vitamin B12 from food&lt;/a&gt; whenever possible. Many animal products naturally contain B12, and some foods—such as breakfast cereals, nutritional yeast, and plant-based milks—are fortified with it.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; However, people who are &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.health.com/nutrition/21-important-facts-about-vitamin-b12-deficiency" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;deficient in vitamin B12&lt;/a&gt;, which can be confirmed with a blood test, may benefit from supplements. Those who follow vegan or vegetarian diets, as well as people with conditions that impair nutrient absorption, such as celiac disease or Crohn’s disease, are more likely to be deficient, Meyer said.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Supplement doses can be as high as 1,000 micrograms—far above the 2.4 micrograms most adults need—but because vitamin B12 is water-soluble and not stored in the body, these amounts are considered safe, Meyer added.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Health: Trusted and Empathetic Health and Wellness Information</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibkFVX3lxTE8wellrYl9SbGIwOE9OY1JsVjVwVWtyemlkRUk2SkZNRk9GSkhzUVI4V25Zck43Qng1c09NNlU2VXJMWXM5LWx1Q3VIN0IyNzY0V1hsT0NBeUx2X21wVUNESzZoakRXdTY1d0FoeUxR</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法， 5种有助于降低血压的最佳减肥零食- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/snacks-for-weight-loss-with-high-blood-pressure-11874848</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Losing weight is often recommended for hypertension since extra weight raises blood pressure.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Protein- and fiber-rich meals boost fullness, while potassium and magnesium support heart health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;For snacks, dietitians suggest unsalted nuts, popcorn, yogurt with fruit, chia pudding and more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Weight loss is often recommended for people with hypertension because carrying excess weight is linked to higher blood pressure levels and increased strain on the heart.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Research shows that even modest weight loss can help lower blood pressure, making sustainable eating habits helpful for managing both.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; That's where snacking comes in. Foods that provide protein and fiber increase satiety and reduce cravings, while those that include potassium and magnesium help regulate blood pressure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Choosing nutrient-dense snacks can increase satisfaction between meals, supporting both weight loss and heart health. Ahead, dietitians share snack ideas that do just that.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-strained-greek-style-yogurt-with-fruit"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Strained (Greek-style) Yogurt with Fruit &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Dietitians agree that strained (Greek-style) yogurt is a great snack option for weight loss if you have high blood pressure, especially when paired with high-potassium fruits like bananas and kiwis.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "Greek yogurt is a good source of protein to keep you feeling full, while banana and kiwi provide potassium to help manage sodium levels in the body," says  &lt;a href="https://www.willowlabs.ai/products/nutu/team" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Dawn Menning, M.S., RD, CDCES&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Potassium helps the kidneys excrete excess sodium and supports the relaxation of blood vessel walls, both of which play an important role in blood pressure regulation.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Not a fan of bananas and kiwi? &lt;a href="https://www.mayazbites.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Maya Oueichek, M.B.A., RDN&lt;/a&gt;, recommends pairing strained (Greek-style) yogurt with berries and chia seeds. In addition to supporting satiety, strained (Greek-style) yogurt's protein helps preserve lean muscle mass during weight loss.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Berries contribute fiber and potassium, while chia seeds provide omega-3 fats and magnesium—nutrients that support healthy blood pressure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-hummus-with-veggies"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Hummus with Veggies &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Hummus is rich in plant-based fiber, protein and magnesium," says Oueichek, nutrients that are helpful for weight loss and managing hypertension.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; For veggies, she recommends carrots and bell peppers because they're a good source of potassium and naturally low in sodium.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "This combo promotes fullness, stable blood sugar and supports vascular function," Oueichek adds, all of which are important for weight loss and managing blood pressure.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It's important to keep sodium in check if you have high blood pressure, so choose low-sodium hummus options or make your own at home.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "Excess sodium intake is directly linked to elevated blood pressure," says Oueichek.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Try our&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/256571/garlic-hummus/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Garlic Hummus&lt;/a&gt; recipe, and enhance flavor with lemon juice, garlic and spices instead of salt.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-unsalted-nuts"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Unsalted Nuts &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Nuts support heart health by improving blood lipids, supporting healthy blood pressure and reducing inflammation. These benefits come from their mix of unsaturated fats, plant protein, fiber, phytosterols and minerals potassium and magnesium—nutrients linked to cardiovascular protection.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Enjoying nuts with a side of fruit can make an even more satisfying snack. "Fruit paired with a handful of nuts promotes satiety since fiber, protein and healthy fat slow digestion," says &lt;a href="https://sheridietitian.com/about-me/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Sheri Gaw, RDN, CDCES&lt;/a&gt;. She notes that this combination also provides potassium and magnesium, minerals that aid in blood pressure control.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The fiber and protein in nuts can also help reduce cravings, which may support weight loss, says Menning.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Go with unsalted varieties to best support your blood pressure.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-chia-pudding"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Chia Pudding &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Chia seed pudding provides healthy fat, protein, fiber, magnesium and potassium—nutrients that help slow digestion, regulate hunger and support heart health and blood pressure control," says Gaw. Research suggests chia seed consumption may help lower both systolic and diastolic blood pressure, likely due to its effects on vascular function and inflammation.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Chia seeds are also a source of omega-3 fatty acids, which have been linked to cardiovascular benefits, including reduced inflammation.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Preparing &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/chia-seed-pudding-8430793" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Chia Seed Pudding&lt;/a&gt; with cow's milk adds calcium and protein, further supporting heart health and satiety.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-air-popped-popcorn"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Air-Popped Popcorn &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Air-popped popcorn contains fiber, which has been linked to benefits for digestive health, blood sugar regulation, heart health and weight management.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; A fiber-rich snack helps slow digestion and promote fullness, which can keep you feeling full and satisfied between meals.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Dietitians recommend being thoughtful when seasoning your snacks. Oueichek suggests sprinkling popcorn with smoked paprika, cinnamon, cumin or chili powder instead of salt. "Or you can add nutritional yeast to give it a cheesy, savory flavor without adding sodium," says Menning. Nutritional yeast also provides B vitamins, fiber and a small amount of protein.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-ways-to-lose-weight-and-support-healthy-blood-pressure"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Ways to Lose Weight and Support Healthy Blood Pressure &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exercise regularly. &lt;/strong&gt;Physical activity helps lower blood pressure by strengthening the heart and improving blood vessel function, while also supporting weight loss.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Aim for 150 minutes of moderate aerobic activity plus 2 days of resistance training per week.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prioritize sleep. &lt;/strong&gt;Missing out on quality sleep is associated with increased appetite and energy intake.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; It can also negatively affect blood pressure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Aim for seven to nine hours of quality sleep each night. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limit alcohol intake. &lt;/strong&gt;Alcohol can raise blood pressure and add to overall caloric intake, making both heart health and weight loss harder to manage.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manage stress. &lt;/strong&gt;Chronic stress can elevate cortisol levels and blood pressure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "Simple practices like breathing exercises, mindfulness, yoga or regular walks can be effective," says Oueichek.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Snacks can help you lose weight and manage blood pressure when chosen thoughtfully. Balanced choices that combine protein and fiber increase satiety, while nutrients like potassium and magnesium support heart and blood vessel health. Rather than skipping snacks, aim to be intentional. Choose whole, nutrient-dense foods—like fruit, vegetables, yogurt, nuts and whole grains—to help you reach your goals.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 18:58:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNSnZRVWZ3LU01TS14WXVORkVCbm81Mkc2SVpIWGZuLUg2S3pISVVicHRCdGQ5REFNZmdZV3dhNG1STHQxODN2ZkRDelZNRWg2NjN5ZS1pSEVZTjdhNDFiSm9pWU5lVG1rS2NYSHF1Zlhia0M5WDNHeFJhNjlBM2N3MFYtbnpYWEJHNDc4</guid></item></channel></rss>