<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>根据科学，这是你孩子在手机和社交媒体上的大脑-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/28/adolescent-brain-development-screen-time/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VYSDLW7ZZVGCJN56XI7VVHOKLQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;University of Pennsylvania researcher Ran Barzilay is a father of three. His first two children received cellphones before they turned 12. But this summer, as early results from his own study on screens and teen health rolled in, he changed course. His youngest? Not getting one anytime soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:01:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxPMGRucUhGT0E2OGVacUQ2alFMSm5jd05mY0RTOFNZVjRJRDJMaTA3Y0EzcERBeEwzdDdkbm8tMnpnWTNjWFE5MWw1cloydWJ4NjJjb2wzRDZLRW1fUUVsNEVudkM5T0o3S01GSzJRRWNxZHg2UTRzNnhWQldib3BxTVFjeVp5RFVmelB3SWc5MEZMYTNH</guid></item><item><title>来自班加罗尔，德里，孟买的顶级医院的3名医生分享了5个脂肪肝的警告标志写在你的脸上|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/3-doctors-from-top-hospitals-in-bengaluru-delhi-mumbai-share-5-warning-signs-of-fatty-liver-written-on-your-face-101766912076278.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/3-doctors-from-top-hospitals-in-bengaluru-delhi-mumbai-share-5-warning-signs-of-fatty-liver-written-on-your-face-101766912076278.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/is-fatty-liver-disease-irreversible-fortis-gastroenterologist-shares-3-best-drinks-to-reverse-fatty-liver-naturally-101764475024883.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Fatty liver disease,"&gt;Fatty liver disease,&lt;/a&gt; often called a 'silent killer', is reaching epidemic proportions in India, with a 2021 &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9168741/" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="study"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; suggesting that nearly 39 percent of adults are now affected. While the liver sits deep within the abdomen, leading hepatologists and gastroenterologists warn that the organ's struggle often manifests in plain sight. &lt;strong&gt;Also read |&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fatty-liver-causes-and-expert-tips-to-combat-the-disease-101709623060882.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Fatty liver: Causes and expert tips to combat the disease"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Fatty liver: Causes and expert tips to combat the disease&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/28/550x309/6663697_1748406405560_1766912359201.jpg" alt="Fatty liver disease can progress to fibrosis and chronic liver failure if untreated. (Freepik)" title="Fatty liver disease can progress to fibrosis and chronic liver failure if untreated. (Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/28/550x309/6663697_1748406405560_1766912359201.jpg" alt="Fatty liver disease can progress to fibrosis and chronic liver failure if untreated. (Freepik)" title="Fatty liver disease can progress to fibrosis and chronic liver failure if untreated. (Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Fatty liver disease can progress to fibrosis and chronic liver failure if untreated. (Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;The face serves as an early external indicator of internal metabolic stress,” Dr Vikram Raut, senior consultant, liver transplant and HPB surgery, Fortis Hospital Mulund, Mumbai told HT Lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt; Because the liver is central to hormone regulation, toxin clearance, and nutrient processing, its dysfunction can trigger visible dermatological and vascular changes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Medical experts from across the country have identified five critical facial signs that could signal your liver is under siege. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;According to them, your face may be telling a story your liver can't – heeding these warnings early could be the key to preventing long-term complications like cirrhosis or liver failure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;1. Yellowing of the skin and eyes (jaundice)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most classic sign of liver distress is a yellow tint, known as Jaundice. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Mallikarjun Sakpal, consultant, HPB and transplant physician, Aster CMI Hospital, Bengaluru, explained that this occurs when the liver fails to process bilirubin — a waste product from red blood cell breakdown.&lt;/span&gt; “When the liver struggles, bilirubin levels rise, causing a &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/doctor-gastroenterologist-shares-7-early-signs-of-liver-cirrhosis-know-5-tips-to-prevent-liver-damage-101747305290844.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="mild yellowing"&gt;mild yellowing&lt;/a&gt; of the whites of the eyes or facial skin that should never be ignored,” he told HT Lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;2. Facial puffiness and under-eye swelling&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you wake up with a consistently bloated look around your cheeks and eyes, it may not just be a lack of sleep. Dr Sudeep Khanna, senior consultant, gastroenterology, Indraprastha Apollo Hospitals, pointed to fluid retention as the culprit. “When the liver is overloaded with fat, it produces less of the proteins needed to keep fluids inside blood vessels. This leads to leakage into facial tissues, causing&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/suffering-from-swollen-puffy-eyes-dermatologist-shares-why-this-may-happen-and-how-to-reduce-puffiness-101756377953013.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="persistent puffiness,"&gt; persistent puffiness,&lt;/a&gt;” he explained in an interview to HT Lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;3. Adult acne and oily breakouts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudden breakouts, particularly around the jawline, cheeks, and forehead, can be a sign of metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD). According to Dr Sakpal, a fatty liver cannot remove toxins or balance hormones like androgens efficiently. This imbalance triggers overactive oil glands and stubborn pimples that resist standard topical treatments.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;4. Red 'spider' veins and rosacea-like flushing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiny red lines branching out like a spider’s web — known as spider angiomas — are frequent markers of severe liver scarring or cirrhosis. Dr Raut explained these are caused by dilated capillaries. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Khanna added that 'rosacea-like flushing' often arises from poor estrogen breakdown, which increases blood flow to the facial skin and triggers visible vascular networks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;5. Dullness, itching, and patchy skin&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liver disease can rob the skin of its natural glow. Dr Sakpal shared that a fatty liver often reduces the absorption of vitamins A and E, leading to dry, flaky, and itchy skin. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Furthermore, Dr Raut added that patients may experience a 'grey-brown' darkening or patchy appearance on the face due to hormonal imbalances and the accumulation of bile salts in the bloodstream.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;A silent epidemic: can it be reversed?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While these signs are alarming, the medical consensus is hopeful. Dr Khanna shared that fatty liver is often asymptomatic in its early stages, usually only detectable via ultrasound. However, once facial signs appear, it is a clear signal to act. “Weight loss of just 5 to 10 percent can significantly shrink liver fat and even reverse disease progression,” Dr Khanna said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Recommended lifestyle swaps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;⦿ Diet: Switch to greens-rich meals and cut out sugary sodas.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Activity: Incorporate at least 30 minutes of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/walking-just-7k-steps-daily-can-reduce-risk-of-death-47-lower-cardiovascular-disease-incidence-25-lancet-study-10k-101753334398446.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="daily walking"&gt;daily walking&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Supplementation: Adding anti-inflammatory spices like turmeric can aid recovery.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Screening: If you have risk factors like obesity or diabetes, consult a doctor for a FibroScan or ultrasound.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:11:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgJBVV95cUxQdFlBdzE2TkM5RmE0dDRlenNmQnVjR3VlTWNXY2ZSRExlN2tRaTYtMXpzYjhCSmhuQUN3WkRFS0ZzZWRhNGliVTdDeEpTeTZoSUVUZnVRTzB0cDFjUWhkMTFzUTRpV01rNzBSMWhMVGhoOU5BSjYwTGY4V1ZUNEtQRTJTcGNPaDFhOXJVWUJodUpHaEJWTzItcEZiYWpjLXg4Nl9oaFRmMUItU21BeGpNUm1xa2IwNjBUMnF1UzhyTUJROHhQcGQ0VUljb3BqOVlqNWdtVmVzbm01dTc1MzFHVXdGX2N2djU0akNfNmRxTDc3M1JpdFZ3b2lLbTRYRmNZWkozZXJnYk5jWWhWWHfSAZMCQVVfeXFMTXoxVnNLOE5nZk5aUXdQczF5WUF1Y09WX3BlcTNaQVl2RmJEOUtQVExhVUJoWVBybzFSSDlpVzRXREw0QWh5S2JMNldJYnROTlhfX1JYUlNNYWprajNrTUgwQ2c0NVZFZ3ZqZFN6d3A4azdaMHU4TXJaVS1TUE5mTjVWUmVjeEt1Y1RrdF9peWZfQjJVdGZXNTlpUzYwemRRaW5TNjVwMlM3TE01dGpPRnRnUG5RS256VmNEdDM3Mk1lci1rYkNnWUhTakhwZmxmbWZvQ2l4Z0VhV1VfbTh2UUQ1SHlRa294dkh1bXpPbDc2d1oxRUZwbTllc0FmaE1BWXc5WGpRSWhMbVBCM3M3NTdhRjg</guid></item><item><title>中年减肥可能隐藏着大脑成本- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251228020004.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Obesity remains one of the most serious health challenges worldwide, and weight loss is often encouraged as a way to lower the risks tied to excess weight. But growing research suggests that the effects of weight loss may change with age. During midlife, losing weight may not always produce the same health benefits seen in younger adults and in some cases, it may also influence brain health.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a new study from Ben-Gurion University of the Negev (BGU), researchers examined how diet-induced obesity and later weight loss affected young adult mice compared with mid-aged mice. In both groups, weight loss successfully restored healthy blood glucose control, showing that key metabolic improvements occur regardless of age. However, the scientists also observed an unexpected difference. In mid-aged mice, weight loss led to increased inflammation in the hypothalamus, a part of the brain involved in regulating appetite, energy use, and other essential functions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brain Inflammation Raises New Questions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This increase in brain inflammation was detected at the molecular level and through detailed microscopic imaging of microglia (the brain's immune cells). The inflammatory response lasted for several weeks before gradually declining. While the long-term effects of this response are still unclear and may even play a role in achieving metabolic improvements, the findings raise important concerns. Persistent or poorly regulated inflammation in the brain has been linked to memory problems and neurodegenerative conditions such as Alzheimer's. As a result, the study highlights new questions about how weight loss during midlife may interact with brain health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Researchers Urge a More Nuanced View of Midlife Weight Loss&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Our findings show that losing weight in midlife is not a simple copy-and-paste of what works in young adulthood," said Alon Zemer, an M.D.-Ph.D. candidate and the first author of this paper. "Weight loss remains essential for restoring metabolic health in obesity, but we need to understand the impact of weight loss on the mid-age brain and ensure brain health is not compromised."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Alexandra Tsitrina added: "Our study characterizes the body's adaptive response to weight loss through two complementary dimensions -- molecular and structural. This high-end imaging by advanced microscopy and image analysis with advanced computational analysis enable detection of sensitive changes with potential health ramifications."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next Steps for Protecting Brain Health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research team stresses the importance of additional studies to better understand why this temporary but concerning brain inflammation occurs during midlife weight loss. Future work could help scientists develop approaches that maintain the metabolic advantages of weight loss while also protecting brain health as people age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study, titled, "Weight loss aggravates obesity-induced hypothalamic inflammation in mid-aged mice" was published in &lt;em&gt;GeroScience&lt;/em&gt; and supported by an internal grant at BGU (with the Ilse Katz Institute of Nanoscale Science and Technology), and grants from theUS-Israel Binational Science Foundation (Grant no. 2021083) and the Israel Science Foundation (Grant No. 194/24).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:41:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBHUkxGTnF5c1UtVERqUWlpZlIzUFZ2UTh2MFR1cFBqbFFQanZWUUZZRWc0NmxHN2QyS0NvMy1PZHBMZnBWcnFLYlh0QlJ1cFFOM2VORlp2ODFwenZTbFY0S0NsNnpUMTBsY2lfNC12TQ</guid></item><item><title>带有健康流行语的食物可能会将添加的糖隐藏在显而易见的地方- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/wireStory/foods-healthy-sounding-buzzwords-hiding-added-sugar-plain-128728905</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;Many consumers feel pride in avoiding the glazed pastries in the supermarket and instead opting for “all natural” granola that comes packed with extra protein. Same goes for low-fat yogurts “made with real fruit,” “organic” plant-based milks and bottled “superfood” smoothies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Buyer beware: Healthy grocery buzzwords like those often cover up an &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/article/heat-hot-climate-sugar-soda-diabetes-dee1cb27322afb3e556fd2c6f8ecf1ae"&gt;unhealthy amount of sugar&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/c147e0085eb842ac9144e8214dddd063"&gt;Added sugars&lt;/a&gt; are difficult to quickly spot because many companies use clever marketing to distract consumers, said Nicole Avena, a professor of neuroscience and psychiatry at Mount Sinai Medical School and Princeton University who has studied added sugars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Avena said while some health-forward brands know people are starting to become aware of the hazards of added sugars, "a lot of the bigger brands don’t worry so much about people’s health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Here’s how to spot hidden sugars and what to do about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Along with saturated fat and salt, eating excess sugar is linked to &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/article/033b68db8ce342cd9cfdcda57a628027"&gt;heart disease, obesity, diabetes and other health risks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The average American consumes 17 grams of added sugar a day, which adds up to 57 pounds (26 kilograms) per year, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/sugar/sugar-shrink-the-sweet-spot-for-blood-sugar-health"&gt;according to the American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt;. About half of that comes from beverages, but much of the rest is sneaked into cereal, salsa, prepared sandwiches, dairy products, bottled sauces and baked goods, including many brands of whole-grain bread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;To help control sugar intake, start by checking the nutrition label. Since 2021, food companies have been required to list the quantity of added sugars separately from total sugar content. But the plan backfired, Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Companies reduced common sweeteners like refined beet sugar and high-fructose corn syrup but added alternatives, such as monk fruit and the sugar alcohol erythritol, which aren’t considered “added sugars” under FDA regulations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“Now our foods are even more sweet than they were back in 2020,” Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Collin Popp, a dietitian and professor at NYU Langone Health, said the current FDA recommendation allows for some flexibility. People should get no more than 10% of their calories from added sugar, which amounts to about 50 grams per day if eating 2,000 calories, or a bit more than what’s in a typical can of soda.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;But that might be too flexible, Popp said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“I would actually like to see that be less than 5%, and closer to zero for some, if they have diabetes or prediabetes,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The key is to &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/hub/food-safety"&gt;be mindful of what you’re eating&lt;/a&gt;, even if the product &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/article/28e626562c88439b96056e843215aa8d"&gt;seems healthy&lt;/a&gt; or if the package is labeled organic, Popp said. Roasted nuts, plant-based milks and wasabi peas, for example, can include a surprising amount of added sugars. So can English muffins and Greek yogurt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;One Chobani black cherry yogurt, for example, has zero grams of fat but 9 grams of added sugar, or more than 2 teaspoons. Silk brand almond milk has 7 grams per cup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Popp recommends taking control of how much sugar goes into your food. That could mean buying plain yogurt and adding honey or berries, or asking the barista if you can put your own oat milk into your coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Although they lower the calorie content of foods, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/article/coke-cane-sugar-corn-syrup-better-d7a70ebd4aef1564e409dd087f6a69c3"&gt;artificial sweeteners&lt;/a&gt; like stevia and sugar alcohols may not be better because they can encourage people to overeat, Avena said. She said research shows that sweet flavors are what activate the reward center of the brain, not the sugar itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;That’s not to write off sugar alternatives, including allulose for people with Type 1 diabetes since it doesn’t affect blood sugar. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;But for the general public, minimizing dependence on the overall sweetness of food is key to improving health, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“Don’t let the food companies decide how much sugar you’re eating," Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;Albert Stumm writes about food, travel and wellness. Find his work at &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.albertstumm.com/"&gt;www.albertstumm.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:23:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxNM21iQVNyTlVyQjR5N2VOYU5xOVZ6Zm9WTFV5S3ZpWGk3TXJ5RHNsSkNSLW1YMWtQWmxPTVE0b0tYVzJ2VE9lOXAxSkR3dWRtYjNMdTYzREN6YmJyLTdrLXhhcUgtbnd0TDlsRDd4VUUya1NVblltSmEzQmlnQjBSbl9TVHVLSGdFM3l3WHM3c2t6TThJWmRtbDBhNkFiQTQ3TG1TTTlyVFZtVmvSAbABQVVfeXFMT3VpMDVtSUUwSy1QMmFMOTBENXo5ZDBPaW9BVEl4a3pySGw1ZGRNVFlIWjB2cWMtQkFXTUdheTVyY1VlUl81a1dCTE04WDM3MmMwaTN0czYxZFRJV1FEeWs0SXhTVDc2WVI1RGJKdllaZ015NUNSZkZKcWV1WjF4amNWS0hBd1VMcUhaWHZJSFpwdXBNazR0QjNTVkt0SUtoUmNCR05FamJVdkQzN0JLQjQ</guid></item><item><title>心脏外科医生解释了“积极毒害”您身体的事情，以及为什么您应该“绝对避免”它们- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/heart-surgeon-avoid-food-drink-heart-health-690012-20251227</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p class="loading-bar_loader__2fNms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;main&gt;&lt;template id="B:0"&gt;&lt;/template&gt;&lt;p class="article-page-skeleton_background__h2J4n"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/main&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 05:56:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxNTTZWMU5GNXFtVG5naWgxQkQ0a21xdlhoNFJRMWVtcFVuQXE3b2RERUFfeE9fT0JNR1JmU3kwVDUtWllWTjNIZHZOVzBjYnRQNmhWaXNSTHdxTmlONGFuUkFsQ3p6OGt3dWprMmJYSkhCVEhKSFUyQk9hT3FmTFpCQVBjVWRpMHMycVdneGVWNURlbVRzY0dHUHhncmE</guid></item><item><title>听起来很健康流行语的食物可能会将添加的糖隐藏在显而易见的地方-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/hidden-added-sugar-health-brands-f1bf6cd53aa3be569e5952b5bc8c773f</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;Many consumers feel pride in avoiding the glazed pastries in the supermarket and instead opting for “all natural” granola that comes packed with extra protein. Same goes for low-fat yogurts “made with real fruit,” “organic” plant-based milks and bottled “superfood” smoothies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buyer beware: Healthy grocery buzzwords like those often cover up an &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/heat-hot-climate-sugar-soda-diabetes-dee1cb27322afb3e556fd2c6f8ecf1ae"&gt;unhealthy amount of sugar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/c147e0085eb842ac9144e8214dddd063"&gt;Added sugars&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are difficult to quickly spot because many companies use clever marketing to distract consumers, said Nicole Avena, a professor of neuroscience and psychiatry at Mount Sinai Medical School and Princeton University who has studied added sugars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Avena said while some health-forward brands know people are starting to become aware of the hazards of added sugars, “a lot of the bigger brands don’t worry so much about people’s health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how to spot hidden sugars and what to do about it.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;What to look for&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Along with saturated fat and salt, eating excess sugar is linked to &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/033b68db8ce342cd9cfdcda57a628027"&gt;heart disease, obesity, diabetes and other health risks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The average American consumes 17 grams of added sugar a day, which adds up to 57 pounds (26 kilograms) per year, &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/sugar/sugar-shrink-the-sweet-spot-for-blood-sugar-health" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;according to the American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. About half of that comes from beverages, but much of the rest is sneaked into cereal, salsa, prepared sandwiches, dairy products, bottled sauces and baked goods, including many brands of whole-grain bread.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To help control sugar intake, start by checking the nutrition label. Since 2021, food companies have been required to list the quantity of added sugars separately from total sugar content. But the plan backfired, Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="Infobox" data-module data-gtm-region="This article is part of AP's Be Well coverage, focusing on wellness, fitness, diet and mental health. Read more Be Well." data-align-center&gt;
    
    &lt;div class="Infobox-items RichTextBody"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article is part of AP’s Be Well coverage, focusing on wellness, fitness, diet and mental health. &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/hub/be-well"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Read more Be Well.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Companies reduced common sweeteners like refined beet sugar and high-fructose corn syrup but added alternatives, such as monk fruit and the sugar alcohol erythritol, which aren’t considered “added sugars” under FDA regulations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Now our foods are even more sweet than they were back in 2020,” Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;What should you do?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Collin Popp, a dietitian and professor at NYU Langone Health, said the current FDA recommendation allows for some flexibility. People should get no more than 10% of their calories from added sugar, which amounts to about 50 grams per day if eating 2,000 calories, or a bit more than what’s in a typical can of soda.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that might be too flexible, Popp said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I would actually like to see that be less than 5%, and closer to zero for some, if they have diabetes or prediabetes,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key is to &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/hub/food-safety"&gt;be mindful of what you’re eating&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, even if the product &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/28e626562c88439b96056e843215aa8d"&gt;seems healthy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; or if the package is labeled organic, Popp said. Roasted nuts, plant-based milks and wasabi peas, for example, can include a surprising amount of added sugars. So can English muffins and Greek yogurt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One Chobani black cherry yogurt, for example, has zero grams of fat but 9 grams of added sugar, or more than 2 teaspoons. Silk brand almond milk has 7 grams per cup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Popp recommends taking control of how much sugar goes into your food. That could mean buying plain yogurt and adding honey or berries, or asking the barista if you can put your own oat milk into your coffee.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Taking from one column to add to another&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although they lower the calorie content of foods, &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/coke-cane-sugar-corn-syrup-better-d7a70ebd4aef1564e409dd087f6a69c3"&gt;artificial sweeteners&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; like stevia and sugar alcohols may not be better because they can encourage people to overeat, Avena said. She said research shows that sweet flavors are what activate the reward center of the brain, not the sugar itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s not to write off sugar alternatives, including allulose for people with Type 1 diabetes since it doesn’t affect blood sugar. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But for the general public, minimizing dependence on the overall sweetness of food is key to improving health, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Don’t let the food companies decide how much sugar you’re eating,” Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Albert Stumm writes about food, travel and wellness. Find his work at &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.albertstumm.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;www.albertstumm.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 05:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxPN0M0a2dHNDFFRHZLNlNOSElNWVd0N3E3cWctSVMwakdmUWs5UUJoN3UtTm9aX1pWR0Q4T0VwYUVNdThaNmJqQnU0N1hpYkF5ZVVpa2xBbldqS3FqWDVsREd2Z3h3dV9hMWV2UlhoSVZJckp5ZERaNjFITm44eVMtbldWeENlaDFLdmZVc1J6UXVBZjNVbXZN</guid></item><item><title>11岁的阿拉巴马州男孩因患流感而死亡- AL.com</title><link>https://www.al.com/news/2025/12/11-year-old-alabama-boy-sickened-with-the-flu-dies.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BD2UG5ESSFFE3H44E5A7GIRO3I"&gt;An 11-year-old boy from Hueytown has died after spending nearly a week in the hospital battling the flu, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/sAbRiNa.eRiN10" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.facebook.com/sAbRiNa.eRiN10"&gt;post shared by a family member on Facebook &lt;/a&gt;Saturday and &lt;a href="https://www.wbrc.com/2025/12/28/11-year-old-hueytown-boy-dies-after-battling-severe-case-flu/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.wbrc.com/2025/12/28/11-year-old-hueytown-boy-dies-after-battling-severe-case-flu/"&gt;confirmed by WBRC-TV. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Q23UL3KCTZEUZLCDJEX37XQJFU"&gt;Jace Watkins, 11, had been hospitalized at Children’s of Alabama in Birmingham since Saturday after suffering a seizure. He became ill just two days earlier, first showing symptoms on December 18. Over the Christmas holiday, Jace remained in critical condition as his family held onto hope and asked the community for prayers for his recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WK73NODLJVBJRG2KCS7E24LM4M"&gt;Watkins was a 5th grade student at Hueytown Intermediate School. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UHKEWAZ67ZEMHN52IVVDRUH6MM"&gt;On Saturday, his aunt, Sabrina Erin Parsons, shared a heartbreaking update earlier Saturday evening on Facebook, asking people to continue praying for Jace as the family prepared to say their final goodbyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CQ6EFD3UGFH4TI7EJEFH7YUBJI"&gt;“Just wanted to come on here and update everyone, I want thank everyone for praying for Jace.. Please pray for our family as we say our goodbyes to Jace.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YB25C2J7XVBLJLR4PCI556IVMQ"&gt;Within an hour of the update about Jace’s condition, hundreds of comments poured in, many from people offering comfort, prayers, and shared grief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WUB7H2MHTZH3BMEEYRHKUOTCNU"&gt;“As a mom who lost her little boy many years ago, my heart is broken for you and your family,” one commenter wrote. “There is nothing more devastating than losing your child. My sister also lost her son almost 10 years ago and has created a Facebook support group for bereaved mothers. I am so very sorry that you are going through this awful loss.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VT6JZHSHJRELTIFZAZ2UTFYMPY"&gt;In the week since Jace fell ill, residents of Hueytown have been holding prayer vigils for him and his family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JV3PMTGOGFBORBL2FOJQEGPS34"&gt;Jace’s death comes as Alabama is seeing a sharp rise in emergency room visits related to influenza.&lt;a href="https://www.alabamapublichealth.gov/data/respiratory.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.alabamapublichealth.gov/data/respiratory.html"&gt; According to the Alabama Department of Public Health&lt;/a&gt;, about 6.3 percent of emergency room visits during the week ending December 21 were for flu like illness. That figure is more than double the rate from the previous week and five times higher than it was on December 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BHOVW5KGSNANDL2JTIHO4IOLCI"&gt;Nationally, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported that 14 states experienced high or very high levels of outpatient visits for influenza like illness during the week ending December 13, the most recent data available. At that time, Alabama was classified as having moderate flu activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:CJCVVKZOSZAXZEWFSDLLOJOKPQ" data-fusion-component="CJCVVKZOSZAXZEWFSDLLOJOKPQ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:CJCVVKZOSZAXZEWFSDLLOJOKPQ" data-fusion-component="CJCVVKZOSZAXZEWFSDLLOJOKPQ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 05:42:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxQRHNQQ0RaYWxPT19UWlZKRTJHaWlQMzJlVGV1YW1tSkFuMGNsVDdTaHdPZDJyQUJqdWFOOUxvdVljU28tYkU2SmRxZ2NOY2pLNXJ3ZFFiTlhEOXctZGVqMTZrMG5LZlBXeWp3RFFvQ0wwZnBFY2lTS1JfWExtUElkVHhxajlNczBoX0JvbTlDeGzSAaQBQVVfeXFMTzZwOV9RRkNtQlBNSGNod21VcUt4QUdVY19kQmpCSzRlcDN2MTJ4bmI0NFBhbExxVDRKZW16a1dIcHItMWk5TGVQem1MMjN1dVItS2VrVEhWSG45VmtISWx5XzJiNE1JSVFsMVBtOEE1UUk5MWNGbGlnVVp5ei1OcFlVZEtLNUhKeEVrMzN5Wl9KVHRmNnFwQUdSOWFwZlhYamlNd2Q</guid></item><item><title>RPD ：房东与房客的冲突导致逮捕，步枪由军官保管- 13wham.com</title><link>https://13wham.com/news/local/rpd-landlord-tenant-clash-leads-to-arrest-rifle-secured-by-officers</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText_storyText__C3hWI StoryText_storyText__C3hWI"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rochester, N.Y. — One person was arrested on Saturday after an alleged landlord-tenant dispute in Rochester.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Rochester Police Department said officers responded to the area of Mt. Hope Avenue and Sanford Street for the report of a "menacing with a rifle." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The department said officers learned that a dispute between a landlord and a tenant had occurred, during which police said the tenant threatened their landlord with a rifle. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The landlord wished to pursue criminal charges, the tenant was arrested, and the rifle was secured. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officers said there were no injuries, and the area is open after being taped off for some time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>13wham.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 03:31:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxPbjZKV1RENTBBQlZvYmkydy14emh6OG12OTM2cnRuczZsdldtX2lweEVwcEF6Wk1OTUJHcl85d2FDRWdQZkNNUVBtZVY1RWJxaVVja3lvOWxpZVloS0d0T2txcU41NnNwOW9DSlIwUWZ2aVRqQnFDdnNKQWNNLVpaWlFrX3NyYldNRnptR0JUdzlsRkFQTzRlZjdLbDI0QQ</guid></item><item><title>新泽西州卫生部门表示，纽瓦克机场的乘客可能已经让其他人接触过麻疹- ABC7纽约</title><link>https://abc7ny.com/post/newark-airport-passenger-may-have-exposed-others-measles-new-jersey-health-department-says/18325181/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;NEWARK, New Jersey (WABC) -- &lt;/span&gt;A passenger at Newark Airport may have exposed people to measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;New Jersey's Health Department says someone with the disease passed through the airport on Friday, December 19.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The person was in terminals B and C between 7 a.m. and 7 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The Health Department hopes to track down people who were likely exposed. It also suggests anyone who is not vaccinated to get the MMR shot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Measles symptoms include a high fever, cough, runny nose, watery red eyes, and a rash that usually appears between three and five days after symptoms begin. The rash usually begins as flat red spots that appear on the face at the hairline and spread downward to the neck, torso, arms, legs, and feet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;----------&lt;br class=" "&gt;*&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/newsletters/" target="_blank"&gt; Get Eyewitness News Delivered&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br class=" "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/new-jersey/" target="_blank"&gt;More New Jersey news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br class=" "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://7ny.tv/submitnewstip" target="_blank"&gt;Send us a news tip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br class=" "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/apps/" target="_blank"&gt;Download the abc7NY app for breaking news alerts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br class=" "&gt;*&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCrlIS7z20CnVaCrMvdkig_g" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt; Follow us on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br class=" "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="RxNCg ykkUm PvZ nIjPJ PMXYp LmsHF SfAHY mNgye lNbol LBPRq rBLIK "&gt;Submit a tip or story idea to Eyewitness News&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Have a breaking news tip or an idea for a story we should cover? Send it to Eyewitness News using the form below.    If attaching a video or photo, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/image-video-solicitation-and-rights-terms-of-use/5101040/" target="_blank"&gt;terms of use apply.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2025 WABC-TV. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC7 New York</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:59:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxQdnJfNkpIR0xhU1ZuVjJXc1lld1ZNYVJXZ1NiV3VibklpVzg2dzd6NWh5MTBCS3g3RWM1cURSRzZaejI0Yk9FZE04aEJIVjFKVmwwMWE2YUdMYm1kUnlpVEtPTG5uTHlfWWh6T0tGcEZadFBtdmlTRXFxN09lMFhFZkJNVWxqeUpWQjlHdWlOZWhyNF9QUGtyMWFtUm1zTXJMTkgxc08wSDlUTnZucmVNcTN5TE43RWNiRGFRWmtLTi04QdIBxwFBVV95cUxQY0Rrc2I3b2NQZ3FNTEQxalAyVmdrb1NGcDBsMldZUHNNcUJDVzVhYWQyMmFLaWllOXdwbnFTemZVeUoteWJET09BS21PSms5aFZIZF90WTdMekEzdUZ5SF9ZMENZbG5FX0RmN0VTZWZRRkhBRDZ0LXdkSnIyQmhJaVQzNG5fYks2aUQ5d1JSRE0zbUQxR1VsQU1xdGgwVTdVUWJGNTRzZ1lyalExUFpVZ2twMzRLYXQ1cncyUUtMdU01dml2ay1R</guid></item><item><title>越南少女服用8片头痛药后几乎死于扑热息痛中毒- VnExpress International</title><link>https://e.vnexpress.net/news/news/vietnamese-teen-girl-nearly-dies-of-paracetamol-poisoning-after-taking-8-tablets-for-headache-4998896.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="fck_detail"&gt;
&lt;p class="Normal"&gt;The patient was rushed to the Cam Khe Regional Medical Center suffering from dizziness, persistent vomiting, and acute pain in the right upper abdomen, doctors said Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Normal"&gt;According to her family, she initially took three tablets, but when the pain persisted, she consumed five more, nearly exhausting an entire blister pack. It is not clear while the family failed to monitor her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Normal"&gt;Doctors diagnosed her with a severe overdose and provided intensive treatment involving antidotes and intravenous fluids, allowing her condition to stabilize after five days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Normal"&gt;While paracetamol is a common over-the-counter pain reliever, medical experts warn of a rising trend in poisoning cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Normal"&gt;Nguyen Duy Long from the center's Toxicology Department noted that while the drug is generally safe, overdoses or even therapeutic doses can be toxic for individuals who are malnourished, alcohol-dependent, or suffering from liver disease. Prolonged use or combining multiple medications containing paracetamol can lead to severe complications, including acute liver injury, liver failure, coagulation disorders, and multi-organ failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Normal"&gt;Medical recommendations state that the maximum daily dose for adults should not exceed 3.5 to 4 grams within 24 hours, with doses spaced four to six hours apart. For the standard 500 mg tablet, this equates to a maximum of six tablets per day. In children, the dosage must be strictly calculated based on body weight, typically 10–15 mg per kilogram per dose, with a daily maximum of 50–70 mg per kilogram. Parents are advised to use powder sachets or rectal suppositories when necessary, ensuring each dose is spaced at least five to six hours apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Normal"&gt;Doctor Long advises against self-medicating with excessive doses or using painkillers for prolonged periods without professional guidance. Medications should always be taken according to the specific instructions of pharmacists or healthcare workers, with a particular warning against combining different drugs that contain the same active ingredient, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Normal"&gt;Parents are urged to supervise medication use for children, store medicines safely to avoid confusion, and seek immediate medical attention if any abnormal symptoms occur after ingestion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="true" data-component-type="tin_xemthem" data-component-value="4856728,4908227,4695117,3639716,3502109" data-thumb="1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VnExpress International</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 23:04:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1wFBVV95cUxPalBiemJTamhNN19jcUIwRTVZVkdUZk5UWk83SWtpbGZJazBKMjJnWFZxbnFxelRIejdyUWxOSGZhbkdoYUo4SDlFWUpaOGE5ZTFPYTZLNV9pOWYwUGVMb0tRZXZQRF96RUNNU20ybTAzdVNySDNsLUZGak0xbW5PVWxiejJrODNDM2FTRkItbXZtLUpTaG9kNkp4emRTam1meFdGam9NMHJLdFUyUldRaE5KZ0RycEQ5QlFyV2xFbU1VVEpRSGlfSGhLay15dDFuNWx4ZVN0dw</guid></item><item><title>7天简单无糖膳食计划，改善血糖，成为营养师- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/7-day-easy-no-sugar-meal-plan-for-better-blood-sugar-11868215</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__table-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;table class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__table"&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Day&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;1&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;2&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;3&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;4&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;5&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;6&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;7&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody data-check="0"&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meals&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breakfast:&lt;/b&gt; Banana–Peanut Butter Yogurt Parfait&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Lunch:&lt;/b&gt; High-Protein White Bean Salad with Feta &amp;amp; Lemon-Garlic Vinaigrette&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Dinner:&lt;/b&gt; Salmon Power Bowl&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breakfast:&lt;/b&gt; Overnight Oats with Chia Seeds &amp;amp; kefir&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Lunch:&lt;/b&gt; Chicken Fajita Soup + orange&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Dinner:&lt;/b&gt; Roasted Potato Tzatziki Bowls&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breakfast:&lt;/b&gt; Overnight Oats with Chia Seeds &amp;amp; kefir&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Lunch:&lt;/b&gt; Chicken Fajita Soup + orange&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Dinner:&lt;/b&gt; Sheet-Pan Mojo Chicken with Green Beans &amp;amp; Potatoes + Pineapple &amp;amp; Avocado Salad&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breakfast:&lt;/b&gt; Overnight Oats with Chia Seeds &amp;amp; kefir&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Lunch:&lt;/b&gt; Chicken Fajita Soup + orange&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Dinner:&lt;/b&gt; 5-Ingredient Avocado &amp;amp; Chickpea Salad&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breakfast:&lt;/b&gt; Overnight Oats with Chia Seeds &amp;amp; kefir&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Lunch:&lt;/b&gt; Chicken Fajita Soup + orange&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Dinner:&lt;/b&gt; Chicken Parmesan Casserole + Garlicky Green Beans&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breakfast:&lt;/b&gt; Banana–Peanut Butter Yogurt Parfait&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Lunch:&lt;/b&gt; Chicken Parmesan Casserole&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Dinner:&lt;/b&gt; Shakshuka + Cabbage Caesar Salad&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breakfast:&lt;/b&gt; Banana–Peanut Butter Yogurt Parfait&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Lunch:&lt;/b&gt; Chicken Parmesan Casserole&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Dinner:&lt;/b&gt; Lemon-Garlic Baked Cod + White Bean, Spinach &amp;amp; Sun-Dried Tomato Orzo&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Daily Totals&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calories:&lt;/b&gt; 1,813&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 87g &lt;b&gt;Saturated Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 14g &lt;b&gt;Protein:&lt;/b&gt; 98g &lt;b&gt;Carb:&lt;/b&gt; 176g &lt;b&gt;Fiber:&lt;/b&gt; 38g &lt;b&gt;Sodium:&lt;/b&gt; 1,067mg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calories:&lt;/b&gt; 1,791&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 84g &lt;b&gt;Saturated Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 13g &lt;b&gt;Protein:&lt;/b&gt; 91g &lt;b&gt;Carb:&lt;/b&gt; 187g &lt;b&gt;Fiber:&lt;/b&gt; 44g &lt;b&gt;Sodium:&lt;/b&gt; 1,678mg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calories:&lt;/b&gt; 1,825&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 86g &lt;b&gt;Saturated Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 14g &lt;b&gt;Protein:&lt;/b&gt; 107g &lt;b&gt;Carb:&lt;/b&gt; 175g &lt;b&gt;Fiber:&lt;/b&gt; 42g &lt;b&gt;Sodium:&lt;/b&gt; 1,670mg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calories:&lt;/b&gt; 1,781&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 81g &lt;b&gt;Saturated Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 11g &lt;b&gt;Protein:&lt;/b&gt; 88g &lt;b&gt;Carb:&lt;/b&gt; 198g &lt;b&gt;Fiber:&lt;/b&gt; 54g &lt;b&gt;Sodium:&lt;/b&gt; 1,262mg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calories:&lt;/b&gt; 1,795&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 80g &lt;b&gt;Saturated Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 13g &lt;b&gt;Protein:&lt;/b&gt; 103g &lt;b&gt;Carb:&lt;/b&gt; 187g &lt;b&gt;Fiber:&lt;/b&gt; 46g &lt;b&gt;Sodium:&lt;/b&gt; 1,754mg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calories:&lt;/b&gt; 1,779&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 72g &lt;b&gt;Saturated Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 14g &lt;b&gt;Protein:&lt;/b&gt; 100g &lt;b&gt;Carb:&lt;/b&gt; 198g &lt;b&gt;Fiber:&lt;/b&gt; 41g &lt;b&gt;Sodium:&lt;/b&gt; 1,727mg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calories:&lt;/b&gt; 1,796&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 80g &lt;b&gt;Saturated Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 14g &lt;b&gt;Protein:&lt;/b&gt; 106g &lt;b&gt;Carb:&lt;/b&gt; 182g &lt;b&gt;Fiber:&lt;/b&gt; 39g &lt;b&gt;Sodium:&lt;/b&gt; 1,941mg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 1 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Daily Totals: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;1,813 calories, 87g fat, 14g saturated fat, 98g protein, 176g carbohydrate, 38g fiber, 1,067mg sodium.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breakfast (301 calories, 35g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lunch (416 calories, 45g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dinner (572 calories, 42g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Snacks&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;¼ cup dry-roasted almonds + 1 medium apple (301 calories, 32g carbs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Make it 1,500 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Omit ¼ cup dry-roasted almonds + 1 medium apple as a snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/252167/massaged-kale-salad/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Massaged Kale Salad&lt;/a&gt; to dinner.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 2 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,791 calories, 84g fat, 13g saturated fat, 91g protein, 187g carbohydrate, 44g fiber, 1,678mg sodium.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breakfast (453 calories, 48g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lunch (374 calories, 46g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Serve with: 1 medium orange&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dinner (514 calories, 57g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Snacks&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Make it 1,500 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Omit kefir at breakfast and omit ¼ cup dry-roasted almonds + ¼ cup blueberries as a snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Increase to 1 cup kefir at breakfast and add 1 cup edamame (in pods) to lunch.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 3 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,825 calories, 86g fat, 14g saturated fat, 107g protein, 175g carbohydrate, 42g fiber, 1,670mg sodium.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breakfast (453 calories, 48g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_63-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lunch (374 calories, 46g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_67-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_69-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_70-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dinner (599 calories, 49g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_71-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_73-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_74-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Snacks&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_75-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_77-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_78-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Make it 1,500 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Omit both the 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/white-bean-stuffed-mini-bell-peppers-8710436" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;White Bean–Stuffed Mini Bell Peppers&lt;/a&gt; and the ¼ cup dry-roasted unsalted shelled pistachios as snacks.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_79-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_80-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 1 cup edamame (in pods) to lunch.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_81-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_82-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 4 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_83-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,781 calories, 81g fat, 11g saturated fat, 88g protein, 198g carbohydrate, 54g fiber, 1,262mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_84-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_85-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breakfast (453 calories, 48g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_86-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_88-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_89-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lunch (374 calories, 46g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_90-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_92-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_93-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dinner (430 calories, 48g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_94-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_96-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_97-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Snacks&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_98-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_100-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_101-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Make it 1,500 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Omit ¼ cup dry-roasted almonds + 1 medium apple as a snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_102-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_103-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Increase to 1 cup kefir at breakfast and add 1 cup edamame (in pods) to lunch.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_104-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_105-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 5 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_106-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,795 calories, 80g fat, 13g saturated fat, 103g protein, 187g carbohydrate, 46g fiber, 1,754mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_107-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_108-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breakfast (453 calories, 48g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_109-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_111-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_112-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lunch (374 calories, 46g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_113-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_115-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_116-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dinner (497 calories, 52g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_117-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_119-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_120-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Snacks&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_121-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_123-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_124-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Make it 1,500 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Omit orange at lunch and omit ¼ cup dry-roasted almonds + ½ cup blueberries as a snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_125-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_126-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Increase to 1 cup kefir at breakfast and add 1 cup edamame (in pods) to lunch.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_127-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_128-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 6 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_129-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,779 calories, 72g fat, 14g saturated fat, 100g protein, 198g carbohydrate, 41g fiber, 1,727mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_130-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_131-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breakfast (301 calories, 35g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_132-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_134-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_135-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lunch (412 calories, 43g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_136-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_138-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_139-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dinner (475 calories, 44g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_140-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_142-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_143-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Snacks&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_144-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_146-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_148-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_149-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 cup edamame (in pods) + 1 medium apple (274 calories, 47g carbs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_150-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_151-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Make it 1,500 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Omit 1 cup edamame (in pods) + 1 medium apple as a snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_152-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_153-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add ¼ cup dry-roasted unsalted almonds to lunch.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_154-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_155-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 7 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_156-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,796 calories, 80g fat, 14g saturated fat, 106g protein, 182g carbohydrate, 39g fiber, 1,941mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_157-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_158-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breakfast (301 calories, 35g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_159-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_161-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_162-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lunch (412 calories, 43g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_163-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_165-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_166-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dinner (559 calories, 49g carbs)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_167-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_169-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_170-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Snacks&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_171-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_173-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_174-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Make it 1,500 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Omit ¼ cup dry-roasted almonds + 1 medium apple as a snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_175-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_176-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 1 cup nonfat plain kefir to breakfast and 1 cup cherries to lunch.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_177-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_178-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-faq mntl-sc-block-universal-faq"&gt;&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-faqs-e1bd0be7-415a-471d-af86-9dae361720eb"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__title"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;noscript id="universal-faq-noscript_1-0" class="comp universal-faq-noscript mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content mntl-accordion js-accordion"&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="1"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_1-0-section-0"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;​​Is it OK to mix and match meals if there is one I do not like?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, feel free to mix and match meals if there's one you don’t like. Because we created this meal plan with healthy blood sugar in mind, you may want to choose a meal with a similar nutritional profile, particularly as it pertains to calories, carbohydrates, fiber and protein. You can feel free to repeat a meal in this list or browse some of our other &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipes/17899/health-condition/diabetic/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;healthy diabetes-friendly recipes&lt;/a&gt; for additional inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="2"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_2-0-section-1"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Can I eat the same breakfast or lunch every day?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_2-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, you can eat the same breakfast or lunch every day if you prefer. Each breakfast ranges from 301 to 453 calories and 35 to 48 grams of carbs. Lunch options span 374 to 416 calories and 43 to 46 grams of carbohydrates. These ranges are fairly similar, so a simple swap should work for most people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="3"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_3-0-section-2"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Why is there not a modification for 1,200 calories?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_3-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We no longer provide modifications for 1,200-calorie days in our meal plans. The 2020-2025 Dietary Guidelines for Americans suggests that limiting calories to 1,200 per day is too low for most people to meet their nutritional needs, plus it’s unsustainable for long-term health and well-being.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="4"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_4-0-section-3"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;How many carbs should I eat per day?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_4-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no one-size-fits-all recommendation for how many carbs you should eat per day.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Factors like body size and activity level can impact how your blood sugar responds to carbohydrates.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Paying attention to how your blood sugar reacts to the foods you eat can help clue you in to the best routine for your body. For more individualized recommendations, consider reaching out to a registered dietitian or certified diabetes educator for guidance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;noscript id="accordion-noscript_1-0" class="comp accordion-noscript mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_179-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-tips-for-healthy-blood-sugar-levels"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_180-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Tips for Healthy Blood Sugar Levels &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_181-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t Overlook Your Heart Health&lt;/strong&gt;: People with type 2 diabetes are twice as likely to be diagnosed with heart disease compared to people without.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; When eating for better blood sugars, consider the impact on your heart health as well. Strategies like increasing fiber and keeping an eye on saturated fat and sodium can help protect your heart.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pair Protein With Carbs&lt;/strong&gt;: To prevent blood sugar spikes and promote more stable levels, aim to pair carbohydrates with protein.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Research shows that this strategy results in lower blood sugar levels compared to a carbohydrate consumed without a protein source.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; To do this in practice, pair a carbohydrate food, like fruit, with a protein source such as nuts, edamame, peanut butter, cottage cheese, yogurt or a hard-boiled egg.  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limit Added Sugar&lt;/strong&gt;: Because total added sugar intake can increase the risk of developing type 2 diabetes, it may be helpful to take inventory of where added sugars may be making their way in your routine.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; While we opted to skip added sugar entirely in this plan, that’s not necessary or sustainable for most people long-term. Instead, aim to follow the American Heart Association's recommendation of limiting added sugar to 9 teaspoons (36 grams) for men and 6 teaspoons (25 grams) for women.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; In addition to dessert items, things like sweetened drinks, flavored yogurt, cereals, granola bars, granola and many prepared foods are common sources of added sugar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot-inline"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pump Up the Fiber&lt;/strong&gt;: Fiber is a type of indigestible carbohydrate that can help promote better blood sugar and improve heart health - a win-win!&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Fiber-rich foods travel through the digestive system slower than refined grains and added sugar, which means it can help you feel fuller for longer and promote a steadier release of glucose, resulting in more stable blood sugar.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Fiber-rich foods include whole-grains, fruits, vegetables, nuts, seeds and legumes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Include Physical Activity&lt;/strong&gt;: The American Diabetes Association recommends people aim for 150 minutes a week of moderate-intensity exercise a week.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; While that’s a great goal to aim for, don’t fret if you’re not there yet. Research shows that walking for just two to five minutes after a meal can help reduce blood sugar levels, further proving that small daily habits can lead to big impacts on health.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_182-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_183-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-generic" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;How We Create Meal Plans&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Registered dietitians thoughtfully create EatingWell’s meal plans to be easy-to-follow and delicious. Each meal plan meets specific parameters depending on the health condition and/or lifestyle goal it is targeting and is analyzed for accuracy using the nutrition database, ESHA Food Processor. As nutritional needs differ from person to person, we encourage you to use these plans as inspiration and adjust as you see fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPRVZ2Tm00RHcxYVdpUkRqc29oQlVRLTU1YV85WHlBR29XNUJCYTVGNmVyYmZYU2locy1XTnQ4Y3hyRThxQmh2bUxucWFiLUoxVk5lS2F1cWVEdWNVY19GLUt6c1BJSXRCdzVXVVlNMGtBR0I5U2VqSlo3XzhyY1R2X1dYakZLLTVEV0hDYzl5N01tZw</guid></item><item><title>看起来总是比实际年龄年轻的人的7个日常习惯-硅运河</title><link>https://siliconcanals.com/x-bt-7-daily-habits-of-people-who-always-seem-years-younger-than-their-actual-age/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Silicon Canals</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 21:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxNQ2h5cEV1bEVhQXFnNS1BTGZIcjNpWUVtRGc1S2tUUFZ2ZTFNVml5SEdwbENsNkc2dmMxekhTOEMwMmJvUHhobGJ3cEd1RldfODlOWEQzWmJ2QTAwYUNwZlFLUlpOQTl4UTVnalZEcnJQOHFTQmY2czRIWEVYWUR1QTk2WE50am1obUc1ZkhoZEswNlhUc1Q2eGxmdHI2N2FUUXl6dmg3enlITmlW</guid></item><item><title>澳大利亚标志着“假”狂犬病刺戳；印度制造商反驳声称- Tribune India</title><link>https://www.tribuneindia.com/news/india/australia-flags-fake-rabies-jab-indian-manufacturer-counters-claim/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="story-detail" class="story_detail2180739 headlessuser hldAlpha" data-guid="2180739"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australian health authorities have raised concerns over alleged counterfeit versions of the rabies vaccine Abhayrab in India, prompting a response from its manufacturer, Indian Immunologicals (IIL). The company clarified that the issue pertained to a single batch identified in January 2025 and did not merit a blanket warning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company strongly refuted the “over-cautionary and misplaced reference” to 2023 made in the recent Australian advisory, stressing that it “does not reflect the current situation”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abhayrab has been manufactured by IIL since 2000, with over 210 million doses supplied across India and 40 countries. It continues to hold a 40 per cent market share in India.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week, the Australian Technical Advisory Group on Immunisation (ATAGI) advised that Australian travellers who received the anti-rabies vaccine Abhayrab in India after November 1, 2023, should consider the vaccination invalid and start a new course. In January 2025, IIL proactively identified a packaging anomaly in one specific batch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A company official said, “The company immediately notified Indian regulators and law enforcement agencies, lodged a formal complaint and worked closely with authorities to ensure swift action. Importantly, this was an isolated incident and the counterfeit batch is no longer available on shelves.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inbtw_content_maindiv"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IIL emphasised that every batch of vaccine manufactured in India was tested and released by the Central Drugs Laboratory before being made available for sale or administration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sunil Tiwari, vice-president &amp;amp; head of quality management, IIL, said the company aimed to reassure stakeholders that its pharmacovigilance and quality systems were robust and the public could continue to trust vaccines supplied directly by IIL and its authorised channels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Tribune India</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 20:30:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxQUDhEZVdxeFJVMk01c0lFZnNuM0YxUF9KUVhQX0hlOTJrR2I0OVdPMnI3NUdmcXhqLUZ5UldWUW5FVllvd3dOd3F5LW43MFZVRFE0TkFNSG9SYUNZdlJ6VjQxZlpGYkxWUFhXSHdVQ0k5T0FDVF8zdVdYdGE3UklBZDFGcjY0bjJnRFd6bEJpZDhZZE4zTHJDZWZOWThUdHluQVUybE10VjNBNlXSAa8BQVVfeXFMTnFIaDRYRFExU21HUHNKeS1Bb2IxUmVQaHpqM3hDTUtkQ1gxclBBUmlzVlVaOE9Gek5uTTZybnJNaDdtUDR1dWJiQUk4a0xWTjAzd1NLNXY2YUIwRWg1dnRSZTBBVjhvUnRHUjFLYVk2aHJVRXNubDF5X3MzSkhadjM0VC1QcWQzT2tITk9sRzloMktkZlVrZUppUDNVeFIta3Q2UFM3OEdxTG9idlVTRQ</guid></item><item><title>一位胃肠病学家说，这种受欢迎的食物正在严重破坏您的肠道- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/gastroenterologist-says-popular-food-wreaking-183000546.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;Avoid This Popular Food for Better Gut Health&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;d3sign - Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Hearst Magazines and Yahoo may earn commission or revenue on some items through these links."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maintaining a &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a69771726/symptoms-of-unhealthy-gut/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:healthy gut;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;healthy gut&lt;/a&gt; and digestive tract has much wider implications for your health than just avoiding GI woes. Fortunately, making simple changes to your diet, such as limiting your intake of a popular food that’s wreaking havoc on your gut, may make a big difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meet the experts: &lt;a href="https://www.medicalofficesofmanhattan.com/our-team/pratima-dibba-md/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Pratima Dibba, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Pratima Dibba, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a gastroenterologist with Medical Offices of Manhattan; &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fletsliveitup.com%2Fpages%2Flena-bakovic&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.prevention.com%2Fhealth%2Fa69849055%2Ffood-impacting-gut%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Lena Bakovic, M.S., R.D.N., C.N.S.C.;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Lena Bakovic, M.S., R.D.N., C.N.S.C.&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian nutritionist at Live It Up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Issues with gut health can have a systemic effect on the body,” &lt;a href="https://www.medicalofficesofmanhattan.com/our-team/pratima-dibba-md/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Pratima Dibba, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Pratima Dibba, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a gastroenterologist with Medical Offices of Manhattan, previously told &lt;em&gt;Prevention&lt;/em&gt;. “When gut health is not prioritized, it can result in systemic symptoms that impede quality of life and also result in long-term complications.” Here, experts share the food that’s hurting your gut (and thus, your overall health), plus other foods you to limit or avoid that may be harming your gut health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The top food wreaking havoc on your gut&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The experts we spoke to agree that the number-one food that could be hurting your gut is highly processed and/or sugary drinks, such as soda and energy drinks. Dr. Dibba explains that processed foods, especially those that are acidic, may damage the gut lining—the barrier that absorbs water and nutrients while preventing toxins and partially digested food from making it to the bloodstream. When the gut lining is damaged, it may cause a condition called leaky gut, which the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/22724-leaky-gut-syndrome" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cleveland Clinic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt; says may play a role in the development of digestive conditions, autoimmune diseases, metabolic disorders, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Regular sodas are a source of empty calories with no nutritive value,” adds &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fletsliveitup.com%2Fpages%2Flena-bakovic&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.prevention.com%2Fhealth%2Fa69849055%2Ffood-impacting-gut%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Lena Bakovic, M.S., R.D.N., C.N.S.C.;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Lena Bakovic, M.S., R.D.N., C.N.S.C.&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian nutritionist at Live It Up. “Foods which are high in added sugars promote an imbalance of healthy bacteria and promote overgrowth of harmful gut bacteria.” That’s a big problem, according to a study in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10699709/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Infectious Medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Infectious Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, which linked an unbalanced microbiome to &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a64770566/how-to-thrive-with-type-2-diabetes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:type 2 diabetes;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, obesity, non-alcoholic liver disease, cardiometabolic diseases, cancer, arthritis, &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a65597974/surprising-symptoms-of-depression/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:depression;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt;, sleep disorders, and &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a69190458/high-blood-pressure-causes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:hypertension;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;hypertension&lt;/a&gt;. It’s not just the sugar-laden options, either: &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a60672537/artificial-sweeteners-may-damage-gut-health-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Research suggests;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Research suggests&lt;/a&gt; that artificial sweeteners may also be damaging to gut health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drinking soda and energy drinks may mean you are not sipping as much water, which also negatively affects your gut health. A 2024 study in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2589004224011258" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:iScience;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;iScience&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;found that &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a65938943/how-much-water-you-should-drink-per-day/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:drinking enough water;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;drinking enough water&lt;/a&gt; is essential for avoiding digestive issues like constipation, plus for maintaining a balanced microbiome and healthy immune system (much of which is housed in the gut).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Other gut-harming foods to avoid&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to processed drinks, Bakovic and Dr. Dibba suggest limiting your intake of the following foods to protect the health of your gut:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Candy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baked goods&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fruit juice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alcohol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spicy foods&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excessive caffeine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:42:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxNQkxFZXNZYldoSGxHMS1BdGstcFBWNE9scDRGdk1rdXhYZ0o2NThSaXhiTXpzOWFVX1Iyd2xxb2FXektmcHBTYWFKa0FoZHJmaGNIX0ZHQVR6QVhDa241NUpOWUtrbTNBeU81M2UtZWRzbV9uUTZuOTNLU1RfcW5Pczg3dWtnVkthS3RIRXJ6cXlrTEk</guid></item><item><title>研究找到逆转阿尔茨海默氏症的方法-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://neurosciencenews.com/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-30070/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;A new study challenges the long-held belief that Alzheimer’s disease cannot be reversed. Researchers showed that a severe drop in NAD+—a core energy molecule—drives Alzheimer’s pathology in both human brains and mouse models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Restoring proper NAD+ balance with the drug P7C3-A20 not only prevented disease in at-risk mice but also reversed advanced pathology, repairing brain damage and fully restoring cognitive function. The findings point to a major shift in how Alzheimer’s may be treated, suggesting that recovery—not just slowing decline—could one day be achievable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Central NAD+ Failure:&lt;/strong&gt; Human and mouse Alzheimer’s brains showed a dramatic loss of NAD+, impairing essential cellular functions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reversal Achieved:&lt;/strong&gt; Restoring NAD+ balance repaired pathology and fully recovered cognition even in mice with advanced disease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Treatment Pathway:&lt;/strong&gt; The targeted drug P7C3-A20 restored healthy NAD+ levels without the dangers linked to over-the-counter NAD+ boosters.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;University Hospital Cleveland Medical Center&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For over a century, Alzheimer’s disease (AD) has been considered irreversible. Consequently, research has focused on disease prevention or slowing, rather than recovery. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite billions of dollars spent on decades of research, there has never been a clinical trial of a drug for AD with an outcome goal of reversing disease and recovering function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-114448"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows an older woman and neurons." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/alzheimers-reversed-neuropharmacology-neuroscience-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;After finding that NAD+ levels in the brain declined precipitously in both human and mouse AD, the research team tested whether preventing the loss of brain NAD+ balance before disease onset, or restoring brain NAD+ balance after significant disease progression, could prevent or reverse AD, respectively. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, a research team from University Hospitals, Case Western Reserve University, and the Louis Stokes Cleveland VA Medical Center has challenged this long-held dogma in the field. They tested whether brains already badly afflicted with advanced AD could recover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, led by Kalyani Chaubey, PhD, from the Pieper Laboratory, published today in &lt;em&gt;Cell Reports Medicine&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Through studying diverse preclinical mouse models and human AD brains, the team showed that the brain’s failure to maintain normal levels of a central cellular energy molecule, NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt;, is a major driver of AD, and that maintaining proper NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; balance can prevent and even reverse the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; levels decline naturally across the body, including the brain, as people age. Without proper NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; balance, cells eventually become unable to execute critical processes required for proper functioning and survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this study, the team showed that the decline in NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; is even more severe in the brains of people with AD, and that this also occurs in mouse models of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While AD is a uniquely human condition, it can be studied in the laboratory with mice that have been engineered to express genetic mutations that cause AD in people. The researchers used two of these models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One line of mice carried multiple human mutations in amyloid processing, and the other mouse line carried a human mutation in the tau protein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amyloid and tau pathology are two of the major early events in AD, and both lines of mice develop brain pathology resembling AD, including blood-brain barrier deterioration, axonal degeneration, neuroinflammation, impaired hippocampal neurogenesis, reduced synaptic transmission, and widespread accumulation of oxidative damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These mice also develop severe cognitive impairments that resemble what is seen in people with AD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After finding that NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; levels in the brain declined precipitously in both human and mouse AD, the research team tested whether preventing the loss of brain NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; balance before disease onset, or restoring brain NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; balance after significant disease progression, could prevent or reverse AD, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was based on their previous work, published in &lt;em&gt;Proceeding of the National Academy of Sciences USA,&lt;/em&gt; showing that restoring the brain’s NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; balance achieved pathological and functional recovery after severe, long-lasting traumatic brain injury.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They restored NAD+ balance by administering a now well-characterized pharmacologic agent known as P7C3-A20, developed in the Pieper lab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remarkably, not only did preserving NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; balance protect mice from developing AD, but delayed treatment in mice with advanced disease also enabled the brain to fix the major pathological events caused by the genetic mutations. Moreover, both lines of mice fully recovered cognitive function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was accompanied by normalized blood levels of phosphorylated tau 217, a recently approved clinical biomarker of AD in people, providing confirmation of disease reversal and highlighting a potential biomarker for future clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We were very excited and encouraged by our results,” said Andrew A. Pieper, MD, PhD, senior author of the study and Director of the Brain Health Medicines Center, Harrington Discovery Institute at UH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; “Restoring the brain’s energy balance achieved pathological and functional recovery in both lines of mice with advanced Alzheimer’s. Seeing this effect in two very different animal models, each driven by different genetic causes, strengthens the idea that restoring the brain’s NAD+ balance might help patients recover from Alzheimer’s.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Pieper also holds the Morley-Mather Chair in Neuropsychiatry at UH and the CWRU Rebecca E. Barchas, MD, DLFAPA, University Professorship in Translational Psychiatry. He serves as Psychiatrist and Investigator in the Louis Stokes VA Geriatric Research Education and Clinical Center (GRECC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results prompt a paradigm shift in how researchers, clinicians, and patients can think about treating AD in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The key takeaway is a message of hope – the effects of Alzheimer’s disease may not be inevitably permanent,” said Dr. Pieper. “The damaged brain can, under some conditions, repair itself and regain function.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Chaubey further explained, “Through our study, we demonstrated one drug-based way to accomplish this in animal models, and also identified candidate proteins in the human AD brain that may relate to the ability to reverse AD.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Pieper emphasized that currently available over the counter NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt;-precursors have been shown in animal models to raise cellular NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; to dangerously high levels that promote cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The approach in this study, however, uses a pharmacologic agent (P7C3-A20) that enables cells to maintain their proper balance of NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; under conditions of otherwise overwhelming stress, without elevating NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; to supraphysiologic levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is important when considering patient care, and clinicians should consider the possibility that therapeutic strategies aimed at restoring brain energy balance might offer a path to disease recovery,” said Dr. Pieper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This work also encourages new research into complementary approaches and eventual testing in patients, and the technology is being commercialized by Cleveland-based company Glengary Brain Health, co-founded by Dr. Pieper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This new therapeutic approach to recovery needs to be moved into carefully designed human clinical trials to determine whether the efficacy seen in animal models translates to human patients,” Dr. Pieper explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Additional next steps for the laboratory research include pinpointing which aspects of brain energy balance are most important for recovery, identifying and evaluating complementary approaches to Alzheimer’s reversal, and investigating whether this recovery approach is also effective in other forms of chronic, age-related neurodegenerative disease.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Key Questions Answered:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq wp-block-yoast-faq-block"&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1766864151217"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: What did researchers discover about NAD+ in Alzheimer’s disease?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; They found that a severe decline in NAD+ is a major driver of Alzheimer’s pathology, disrupting energy balance and damaging key brain systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1766864152647"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Can restoring NAD+ actually reverse advanced Alzheimer’s effects?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes. In two distinct Alzheimer’s mouse models, restoring NAD+ balance repaired structural and functional brain damage and fully restored cognitive performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1766864152431"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Why is P7C3-A20 different from common NAD+ supplements?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; Over-the-counter NAD+ precursors can push NAD+ to unsafe levels, but P7C3-A20 helps the brain maintain proper NAD+ balance under stress without causing harmful elevations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Editorial Notes:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list has-background"&gt;&lt;li&gt;This article was edited by a Neuroscience News editor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Journal paper reviewed in full.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Additional context added by our staff.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this Alzheimer’s disease research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#01606f726d64782f6a646d6c417469696e72716875606d722f6e7366" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Ansley Kelm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;Source: &lt;a href="https://uhhospitals.org" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;University Hospitals Cleveland Medical Center&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact: Ansley Kelm – University Hospitals Cleveland Medical Center&lt;br&gt;Image: The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.xcrm.2025.102535" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Pharmacologic reversal of Alzheimer’s disease in mice reveals potential therapeutic nodes in human brain&lt;/a&gt;” by Kalyani Chaubey et al. &lt;em&gt;Cell Reports Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pharmacologic reversal of Alzheimer’s disease in mice reveals potential therapeutic nodes in human brain&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer’s disease (AD) is traditionally considered irreversible. Here, however, we provide proof of principle for therapeutic reversibility of advanced AD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In advanced disease amyloid-driven 5xFAD mice, treatment with P7C3-A20, which restores nicotinamide adenine dinucleotide (NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt;) homeostasis, reverses tau phosphorylation, blood-brain barrier deterioration, oxidative stress, DNA damage, and neuroinflammation and enhances hippocampal neurogenesis and synaptic plasticity, resulting in full cognitive recovery and reduction of plasma levels of the clinical AD biomarker p-tau217.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;P7C3-A20 also reverses advanced disease in tau-driven PS19 mice and protects human brain microvascular endothelial cells from oxidative stress. In humans and mice, pathology severity correlates with disruption of brain NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; homeostasis, and the brains of nondemented people with Alzheimer’s neuropathology exhibit gene expression patterns suggestive of preserved NAD&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; homeostasis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forty-six proteins aberrantly expressed in advanced 5xFAD mouse brain and normalized by P7C3-A20 show similar alterations in human AD brain, revealing targets with potential for optimizing translation to patient care.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:41:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFBXeHI4RXRfalQ5MVEyZmlucDdQV1dZWGlBTTAwd3JBZGVvU1ZrY3NxUEJORVR2LXlVS0dYRDdKeUJzbWE0czJ6Q2xXVXV1OEdjS3pVN05hMEswMk1HTHBNUUFDOThYaU1neUJ4dE96dnY2V0xUMFNKckpDVU8xUQ</guid></item><item><title>女人的妈妈不可信，最终假装心脏病发作，所以她的女儿拒绝拨打911 ，让她忍受后果- TwistedSifter</title><link>https://twistedsifter.com/2025/12/womans-mom-fakes-a-heart-attack-so-her-daughter-refuses-to-call-911-and-leaves/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article"&gt;
						
						&lt;div id="attachment_685715" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-685715" class="wp-image-685715" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="upset woman sitting in window seat" title="Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-09T143801.846.png" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-09T143801.846.png 1200w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-09T143801.846.png?resize=150,79 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-09T143801.846.png?resize=300,158 300w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-09T143801.846.png?resize=768,403 768w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-09T143801.846.png?resize=1024,538 1024w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-09T143801.846.png?resize=586,308 586w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-685715" class="wp-image-685715" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-09T143801.846.png" alt="upset woman sitting in window seat" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-09T143801.846.png 1200w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-09T143801.846.png?resize=150,79 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-09T143801.846.png?resize=300,158 300w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-09T143801.846.png?resize=768,403 768w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-09T143801.846.png?resize=1024,538 1024w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-09T143801.846.png?resize=586,308 586w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;p id="caption-attachment-685715" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Pexels/Reddit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What would you do if a family member constantly pretended that had a medical problem, but you knew they were just faking it for attention?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mm-player"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Would you humor them and call 911, or would you ignore the situation?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AmItheAsshole/comments/1pek061/aita_for_not_calling_an_ambulance_for_my_mother/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;In this story&lt;/a&gt;, one woman is in this exact situation with her mother, and she refused to call 911. Now, she wondering if that was the wrong decision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s read the whole story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;AITA for not calling an ambulance for my mother?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My (20f) mother (55f) is a narcissist. It’s become worse as I’ve gotten older, but basically, she has to make everything about herself always.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She’s always twisting someone else’s problems to make it about her or lying about the dumbest stuff to gain attention or screaming and fake crying when someone says she’s in the wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She’s a complete attention seeker, and I’m convinced she has a personally disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But her mother is convinced she has other medical problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, she’s taken to faking medical issues or illness to get attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She’s done this before like faking a gluten allergy despite still eating gluten with no problems, or pretending to have the most obviously fake panic attack when being called out for her nonsense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, it seems, that isn’t enough, and for the past few weeks, she’s been talking about being diagnosed with heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was an argument at dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today we had dinner and my brother (25m) told us that he wanted to marry his girlfriend (just said it casually, not like he actually proposed yet or anything).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mom doesn’t like brother’s girlfriend ever since they started dating (even though she’s only meet her a handful of times), and decided to get into a screaming-match about it with my brother.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He wasn’t having any of it, and just got up and walked out of the room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I went with him because, jokes on me if I’m going to stay with her when she’s like that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their mother’s next move was pretty extreme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, she then ‘fainted’, making pain-noises, while writhing on the ground. I think she was trying to imitate a seizure while conscious? IDK but she looked like a fish flopping around crazily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My brother and I just stared at her, as it honestly looked like an adult throwing a tantrum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She told us she was having a heart attack and to call 911.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When neither of us did, she screamed that we were selfish children letting her die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was definitely faking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;We didn’t end up leaving then, but we did stay to see what she’d do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After neither of us really reacted for a few minutes, she got up, totally fine, but was mad at us for not helping her and started screaming again about how we’re abusing her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then brother and I left for real, and went to his girlfriend’s house. That’s where I am now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, she’s wondering if she should’ve called 911.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apparently she posted on Facebook about how she survived her heart attack, while berating my brother and me for not caring about her and being emotionally abusive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My aunt (not actually my aunt but mom’s best friend), messaged me and my brother about it and I told her what happened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She said I should have just called 911 anyway because it wasn’t my place to say and they could have determined if she was really fine or not, but I’m so sick of her lying nonsense and I’m not wasting 911’s time on this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So AITA because I didn’t call them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Calling 911 would’ve been a waste of time for 911. She did the right thing. Her mom needs therapy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s see how Reddit reacted to this story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This person would’ve called 911.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-685716" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 09 at 2.34.44 PM Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" title="Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.44-PM.png" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.44-PM.png 498w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.44-PM.png?resize=133,150 133w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.44-PM.png?resize=266,300 266w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-685716" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.44-PM.png" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 09 at 2.34.44 PM Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.44-PM.png 498w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.44-PM.png?resize=133,150 133w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.44-PM.png?resize=266,300 266w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another person would’ve handled it differently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-685717" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 09 at 2.34.56 PM Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" title="Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.56-PM.png" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.56-PM.png 412w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.56-PM.png?resize=150,74 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.56-PM.png?resize=300,147 300w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-685717" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.56-PM.png" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 09 at 2.34.56 PM Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.56-PM.png 412w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.56-PM.png?resize=150,74 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.34.56-PM.png?resize=300,147 300w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s a vote for going no contact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-685718" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 09 at 2.35.10 PM Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" title="Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.10-PM.png" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.10-PM.png 494w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.10-PM.png?resize=119,150 119w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.10-PM.png?resize=238,300 238w" data-lazy-sizes="auto, (max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-685718" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.10-PM.png" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 09 at 2.35.10 PM Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.10-PM.png 494w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.10-PM.png?resize=119,150 119w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.10-PM.png?resize=238,300 238w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a good idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-685719" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 09 at 2.35.27 PM Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" title="Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.27-PM.png" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.27-PM.png 502w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.27-PM.png?resize=109,150 109w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.27-PM.png?resize=218,300 218w" data-lazy-sizes="auto, (max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-685719" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.27-PM.png" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 09 at 2.35.27 PM Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.27-PM.png 502w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.27-PM.png?resize=109,150 109w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.27-PM.png?resize=218,300 218w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s another vote for going no contact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-685720" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 09 at 2.35.53 PM Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" title="Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.53-PM.png" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.53-PM.png 504w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.53-PM.png?resize=87,150 87w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.53-PM.png?resize=174,300 174w" data-lazy-sizes="auto, (max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-685720" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.53-PM.png" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 09 at 2.35.53 PM Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.53-PM.png 504w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.53-PM.png?resize=87,150 87w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-09-at-2.35.53-PM.png?resize=174,300 174w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Womans Mom Cant Be Trusted And Eventually Fakes A Heart Attack, So Her Daughter Refuses To Call 911 And Leaves Her To Suffer The Consequences"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her mother needs serious help but not an ambulance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you liked this post, you might want to read this story about &lt;a href="https://twistedsifter.com/2023/11/teacher-taught-schools-administration-a-lesson-after-they-tried-to-make-a-sick-kid-take-a-final-exam/?utm_source=IN-ARTICLE&amp;amp;utm_medium=IN-ARTICLE&amp;amp;utm_campaign=IN-ARTICLE" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;a teacher who taught the school’s administration a lesson after they made a sick kid take a final exam&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

						
						 	
						

						
												
						
						
						
					&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TwistedSifter</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:18:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQSmhST01LNVp0cGV6Z3UtRlM5NFVHS3BKSXBneWF5cWw5Q21Jb05GZ1pSbWU0ZkhoS25CTGZhcXRWMFAyY2RqUWpFSF9ZUVhiaUdLMWVZU3pISkpEZEp1VE5EaHJxU3p3SlV2QTVCLTBpcVAyWFI5QjRrQmVaSE0xVmpHNFpMb1BveFViUUI0aDhEajRYVEtUdWdqNWhjQTNMZDdPQ1F0ZnZkYVc4dEttWWwtSQ</guid></item><item><title>新的研究揭示了咖啡和巧克力中的一种有益化合物--《波士顿环球报》</title><link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/12/27/lifestyle/coffee-and-chocolate-aging-study/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body | gutter_16--desktop gutter_16--tablet paywalled_content
              "&gt;&lt;ul class="list |  list_unstyled list_counter_reset unordered font_size_18"&gt;&lt;li class="list_counter_increment flex align_items_base"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The researchers used data from participants in two groups: 509 women from the TwinsUK cohort; and 1,160 men and women from the KORA group in Germany. Both groups had an average age of 60.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="list_counter_increment flex align_items_base"&gt;&lt;span&gt;They measured the amount of theobromine in the participants’ blood and analyzed their DNA using models that estimate aging based on molecular biomarkers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="list_counter_increment flex align_items_base"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The researchers discovered that higher levels of theobromine in the blood was associated with a reduced pace of aging, as seen by two of these “clocks.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="list_counter_increment flex align_items_base"&gt;&lt;span&gt;When the team investigated whether other substances in dark chocolate had that effect, they found the link persisted only with theobromine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="flex align_items_base justify_space_between heading-container"&gt;&lt;h3 id="can_dark_chocolate_really_affect_cellular_aging" class="heading | bold font_secondary gutter_20_0--mobile 
             padding_top_24"&gt;Can dark chocolate really affect cellular aging?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Much of how we age is determined by our genes. But epigenetic factors such as our behaviors, environments and diets can turn some genes on or shut others off through different processes. One such mechanism is DNA methylation, the focus of the new study.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“What we were looking for here are the chemical ‘tags’ that can be added onto your DNA,” said Jordana Bell, a professor in epigenomics at King’s College London and the lead author of the study.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Consider it the “grammar” of your genome, said José M. Ordovás, a senior scientist and leader of the Precision Nutrition &amp;amp; Healthy Aging directive at Tufts University who was not involved in the study. These markers don’t alter the fixed sequence of your DNA, but the tags (like punctuation marks) affect how they are expressed,&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;DNA methylation patterns also shift with age, allowing for the development of epigenetic clocks that estimate biological (rather than chronological) age.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Using these clocks to compare epigenetic markers of aging among the study participants, the researchers found a link between higher levels of theobromine in the blood and reduced signs of cellular aging.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;After running further tests to see whether other cocoa components - including caffeine - showed similar patterns, Bell and her team discovered it occurred only with theobromine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“What our results are suggesting is that [theobromine] might be affecting the activity of genes,” Bell said. “And then that contributes to aging and health.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;It’s also possible that something synergistic is going on with the theobromine and other chocolate components they &lt;i&gt;didn’t &lt;/i&gt;measure in the study, such as polyphenols, Bell said. These anti-inflammatory compounds, which are also found in dark chocolate, are linked to better brain function, a more varied gut microbiome, and lower risks of conditions such as cancer, heart disease and diabetes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="flex align_items_base justify_space_between heading-container"&gt;&lt;h3 id="what_are_the_study_limitations" class="heading | bold font_secondary gutter_20_0--mobile 
             padding_top_24"&gt;What are the study limitations?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;While the findings are interesting - and who &lt;i&gt;doesn’t&lt;/i&gt; want to hope that their favorite treat might be a fountain of youth - there are a few limitations to recognize before you eat up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The study didn’t dig into diet, so it’s not clear whether people had high levels of theobromine because of chocolate. “They did not measure the intake of chocolate; they looked at a biomarker of something that is &lt;i&gt;in&lt;/i&gt; chocolate," Ordovás said. One of the sample groups did complete a food questionnaire that asked how frequently the participants ate chocolate, but it didn’t delve into specifics such as what kind they were eating, the percentage of cocoa it had, or how much of it they ate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The data also comes from one single point in time, so the study wasn’t able to see how theobromine levels over weeks, months or years might relate to aging rates, Bell said. “You need to see things moving one time after another,” Ordovás said. “That brings more confidence.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;And epigenetic clocks aren’t set in stone. “These are dynamic estimates,” Bell said. “It just means that at this point in time, looking at your DNA, we estimate that you seem to be aging a little bit slower or faster than we would expect based on your chronological age.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;This is a good thing because you can use this knowledge to guide diet or other health interventions to change your biological age estimate, she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="flex align_items_base justify_space_between heading-container"&gt;&lt;h3 id="what_does_this_mean_for_choosing_chocolate" class="heading | bold font_secondary gutter_20_0--mobile 
             padding_top_24"&gt;What does this mean for choosing chocolate?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The findings about theobromine add to what we know about the other health-promoting compounds in dark chocolate, such as polyphenols. And here are some recommendations about dark chocolate from Alexis Supan, an outpatient dietitian at the Bariatric &amp;amp; Metabolic Institute with the Cleveland Clinic:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="list |  list_unstyled list_counter_reset unordered font_size_18"&gt;&lt;li class="list_counter_increment flex align_items_base"&gt;&lt;span&gt;While anything above 50 percent cocoa solids can be considered “dark” chocolate, that range is a big one, and you’d probably be better served aiming for 70 percent or greater.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="list_counter_increment flex align_items_base"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The higher the percentage, the more bitter it will be, but it will also bring a higher concentration of the beneficial compounds and less of the “not-so-healthy things like the saturated fat and the sugar.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="list_counter_increment flex align_items_base"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Make sure that cocoa is the first ingredient listed on the label. Ideally, you’d want just three ingredients: cocoa, sugar and cocoa butter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="list_counter_increment flex align_items_base"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Choose chocolate that isn’t Dutch-processed, which is sometimes listed on the label. This alkalization process mellows its flavor, but also strips away some of the polyphenols. “You’re not getting quite as much antioxidant power,” Supan said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="list_counter_increment flex align_items_base"&gt;&lt;span&gt;For balance in your diet, keep the rest of your daily added sugar in check. A one-ounce serving of dark chocolate can provide about one-third of the daily upper limit for women and one-quarter for men.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="list_counter_increment flex align_items_base"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dark chocolate can contain higher levels of harmful metals such as cadmium and lead, which are riskier for pregnant people or younger children, Supan said. Consumer Reports has a list of levels in many popular brands, so you can make an informed decision.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;As long as the chocolate fits this criteria, what form you choose to consume it in, whether in a mug or bar, shouldn’t matter. But when used in baking - say, that dark chocolate cake or rich, gooey cookies - keep in mind that the cocoa is competing with ingredients such as butter, sugar and flour, so you’re probably taking in less of the good products, Supan said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Her tip for the holidays? Try a dark chocolate bark. You can make it festive with some fruit and nuts, but you’ll still be getting a solid dose of the actual dark chocolate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Finally, if you aren’t a fan of chocolate, don’t force yourself to eat it simply for some type of cellular benefits that theobromine might bring. After all, “methylation is involved in aging, but it is a tiny percentage compared with all the many other factors,” Ordovás said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;These include your diet as a whole, physical activity, sleep and stress levels. “This is one tiny little sliver, and it’s a great reason to not feel bad about having an ounce of dark chocolate today,” Supan said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Boston Globe</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:58:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQdXNQR19uMmJzOXc4QWh5MzNucXk2UkxyS0IyNUxDWElsRmhDYmQxZGhnWEM5VDRSUTl2RGJHN28wSXYwZnJfa1lPSFNiWnNVR3VmT3Rib1EtNG1OUjJkTmZ6UTF3VkFCaFh1ZUpUZWw0ZWJLZEphQlVvNzNxWkdyWlVOMkNZcGxIdEE</guid></item><item><title>与大学生多动症症状增加相关的童年不良经历- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/adverse-childhood-experiences-linked-to-increased-adhd-symptoms-in-college-students/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent study published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10870547251370427" target="_blank"&gt;Journal of Attention Disorders&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; provides new evidence that difficult childhood experiences may contribute to symptoms of Attention Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) in young adults. The findings suggest that these adverse events disrupt an individual’s ability to regulate emotions and practice self-compassion, which in turn exacerbates attention and hyperactivity issues. This research highlights the potential for psychological interventions focusing on self-kindness to help mitigate ADHD symptoms stemming from early life adversity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ADHD is a neurodevelopmental condition characterized by patterns of inattention, hyperactivity, and impulsivity. Individuals with the inattentive presentation often struggle to sustain focus, stay organized, and remember daily tasks. Those with the hyperactive-impulsive presentation may experience inner restlessness, excessive physical movement, and difficulty waiting their turn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While ADHD is often viewed as a biological or genetic condition, environmental factors also play a significant role in its development and severity. Previous scientific literature has established that adverse childhood experiences, often referred to as ACEs, are linked to a variety of negative mental health outcomes. ACEs include events such as emotional, physical, or sexual abuse, as well as household dysfunctions like domestic violence, parental divorce, or family incarceration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the known link between early trauma and general psychological distress, fewer studies have specifically examined how these events influence ADHD symptoms in college students. There is also a lack of research regarding the internal protective factors that might buffer these effects. The authors of the current study aimed to fill this gap by investigating the psychological mechanisms connecting early adversity to adult ADHD symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers specifically sought to understand the role of emotion regulation and self-compassion. Emotion regulation refers to the processes by which individuals influence which emotions they have and how they experience and express them. Self-compassion involves treating oneself with warmth and understanding during difficult times rather than reacting with harsh self-judgment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was conducted in Türkiye, a cultural context where traditional child-rearing practices and family structures may influence how adverse experiences are processed. The research team recruited a sample of 442 young adults from a public university. The participants ranged in age from 18 to 29 years, with an average age of approximately 20.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sample was predominantly female, making up 67.4% of the group, while males accounted for 32.6%. The researchers collected data using a web-based survey tool. Participants were informed of their rights and provided consent before completing a battery of validated psychological measures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To assess early life difficulties, the researchers used the Adverse Childhood Experiences Checklist. This 10-item measure asks participants to indicate whether they experienced specific types of abuse or household dysfunction before the age of 18. Responses were recorded using a simple yes or no format.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Current ADHD symptoms were measured using the Adult ADHD Self Report Scale (ASRS-v1.1). This 18-item questionnaire screens for symptoms experienced over the past six months. It includes two subscales: one for inattention and one for hyperactivity-impulsivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers assessed emotion regulation using the Emotion Regulation Questionnaire-Short Form. This scale measures how frequently individuals use strategies like cognitive reappraisal or expressive suppression to manage their emotions. For this study, the authors focused on the general ability to manage emotional experiences effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Self-compassion was measured using the Self-Compassion Scale-Short Form. This 12-item instrument assesses how kind and caring individuals are toward themselves during instances of pain or failure. It includes elements such as self-kindness, common humanity, and mindfulness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results indicated that adverse childhood experiences were common among the participants. Approximately 76% of the students reported experiencing at least one adverse event. About 27% of the sample reported four or more adverse experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The statistical analysis revealed clear associations between the variables. Students who reported a higher number of adverse childhood experiences tended to have lower levels of self-compassion. These students also exhibited lower levels of emotion regulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simultaneously, higher scores on the ACEs checklist were associated with higher levels of both attention deficit and hyperactivity-impulsivity symptoms. The researchers used a technique called path analysis to test how these variables influenced one another. This analysis suggested that the relationship between early adversity and ADHD symptoms was not entirely direct.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The data supported a model where adverse childhood experiences lead to lower self-compassion. This lack of self-compassion then predicts difficulties in emotion regulation. Finally, poor emotion regulation predicts increased severity of ADHD symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Self-compassion appeared to play a mediating role. The analysis showed that self-compassion had an indirect effect on the relationship between ACEs and emotion regulation. It also had an indirect effect on the association between ACEs and ADHD symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study found that emotion regulation mediated the link between self-compassion and ADHD symptoms. This implies that one reason self-compassion helps reduce ADHD symptoms is that it improves an individual’s ability to manage their emotions. All variables together accounted for 22% of the variance in attention deficit symptoms and 16% of the variance in hyperactivity-impulsivity symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings suggest that individuals with high levels of self-compassion are better equipped to process adverse experiences constructively. They are less likely to engage in self-criticism or shame. This positive self-regard appears to foster better emotional control, which subsequently reduces the intensity of ADHD-like behaviors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors noted that adaptive emotion regulation strategies serve as protective factors. When individuals can reappraise stressful situations rather than suppressing their feelings, they may experience less impulsivity and better focus. The disruption of these skills by early trauma appears to be a key pathway to ADHD symptomatology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some limitations to this study that should be considered. The research relied on self-reported data, which can be subject to memory errors or social desirability bias. Participants may not have remembered childhood events accurately or may have been hesitant to report them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study utilized a cross-sectional design, meaning data was collected at a single point in time. This prevents the researchers from establishing definitive cause-and-effect relationships. It is possible that the relationships between these variables work in different directions than hypothesized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sample consisted solely of university students in Türkiye. This specific demographic means the results may not generalize to other populations, such as older adults, those not in college, or people from different cultural backgrounds. Additionally, the participants were screened for symptoms but were not clinically diagnosed with ADHD by the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors also highlighted the potential overlap between ADHD and Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD). Individuals with PTSD often display hypervigilance and intrusive thoughts that can mimic the inattention seen in ADHD. It is important for clinicians to distinguish between trauma-related inattention and neurodevelopmental attention deficits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research should employ longitudinal designs to track these variables over time. This would help clarify how early adversity impacts the development of these symptoms throughout young adulthood. Including clinical samples with formal ADHD diagnoses would also strengthen the validity of the findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these limitations, the study offers significant implications for mental health support. The results suggest that interventions aimed at increasing self-compassion could be beneficial for college students with ADHD symptoms, particularly those with a history of trauma. Teaching students to be kind to themselves may improve their emotional regulation and attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10870547251370427" target="_blank"&gt;Adverse Childhood Experiences and ADHD in College Students: Exploring the Role of Emotion Regulation and Self-Compassion&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Fikriye Eda Karaçul and Gökmen Arslan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:07:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxQVXl0eHpUSDdOZ0M1MWlxNG9QLW1mT0FvQlVYajQtTGd1RDZkRnJwZHVJeEdDSU92Z1Ayci0wVTV5cVE4Q3VWWmpVUURteDFQSnJPdXAyRk1vNDVIWFdTTkpCTTZuODdwR3VJY19wTDQyOGEyblBYU0l4WWQyeVRUZExrenlwZHA4U0JMUkczQjNtdE0ybzgxQ19FNUxFYnJ0S3ZMd3llVklIY01a</guid></item><item><title>狗在多大程度上减轻了我们的压力？ -《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/podcasts/post-reports/how-much-do-dogs-reduce-our-stress-1/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-hEgojh wpds-c-hEgojh-ikjuZWZ-css PodcastCarousel_storyCard__hJIce"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" alt="Broken Doors " src="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https%3A%2F%2Fpodcast.posttv.com%2Fseries%2F20220324%2Ft_1648139452139_name_RelatedImage_900x300.jpg&amp;amp;w=400"&gt;&lt;p class="PodcastCarousel_storyDesc__ZCeG0"&gt;An investigation into no-knock warrants in the American justice system — and what happens when accountability is flawed at every level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:02:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxONnRWQjlnN0trWGFaMGJnT1NieGpVdGN6SjEyTm1rWVBWenFKZFNyN3U0UkViNE9hTUg0bk1PX1lRNTBaZEROOEdHMXNRU3hGYUZtbEp0RkMzV2VpYTZ0UmZBVXRfRGJvSmphck1RWFJQcDdSMFB2dmw3YjIwN21aYXV3MHdlZVVRcEdXSGxDV0F6TEcw</guid></item><item><title>我每天早上喝柠檬水，并注意到身体的这3个好处-健康：值得信赖和富有同情心的健康信息</title><link>https://www.health.com/daily-lemon-water-benefits-11831207</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Drinking lemon water is the first thing I do every single morning. I have done it for as long as I can remember. Why? It keeps me hydrated, supports digestion, and boosts my immune system—and it might even make my skin glow.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-it-hydrates-me"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; I love water, but lemon makes it more fun. Starting every morning with lemon water helps hydrate me after sleep and sets me up for my morning workout. It also knocks several cups of water off my daily hydration goal of at least ten.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-it-supports-digestion"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; I always appreciate simple digestive aids that don't require supplements. Lemons are one answer. For example:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;One very small study found that the acid in lemons increases gastric emptying (how quickly the stomach digests food).&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Another study found that taking vitamin C supplements improves "good" gut bacteria called &lt;em&gt;Bifidobacterium&lt;/em&gt;, which also helps fight infection.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3-it-supports-heart-health-and-healing"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Citrus fruits like lemons are high in vitamin C and other antioxidants.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phenolic compounds are antioxidants that support healthy blood pressure, blood flow, and &lt;a href="https://www.health.com/lower-cholesterol-naturally-8350243" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;low-density lipoprotein (LDL) cholesterol&lt;/a&gt; ("healthy cholesterol") levels. All of this reduces your risk of heart disease.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vitamin C helps with tissue repair and growth. It's an important part of collagen, a key protein in skin, joints, and bones that loses strength with age.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-my-process"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; So, what exactly do I do? (Hint: It's very simple.)
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Warm up water:&lt;/strong&gt; I fill a 24-ounce mason jar with water and microwave it for about 45 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add lemon:&lt;/strong&gt; I add half a lemon per 24 ounces of water.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drink slowly:&lt;/strong&gt; This is the first thing I consume every day, before tea/coffee or breakfast.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; I continue this trend when traveling as much as possible—because how hard is it to bring or buy a lemon? It's especially helpful after later-than-usual bedtimes.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Morning lemon water is simply what I do now: it is a fully-formed habit. It reminds me that health doesn't need to be overcomplicated, time-consuming, or expensive. It also reminds me that the smallest habit can make a difference.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-my-1-tip"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Lemon water has a few caveats due to its acidic nature.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tooth erosion:&lt;/strong&gt; Highly acidic foods can contribute to dental erosion—loss of tooth enamel, the outer protective layer.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Acid reflux: &lt;/strong&gt;Consuming citrus regularly (e.g., daily) can contribute to acid reflux—when acid from your stomach bubbles up into your esophagus, causing symptoms like heartburn.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;My top tip: Wait about an hour before brushing your teeth.&lt;/strong&gt; This allows your saliva to wash away the acid and protects tooth enamel.
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The American Dental Association (ADA) also recommends rinsing your mouth with water or eating dairy after highly acidic meals or beverages and using a straw for acidic beverages, which I will start doing.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Side note: I often do oil-pulling, otherwise known as swishing coconut oil in my mouth for several minutes and spitting it out. Many people believe it has benefits, but the ADA points out the lack of research.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; That said, my dental hygienist recently commented on the whiteness of my teeth and told me I have basically no plaque. So, I'm still a believer.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Health: Trusted and Empathetic Health and Wellness Information</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE1vMThvTlBKSm1YYzhsSG5waENWajJfWVA1QkozSm5lbDFvNnJWRHpBZzRXOS1FcFZCWl9tVDVXdVBhZVdvenVBa1Jabm1UWk1LRmdvc20zZEIxUzEwLUU5TkNuSmJqLWN4Mnc</guid></item><item><title>纽约州在旺季之前创下了流感病例的记录- Gothamist</title><link>https://gothamist.com/news/new-york-state-has-set-a-record-for-flu-cases-ahead-of-peak-season</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="streamfield-paragraph rte-text"&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="bjf38"&gt;New York state logged the most flu cases ever recorded in a single week as hospitalizations surged past last winter’s peak — a development Health Commissioner Dr. James McDonald said caught his attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="21ek1"&gt;“It just shows that flu season’s more severe in New York this year, and we’re not even close to the peak yet,” McDonald said, noting that recent holiday gatherings are likely fueling continued spread. “When we’re together, we spread love and joy, but we also spread our germs.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="dhuks"&gt;Officials reported 71,123 new cases for the seven days ending Dec. 20. The new weekly toll marks a 38% week-over-week surge in laboratory-confirmed flu infections. It's a milestone in an already rough flu season that &lt;a href="https://gothamist.com/news/flu-season-arrives-in-ny-with-major-spike-in-cases" rel="noopener" target="_blank"&gt;arrived early&lt;/a&gt; and drove down &lt;a href="https://gothamist.com/news/nyc-school-attendance-drops-parents-freak-out-as-flu-season-foils-christmas-plans" rel="noopener" target="_blank"&gt;attendance at the city’s public schools&lt;/a&gt; during the week leading into the holidays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="1gcvh"&gt;Hospitalizations tied to influenza jumped sharply, with 3,666 New Yorkers requiring inpatient care compared to 2,251 the week before, continuing a trend of rising severe cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="fhqm6"&gt;“We can look at how hospitals are doing around New York every two hours, so we can monitor whether hospitals are being overwhelmed or not,” McDonald said. “Right now things are going smoothly, but this is something we're paying close attention to.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="khon"&gt;Health officials declared influenza “prevalent” across New York state earlier this month, requiring health care facilities to have unvaccinated personnel wear masks around patients and residents. The designation reflects widespread transmission across all regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="9lh0v"&gt;McDonald said it was too early to say when the season would reach its peak, but warned “it is gonna get worse before it gets better.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="djg7s"&gt;State health officials say it's not too late to get a flu vaccine. This year’s vaccination rate is roughly in line with past years. But this year's flu strain is more severe, McDonald said, so “if you haven't had your flu vaccine this year, this is the year to get it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="ee2bu"&gt;Those who are sick — especially children, people who are older or people who have underlying health conditions — should reach out to their doctors for antiviral drugs that can reduce symptoms and complications. However, the drugs must be started within 48 hours of coming down with the flu to be most effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="7cft6"&gt;People who are feeling ill “should really not go to work or not visit family,” McDonald said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="f2epd"&gt;He also suggested those who are immunocompromised or have a serious underlying disease wear an N95 or KN95 mask in crowded indoor spaces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="bpmrs"&gt;COVID-19 and RSV — another respiratory illness — also continue to circulate, but state data shows COVID-19 hospitalizations have been relatively stable in recent weeks and RSV activity has seen smaller increases compared with influenza.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gothamist</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:52:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPa1I2U1VoLVROOEJOVDBlN2ExbGlYTFlwb1pfMHpXRFg3MHhoVUJ3ZFBhMGJpZ3BON1RENWZIWDdWZ0gtT1A2QkhmTGVUaXNueHZ6VTZlclRGRkFrUklmcWxCQXRTWlZLZVRNb3FOUDZEQmtScFNyUWdZWm5hV08zblNyZmh2eTV5czdTNkhuX3V3V01CLXFyaQ</guid></item><item><title>专家说，世界上超过60 ％的人缺乏这种1维生素—这会增加您生病的风险- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/jillianwilson/vitamin-d-deficiency-colds-covid-viruses</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-11
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="skincare" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139928886" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It’s common for PCPs to recommend between 1,000 to 2,000 IUs per day of vitamin D3, Stadler said. Holick thinks adults should be on a higher amount than this, though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Typically, I recommend adults should be on minimum 2,000 units per day — and most I recommend 5,000 units a day because you want to get your blood level, in my opinion, of [vitamin D] between 40 and 60 ng/mL, [but] up to 100 is perfectly safe,” said Holick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once you get the go-ahead from your doctor, you can buy vitamin D supplements online or in stores like CVS and Walgreens. You’ll likely find vitamin D3 and vitamin D2 on the shelves, but vitamin D3 is more readily available and tends to be more recommended. Holick said vitamin D2 is perfectly acceptable, too, and is often preferred by vegans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it’s better to get &lt;em&gt;some&lt;/em&gt; nutrients directly from food, that isn’t easy or potentially even possible with vitamin D. Oily fish, milk and orange juice are all good for increasing vitamin D levels, but can’t do so to the level necessary, said Holick. The same goes for the sun, which also carries a risk of skin cancer with too much exposure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holick said he recommends vitamin D supplementation to all of his patients, friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You cannot get enough from your diet. You aren’t able to get enough from sunlight, unless you’re a ... hunter-gatherer, so vitamin D supplementation is essential,” Holick said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Older adults and people with darker skin are at higher risk of vitamin D deficiency, Stadler added. But, once again, it’s advisable for most people to take a supplement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:31:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxQSVVGSGZmVnIyWVVlVm5EUEhQenBQRnVXTnFJaHJfQjZTMGx0QVg0eGtMcHZ3aHNwOUEyUDIwcm5Za1k3bkdPUV85dzJ6ZHBpSXdsQ2x6YkNkM3FFbk5hbE9UcEZ4czM2UjE3MFgyUlBERVhOSDltazZEU3g0NUZzVHhxbDhWZw</guid></item><item><title>专家说，世界上超过60 ％的人缺乏这种1维生素，这会增加您患病的风险- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/jillianwilson/vitamin-d-deficiency-colds-covid-viruses?origin=web-hf</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-11
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="skincare" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139928886" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It’s common for PCPs to recommend between 1,000 to 2,000 IUs per day of vitamin D3, Stadler said. Holick thinks adults should be on a higher amount than this, though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Typically, I recommend adults should be on minimum 2,000 units per day — and most I recommend 5,000 units a day because you want to get your blood level, in my opinion, of [vitamin D] between 40 and 60 ng/mL, [but] up to 100 is perfectly safe,” said Holick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once you get the go-ahead from your doctor, you can buy vitamin D supplements online or in stores like CVS and Walgreens. You’ll likely find vitamin D3 and vitamin D2 on the shelves, but vitamin D3 is more readily available and tends to be more recommended. Holick said vitamin D2 is perfectly acceptable, too, and is often preferred by vegans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it’s better to get &lt;em&gt;some&lt;/em&gt; nutrients directly from food, that isn’t easy or potentially even possible with vitamin D. Oily fish, milk and orange juice are all good for increasing vitamin D levels, but can’t do so to the level necessary, said Holick. The same goes for the sun, which also carries a risk of skin cancer with too much exposure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holick said he recommends vitamin D supplementation to all of his patients, friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You cannot get enough from your diet. You aren’t able to get enough from sunlight, unless you’re a ... hunter-gatherer, so vitamin D supplementation is essential,” Holick said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Older adults and people with darker skin are at higher risk of vitamin D deficiency, Stadler added. But, once again, it’s advisable for most people to take a supplement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:31:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxOekxfTEdpT0dKWWo4djVuRThiZEp6eEZYWnUwRVdmRklfNmRUVnhULWtqYUVTa2dyWGhlTmtQZFc3MVlsZl9HOWJxeGMxUS1JRUVCMmVqV0YtSHJtSkJMaUo3bmJIaktEelJ3RGhkNWNyaTBYQkpKamV2MUdRR1BGRFM2ZHdqS1E3VGwxS01qWW1MbWFGYzdTcQ</guid></item><item><title>新研究后“午餐肉类”和碳酸饮料的肺癌警告- Metro.co.uk</title><link>https://metro.co.uk/2025/12/27/ultra-processed-foods-linked-increased-risk-lung-cancer-25852217/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-overlay__content"&gt;
							&lt;p class="newsletter-overlay__close"&gt;
								&lt;svg&gt;&lt;title&gt;Close Overlay&lt;/title&gt;&lt;use xlink:href="#common-close" href="#common-close"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
							&lt;/p&gt;
							&lt;h4&gt;News Updates&lt;/h4&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;Stay on top of the headlines with daily email updates.&lt;/p&gt;

							
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Metro.co.uk</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxNdjYtcEpBUjBlZ05jS2x0QU9qMThYS2FlSTB1RWFnYTJaYWZ1cWh5SGlLQ1RGb0dHQlVsVkNyZnZnbDFKWW1RUUhwSk82X0ctdUdmYlpIajhfWTM2amlKQUlGcW1IVUVsZ0UwWkVqOTZvdVdjbnVjcmhEWU10Ny11MU4wbXNONkc3R1VBSWdBbzVsOXg1bF9aZmVRaVXSAaIBQVVfeXFMTkZOdFdoN2tQZjgwTVJGQWk4RlpHcDFuMjl4Z1BNbkZ1SzVnaGtJRkhCNEVQaFB5T1R0WVlQUnREU2ViWjRjM0laUDlsenZ6cDVUS25fU0xSOUFsSkljbkZENGZRM2czd1hqSjdTVGVJS0M1QkdjbXRvR1J6UENBaXBTYkhpeXJjZUljVlphaHF3QzJHbkZNRl9RT1dVVXNhdWx3</guid></item><item><title>新研究后“午餐肉类”和碳酸饮料的肺癌警告- Metro.co.uk</title><link>https://metro.co.uk/2025/12/27/ultra-processed-foods-linked-increased-risk-lung-cancer-25852217/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-overlay__content"&gt;
							&lt;p class="newsletter-overlay__close"&gt;
								&lt;svg&gt;&lt;title&gt;Close Overlay&lt;/title&gt;&lt;use xlink:href="#common-close" href="#common-close"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
							&lt;/p&gt;
							&lt;h4&gt;News Updates&lt;/h4&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;Stay on top of the headlines with daily email updates.&lt;/p&gt;

							
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Metro.co.uk</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxNdjYtcEpBUjBlZ05jS2x0QU9qMThYS2FlSTB1RWFnYTJaYWZ1cWh5SGlLQ1RGb0dHQlVsVkNyZnZnbDFKWW1RUUhwSk82X0ctdUdmYlpIajhfWTM2amlKQUlGcW1IVUVsZ0UwWkVqOTZvdVdjbnVjcmhEWU10Ny11MU4wbXNONkc3R1VBSWdBbzVsOXg1bF9aZmVRaVU</guid></item><item><title>她研究了野火对健康的影响，直到环保局削减补助金--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/27/science/trump-wildfires-vance-epa.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:21:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFBaZ05tOU9WdlFUU29zcGd0MmFIMm9EMHhsTlcyVFltMjlMdzkzTXlzal9yM0l0V1RoSUhxQkJyXzhnNl84WC00aVk3SURXNFRRYXNkcVNSaVJoSkZXUFJGN25GWERKS08yT09WRVg4TDJ2OGZGelRQdXJFeUJHdw</guid></item><item><title>美国国立卫生研究院神经系统疾病研究所所长被罢免，增加了领导层的流失- statnews.com</title><link>https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/27/nih-neurological-disorders-stroke-institute-director-koroshetz-ousted/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walter Koroshetz, director of the National Institute of Neurological Disorders and Stroke, will soon be leaving his role, STAT has learned. His departure in the coming days means nearly half the 27 NIH divisions will have interim leaders.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Koroshetz sent an email to NINDS staff late Friday night explaining that a request to reappoint him was denied, adding that his current temporary extension ends Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“There’s some possibility for a short term extension, but iffy at best,” he wrote in an email obtained by STAT.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker article" aria-labelledby="restricted-story-heading" aria-describedby="restricted-story-description" checked&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-bar"&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-text"&gt;STAT+ Exclusive Story&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-login"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;img class="restricted-content-breaker-bg" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-breaker-bg.png" alt="STAT+"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper"&gt;
				&lt;span class="stat-paywall-archive"&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/"&gt;
						&lt;img class="stat-plus-logo" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-logo-white.svg" alt="STAT+"&gt;
					&lt;/a&gt;
				&lt;/span&gt;
				&lt;h2 id="restricted-story-heading"&gt;This article is exclusive to STAT+ subscribers&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;h3 id="restricted-story-description"&gt;Unlock this article — plus in-depth analysis, newsletters, premium events, and news alerts.&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper-cta mobile"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta mobile"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-cards"&gt;
					&lt;div class="slider-container" aria-label="Subscription plan toggle"&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="individual" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Individual plans&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;p class="switch" role="switch" tabindex="0" aria-checked="false"&gt;
							&lt;button class="slider"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="group" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Group plans&lt;/button&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
							

		
						&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button view-all" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker view all plans" aria-label="View All Plans"&gt;View All Plans&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="restricted-message-breaker"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-wrapper"&gt;
								
								&lt;div class="restricted-content-message"&gt;
					&lt;p class="restricted-content-text"&gt;
						To read the rest of this story subscribe to STAT+.					&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button restricted-button" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker subscribe cta 1"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
								
							&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:20:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxPc054TG1HRHJ5eUVvelVJZU5zcWJFXzNrc2o5TW9yZFAwQ0VWcnUxd09ZQkdzVkY5cEEwVEdzRmFUUDJkYjh2Yl9kdWV2ZkJaWlg3MC1iU2k4Y0FXTEhPeG1BZXdma3U1TGRLSjZXYTNyWWFvU3BVTXVvR2dUTXJqVWRyakdqV3AyU3VSWURHNVh6WmpsYnNaQk9VbV9rY1VXTEEyaG9iNERYZw</guid></item><item><title>纽约流感季节见证创纪录的一周-新闻日</title><link>https://www.newsday.com/news/region-state/flu-new-york-health-department-x80tlp8h</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="continue-reading ContinueReading_continue-reading__uTArZ active ContinueReading_active__SOMMR"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Influenza season is raging across New York. The state came down with a record-breaking 71,123 cases the week ending Dec. 20 — the highest since flu became a reportable disease in 2004, officials said Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 15,000 of those lab-confirmed flu cases &lt;a class="nd-link" target="_blank" href="https://nyshc.health.ny.gov/web/nyapd/new-york-state-flu-tracker"&gt;were on Long Island&lt;/a&gt; during that period — 7,924 in Nassau and 7,571 in Suffolk, state data shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We are seeing the highest number of flu cases ever recorded in a single week,” State Health Commissioner Dr. James McDonald said in a statement, adding that the agency is monitoring hospital bed capacity “to better understand hospitalization trends and to guide any necessary response related to impacts from respiratory viral infections.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;State hospitalizations &lt;a class="nd-link" target="_blank" href="https://www.health.ny.gov/diseases/communicable/respiratory_viruses/activity/2025-2026/docs/current_respiratory_report.pdf"&gt;due to influenza went up 63% &lt;/a&gt;over the last two reporting weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="nd-link" target="_blank" href="/news/health/flu-cases-ahead-uwosj55h"&gt;Experts have warned of a likely severe flu season&lt;/a&gt; attributed to low vaccination rates and a surprise variant that emerged after the vaccine was formulated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Statewide, there have been 189,312 positive flu cases reported since October, including &lt;a class="nd-link" target="_blank" href="https://nyshc.health.ny.gov/web/nyapd/new-york-state-flu-tracker"&gt;20,415 in Nassau and 18,109 in Suffolk&lt;/a&gt;. Infectious disease doctors have said lab-confirmed tests represent only a portion of actual flu cases because many people who are sick may not seek medical help or get tested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hospitalization rate in Suffolk County more than doubled over the last two weeks, from 8.79 to 20.38 per 100,000 people, while Nassau County's increased from 15.4 to 23.2 per 100,000 people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;State health officials noted that reporting of flu cases has gone up in recent years due to increased testing but "the record number underscores that this season is impacting more people than in other recent years."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;McDonald advised all eligible New Yorkers to get vaccinated against the flu, and stay home when they get sick. People at higher risk of severe flu, such as the elderly and those with compromised immune systems, can benefit from antiviral medication if it is administered within 48 hours of symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though the current flu vaccine is not a perfect match to the circulating strain, it is still worth getting, said Dr. Bruce Farber, chief of public health and epidemiology at Northwell Health, during a briefing last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“[The flu vaccine] is very good at preventing hospitalizations and deaths,” he said. “It's not as good at preventing flu per se, but if you get flu, more likely than not, it will be a lot less severe than if you are not vaccinated.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only about &lt;a class="nd-link" target="_blank" href="https://coronavirus.health.ny.gov/covid-19-and-influenza-vaccination-data"&gt;25% of eligible New Yorkers&lt;/a&gt; have received flu shots as of Dec. 24, including 20% in Suffolk County and 24% in Nassau County. The state Health Department and the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention have recommended the flu vaccine for everyone over the age of 6 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="byline Byline_byline__7W6Ao ux Byline_ux__K0907 bot Byline_bot__Vn8AK"&gt;&lt;span class="author-image Byline_author-image__kHthS"&gt;&lt;img alt="Lisa L. Colangelo" loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" srcset="/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fcdn.newsday.com%2Fimage-service%2Fversion%2Fc%3AN2U4YjNmMmEtMjAxYy00%3AMmEtMjAxYy00MWIwOWI1%2Fimage.jpg%3Ff%3DMugshot%26w%3D100%26q%3D1&amp;amp;w=96&amp;amp;q=75 1x, /_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fcdn.newsday.com%2Fimage-service%2Fversion%2Fc%3AN2U4YjNmMmEtMjAxYy00%3AMmEtMjAxYy00MWIwOWI1%2Fimage.jpg%3Ff%3DMugshot%26w%3D100%26q%3D1&amp;amp;w=256&amp;amp;q=75 2x" src="/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fcdn.newsday.com%2Fimage-service%2Fversion%2Fc%3AN2U4YjNmMmEtMjAxYy00%3AMmEtMjAxYy00MWIwOWI1%2Fimage.jpg%3Ff%3DMugshot%26w%3D100%26q%3D1&amp;amp;w=256&amp;amp;q=75"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	Lisa joined Newsday as a staff writer in 2019. She previously worked at amNewYork, the New York Daily News and the Asbury Park Press covering politics, government and general assignment.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Newsday</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:16:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNYzhnODVFWTQ4Y3dvQWRUT1UzQXNQSkxfYXZrblBrR2o3ZzRGMWVJVTZfQmdJZXpjZmhNUkNocE9lRFRiMFN4dnU4cU9DRHNLZkhuWUJ3WUdXTzgzdnVzeTNweC1yNjQtb3BtVUdzaGl3UnVJNXVqUlBtSWwydjE1TFlmY1FXd0Nj</guid></item><item><title>斯坦福大学的科学家揭示了为什么mRNA COVID疫苗会引发心脏炎症- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251227082716.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Researchers at Stanford Medicine have identified the biological steps that explain how mRNA-based COVID-19 vaccines can, in rare cases, lead to heart inflammation in some adolescent and young adult males. Their work also points to a potential strategy for lowering that risk.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By combining modern laboratory techniques with previously published data from vaccinated individuals, the team uncovered a two-stage immune response. In this process, the vaccine activates one type of immune cell, which then stimulates another. Together, these immune reactions drive inflammation that can damage heart muscle cells and set off additional inflammatory effects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vaccines Remain Highly Safe and Effective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings come despite the fact that mRNA COVID-19 vaccines have been given billions of times worldwide and continue to show an excellent safety record, said Joseph Wu, MD, PhD, director of the Stanford Cardiovascular Institute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The mRNA vaccines have done a tremendous job mitigating the COVID pandemic," said Wu, the Simon H. Stertzer, MD, Professor and a professor of medicine and of radiology. "Without these vaccines, more people would have gotten sick, more people would have had severe effects and more people would have died."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;mRNA vaccines are considered a major advance because they can be developed quickly, adjusted as viruses change, and tailored to target very different pathogens. Still, as with any medical intervention, reactions are not identical for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understanding Vaccine-Associated Myocarditis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One uncommon but documented side effect of mRNA COVID-19 vaccines is myocarditis, which refers to inflammation of the heart muscle. Symptoms can include chest pain, shortness of breath, fever and heart palpitations. These symptoms occur without a viral infection and typically appear within one to three days after vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most affected individuals show elevated levels of cardiac troponin in their blood, a widely used marker of heart muscle injury. (Cardiac troponin is normally found exclusively in the heart muscle. When found circulating in blood, it indicates damage to heart muscle cells.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The condition occurs in roughly one out of every 140,000 people after a first vaccine dose and increases to about one in 32,000 after a second dose. Rates are highest among males age 30 and younger, where it affects about one in 16,750 vaccine recipients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outcomes Are Usually Mild and Temporary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wu emphasized that the majority of myocarditis cases linked to vaccination resolve quickly, with heart function either fully preserved or restored.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It's not a heart attack in the traditional sense," he said. "There's no blockage of blood vessels as found in most common heart attacks. When symptoms are mild and the inflammation hasn't caused structural damage to the heart, we just observe these patients to make sure they recover."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In rare instances, however, severe inflammation can cause serious injury, leading to hospitalization, intensive care treatment or death.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"But COVID's worse," Wu said. He noted that a COVID-19 infection is about 10 times more likely to cause myocarditis than an mRNA-based COVID-19 vaccine, in addition to the many other risks posed by the disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Closer Look at the Immune Response&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wu is a senior author of the study, publisded Dec. 10 in &lt;em&gt;Science Translational Medicine&lt;/em&gt;, along with Masataka Nishiga, MD, PhD, a former Stanford postdoctoral scholar now at The Ohio State University. The study's lead author is Xu Cao, PhD, also a postdoctoral scholar at Stanford.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Medical scientists are quite aware that COVID itself can cause myocarditis," Wu said. "To a lesser extent, so can the mRNA vaccines. The question is, why?"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suspects Identified&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To answer that question, the team analyzed blood samples from vaccinated individuals, including some who developed myocarditis. When they compared these samples with those from people who did not develop heart inflammation, two proteins stood out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Two proteins, named CXCL10 and IFN-gamma, popped up. We think these two are the major drivers of myocarditis," Wu said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both CXCL10 and IFN-gamma are cytokines, signaling molecules that immune cells use to communicate and coordinate their activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Immune Cells Interact After Vaccination&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers grew human immune cells called macrophages in laboratory dishes and exposed them to mRNA vaccines. Macrophages act as early responders in immune defense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After exposure, the macrophages released multiple cytokines, with especially high levels of CXCL10. Their behavior closely matched immune responses previously documented in vaccinated people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When T cells were added to the system, either directly or by exposing them to fluid from the macrophage cultures, the T cells began producing large amounts of IFN-gamma. In contrast, T cells exposed to the vaccine alone did not show this spike. These findings showed that macrophages primarily produce CXCL10, while T cells are the main source of IFN-gamma following vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How the Cytokines Affect the Heart&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To determine whether these cytokines directly harm the heart, the team vaccinated young male mice and observed increased cardiac troponin levels, indicating heart muscle injury.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They also found that immune cells, including macrophages and neutrophils, had entered heart tissue. Neutrophils are short-lived immune cells that respond aggressively to threats and are a major component of pus. Similar immune cell infiltration is seen in people who develop myocarditis after vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blocking CXCL10 and IFN-gamma reduced the number of these immune cells entering the heart and limited damage to healthy tissue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers also detected increased levels of adhesion molecules in heart blood vessels. These molecules help immune cells latch onto vessel walls, making it easier for them to move into heart tissue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together, these findings confirmed that CXCL10 and IFN-gamma directly contribute to heart injury. Blocking them preserved much of the immune response to vaccination while lowering signs of heart damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Testing Human Heart Tissue Models&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wu's lab specializes in converting human skin or blood cells into stem-like cells that can become heart muscle cells, immune cells and blood vessel cells. These cells can be assembled into small, beating clusters that mimic aspects of heart function.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When these cardiac spheroids were exposed to CXCL10 and IFN-gamma collected from vaccinated immune cells, markers of heart stress rose sharply. Using inhibitors to block the cytokines reduced this damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Measures of heart function, including contraction strength and beating rhythm, were impaired by the cytokines but improved once the signaling was blocked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saved by a Soybean&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wu suspected that a widely available dietary compound might help protect the heart. Since myocarditis is more common in males and estrogen has anti-inflammatory effects, he revisited genistein, a soy-derived compound his team had studied previously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a 2022 study published in Cell, the researchers showed that genistein has anti-inflammatory properties and can counter marijuana-related damage to blood vessels and heart tissue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Genistein is only weakly absorbed when taken orally," Wu said. "Nobody ever overdosed on tofu."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Testing Genistein's Protective Effects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team repeated their experiments while pre-treating cells, cardiac spheroids and mice (the latter by oral administration of large quantities) with genistein. This treatment reduced much of the heart damage caused by either mRNA vaccination or the CXCL10 and IFN-gamma combination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The form of genistein used in the study was more purified and concentrated than supplements commonly sold in stores.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It's reasonable to believe that the mRNA-vaccine-induced inflammatory response may extend to other organs," Wu said. "We and others have seen some evidence of this in lung, liver and kidney. It's possible that genistein may also reverse these changes."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Broader Implications Beyond COVID Vaccines&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heightened cytokine signaling may be a broader feature of mRNA vaccines. IFN-gamma, in particular, plays a critical role in defending the body against foreign DNA and RNA, including viral genetic material.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Your body needs these cytokines to ward off viruses. It's essential to immune response but can become toxic in large amounts," Wu said. Excessive IFN-gamma can lead to myocarditis-like symptoms and breakdown of heart muscle proteins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This risk is not limited to COVID vaccines alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Other vaccines can cause myocarditis and inflammatory problems, but the symptoms tend to be more diffuse," Wu said. "Plus, mRNA-based COVID-19 vaccines' risks have received intense public scrutiny and media coverage. If you get chest pains from a COVID vaccine you go to the hospital to get checked out, and if the serum troponin is positive, then you get diagnosed with myocarditis. If you get achy muscles or joints from a flu vaccine, you just blow it off."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding and Support&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study was supported by the National Institutes of Health (grants R01 HL113006, R01 HL141371, R01 HL141851, R01 HL163680 and R01 HL176822) and the Gootter-Jensen Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:53:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE42QlR0RXFILTk2WDR2NzhNNlpNTkZURlB3YWFVUUNVbEoyVEhEb0NwNGZMRVQyNTRmYWp6VjE5djBIN2xpLUhCYWpWRWRTYjhvU1FuM25UVVhIOHdHQTRaNGZnaHRuMFNqUjlsX01xYw</guid></item><item><title>没有药丸或注射剂：研究揭示了一个令人惊讶的简单习惯，可以帮助控制血糖-经济时报</title><link>https://m.economictimes.com/magazines/panache/no-pills-or-injections-research-reveals-a-surprisingly-simple-habit-that-could-help-manage-blood-sugar-in-type-2-diabetes/articleshow/126206028.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-brcount="23" class="artText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study suggests that something as ordinary as sitting by a window during the day may help people with &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/type-2-diabetes" target="_blank"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; manage their &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/blood-sugar-levels" target="_blank"&gt;blood sugar levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; more effectively. The findings add a fresh dimension to how daily environment and mental wellbeing intersect with &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/metabolic-health" target="_blank"&gt;metabolic health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/natural-light" target="_blank"&gt;Natural light&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; has long been associated with improved mood, alertness and emotional balance. According to a report from &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="https://www.newscientist.com/article/2509031-sitting-by-a-window-may-improve-blood-sugar-levels-for-type-2-diabetes/" data-type="tilCustomLink" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;New Scientist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, now, researchers say it may also quietly support blood sugar regulation. Scientists explain that the human body operates on &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/circadian-rhythms" target="_blank"&gt;circadian rhythms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, internal 24 hour cycles that influence metabolism, hormone release and glucose control. These rhythms are highly sensitive to light exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-newpos-mgid="mgid_126206028" id="div-mgid-mid-newpos-126206028"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous research has shown that artificial light at night can disrupt these cycles and raise blood sugar levels. Conversely, spending time outdoors in daylight appears to improve the body’s response to insulin. What remained unclear until now was whether similar benefits could be achieved indoors through natural light alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="E_3" class="etoro"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Inside the study rooms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To explore this question, researchers led by Joris Hoeks at Maastricht University in the Netherlands conducted a small but closely monitored experiment involving 13 older adults with type 2 diabetes. According to the New Scientist report, participants spent 4.5 days in rooms where they were exposed to daylight through large windows from morning to evening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They followed controlled routines. Meals, exercise and sleep schedules were kept consistent. Participants continued their usual diabetes medications and spent most of the day seated, using phones and computers with dim screen settings. Nights involved low artificial lighting before sleep in complete darkness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-vdoai="vdoai_126206028" id="div-vdoai-mid-126206028"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same participants later repeated the experiment in windowless rooms lit only by artificial light, allowing researchers to compare the two environments directly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-msid="126206028" class="masterclass_carousel"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID_INTL_300" data-loc="100" id="div-gpt-ad-858478126-1-126206028" class="country_specAD"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What the blood sugar data revealed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Continuous glucose monitors showed that during the days spent with natural light exposure, participants stayed within a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/healthy-blood-sugar-range" target="_blank"&gt;healthy blood sugar range&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; about 50 percent of the time. During the artificial light phase, that figure dropped to 43 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="2" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-126206028" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="5" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-126206028" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="3" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-126206028" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the difference may appear modest, Hoeks told New Scientist that prolonged periods outside the healthy range can meaningfully increase the risk of diabetes related complications such as heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers defined healthy blood sugar levels in line with guidance from health authorities such as the UK National Health Service and the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why light through a window matters&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers believe the effect may stem from light sensitive cells in the eyes that help regulate metabolic cycles. These cells respond more strongly to the shorter wavelengths found in natural daylight than to artificial lighting, potentially reinforcing healthier circadian signals throughout the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the exact biological mechanisms require further investigation, the implication is clear. Exposure to daylight does not require strenuous effort, special equipment or lifestyle overhaul. Experts caution that larger studies are needed before drawing firm conclusions. Glen Jeffery from University College London, quoted in New Scientist, noted that scientific understanding of daylight’s importance is still developing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even so, the takeaway is striking in its simplicity. For many people with type 2 diabetes, improving blood sugar control may begin with something that also lifts mood and mental clarity. Sitting by a window, letting daylight shape the day, could be one small but meaningful step toward better metabolic health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="inSideInd"&gt;&lt;div data-ga-action="Preference Banner InArticle Widget" data-ga-impression="Preference Banner InArticle Widget#Impressions | Preference Banner | Articleshow#url" class="Pbanner"&gt;&lt;div class="Pbannertext"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img alt="ET Logo" src="https://img.etimg.com/photo/123467569.cms"&gt;&lt;p&gt; as a Reliable and Trusted News Source&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Economic Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:35:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingJBVV95cUxNeEVYZHVkYzRKdnFva3pzX0RQNHhxOThyWWg2UmlaUjFmWDNBa1FHQVpCOE0yVDA3YnEtMUJGWHMzd0hpTjlGT25Jd1lLUm5tLVBpbnQ3czJsRXJOWFR3Z0ktWm9JWUlfMlZOSksxNzFLa2NWWGpCR3BPaXVmMkJpSmcxdUNucm45TnFCeV80UjJUeEcxYjBDdm45ZUNNT0hUWmhHT1YxV2xyYmgzaEo3UG1wZ2RDMGF1RWZyYURGUERXeGNZTWF3dFJwUVZ6WkFMWFFMTzJFSkNGdVdmVjMwSTFnVGt2ck5EQWhXcXFsMnV6Y1lzcTlwUGlMX2dKNFRZN09PODRGMFlPaXJZTmg3a1FqVmUxakt4T2o5dHFB0gGjAkFVX3lxTE1QNW1lX3g0ZVdoNTFSOEZGdDNsUTNqYnhnVVN4SUF4eUdDeUNJX1lrSUhUaVdsdmhjNnk4aThoNDNsNGFfV3BxNE1ORFhuVDVsUDRNTUV1VDM4bFpOcWJydGVkTl9zV0dJYm9kUnNoMW1ScjFtVjlKTU9ZNlZxT2ZGV29XMkZWQ042V3hrWEpETmxFQVJjQlRhbGgwTWtEdG5MU0YyX1NVSU45amZFMEY0WWxXVXpwUnBVTkFINzhzODUyMEZTcHZXaEFWUnNOb3h3QUFsbDFqX0JlT2tVamJnMmJjVzY2MGZpLWxiVEdJaGN4M2tHcTFBX2FPbkoyZ1N3SFRURHd2M2RlY3ZmTVc1cWdNVGZIMkg3NUtGdmtvVTRncw</guid></item></channel></rss>