<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>生酮饮食与奇怪的瘙痒皮疹有关-但没有人知道为什么- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/health/2026/01/a-weird-itchy-rash-is-linked-to-the-keto-diet-but-no-one-knows-why/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
          
          
&lt;h2&gt;Diet downsides&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, the keto diet is popular among people trying to lose weight, particularly those trying to lose visceral fat, like the man in the case study. Anecdotal reports promote the keto diet as being effective at helping people slim down relatively quickly while also improving stamina and mental clarity. But robust clinical data supporting these claims are lacking, and medical experts have raised concerns about long-term cardiovascular health, among other things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are also clear downsides to the diet. Ketones are acidic, and if they build up too much in the blood, they can be toxic, causing ketoacidosis. This is a particular concern for people with type 1 diabetes and for people with chronic alcohol abuse. For everyone else, there’s a list of &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK499830/"&gt;common side effects&lt;/a&gt;, including nausea, vomiting, constipation, diarrhea, bad breath, headache, fatigue, and dizziness. Ketogenic diets are also linked to high cholesterol and kidney stones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there’s one side effect that’s well established but little known and still puzzling to doctors: the “keto rash” or &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK599559/"&gt;prurigo pigmentosa&lt;/a&gt;. This rash fits the man’s case perfectly—red, raised, itchy bumps on the neck, chest, and back, with areas of hyperpigmentation also developing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rash was first identified in Japan in 1971, where it was mostly seen in women. While it has been consistently linked to metabolic disorders and dietary changes, experts still don’t understand what causes it. It’s seen not only in people on a keto diet but also in people with diabetes and those who have had bariatric surgery or are fasting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1155/drp/1993385"&gt;a review this month&lt;/a&gt;, researchers in Saudi Arabia noted that a leading hypothesis is that the high levels of ketones in the blood trigger inflammation around blood vessels driven by a type of white blood cell called neutrophils, and this inflammation is what causes the rash, which develops in different stages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the condition remains poorly understood, effective treatments have at least been worked out. The most common treatment is to get the person out of ketosis and give them an antibiotic in the tetracycline class. Antibiotics are designed to treat bacterial infections (which this is not), but they can also dampen inflammation signals and thwart the activity of neutrophils.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the man’s case, doctors gave him a two-week course of doxycycline and told him to ditch his keto diet. A week later, the rash was gone.&lt;/p&gt;


          
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                  
          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:00:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNOTgwd1dsUW1pSTAtUXROb3M5QTF6c09QdTVwdXVyZVVyWlFKQmxhWmMxU3NLaDZXWVZOMUUtVVFnS0lHcGd0dmR3OEtmckNweXRoLTdRSnoxX2FnajJkOU1hSmRwNUFSeEVfQ3NQU2VjMGNCWGpYMlpKUmg0ZmtnMFdQVEJsNV9KdDhzQXFDakYyY0YzMU5xSWk3MTRDRnJLclU2QnhDYUdFdw</guid></item><item><title>关于医学和医疗保健的6个播客-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/24/arts/podcasts-medicine-health-science.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:00:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxOd1h5RVF1VnhjR1JEY2hDNTJxTWttcDJxMW9CVnIwOWtuLWI3SzdRYXE3THlBSHBVMkVKRGlINGUzb1ZNdUlsMmx6MHJhUG9xRjZ2Rk5QLU1YNTdhenRBeHlUM0VraFE1VjRoQjBaQk9KQWZPSG9URkd1dkJwbTFfc1ljNA</guid></item><item><title>随着年龄的增长，忘记肌肉质量，专注于力量-纽约时报</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/24/well/move/muscle-strength-versus-mass.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:00:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNTFpnUUNCMl9IamxhdzF3Y042WW10VmNJazMtN0g0NXJnd2Nia3QyTnBqeXNXM0c3SnBNSVptYnlHRmRfZGFocjkxUGlkYS00ejFpeW5FeHkya05QRnEtVEdMZTRGd1FzdFNLTHFCUFJ0OFI5RDQwMmc3UjBYMlg3ZllqVQ</guid></item><item><title>允许家庭检查风险的NHS癌症基因数据库- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c62v7l4v7gro</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A new NHS database of genes linked to cancer could enable patients and their families in England to find out whether they are at risk of developing the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;People will be able to have their genetic information compared to the world-first register of 120 genes known to increase the likelihood of getting cancer, NHS England has said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Those identified as having an inherited risk will be offered routine check-ups and screening for certain cancers, including breast and prostate cancer. Patients could also be tested to see whether they would respond better to particular treatments, allowing for personalised care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Health Secretary Wes Streeting said the "life-changing and life-saving" tool would fast-track screening and allow more cancers to be caught sooner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Tens of thousands of cancer patients and those with a family history of the disease already undergo genetic testing on the NHS every year. Those known to have a higher risk profile will be added to the new register.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;They will be given tailored information about what they can do to lower their chance of developing cancer or detect it early.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The NHS said it was building the register&lt;b id="" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt; &lt;/b&gt;as part of a 10-year plan to improve prevention and treatment of cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;NHS England's national cancer director told BBC Radio 4's Today programme it was "the first time any health care system has brought together all the information about all the genetic risk into a single place."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Prof Peter Johnson said it pulled together the tests patients were already offered to check their cancer susceptibility into a single register, "so that we can contact people to offer them screening and in some cases preventative treatment".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This will allow practitioners to "keep tabs on people" and offer them new tests and treatments as they are rolled out, he added, while stressing it would be "incredibly confidential and secure".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Johnson said that while it could be "very daunting" for people to find out their cancer risk, it meant the disease could be picked up as early as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The NHS National Inherited Cancer Predisposition Register follows a similar database for Lynch syndrome which saw more than 12,000 people offered routine preventative screening after they were identified as being at higher risk, according to the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Charlie Grinstead, a 32-year-old diagnosed with bowel cancer in 2020, said his Lynch syndrome diagnosis gave him access to immunotherapy after unsuccessful chemotherapy - and proved to be the "the key to my recovery".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Streeting said: "One in every two people will get cancer in their lifetime but that does not mean the chances are random - many people face a higher risk through the genes they inherit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"And while we cannot do anything about inherited genes, we can do something about what we do with that information."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He said the "world-leading genetic register" would allow personalised and preventative care to be provided sooner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"This register won't just supercharge innovation - it will be life changing and life-saving, allowing the NHS to develop individual care, fast-track screening and tailored information to enable more cancers to be caught earlier."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Claire Rowney, the chief executive of Breast Cancer Now, said the move would "transform the lives of women who are at increased risk of breast cancer due to their family history or genetics".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She said it had to be accessible to all clinicians and designed to ensure those with an increased risk profile received "joined-up care".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:28:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1MbEtzWWxNVUptTm9Pb2I0bmpGQ1QtZzlIVzBrMXAzc3pDTGFSaXpTcTJRelhXSkg4X1NmU09EMnd3TnJhMGdWWjVLUG9MZnRDQ3c0WHFmeXJfQdIBX0FVX3lxTFBGSEVLMzhCRjJDSTlWTmZoR25iSnJnOF9yY0poOHNGSHRmclN4aFJCaHA2aGlpdktEbHV1TXFoRlFYTllySG13NFFxdlJ1ZDdRbGJyR18xMHp3cXVkMkk4</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法， 50岁以上的男性应该吃5种抗炎食物- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/anti-inflammatory-foods-men-over-50-should-eat-11891280</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anti-inflammatory foods support gut and heart health and may lower cancer risk in men over 50.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Men over 50 should add foods like oats, fatty fish, berries and beans to their diet.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Managing stress, drinking less and getting ample sleep can also help reduce inflammation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For men over 50, concerns like achy joints, heart health and maintaining muscle often start to feel more front-of-mind. And while inflammation isn’t always harmful—short-term inflammation plays an important role in healing and immune defense—&lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-is-inflammation-8766645" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;chronic inflammation is linked to poorer health outcomes&lt;/a&gt;, including a higher risk of heart disease and diabetes.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Regular human metabolism naturally produces inflammation throughout the body, but it tries to control it through anti-inflammatory pathways," shares &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/dustin-moore-phd-rd-a1bb294a/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Dustin Moore, PhD, RD&lt;/a&gt;. "It’s not often discussed, but the pro- and anti-inflammatory mechanisms work in tricky balance with one another, and certain actions can influence that balance." The foods we eat play a big role in either &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/habit-to-avoid-for-chronic-inflammation-8644317" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;triggering or reducing inflammation&lt;/a&gt;. Focusing on fruits and vegetables, lean protein, healthy fats and whole grains is a core piece of anti-inflammatory diets.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; We dug into the research more and chatted with registered dietitians to highlight &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/anti-inflammatory-foods-for-women-over-50-11794640" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;top anti-inflammatory foods that men over 50 should be eating&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-fatty-fish"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 1. Fatty Fish &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you're looking for a food to do double duty—&lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7595044/the-10-best-anti-inflammatory-foods-for-heart-health/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;reducing inflammation and keeping your heart healthy&lt;/a&gt;—fatty fish should be at the top of your list. Fish like salmon, anchovies and herring deliver omega-3 fatty acids.&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/author/christopher-mohr/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Chris Mohr, Ph.D., RD&lt;/a&gt;, recommends, "Sardines. Yes, yes—sardines. They're rich in omega-3 fats, vitamin D, calcium and other important nutrients for everyone." He adds, "Most adults don't eat adequate amounts of omega-3 fats and sardines can help fill the gap for this nutrient and others."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Omega-3 fats are anti-inflammatory and the American Heart Association recommends eating seafood twice a week to help &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/15297/our-top-15-heart-healthy-foods/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;reduce the risk of heart disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Omega-3's may also help reduce the risk of certain cancers, dementia and age-related macular degeneration.&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Not everyone loves sardines, but they work well in salads and pasta dishes. &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/249244/honey-soy-broiled-salmon/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Honey-Soy Broiled Salmon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7944627/garlic-anchovy-pasta-with-broccolini/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Garlic-Anchovy Pasta with Broccolini&lt;/a&gt; are two other yummy ways to get your omega-3's.   
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-berries"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 2. Berries &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Berries deliver an antioxidant punch. "Whatever the mix—raspberries, blueberries, blackberries—just eat a serving of berries," says Moore. "They're a rich source of antioxidants, and they also provide a good dose of fiber, a key component of the diet that older men are frequently missing." 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Berries get their color from flavonoids, including anthocyanins, which &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-foods-to-fight-inflammation-11762781" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;help reduce inflammation and disease risk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The compounds in berries may also help keep hearts healthy by improving cholesterol, specifically decreasing LDL or "bad" cholesterol levels.&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Eat them as is, or throw them in some Greek yogurt with a little granola for crunch," advises Moore. &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/8031379/dietitian-favorite-recipes-with-frozen-berries/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Frozen berries are a great option&lt;/a&gt; to save some money and always keep berries on hand. They work well in smoothies and in these &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/blueberry-pie-inspired-overnight-oats-11721962" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Blueberry Pie-Inspired Overnight Oats&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3beans"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 3.Beans &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Beans and legumes may not be top of mind, but they are &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/you-just-started-anti-inflammatory-diet-recipes-to-make-first-8770807" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;part of an anti-inflammatory diet&lt;/a&gt; and contain many plant compounds that help reduce inflammation.&lt;strong&gt;  &lt;/strong&gt;Mohr notes,&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "The unsung hero of the nutrition world is fiber, and beans top the list as one of the best sources of fiber, among other nutrients as well." Hitting your fiber goals “can drastically lower the risk of cardiovascular disease, many cancers, and more," he adds. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Beans add a source of plant-based protein and can help improve the diversity of your gut microbiome, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/swap-to-lower-risk-of-heart-disease-and-diabetes-8679543" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;reduce your risk for heart disease and type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; and reduce chronic inflammation.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;The polyphenols in beans have antioxidant properties to help keep you healthy. Eating beans may also help with weight loss.&lt;span data-cite="5" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Mohr notes, "Beans are versatile, inexpensive and can complement almost any dish." Try them in soups, salads, casseroles and in this &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/roasted-vegetable-breakfast-grain-bowl-8742347" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Anti-Inflammatory Breakfast Bowl&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-4-cruciferous-vegetables"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 4. Cruciferous Vegetables &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Cruciferous vegetables, which include broccoli, cauliflower and Brussels sprouts, are a good source of antioxidants and fiber," shares Moore. They're known for their key flavonoids, such as quercetin and kaempferol, which help reduce inflammation. Cruciferous veggies, in particular, when eaten as part of a balanced diet, are &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/vegan-vegetarian-cancer-risk-study-11790465" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;linked to reduced cancer risk&lt;/a&gt;. That includes colorectal cancer and prostate cancer, two of the most common cancers in men.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span data-cite="6" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Moore likes roasting his veggies in the oven or in the air fryer with some salt and cheese. There are so many ways to enjoy more cruciferous vegetables: add kale to a salad, cabbage to stir-fry or add them to a soup, stew or curry like this &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/slow-cooker-cauliflower-chickpea-tikka-masala-8580545" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Slow-Cooker Cauliflower &amp;amp; Chickpea Tikka Masala&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-5-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 5. Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Mohr likes oats because they contain &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/fiber-foods-to-help-lower-cholesterol-11770161" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;soluble fiber, which helps reduce your risk of heart disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span data-cite="7" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Fiber is important for your health in many ways, and it helps reduce inflammation because of what it does in your gut. Eating more fiber from whole grains, including oats, increases the production of short-chain fatty acids in your colon, which feed your gut bacteria, helps reduce your risk of colon cancer, and reduces inflammation in the gut.&lt;span data-cite="8" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Fiber helps keep your blood sugar steadier, which can reduce oxidative stress from glucose spikes, and in turn tamps inflammation.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Oats also contain &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/the-top-nutrients-to-fight-inflammation-8675325" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;anti-inflammatory compounds, like avenanthramides&lt;/a&gt;, to help reduce oxidative stress in the body.&lt;span data-cite="7" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "They can be soaked overnight and enjoyed in the morning, cooked, or eaten raw, with milk and berries," adds Mohr. Get your fill with our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/high-protein-apple-peanut-butter-overnight-oats-11784430" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;High-Protein Apple &amp;amp; Peanut Butter Overnight Oats&lt;/a&gt; or try a classic &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/269639/old-fashioned-oatmeal/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Old-Fashioned Oatmeal&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-strategies-to-reduce-inflammation"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Strategies to Reduce Inflammation &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Manage stress: "&lt;/strong&gt;Uncontrolled and unmanaged stress is well studied and fairly destructive at the cellular level. Long-term, it can even contribute to chronic illness," notes Moore. "I tell men all the time, build and maintain appropriate outlets that help you manage your stress, whether that’s exercise, sports or engaging in hobbies."&lt;span data-cite="9" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Exercise regularly&lt;/strong&gt;: Research links exercise with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7908639/the-fastest-way-to-reduce-inflammation/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;reducing chronic low-grade inflammation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span data-cite="10" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Find movement that you enjoy and commit to staying active. That might look like walking, swimming, cycling, jogging, lifting weights or yoga. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Prioritize sleep&lt;/strong&gt;: It's recommended to get at least 7 hours of sleep per night but about a third of Americans aren't getting enough sleep. Falling short on sleep not only leaves you feeling tired, it can also &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-inflammation-ages-you-8744048" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;increase inflammation&lt;/a&gt;. Getting adequate sleep can also help reduce your risk of high blood pressure and type 2 diabetes.&lt;span data-cite="11" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span data-cite="12" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Turn off screens before bed, limit caffeine in the afternoon and try to establish a healthy evening routine to be sure you're getting enough shut-eye.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Limit alcohol:&lt;/strong&gt; While the occasional beer or glass of wine isn't likely to do much harm, drinking alcohol can cause oxidative stress and inflammation.&lt;span data-cite="13" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Keep your alcoholic drinks to a minimum for your overall health and for the most anti-inflammatory diet.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It might feel overwhelming to start making changes to your diet, but there's no need for an overhaul. Start small by adding a handful of berries to breakfast or making oatmeal a few times a week. "It’s never too late to start," adds Moore. "There’s still plenty of life ahead of you. Make a simple change today, do it again tomorrow, and keep that practice going until it becomes habitual."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While these anti-inflammatory foods can benefit everyone, they may be especially important for men over 50 to help improve gut health, heart health and reduce the risk of certain cancers. When you think of an overall diet to reduce inflammation, aim to eat a variety of colorful plant foods and a well-balanced diet. And it's not about perfection. "The most important factor is consistency with any lifestyle habit, whether it is a dietary change, lifestyle change or other," notes Mohr.  
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:48:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQYWUwd3I5Vlo1WVBEWjBjNkFDZTlzLW9TRnM3cUdNd0JacmI4Zzhmd2lZREJBQnlNdVlmV09lZWpvbkQ1TWdXSUVFNlo1b0Q0eDRLWEV2TC1iSUFHYjRkTTMyNzN6M0tSRDZvOGFWVHJuOTJCRXNxREJfemtlbk1yajdDX01BUktxY3c</guid></item><item><title>专家说，即使你锻炼身体，这种日常习惯也会缩短你的寿命--《独立报》</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/health-and-fitness/sitting-work-heart-disease-risk-live-longer-b2897509.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 gIQPHK sc-jbiisr-1 sc-1wfc891-0 fooWDH" id="main"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="big-letter"&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;re you sitting comfortably? Probably. According to the NHS, many UK adults spend upwards of nine hours each day sitting down. But too much sitting could seriously damage your health, according to &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.brunel.ac.uk/news-and-events/news/articles/Sitting-for-long-stretches-raises-heart-and-diabetes-risks"&gt;new research&lt;/a&gt; from Brunel University – even if you meet weekly &lt;a href="/topic/exercise"&gt;exercise&lt;/a&gt; recommendations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We reviewed the published evidence available regarding associations between sedentary behaviour [sitting or lying down] and different risk markers for &lt;a href="/topic/heart-disease"&gt;cardiovascular disease&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="/topic/diabetes"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; in people aged 60 and above,” says sedentary behaviour specialist Dr Daniel Bailey who is, perhaps predictably, stationed at a standing desk during our video call. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The review found that people who sat down for large chunks of their day were far more likely to have a higher waist circumference and body fat levels. They also recorded worse readings for several biomarkers linked to heart disease and diabetes, such as blood pressure, glucose levels, triglycerides and cholesterol. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Those risks were there regardless of the amount of physical activity these older adults were engaging in,” he adds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How much sitting is too much?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people spend upwards of eight hours at a desk each day. Add in the journey home from work and sofa time watching telly, and it’s easy to see how daily sitting times are so high for many of us. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Over the past few decades, we’ve seen all of this technology come into play, which gives us more opportunities to sit down,” Dr Bailey says. “With that, we have seen a massive increase in obesity and the diseases that come with it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data suggests older populations are the most sedentary group, and it is this demographic that will likely experience the greatest benefits from cutting down their daily sitting time. However, Dr Bailey adds, “It is an important consideration for all ages,” with studies on children and working-age adults also linking excessive sitting to increased health risks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Some studies show the threshold is somewhere between seven and 10 hours of sitting per day being too much,” Dr Bailey tells me. “That’s where your risk of early mortality and several different diseases really starts to increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/strength-training-for-longevity-b2826608.html"&gt;The science-backed exercise method that can help fight the effects of ageing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obviously, if you move less, you burn less energy during the day, which can contribute to weight gain. Muscles can lose strength when unused, joints can become stiff, and because you are asking less of your heart and lungs each day, fitness can fade away. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 bcLYNA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2019/11/08/16/woman-work-desk.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2019/11/08/16/woman-work-desk.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2019/11/08/16/woman-work-desk.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Many people spend nine hours or more of their day sitting down, according to the NHS" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-264724"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Many people spend nine hours or more of their day sitting down, according to the NHS&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research shows that the negative effects of excessive sedentary time are linked to the amount of time you spend sitting down at a time. “There have been a number of studies that show the benefits of breaking up your sedentary time every 30 to 60 minutes,” explains. Dr Bailey added that the mechanism behind this is not yet fully understood. He describes it as a series of “metabolic switches that help regulate blood sugar, glucose levels and cholesterol levels.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you’re not doing regular muscular contractions, these metabolic switches switch off. That’s when we get higher levels of glucose in the blood, higher cholesterol in the blood, and our blood pressure isn’t as well regulated.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/10000-steps-walking-workout-heart-health-b2886117.html"&gt;If you struggle to walk 10,000 steps a day, a scientist recommends trying this instead&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to fight back&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The primary ways to fight the negative effects of sitting down is to do less of it, and to ensure you are getting regular muscular contractions – ie using your muscles and moving. Based on his research, Dr Bailey prescribes trying to move in some form every 30 to 60 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 bHmhpR"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/24/13/iStock-2210705103.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/24/13/iStock-2210705103.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/24/13/iStock-2210705103.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Regular muscular contractions – through moving or simply standing up – can combat the negative effects of too much sitting" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-264725"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Regular muscular contractions – through moving or simply standing up – can combat the negative effects of too much sitting&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Every movement counts,” he says. “We’ve published a lot of studies in our group that show how regular, short bouts of light activity keep these metabolic switches turned on, and your blood sugar levels and cholesterol stay lower throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It doesn’t need to be structured exercise. Simply standing up seems to be beneficial in people that are overweight, obese or have type two diabetes. We’ve also looked at slow walking – people can get these metabolic benefits from things we do in our everyday lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Every half an hour, get up, move around for a few minutes, and that should help reduce your risk of the different diseases we’ve discussed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/exercise-snacking-workouts-heart-health-b2859776.html"&gt;The science-backed two-minute daily workouts for improving heart health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another easy change Dr Bailey suggests is reorganising your workstation to encourage more movement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Changing your setup so not everything is at hand can help,” he explains. “If you need a pen, to print something or put something in the bin, having those things located away from your desk might encourage you to move more often. And rather than sending a colleague an email, go and talk to them at their desk.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 iLHiBm"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/17/15/12/iStock-2194826147.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/17/15/12/iStock-2194826147.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/17/15/12/iStock-2194826147.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Dr Daniel Bailey recommends moving for a few minutes every half an hour where possible" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-264726"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Dr Daniel Bailey recommends moving for a few minutes every half an hour where possible&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;You could also make a conscious effort to move after you finish certain tasks at your computer, he adds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Sometimes you might ignore an alert to move from your wearable or an app because you are working on something. Instead, wait until the end of a task, then use that as your cue to get up and move around. If you’re working from home, you could spread your housework across the day rather than doing it in one big chunk, and use these opportunities to do it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Reap the benefits &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is that the results of reducing your daily sitting time and making even these small tweaks are pretty remarkable. “If we can limit our sedentary time and be physically active, we’re going to live a longer and healthier life, which is what I think we’re all striving for,” says Dr Bailey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Benefits you might see and feel quite quickly are [a] better mood, more energy and less fatigue. Then, in the longer term, you might start to see reductions in body fat or body weight because you are burning more calories from movement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The deeper impacts won’t be as obvious, but you could benefit from a reduction in blood sugar levels and a reduction in blood pressure. That will help reduce your risk of heart disease, stroke, diabetes and some cancers as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/heart-health-attack-cardio-exercise-b2785415.html"&gt;A cardiac nurse says these five daily behaviours can reduce your risk of heart disease&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxQM3ZmU291bUhjUFRiX0kwQUJsTDUtVFJybVlJR2MxbUlENW1yTnRQUENtZlMwYVBSMkRUWE5xeUUyMWlVcURISU5HUTkwNjk3dVFfNm15SFBNMWFRYmEybkxwYk55WmFkYkRySW1RS0FoaUVJMlM3dGRzOTR5VHU2WTNwSFRhZ2lLWXhUcWdtMkhWN09rWk51SDRlNzFqM2lTS0RKNjA2VXpGQQ</guid></item><item><title>官员说，感染麻疹的成年人在传染期间访问了克拉克县的高中- kptv.com</title><link>https://www.kptv.com/2026/01/24/adult-with-measles-visited-high-school-clark-county-while-contagious-county-officials-say/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body | article w-100"&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;RIDGEFIELD, Wash. (KPTV) - Clark County Public Health says an adult with a confirmed case of measles was at a local high school while they were contagious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Health officials say the person, whose vaccination status is unverified, was at Ridgefield High School from January 14 through January 16 while they were contagious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Anyone who was at Ridgefield High School during those days and has not been vaccinated or has not had measles in the past are at risk of getting sick, according to the department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Clark County Public Health says they are working with Ridgefield School District to identify students and staff who are not protected against measles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="w-100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;No other public locations have been identified as possible exposure sites in this case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Community members who gave questions about the vaccine or are unsure if they’re protected should contact their healthcare provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Vaccination records are also available through Washington’s &lt;a href="https://links.us1.defend.egress.com/Warning?crId=697439c7e1768fa5cf912299&amp;amp;Domain=gray.tv&amp;amp;Threat=eNpzrShJLcpLzAEADmkDRA%3D%3D&amp;amp;Lang=en&amp;amp;Base64Url=eNrLKCkpKLbS18-tzCzKzU_KzEnVS87P1QcAad4IoQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;@OriginalLink=myirmobile.com" rel="" title="https://links.us1.defend.egress.com/Warning?crId=697439c7e1768fa5cf912299&amp;amp;Domain=gray.tv&amp;amp;Threat=eNpzrShJLcpLzAEADmkDRA%3D%3D&amp;amp;Lang=en&amp;amp;Base64Url=eNrLKCkpKLbS18-tzCzKzU_KzEnVS87P1QcAad4IoQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;@OriginalLink=myirmobile.com"&gt;MyIR Mobile system&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="copyright |"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Copyright 2026 KPTV-KPDX. All rights reserved.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>kptv.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:33:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxPdHhCUE1RWXl5aDZacE1ka1hqRXppYlhtalRaN284MnJjUHVJLUJZaFlHMkhiek9yRUd0M2NSblBOV19WNHhPeG1kYzBrXzVZRVVab3BqVWt2QkwxM19kVE5KdjVDd1V1a1RUSkR3ekFzN2hSUC12bTYwaWwyYmpMcEx1TXYtSGtnNXdUOE1zNVlDQWV3OUVYNWUwVC1TdEM4UkswU2h6NEdyTzhiR3JMbGxzLTBSb2lpZjF0OGkzSQ</guid></item><item><title>星期五晚上争吵后，一名男子在东岭用车撞到另一名男子- newschannel9.com</title><link>https://newschannel9.com/news/local/man-hits-another-man-with-car-in-east-ridge-after-argument-friday-night</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText_storyText__C3hWI StoryText_storyText__C3hWI"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;EAST RIDGE, Tenn. — &lt;/span&gt;A man hit another man with his car in East Ridge after the two got into an argument Friday night, police say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;East Ridge Police say 2 men got into an argument in the 4000 block of Ringgold Road.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the men got into his car and hit the other with the vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police say the victim has non-life-threatening injuries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is a developing story and will be updated.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>newschannel9.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:03:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxPVFVsODJqUGY1bDAwQ3lLaFVhT0k5X09qbGEtOEtHaTl4LVU2cEh2dmNxMFpYRmc3Z3pSck1JckxOemM0eGVFTG9CX0pKRnFQMmV3TlhTUlhsdGFWYjlvX0c4X0xlSHZwUFY2aFd2by1lT2VNaUFpTGVJVUdzMV90M0kyTzU5N0JzVjB3WTNtTWtGTHA1dFFCbE1vd0tGY0FmcUFFSThwcHRwVUU</guid></item><item><title>在劳伦斯废水中高浓度检测到六种病毒- lawrencekstimes.com</title><link>https://lawrencekstimes.com/2026/01/23/kr-viruses-detected-lawrence/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;
		&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="heateor_sss_sharing_container heateor_sss_horizontal_sharing" data-heateor-sss-href="https://lawrencekstimes.com/2026/01/23/kr-viruses-detected-lawrence/"&gt;&lt;p class="heateor_sss_sharing_title"&gt;Share this post or save for later&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Lawrence sees early flu peak as some health care providers require masking&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Six viral diseases — including COVID-19, the flu and norovirus — have been found at high concentrations in Lawrence wastewater as Kansas communities face peak flu season.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;COVID-19, influenza A and B, RSV, human metapneumovirus, and norovirus have all been detected at high concentrations in Lawrence &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/4niF8mr" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;wastewater&lt;/a&gt; within the last three weeks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lawre-507379751df59046d9a030f03d59d14c lawre-content_2" id="lawre-507379751df59046d9a030f03d59d14c"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Wastewater data indicates trends of illnesses spreading within a community but does not correlate to exact case numbers, with doctors saying it’s normal to see high concentrations of respiratory illness during flu season. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Wastewater data does not measure individual cases, but it provides a reliable picture of how much virus is circulating in a community,” said Veronica White, preparedness and epidemiology coordinator for Lawrence-Douglas County Public Health. “This data captures viral genetic material shed by everyone using the sewer system. One factor that may be contributing to the higher concentrations of respiratory viruses seen in Lawrence’s wastewater is its larger population.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-coblocks-accordion"&gt;
&lt;div class="wp-block-coblocks-accordion-item has-custom-font"&gt;&lt;details&gt;&lt;summary class="wp-block-coblocks-accordion-item__title has-background has-text-color"&gt;Don’t miss a beat … Click here to sign up for our email newsletters&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;div class="wp-block-coblocks-accordion-item__content"&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://lawrencekstimes.com/newsletters/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click here&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about our newsletters first&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/details&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Lawrence is also seeing an early peak in influenza B compared to the rest of the country. Positive flu tests spiked the last week of 2025, with 32% of total flu tests coming back positive, according to data from the University of Kansas Health System.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Some health care providers such as Watkins Health Center at the University of Kansas are requiring masks for all visitors, patients and staff due to a “record surge in respiratory illnesses,” according to a sign at the front door.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;White said early rise in the flu doesn’t indicate a more dangerous flu season, but rather earlier circulation of the virus than usual. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Identifying this trend early through wastewater data allows people to take preventive steps, such as getting vaccinated, monitoring symptoms, and staying home when sick,” White said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Wastewater data also indicated that a newer strain of COVID, known as the XFG or the Stratus variant, has accounted for 82.5% of positive COVID samples, with concentrations increasing by 25% in the last month. The variant has also been increasing nationally, White said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Dana Hawkinson, medical director for Infection Control and Prevention program at University of Kansas Health System, said there are still large populations of people across the state who have not received a flu shot.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“There have been a large number of people ill and circulators too in our communities. But (the flu) still remains at a high level at this point in time,” Hawkinson said. “There have been extremely low numbers of people not getting the vaccine. We know that we can help prevent this and people’s chances of severe illness and death with it.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Steve Stites, chief medical officer at the University of Kansas Health System, said that &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/p7chEnUW0EI?si=2KN1bC2byLQI_f0H&amp;amp;t=678" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;vaccines&lt;/a&gt; are incredibly safe and effective.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Hawkinson said flu symptoms include fever, cough, congestion, body aches and a sore throat rather than stomach bug symptoms, with the definitions often getting mixed up during flu season.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p class="lawre-c9b79c6582bb301aaf6b39082e01c8ce lawre-bonus-banners" id="lawre-c9b79c6582bb301aaf6b39082e01c8ce"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Wastewater data has also indicated that Salina is seeing medium concentrations of the same illnesses, except for influenza A, which is considered to be at a high concentration.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Based on the data, we expect viral activity to continue in both Lawrence and Salina over the next few weeks,” White said. “As we move through flu season, we anticipate seeing elevated influenza activity reflected in the wastewater, especially as the season approaches its typical peak.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Medical experts continue to advise washing hands, covering coughs and not going into large public spaces when sick to prevent illnesses from spreading.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“You can still go get the flu vaccine,” Hawkinson said. “It’s still recommended, and you can do it now to protect yourself from infection.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://kansasreflector.com/"&gt;Kansas Reflector&lt;/a&gt; is part of States Newsroom, a network of news bureaus supported by grants and a coalition of donors as a 501c(3) public charity. Kansas Reflector maintains editorial independence. Contact Editor Sherman Smith for questions: &lt;a href="mailto:info@kansasreflector.com"&gt;info@kansasreflector.com&lt;/a&gt;. Follow Kansas Reflector on &lt;a href="https://facebook.com/kansasreflector"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/@kansasreflector"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-no-padding"&gt;&lt;div class="wp-block-group__inner-container is-layout-flow wp-block-group-is-layout-flow"&gt;




&lt;h5 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Don’t miss a beat — get the latest news from the Times delivered to your inbox:&lt;/h5&gt;






&lt;p class="has-helvetica-font-family has-custom-font"&gt;&lt;a href="https://lawrencekstimes.com/newsletters/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click here&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about our newsletters first&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;







&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Latest Lawrence news:&lt;/h3&gt;


&lt;div id="block-f78eea-0ae4-49" class="wp-block-gutenbee-post-types block-f78eea-0ae4-49 is-style-ignition-public-opinion-entries-compact"&gt;&lt;div class="row row-items row-columns-1"&gt;								&lt;div class="lawrence-news public-safety term-73 term-592 col-12"&gt;
&lt;article id="entry-110792" class="entry-item entry-item-media post-110792 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-lawrence-news category-public-safety tag-kswx tag-top2 pmpro-has-access"&gt;
		&lt;figure class="entry-thumb"&gt;
		&lt;a href="https://lawrencekstimes.com/2026/01/23/kswx-20260123-update/"&gt;
			&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx-2.jpg?fit=768%2C432&amp;amp;ssl=1" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx-2.jpg?w=1200&amp;amp;ssl=1 1200w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx-2.jpg?resize=300%2C169&amp;amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx-2.jpg?resize=1024%2C576&amp;amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx-2.jpg?resize=150%2C84&amp;amp;ssl=1 150w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx-2.jpg?resize=779%2C438&amp;amp;ssl=1 779w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx-2.jpg?resize=880%2C495&amp;amp;ssl=1 880w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx-2.jpg?resize=525%2C295&amp;amp;ssl=1 525w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px"&gt;		&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
	
	&lt;div class="entry-item-content"&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="entry-item-excerpt"&gt;
			&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="heateor_sss_sharing_container heateor_sss_horizontal_sharing" data-heateor-sss-href="https://lawrencekstimes.com/2026/01/23/kswx-20260123-update/"&gt;&lt;p class="heateor_sss_sharing_title"&gt;Share this post or save for later&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several inches of snow, extreme cold and dangerous wind chills are en route to Lawrence. A cold weather advisory and winter storm warning will be in effect starting Friday evening. &lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;				&lt;div class="lawrence-news public-safety term-73 term-592 col-12"&gt;
&lt;article id="entry-110782" class="entry-item entry-item-media post-110782 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-lawrence-news category-public-safety tag-kswx pmpro-has-access"&gt;
		&lt;figure class="entry-thumb"&gt;
		&lt;a href="https://lawrencekstimes.com/2026/01/23/kswx-closures-20260123/"&gt;
			&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx.jpg?fit=768%2C432&amp;amp;ssl=1" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx.jpg?w=1200&amp;amp;ssl=1 1200w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx.jpg?resize=300%2C169&amp;amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx.jpg?resize=1024%2C576&amp;amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx.jpg?resize=150%2C84&amp;amp;ssl=1 150w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx.jpg?resize=779%2C438&amp;amp;ssl=1 779w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx.jpg?resize=880%2C495&amp;amp;ssl=1 880w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-kswx.jpg?resize=525%2C295&amp;amp;ssl=1 525w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px"&gt;		&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
	
	&lt;div class="entry-item-content"&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="entry-item-excerpt"&gt;
			&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="heateor_sss_sharing_container heateor_sss_horizontal_sharing" data-heateor-sss-href="https://lawrencekstimes.com/2026/01/23/kswx-closures-20260123/"&gt;&lt;p class="heateor_sss_sharing_title"&gt;Share this post or save for later&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Lawrence Public Library will be closed Saturday as heavy snow is in the forecast for the area and most of the state. We’ll add other closures here as we receive them. &lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;				&lt;div class="lawrence-news public-safety term-73 term-592 col-12"&gt;
&lt;article id="entry-110767" class="entry-item entry-item-media post-110767 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-lawrence-news category-public-safety tag-by-molly-adams tag-lpd tag-shooting tag-top1 pmpro-has-access"&gt;
		&lt;figure class="entry-thumb"&gt;
		&lt;a href="https://lawrencekstimes.com/2026/01/23/20260123-shooting/"&gt;
			&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-Apartment-shooting-lynch-ct-1.jpg?fit=701%2C438&amp;amp;ssl=1" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-Apartment-shooting-lynch-ct-1.jpg?w=1200&amp;amp;ssl=1 1200w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-Apartment-shooting-lynch-ct-1.jpg?resize=300%2C188&amp;amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-Apartment-shooting-lynch-ct-1.jpg?resize=1024%2C640&amp;amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-Apartment-shooting-lynch-ct-1.jpg?resize=150%2C94&amp;amp;ssl=1 150w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-Apartment-shooting-lynch-ct-1.jpg?resize=701%2C438&amp;amp;ssl=1 701w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-Apartment-shooting-lynch-ct-1.jpg?resize=792%2C495&amp;amp;ssl=1 792w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/20260123-Apartment-shooting-lynch-ct-1.jpg?resize=525%2C328&amp;amp;ssl=1 525w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 701px) 100vw, 701px"&gt;&lt;span class="media-credit"&gt;Molly Adams / Lawrence Times&lt;/span&gt;		&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
	
	&lt;div class="entry-item-content"&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="entry-item-excerpt"&gt;
			&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="heateor_sss_sharing_container heateor_sss_horizontal_sharing" data-heateor-sss-href="https://lawrencekstimes.com/2026/01/23/20260123-shooting/"&gt;&lt;p class="heateor_sss_sharing_title"&gt;Share this post or save for later&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A person is in critical condition following a shooting Friday afternoon in the Hawks Pointe apartment complex. Police say they have arrested a man who they suspect “went to an apartment, knocked on the door, then shot another man at the entrance.”&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;				&lt;div class="edu lawrence-news local-gov term-4 term-73 term-8 col-12"&gt;
&lt;article id="entry-110743" class="entry-item entry-item-media post-110743 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-edu category-lawrence-news category-local-gov tag-lawrence-ks-school-board tag-lawrence-public-schools tag-usd-497 pmpro-has-access"&gt;
		&lt;figure class="entry-thumb"&gt;
		&lt;a href="https://lawrencekstimes.com/2026/01/23/usd497bd-20260126pre/"&gt;
			&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/20230724-School-Board-Meeting-19.jpg?fit=768%2C432&amp;amp;ssl=1" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/20230724-School-Board-Meeting-19.jpg?w=1200&amp;amp;ssl=1 1200w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/20230724-School-Board-Meeting-19.jpg?resize=300%2C169&amp;amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/20230724-School-Board-Meeting-19.jpg?resize=1024%2C576&amp;amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/20230724-School-Board-Meeting-19.jpg?resize=150%2C84&amp;amp;ssl=1 150w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/20230724-School-Board-Meeting-19.jpg?resize=779%2C438&amp;amp;ssl=1 779w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/20230724-School-Board-Meeting-19.jpg?resize=880%2C495&amp;amp;ssl=1 880w, https://i0.wp.com/lawrencekstimes.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/20230724-School-Board-Meeting-19.jpg?resize=560%2C315&amp;amp;ssl=1 560w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px"&gt;		&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
	
	&lt;div class="entry-item-content"&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="entry-item-excerpt"&gt;
			&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="heateor_sss_sharing_container heateor_sss_horizontal_sharing" data-heateor-sss-href="https://lawrencekstimes.com/2026/01/23/usd497bd-20260126pre/"&gt;&lt;p class="heateor_sss_sharing_title"&gt;Share this post or save for later&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="heateorSssClear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Lawrence school board on Monday will consider approving a tax incentive for developments at the former Reuter buildings, multiyear district calendars for 2026-27 and 2027-28, and a 4.5% increase to preschool tuition. &lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p class="has-text-align-right has-helvetica-font-family has-custom-font"&gt;&lt;a href="https://lawrencekstimes.com/news/" data-type="page" data-id="8856"&gt;MORE …&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;/div&gt;

			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>lawrencekstimes.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:02:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE9pb01FMmNpVlZWT0ltY0hndkxqV0VHRGZOekFxUW8yRkw4TWU5ZTJ3aGpVSXUxc1JpRTQxWl9JWm5IM0ZjdGp2Uk50TTFVc1Zpb0lCbFhUcGVsUnJMUTZHQVZoMGhSRE9obXpNLXk0R3RwWm1NQnNr</guid></item><item><title>美国疫苗小组负责人质疑脊髓灰质炎建议-路透社</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-vaccine-panel-head-questions-polio-recommendation-2026-01-23/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Reuters</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:04:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPODk1VnVxYTlXWTI2bjZKY21kWExoaV9HdlZRand3SlZrSnhxeGM5cFVnaFNYZGdrS09BY3VKN2YzTWw5SDU1eVMwc1JIX3Q0eURadlhpc2h0dVhsdng3UWV0S0I1WXFBSFpzX1ItYVRnUFEtV09CMnlJMEo5cmEzc3ZrcEpSU2pIZjFnaTI0WW1LQWl3TlZaX0dGdS1uQXMxQm1CVkZpNjFieE9ya2R1S1RYQkw2bzJ1TW9ncUlpN05WUQ</guid></item><item><title>研究揭示了您每周需要进行多少运动来控制血压- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/study-reveals-how-much-exercise-you-need-weekly-to-control-blood-pressure</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;When it comes to exercising for your heart's sake, you don't want to peak too early in life. Research suggests that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/turning-point-in-heart-health-occurs-at-1-key-age-its-younger-than-youd-think"&gt;to protect yourself&lt;/a&gt; against high blood pressure in your twilight years, you need to keep your exercise levels up through middle age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But according to a study of more than 5,000 people across four US cities, social factors can make this more difficult for some people than others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Teenagers and those in their early 20s may be physically active but these patterns change with age," epidemiologist Kirsten Bibbins-Domingo from the University of California, San Francisco (UCSF) &lt;a href="https://www.ucsf.edu/news/2021/04/420281/want-be-robust-40-plus-meeting-minimum-exercise-guidelines-wont-cut-it"&gt;explained&lt;/a&gt; in April 2021, when the research was published.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-simple-daily-habit-could-help-lower-your-blood-pressure"&gt;This Simple Daily Habit Could Help Lower Your Blood Pressure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Numerous studies have shown that exercise lowers blood pressure, but the 2021 research suggests that "maintaining physical activity during young adulthood – at higher levels than previously recommended – may be particularly important," Bibbins-Domingo &lt;a href="https://www.ucsf.edu/news/2021/04/420281/want-be-robust-40-plus-meeting-minimum-exercise-guidelines-wont-cut-it"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_96226" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-96226" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2023/05/ExerciseScienceWeightLoss-642x260.jpg" alt="Older man running on street wearing orange t-shirt." class="wp-image-96226 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2023/05/ExerciseScienceWeightLoss-642x260.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2023/05/ExerciseScienceWeightLoss.jpg 1024w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2023/05/ExerciseScienceWeightLoss-768x311.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2023/05/ExerciseScienceWeightLoss-600x243.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-96226" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Maintaining physical activity could be even more important than we knew. (South_agency/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hypertension, also known as high blood pressure, is a serious condition affecting billions of people worldwide. It can lead to heart attacks and stroke; it's also a risk factor for &lt;a href="study-suggests-diabetes-and-high-blood-pressure-might-also-be-affecting-your-mind" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;developing dementia in later life&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-blood-pressure-guidelines-mean-you-could-now-have-hypertension"&gt;New Blood Pressure Guidelines Mean You Could Now Have Hypertension&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upwards of one in four men and about every fifth woman has hypertension, &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/health-topics/hypertension/#tab=tab_1"&gt;according to the World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;. But most people with high blood pressure don't even know they have it – hence why it's often called the "silent killer".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet there are ways to turn high blood pressure around: exercise is the focus of this study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over 5,100 adults were recruited for the study, which tracked their health over three decades through physical assessments and questionnaires on exercise habits, smoking status, and alcohol intake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At each clinical assessment, blood pressure was measured three times, 1 minute apart, and, for data analysis, participants were grouped into four categories by race and gender.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/castingcall?utm_source=SA_website&amp;amp;utm_medium=article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=casting_call"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg" alt="Audition now for ScienceAlert's Casting Call" class="alignnone wp-image-189354 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-1200x509.jpg 1200w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1.jpg 1266w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across the board – amongst men, women, and in both racial groups – levels of physical activity slumped from 18 to 40 years of age, with rates of hypertension rising and physical activity falling over subsequent decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the researchers, this suggests that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-simple-change-to-your-standing-desk-could-make-workdays-healthier"&gt;young adulthood is an important window for intervening&lt;/a&gt; to prevent midlife hypertension with health promotion programs designed to boost exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-5-minute-workout-each-day-can-still-make-a-huge-health-difference"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A 5-Minute Workout Each Day Can Still Make a Huge Health Difference&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Nearly half of our participants in young adulthood had suboptimal levels of physical activity, which was significantly associated with the onset of hypertension, indicating that we need to raise the minimum standard for physical activity," &lt;a href="https://www.ucsf.edu/news/2021/04/420281/want-be-robust-40-plus-meeting-minimum-exercise-guidelines-wont-cut-it"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; lead author Jason Nagata, a UCSF expert in young adult medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_80404" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-80404" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2022/11/DumbbellExercise-642x260.jpg" alt="Someone lifting a dumbbell behind their head" class="wp-image-80404 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2022/11/DumbbellExercise-642x260.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2022/11/DumbbellExercise.jpg 1024w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2022/11/DumbbellExercise-768x311.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2022/11/DumbbellExercise-600x243.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-80404" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Physical activity often declines with age, but this can have consequences for your health. (Watchara Piriyaputtanapun/Moment/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the researchers looked at people who had done 5 hours of moderate exercise a week during early adulthood – double the minimum amount currently recommended for adults – they found that this level of activity lowered the risk of hypertension considerably, especially if people maintained their exercise habits until age 60.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Achieving at least twice the current minimum adult [physical activity] guidelines may be more beneficial for the prevention of hypertension than simply meeting the minimum guidelines," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.amepre.2020.12.018"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; in their paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it's not easy to step up physical activity each week amid life-changing decisions and growing responsibilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This might be especially the case after high school when opportunities for physical activity diminish as young adults transition to college, the workforce, and parenthood, and leisure time is eroded," &lt;a href="https://www.ucsf.edu/news/2021/04/420281/want-be-robust-40-plus-meeting-minimum-exercise-guidelines-wont-cut-it"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; Nagata.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/not-all-sitting-is-equal-one-type-was-just-linked-to-better-brain-health"&gt;Not All Sitting Is Equal. One Type Was Just Linked to Better Brain Health.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for another sobering truth, the study also showed how Black men and Black women experience starkly different health trajectories compared to their White counterparts. At 40 years of age, physical activity levels plateaued among White men and women, whereas activity levels in Black participants continued to decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By age 45, Black women surpassed White men in rates of hypertension, while White women in the study experienced the lowest rates of hypertension through midlife.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And by age 60, between 80 and 90 percent of Black men and women had hypertension, compared with just below 70 percent for White men and around half of White women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team attributed these well-known racial disparities to a multitude of social and economic factors; however, these factors were not assessed in this study, although high school education was noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although Black male youth may have high engagement in sports, socioeconomic factors, neighborhood environments, and work or family responsibilities may prevent continued engagement in physical activity through adulthood," Nagata &lt;a href="https://www.ucsf.edu/news/2021/04/420281/want-be-robust-40-plus-meeting-minimum-exercise-guidelines-wont-cut-it"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.amepre.2020.12.018"&gt;American Journal of Preventive Medicine.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in April 2021.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:03:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxQQTFuMkRieWFxdkQydVpHSUFiS2NJSi0zQ3Y0V3pvNlJjUHlwV1BFa3dTclpLNGZSMktTQ3IzNk5PTEwzbjhSbXNySFdxTTVoUWpCU0lFUU5oOXIwUkdvSXQ2NDhnV1hPcEVMNlpWR1lXSl9GVnVRRkVVdEs2YWw2OTdZYkliYkNGS1hZRUt4ZnpRdlhpNm9xcmxQVXBtRG5CQTM2RA</guid></item><item><title>未接种疫苗的儿童标志着湾区县十多年来首例麻疹病例- SFGATE</title><link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/unvaccinated-child-bay-area-measles-21311776.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>SFGATE</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:59:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxQVmh4MXJjaXhITDkxTzF0T0ZZOC1MMlc3VVJEOU1WZDY3cG5NcXJJT3ZhZ3hRVmM0bjJmcURYVFJLUC1nbHIxM3VQaTNTa3BfbDVyb1dCQlZqRTVBT3FGcG51b3QzT0NCWTBBdE1BNDN3bUhULWJWMWUwQi13RTZKRms5RWpiT0tHS25iTGlfdks</guid></item><item><title>科学家可能已经找到了复活旧细胞的蓝图- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-may-have-found-a-blueprint-to-revive-old-cells</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Many of the body's processes slow down or falter as we get older, including &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/body-resurrects-cells-marked-for-death-solving-a-50-year-mystery"&gt;tissue regeneration&lt;/a&gt;. In a new study, researchers detail a promising method to get this vital repair work back up to speed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, from a team at the University of California, San Francisco, identified four &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transcription_factor"&gt;transcription factors&lt;/a&gt; – proteins that control the activity of other genes – that have a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-discover-a-way-to-recharge-aging-human-cells"&gt;rejuvenating effect&lt;/a&gt; on cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the researchers boosted production of one of these transcription factors in the liver cells of elderly mice, they noticed numerous benefits: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/5-daily-habits-could-be-causing-your-liver-serious-harm"&gt;fat and scarring&lt;/a&gt; were significantly reduced, and glucose tolerance improved – all signs of a more youthful organ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/blood-of-exceptionally-long-lived-people-reveals-crucial-differences"&gt;Blood of Exceptionally Long-Lived People Reveals Crucial Differences&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team also tinkered with the levels of all four transcription factors in lab-grown human &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fibroblast"&gt;fibroblast cells&lt;/a&gt;. Fibroblasts make up connective tissue and provide scaffolding around other cells and organs. Again, multiple signs of youthfulness were spotted as a result, including increased cell division and boosted energy levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"By altering gene expression using the transcription factors we identified, old fibroblasts behaved as if they were younger, and improved the health of old mice," &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1112231"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; biochemist Hao Li.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_188901" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188901" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/LiverScarring.jpg" alt="Liver scarring diagram" class="wp-image-188901 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/LiverScarring.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/LiverScarring-600x419.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-188901" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Increasing the expression of EZH2 (bottom row), one of four transcription factors identified, reduced liver scarring (blue stain) in older mice compared to controls (top row). (Sengstack et al., &lt;em&gt;PNAS&lt;/em&gt;, 2026)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;To identify the four key transcription factors, the researchers first compared old and young human fibroblast cells using a computational model to see how &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/hundreds-of-genes-act-differently-in-male-vs-female-brains-scientists-discover"&gt;gene expression&lt;/a&gt; differed with age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having drawn up a shortlist of 200 transcription factors that could be controlling the 'youthfulness' of cells, they began systematically toggling them on and off – changing the transcription factors produced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results of this tinkering led the researchers to the final four transcription factors that they tested in more detail: E2F3, EZH2, STAT3, and ZFX. Altering the levels of these factors in liver cells of mice and human fibroblast cells grown in plastic dishes shifted the cells &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-restore-aging-blood-stem-cells-to-a-more-youthful-state-in-mice"&gt;towards a younger mode&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/castingcall?utm_source=SA_website&amp;amp;utm_medium=article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=casting_call"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg" alt="Audition now for ScienceAlert's Casting Call" class="alignnone wp-image-189354 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-1200x509.jpg 1200w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1.jpg 1266w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fact that these proteins had an effect across two different species and cell types suggests we could be looking at a universal blueprint of sorts, one that could be broadly applied to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/young-immune-cells-partly-reverse-alzheimers-symptoms-in-mice"&gt;reactivate youthful states&lt;/a&gt; in older cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These results suggest a shared set of molecular requirements for cellular and tissue rejuvenation across species," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.2515183123"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's still early days for this research, and we're not yet talking about &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/gains-in-human-life-expectancy-may-have-already-passed-their-peak"&gt;extending lifespans&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/axolotl-discovery-brings-us-closer-than-ever-to-regrowing-human-limbs"&gt;replacing limbs&lt;/a&gt; or rejuvenating the whole body. We only have the results from a few cell types.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long-term safety needs to be considered, too. The experiments in mice lasted only a few weeks, so we still don't know what effects rejuvenating cells in this manner might have over extended periods. Too much cell growth connected to EZH2 has been &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.1933744100"&gt;linked with cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, with a global population that's growing older and living longer, potential ways of keeping our bodies &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-reveal-turning-point-when-your-bodys-aging-accelerates"&gt;healthier for longer&lt;/a&gt; should warrant further investigation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our work opens up exciting new opportunities to understand and ultimately reverse aging-related diseases," &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1112231"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; biochemist Janine Sengstack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.2515183123"&gt;&lt;em&gt;PNAS&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:01:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxNTXBBVWxDUTBCNjZFbXlOZGliOVVib0ZrdjFOOTVSSjV6SFd5c0hjQ1RNVkVYZDIwdElkdXU1VEdtUkN1aDR5VGN2QjdaNVF0V2hrckpmQldQTmNEcFlEN0VILXhyMlU2SXl1ZFNhZ2N2alA4c1I0UGlmTDNIZkwzSGpTTi03X091Z3Zkcjhxbw</guid></item><item><title>卫生官员表示，新不伦瑞克省没有神秘脑部疾病的证据- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cy4qwyp3gpno</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A report by Canadian officials has found no evidence of a new disease after hundreds of reports of neurological symptoms led to claims of a mystery brain condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The results of the investigation by New Brunswick's Chief Medical Officer of Health add to a growing body of research that suggests patients may have diagnosable illnesses instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;About 500 people in New Brunswick and other provinces have been identified by neurologist Dr Alier Marrero as having unexplained neurological symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Officials said they also found no evidence to support Marrero's claims that patients' symptoms were caused by elevated levels of herbicides and heavy metals. The BBC has contacted Marrero for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Regardless of the findings of our investigation, the fact remains there are patients who are very ill and need support," said New Brunswick's chief medical officer of health Dr Yves Léger on Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c623r47d67lo" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;BBC report published earlier this month&lt;/a&gt; questioned the legitimacy of the cluster of patients and asked whether hundreds may have been misdiagnosed by Marrero, and had suffered instead from known neurological illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The BBC report also revealed that at least one cluster patient had opted for death via medically assisted dying – with the mystery disease cited as the cause on the death certificate – and that at least one other patient was considering medically assisted dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The provincial study published on Friday examined the cases of 222 of Marrero's patients and reviewed results of extensive testing he had ordered on the patients which he said showed elevated levels of herbicides and heavy metals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;After comparisons with test results from among the broader population in the Atlantic Canada region, the province's findings showed that the herbicide levels among the cluster patients were normal, officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A small number of patients did show higher than expected levels of heavy metals, the report found, but officials said it was difficult to confirm the results because of issues with the way they had been tested and they said there was no clear evidence to suggest the elevated levels could have led to adverse neurological health effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Officials said the provincial review was limited by several factors, including that some of Marrero's initial testing had not been done according to correct guidelines and that most patients had not been regularly retested to establish a pattern of elevated levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The report also found that close to 60% of patients in the group had also been seen by a second neurologist, and that none of the other neurologists had raised concerns to health authorities regarding the patients' conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In response to the report's findings, health officials said that any patient referred to the province with an unexplained neurological condition would now have to be examined by two separate specialists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Léger told reporters on Friday that there was "mounting evidence that these patients have diagnosable conditions", adding that the province was "certainly concerned about that and about patient care".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He said the province's findings would be shared with Marrero, and that it was important the neurologist "understand what we've found from our analysis".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The data will also be shared with the Public Health Agency of Canada, Leger said, which will conduct a further review.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Sarah Nesbitt, a patient in the cluster and an environmental advocate, said she was concerned about the limitations of the study and that some patients did prove to have elevated levels of metals in their system. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But Nesbitt told the BBC she is hopeful that this a step towards helping patients, especially those with elevated levels, get more answers and additional support for their illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"At the end of the day, it's about finding the problem with the patients, helping them heal or cure or symptom manage," she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Friday's study is the second conducted by the province into the purported mystery illness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Results of the previous study, which examined the first 48 patients in the cluster, was published in 2022 and similarly found no common exposures and concluded the patients were likely suffering from a range of different illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Last year, a separate research paper published by the JAMA neurology journal echoed the conclusions of the 2022 provincial report. The paper, based on a review of 25 cluster cases, found that the patients had all suffered from known and diagnosable illnesses including cancer and dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The lead author of the JAMA paper, Dr Anthony Lang, told the BBC on Friday that the provincial report "confirms our suspicion or belief that there was no environmental factor that could have accounted for such a broad range of neurological problems". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"There was no consistent neurological disease that we had seen in this small group of patients we described," Lang added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"So this just confirms exactly what we've suspected and really emphasises the suffering and pain that patients and families have had."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Nesbitt and other patients have rejected accusations that Marrero has misdiagnosed patients, and said he rightfully raised concerns about their test results of elevated metals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She added some patients have expressed they do not want to see another neurologist "because they don't trust anybody anymore".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"He's a kind man, he's intelligent, he does due diligence," Nesbitt said, adding that he has done a considerable amount of testing on patients to help give them answers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero did not immediately reply to a request for comment about Friday's report. In September, he told the BBC that other senior federal and provincial scientists had also believed there was a novel syndrome in New Brunswick and that he was now being portrayed as the sole purveyor of the idea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They are trying to present me as it," he said. "I was part of it, but I was not it. The only difference is, when the table was empty, I stayed."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:01:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1VMzBWT2dPdmFsTTlfbUhfc3ZncVlEMlV3NGRhS3J3SU10TGkxRERiLXp1RVFzN1NPRzVBUnlKQmVkRmdZQ2JMdmM0ZWc2bHIxMjdBWmI5a3RPd9IBX0FVX3lxTFBwTFVWUjFHV0tkUG43M3NyRVFjc0d6N3c0aWU4ZF9xVU5BSWMtUjhib1ZYUC1hOEEtOW96Rk83cEZIQkRpN1NoNEY4YWpFYTE1bnBaUnFPU0JIZlEtdTlz</guid></item><item><title>湾区新增麻疹病例：如何检查疫苗接种状况和谁需要加强疫苗接种- KQED</title><link>https://www.kqed.org/news/12070907/measles-san-francisco-bay-area-2026-is-there-outbreak-mmr-vaccine-booster</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Most Americans who went to school in America will have both MMR vaccines completed, and then should be protected against the measles,” Napa public health officer Dr. Christine Wu said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s also a combined Measles, Mumps, Rubella and Varicella, or MMRV, vaccine, but it’s &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/vpd/mmr/public/index.html"&gt;only licensed&lt;/a&gt; for use in children between ages 1 to 12 years old.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CDPH &lt;a href="https://myturn.ca.gov/en_US/Questions-and-answers.html?name=question&amp;amp;tab=9"&gt;affirms&lt;/a&gt; that “MMR vaccines are very safe and effective,” and as with “any medicine, there can be side effects, but they are usually mild and go away on their own.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The CDC recommends that everyone over 12 months of age be vaccinated against measles, with children receiving the first of &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/vpd/mmr/public/index.html"&gt;two doses of the MMR vaccine &lt;/a&gt;between 12 to 15 months of age. The second dose is recommended between 4 to 6 years of age. This vaccine provides lifetime protection against measles, so if you got your MMR vaccine as a child, you’re considered up-to-date on your vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to CDC data from the 2023-24 school year, California has &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html"&gt;a 96.2% &lt;/a&gt;vaccination rate against measles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If &lt;a id="booster"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;I’m up-to-date on my measles vaccines, do I need a measles booster?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No. The CDC’s longtime advice says: If you had two doses of measles vaccine as a child according to the U.S. &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/questions.html?CDC_AAref_Val=https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/faqs.html"&gt;vaccination schedule&lt;/a&gt;, the CDC considers you “protected for life” and you “do not ever need a booster dose.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fact, said Wu, the second dose of your MMR vaccine is actually considered your booster “that provides a lifelong immunity.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are, however, two groups of older adults who received childhood measles vaccinations but who should still talk to their health care provider about possibly getting another vaccination:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People born between 1957 and 1969&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are in this age group, which would make you between 56 and 68 years old today, it’s likely you only received one dose of the MMR vaccine and should consider getting a second dose, according to Bay Area health officers in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What if you were born before 1957?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the CDC, everyone born before this year is presumed to have&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/vpd/mmr/hcp/recommendations.html#immunity"&gt; immunity from measles &lt;/a&gt;from a previous infection, given how widespread the virus was during that period — although &lt;a href="https://www.yalemedicine.org/news/should-you-get-a-measles-vaccine-booster"&gt;people &lt;/a&gt;in this age group who work in health care and who don’t have any written evidence of this immunity should get the MMR vaccine anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People who received the ‘killed’ measles vaccine between 1963 and 1967&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The “killed,” or inactivated, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/questions.html?CDC_AAref_Val=https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/faqs.html#cdc_generic_section_1-protection-against-measles"&gt;measles vaccine &lt;/a&gt;was an earlier formulation of the measles vaccine that was only used for this brief period in the 1960s, for fewer than one million people. Because it was found to be ineffective and replaced with the current live vaccine, people who know they received this particular version of the vaccine “should talk to their health care provider about&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/questions.html?CDC_AAref_Val=https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/faqs.html#cdc_generic_section_1-protection-against-measles"&gt; getting revaccinated&lt;/a&gt;” with the MMR vaccine, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There is no harm in &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/questions.html"&gt;getting another dose &lt;/a&gt;of MMR vaccine if you may already be immune to measles (or mumps or rubella),” according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I don’t know if I’m vaccinated against measles. How can I check?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s no national organization that maintains Americans’&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines-adults/recommended-vaccines/keeping-vaccine-records-up-to-date.html?CDC_AAref_Val=https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/adults/vaccination-records.html"&gt; vaccination records&lt;/a&gt;. Ways that the CDC suggests to track down your own records include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ask your parents or caregivers for &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines-children/records/?CDC_AAref_Val=https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/parents/records/keeping-track.html"&gt;records &lt;/a&gt;of your childhood immunizations (or look in saved documents from your childhood, like baby books).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consult a state immunization registry like the California Department of Public Health’s &lt;a href="https://myvaccinerecord.cdph.ca.gov/"&gt;Digital Vaccine Record &lt;/a&gt;portal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ask your doctor or public health clinic, but remember that these records may only be stored for a limited time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The CDC&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines-adults/recommended-vaccines/keeping-vaccine-records-up-to-date.html?CDC_AAref_Val=https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/adults/vaccination-records.html"&gt; has a guide &lt;/a&gt;to tracking down your vaccination records.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_11980289" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://cdn.kqed.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/10/2024/03/GettyImages-1718981175_qut.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-11980289" src="https://cdn.kqed.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/10/2024/03/GettyImages-1718981175_qut.jpg" alt="A pair of gloved hands fills a syringe from a vial of vaccine." srcset="https://cdn.kqed.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/10/2024/03/GettyImages-1718981175_qut.jpg 1920w, https://cdn.kqed.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/10/2024/03/GettyImages-1718981175_qut-800x534.jpg 800w, https://cdn.kqed.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/10/2024/03/GettyImages-1718981175_qut-1020x681.jpg 1020w, https://cdn.kqed.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/10/2024/03/GettyImages-1718981175_qut-160x107.jpg 160w, https://cdn.kqed.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/10/2024/03/GettyImages-1718981175_qut-1536x1025.jpg 1536w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The measles vaccine is offered as part of routine childhood immunizations in the United States. &lt;cite&gt;(Andrii Zorii/Getty )&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another reason to check your vaccination status if you’re unsure: Possessing documentation of your vaccination status “can help you avoid being quarantined if you are exposed,” according to a 2025 advisory from Bay Area health officers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And if you can’t find any sign that you or your family have received a measles vaccine?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Teenagers and adults with no evidence of immunity should be vaccinated right away,” they added — something the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines-adults/recommended-vaccines/keeping-vaccine-records-up-to-date.html?CDC_AAref_Val=https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/adults/vaccination-records.html"&gt;CDC echoes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your health provider can also order “a simple blood test,” said Wu, to check whether or not you are immune from measles, either from vaccination or from a childhood infection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If I’m vaccinated,&lt;a id="still"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; am I still at risk of getting measles?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Six years of living with COVID-19 have taught us that being vaccinated against a virus doesn’t necessarily mean you won’t get infected with that virus. The COVID-19 vaccine, for example, does somewhat reduce your chances of being infected — although the&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/ncird/whats-new/5-things-you-should-know.html"&gt; CDC said &lt;/a&gt;that “protection against infection tends to be modest and sometimes short-lived” — but it also means you’re much less likely to get severely ill if you do get infected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the measles vaccine &lt;em&gt;is &lt;/em&gt;incredibly effective at protecting against infections, the&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/questions.html?CDC_AAref_Val=https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/faqs.html"&gt; CDC said&lt;/a&gt;, and two doses of measles vaccine are “about 97% effective” at preventing measles if you’re exposed. (One dose is “about 93% effective.”)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for why “about three out of 100” people vaccinated against measles will still get measles after exposure — also known as breakthrough cases — &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/questions.html?CDC_AAref_Val=https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/faqs.html"&gt;the CDC said &lt;/a&gt;that experts “aren’t sure why” and that this could be due to the responsiveness of an individual’s immune system to the vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But the good news is, fully vaccinated people who get measles seem more likely to have a milder illness,” the CDC said — and fully vaccinated people “seem also less likely to spread the disease to other people.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where can I find a measles vaccine in the Bay Area?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have health insurance, the&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/vaccines/index.html?CDC_AA_refVal=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Fvaccines%2Fvpd%2Fmmr%2Fpublic%2Findex.html"&gt; CDC’s &lt;/a&gt;recommendation of these shots means that your insurer should cover the costs. The CDC’s&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2026/01/05/nx-s1-5667199/cdc-vaccine-schedule-children"&gt; recent changes&lt;/a&gt; to the U.S. vaccine schedule for children under the leadership of U.S. Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. do not affect the agency’s recommendation of the MMR vaccine or insurance coverage of these shots. In 2025, Kennedy dissolved the CDC’s Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices and &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-health-chief-kennedy-names-new-members-vaccine-advisory-committee-2025-06-11/"&gt;replaced its members with a number of doctors and researchers &lt;/a&gt;who have repeatedly questioned, without evidence, the safety of commonly used vaccines and ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find appointments for an MMR vaccine at:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those without insurance: Uninsured children ages 18 and under can get free DTaP vaccines — and other no-cost immunizations — as part of the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/programs/vfc/index.html"&gt;Vaccines for Children Program&lt;/a&gt;. People without insurance can get the MMR vaccine at a lower cost — or even free&lt;a href="https://eziz.org/assets/docs/IMM-1247.pdf"&gt; if they qualify &lt;/a&gt;for the Vaccines for Adults Program — from several providers and community clinics around the Bay Area, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;KQED’s &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kqed.org/author/skennedy"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Samantha Kennedy &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kqed.org/author/nkhan"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nisa Khan&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; contributed to this report. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KQED</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:57:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxNUFZLVmpNbzBndU9vbldRN0p1dDBxdlVOc24wSXhkQVFUOUNiNFVQcVBKdXhqTnNkXzZPNjlMZ3k0SWlaNUtWTS1DeFBkRXdzdFRmdEtxci01Zi1TU2hQTHk5SU1jT1diNnlodTV3N0hpZXl1ZWZPOTRpZWY2TF8zdy1NaTJmSG5MYkI2RXlvOHlKR3Q3ejNoSlNmZ2ViajA2WkpsclB6dkxLUWIy</guid></item><item><title>疫苗小组主席拒绝接受数十年的科学研究，称脊髓灰质炎和其他疫苗应该是可选的-西雅图时报</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/rejecting-decades-of-science-vaccine-panel-chair-says-polio-and-other-shots-should-be-optional/</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi0wFBVV95cUxQTDNNakRBaE1zem5pQWpDdlk3d3A4d0NVcml4c1JZdzhnRDQwUW1ua0xYX215czY4R0J5cGJlaGxsZkhDeENWak5iMFR3YmNwbHVWM09xa0l3aC1jTDVjYXZXZG1BOVBucjU1dzlJV2ZQUlpZem1SZjhjc1FCVk9qUmRkUXREWWVMT2dBbFBXR0V1T2ZKdjlFVGdLREdoZGkwU053dXl5ejdhLTh5VkdHSW1xbDRKVGxLMllTdF84cE1vR2JEdDB4eWlDZkxvM1lpN0Fn?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Rejecting decades of science, vaccine panel chair says polio and other shots should be optional&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqNggKIjBDQklTSGpvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoRUtEd2pranZpekVCRk1KWGc2WEEwMUJpZ0FQAQ?hl=en-US&amp;amp;gl=US&amp;amp;ceid=US:en&amp;amp;oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View Full Coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:33:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0wFBVV95cUxQTDNNakRBaE1zem5pQWpDdlk3d3A4d0NVcml4c1JZdzhnRDQwUW1ua0xYX215czY4R0J5cGJlaGxsZkhDeENWak5iMFR3YmNwbHVWM09xa0l3aC1jTDVjYXZXZG1BOVBucjU1dzlJV2ZQUlpZem1SZjhjc1FCVk9qUmRkUXREWWVMT2dBbFBXR0V1T2ZKdjlFVGdLREdoZGkwU053dXl5ejdhLTh5VkdHSW1xbDRKVGxLMllTdF84cE1vR2JEdDB4eWlDZkxvM1lpN0Fn</guid></item><item><title>旧金山报告本季首例流感死亡病例，加利福尼亚州各地病例呈上升趋势--《旧金山纪</title><link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/health/article/san-francisco-flu-deaths-21311591.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>San Francisco Chronicle</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:15:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxPOWhkbl8tM0NUd214MUJjeS1FTi05UVEyb2F4a3JJVnZleEd6bVIyOExGb2hmMUY3c1FjbzA1Wnoyb0NER0pCbzh0X09IQ0VMSXZGeEg1Y280bGQweUo5aXJ6cnR0b2lBLUNtTWIwcFk0ZGV0UkJrNV9FaWRBVzRfSHR5N3NLOGc</guid></item><item><title>死于流感的2岁儿童的家人威胁要起诉送他回家的新泽西州医院- nj.com</title><link>https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2026/01/family-of-2-year-old-who-died-of-the-flu-threatens-to-sue-nj-hospital-that-sent-him-home.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NDQ7U7JDIBBWPBASFS4VRT7K4E"&gt;A New Jersey family is threatening to sue Morristown Medical Center for $25 million after their &lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2026/01/2-year-old-with-beautiful-smile-identified-as-first-child-flu-death-this-season-in-nj.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2026/01/2-year-old-with-beautiful-smile-identified-as-first-child-flu-death-this-season-in-nj.html"&gt;2-year-old son was discharged and died from complications of the flu&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5KDDXK2JK5BQ3HW4FQE7QIS3VQ"&gt;Isais Castillo IV, who died Jan. 6, wasn’t vaccinated for the flu. He was scheduled to get a shot later this month, his family said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VCAGNCOE6JGWRERIRCSQS65CLA"&gt;His mom &lt;a href="https://abc7ny.com/post/nj-child-flu-death-mom-speaks-2-year-old-son-was-sent-home-morristown-medical-center/18392336/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://abc7ny.com/post/nj-child-flu-death-mom-speaks-2-year-old-son-was-sent-home-morristown-medical-center/18392336/"&gt;told ABC7 &lt;/a&gt;that he had a fever and they took him to the emergency room, but he died one day after being sent home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EOJKBVMQAZE6JDTSCB2EWPLK5Y"&gt;Morristown Medical Center staff allegedly “deviated from accepted standards of care” when they discharged Isais on Jan. 5, causing his death the next day, according to a notice of tort claim filed against the hospital. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="N6VB3IK2INDZXMFGS44UT5U4XU"&gt;The legal notice claims $25 million in damages, which include “emotional distress, suffering, loss of enjoyment of life, extraordinary medical expenses, economic damages and loss of child’s services.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CPXH7EE5OVCQDMK5UY4S537GMQ"&gt;Darryl L. Zaslow, the family’s attorney, told NJ Advance Media on Friday that “the tragedy here is unimaginable.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="L7GMLZFPVJAGXNDKK5CIJZXLWA"&gt;“I will be doing a thorough investigation upon receiving the medical records and then I’ll determine if a lawsuit will be filed,” said Zaslow. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Z545SCSJBZFU3L3JAVR5TGLICM"&gt;Spokespeople for Atlantic Health, which owns Morristown Medical Center and is also named in the legal notice, did not immediately respond Friday to requests for comment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VK22N72QCJGY3EFYZOHSK6G75U"&gt;Giselle Castillo described her son’s death as “the biggest loss of our lives,” in a public Facebook post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DSXPM5WOSFERLJKH3XYUE364UA"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/support-for-the-castillo-familys-healing" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.gofundme.com/f/support-for-the-castillo-familys-healing"&gt;GoFundMe campaign&lt;/a&gt; created to support the family has raised more than $18,000 as of Friday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="72V2MUBXXFGEXNOHY4QZ6JVHAM"&gt;Isais was the &lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2026/01/child-dies-from-the-flu-in-nj-marking-first-pediatric-case-as-infections-increase.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2026/01/child-dies-from-the-flu-in-nj-marking-first-pediatric-case-as-infections-increase.html"&gt;first pediatric flu death in New Jersey&lt;/a&gt; this season. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FJ3IMGCICVHXJOUA455YSTB4MU"&gt;There have been 104 total flu-related deaths in New Jersey since the fall, most of which were people 65 and older, according to state data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3LAK2UTGARG4DAWNRDZNMRHMHI"&gt;However, the flu can cause severe illness and death in anyone, including children. Last year, the state reported five pediatric flu deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:IGXK2EJOF5ELPCPCMKDVBWN26U" data-fusion-component="IGXK2EJOF5ELPCPCMKDVBWN26U"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:IGXK2EJOF5ELPCPCMKDVBWN26U" data-fusion-component="IGXK2EJOF5ELPCPCMKDVBWN26U"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>nj.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:07:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiygFBVV95cUxPbG82RDc4OFV5R1hTZVJJaTl3Nm12SENfVHJFb2VpSUNOTV9PMk5MdklKNWVDREZfZ0J6QnVWOERMUkFoSThhMDJlRVM4RGJvdXpHVE1tVmJxOVRfMk1Jd3ZYVmVUbUU4TC1VUVdYLWp3d081NHRUcWxsN19mWkpaQUNkVHRISldZOTY4czVDeHhSWWJVbWpHcS16bGpmUkNZT3JEM2JGNkwzdEUzRTZtdk1oMHRfTDRkdFRuUWhaZDJISENKd0lTVnlB</guid></item><item><title>超薄无线视网膜植入物为安全恢复视觉信号带来希望- Phys.org</title><link>https://phys.org/news/2026-01-ultra-thin-wireless-retinal-implant.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:00:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE96cFhidVMyejRmRnRhY1JMdGhvUEFOeVlmRFFFVS1uM1Q4NUxHdkZpSThQUlFuS2p3cHlITENhU0wyUGZaVVY1b2VsX2ZmbzVJYTNCeXU4bE1lTkNINENQOTVaazNaM1pkaWkxY2xIaDhhVDBaVHA0SFJ3</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，在家中燃烧木材会在冬季造成危险的空气污染- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-wood-homes-dangerous-air-pollution.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxNRV9SNFJRN0RQaTZBRHNaXy0yOU5KdFFGUzg0MnMzbEhFbEpVNUhuNlRpSUFCbEEzZ2NfcG1ORnBkdjJyUFpZdnRISHRlV1FyYmpDRXBKR2xSdVZvNEhXRWhRSERvaVAxcVUtN05Tb1Ficjl2Q1BZWU04WlFPb3p6VlJCYUY</guid></item><item><title>Baptist Health在杰克逊维尔确认2例小儿麻疹病例- news4jax.com</title><link>https://www.news4jax.com/news/local/2026/01/23/baptist-health-confirms-two-pediatric-measles-cases-in-jacksonville/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 fURyTV iQviKm articleBody" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JACKSONVILLE, Fla. &lt;/strong&gt; – Baptist Health has confirmed two pediatric measles cases in Jacksonville.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;According to a press release from the health system, the two children, who live in the same household, sought emergency care at Baptist Health’s main campus on Jan. 16.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Hospital officials said both children received appropriate treatment and were sent home without needing hospital admission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Baptist Health shared this statement:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;&lt;i&gt;“Baptist Health remains deeply committed to the safety and well-being of our patients and team members. We have shared the names of anyone who may have been exposed with the Department of Health (DOH). The DOH will contact those individuals directly.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;&lt;i&gt;We want to assure you that the risk of infection from exposure within our facility is very low, because our team of pediatric Emergency Center specialists is expertly prepared and ready to care for these children and our community.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__FlexBase-sc-1fnzlkn-1 jGlKin adWrapper" aria-label="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Measles is an airborne infection that can spread when an infected person coughs or sneezes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Symptoms typically appear 7 to 14 days after exposure, including high fever, cough, runny nose, and watery eyes. Then, a rash of tiny red spots appears. It starts at the head and spreads to the rest of the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;The Florida Department of Health in Duval County said it cannot comment on the specifics of an ongoing epidemiological investigation, but shared the following with News4JAX:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 bqJyUE iQviKm block-quote"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 ewwUYq"&gt;When a communicable disease is reported in the county, DOH-Duval immediately initiates an epidemiological investigation to protect the public’s health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 ewwUYq"&gt;If an individual is experiencing symptoms of measles, they are advised to not abruptly visit a health care provider without contacting them ahead of time. Instead, they should contact their health care provider or local county health department to receive instructions on how to safely seek medical attention without exposing others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;cite class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 fwWldV"&gt;Florida Department of Health in Duval County&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Dr. Shalika Katugaha, system medical director of infectious diseases at Baptist Medical, explained that measles symptoms can be more severe in children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;“Children younger than 5 years are at the highest risk for complications and death. So children do experience it more severely than adults,” Katugaha said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Infants younger than 12 months face significantly higher risks for severe complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Katugaha explained why this is the case. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__FlexBase-sc-1fnzlkn-1 jGlKin adWrapper" aria-label="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;“The mom’s antibodies wane in these children, and they are ineligible for routine vaccines before 9 to 12 months of age,” she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Measles is highly contagious and can be contracted by other family members, including children and adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;To help protect families, the local Department of Health is offering immunizations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;DOH-Duval will hold a “Pop-Up” Immunization Clinic on Sunday, Feb. 1, from 9 a.m. to 12 p.m. at the Regency Library, 9300 Regency Square Boulevard. Vaccines available include MMR, influenza, and hepatitis A.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Immunizations are also available Monday through Friday, 8 a.m. to 5 p.m., at these locations:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 kDvXdO font_openSans articleList"&gt;&lt;li class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 ecGWWE iQviKm"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 hxqFXA fYWDEy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 6 6" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" aria-hidden="true" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;circle cx="3" cy="3" r="3" fill="#212121"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;span class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 gJUqRf"&gt;515 W. 6th Street, Jacksonville, FL 32206&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 ecGWWE iQviKm"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 hxqFXA fYWDEy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 6 6" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" aria-hidden="true" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;circle cx="3" cy="3" r="3" fill="#212121"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;span class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 gJUqRf"&gt;3225 University Blvd. South, Jacksonville, FL 32216&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Walk-ins are welcome, or appointments can be made by calling 904-253-1130.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) recommends that children receive two doses of the MMR (measles, mumps, rubella) vaccine: the first at 12–15 months of age and the second at 4–6 years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;For infants aged 6–11 months who will be traveling internationally, the CDC recommends one MMR dose before departure, followed by two additional doses after the child’s first birthday (according to the routine schedule).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__FlexBase-sc-1fnzlkn-1 jGlKin adWrapper" aria-label="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 nALdY copyright"&gt;Copyright 2026 by WJXT News4JAX - All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>news4jax.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:59:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxObUswOVd3cEFKc1J4MmhFb0xYdzd1clVlUngxaDZwM1BYUV92MEZOSFJsOXhFZTc2dUxKZXhOWm9sbWNxM0xtZmZ1MzNkbmVRX0diSW5pRGFHa1lObEtqUGlrWVBKaE12eXFwb2JLV2h0MEhXUDRGUmFyMkNwa1JsZEszV1pJX1c0ZXJhQlB6OE1LbnRpRHZlUHVMcXpXUDZROTM0cktxcG9vbk9QR0I3RS1pU09lUQ</guid></item><item><title>7天高蛋白高纤维饮食计划- Skinnytaste</title><link>https://www.skinnytaste.com/7-day-high-protein-high-fiber-diet-meal-plan-3/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content clear" data-ast-blocks-layout="true"&gt;

		
		
&lt;span id="dpsp-post-content-markup" data-image-pin-it="true"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="content-disclaimer-text disclaimer-location-top"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post may contain affiliate links. Read my &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/legal/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;disclosure policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A free, 7-day &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-protein/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;high protein&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-fiber-recipes/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;high fiber&lt;/a&gt; diet meal plan including &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/recipes/breakfast-brunch/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;breakfast&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/recipes/lunch/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;lunch&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/recipes/dinner-recipes/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;dinner ideas&lt;/a&gt; and a shopping list. All recipes include &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/what-are-macros/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;macros&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/smart-points/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Weight Watchers&lt;/a&gt; points.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" src="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Week_525_Jan-26-Feb-1_High-Protein.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-158151" srcset="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Week_525_Jan-26-Feb-1_High-Protein.jpg 1200w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Week_525_Jan-26-Feb-1_High-Protein-500x625.jpg 500w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Week_525_Jan-26-Feb-1_High-Protein-550x688.jpg 550w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Week_525_Jan-26-Feb-1_High-Protein-600x750.jpg 600w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Week_525_Jan-26-Feb-1_High-Protein-150x188.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading has-text-align-center"&gt;7 Day High-Protein High-Fiber Diet Meal Plan&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/holiday-recipes/superbowl-recipes/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Game days&lt;/a&gt; are all about big plays, loud cheers, and even better food. Whether you’re hosting a football watch party or pulling up to a sports-filled weekend with friends, these party &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/recipes/appetizers/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;apps&lt;/a&gt; prove you don’t have to choose between great flavor and hitting your &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-protein/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;protein&lt;/a&gt; goals. Perfect for sharing (or keeping all to yourself),  these &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/mini-bell-pepper-loaded-turkey-nachos/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Mini Bell Pepper Loaded Turkey Nachos&lt;/a&gt; (18g protein), &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/air-fryer-chicken-wings/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Air Fryer Chicken Wings&lt;/a&gt; (25.5g protein) or &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/guacamole-recipe/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Best Guacamole Recipe&lt;/a&gt; (4g fiber) are sure to be crowd-pleasers—bringing feel-good fuel to every celebration. Because the best game-day spreads let you enjoy every bite and the win!&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;span id="more-158113"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;


&lt;div id="callout-box-block_8de5bb252b0c1a2ad0ab188737abb1ae" class="callout-box-block callout-box-style-1"&gt;&lt;p class="callout-box-tag"&gt;&lt;h2 class="callout-box-title"&gt;Update About New WW Points Plan&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="callout-box-content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all my WW friends, WW added new 0 point foods (yay for oatmeal!) but it will take time for me to update my recipes. So far I have everything from 2025 to 2018 updated. The great news is every recipe on my site is linked to WW recipe builder (only works from your phone) so it will automatically give you the new points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Why High Protein?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As many of you know, I’ve been following a &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-protein/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;high-protein&lt;/a&gt; diet for the past few years for muscle gain, and it’s been a total game changer for me! I feel stronger and more satisfied, which keeps me from reaching for sweets or chips between meals or at the end of the day. I know a lot of you struggle with hitting your protein goals, so I was inspired to create this &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-protein/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;high-protein&lt;/a&gt; meal plan for the week. If you enjoy it, I’ll share 1 or 2 each month. Plus, I’m working on a high-protein cookbook, so stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To reach my protein goals, I typically divide it across three meals. For example, if my goal is 120 grams of protein per day, I aim for at least 30 grams per meal, plus 10 to 30 grams with each snack. If you’re not sure how much protein you should eat in a day, this &lt;a href="https://examine.com/guides/protein-intake/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow external" data-wpel-link="external"&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; may be helpful.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;How It Works&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;If you’re new to my &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/meal-plans/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;meal plans&lt;/a&gt;, these are meant as a guide, with &lt;strong&gt;plenty of wiggle room&lt;/strong&gt; for you to &lt;strong&gt;add more food&lt;/strong&gt;, coffee, beverages, fruits, &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/recipes/snacks/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;snacks&lt;/a&gt;, dessert, etc. or swap recipes out for meals you prefer, you can search for &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/recipes/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;recipes&lt;/a&gt; by course in the &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/recipes/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;index&lt;/a&gt;. Depending on your goals, you should aim for at least 1500 calories* per day. There’s no one size fits all, this will range by your goals, your age, weight, etc. Always talk to your nutritionist or dietician for your specific needs.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Note&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Those with kidney or liver disease, gout, specific metabolic disorders, or older adults with reduced kidney function may need to limit protein to avoid complications. It’s always best to consult a healthcare provider or dietitian before significantly increasing protein intake, especially if you have any underlying health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Lastly, if you’re on Facebook join my &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/1934885496754505/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow external" data-wpel-link="external"&gt;Skinnytaste Facebook Community&lt;/a&gt; where everyone’s sharing photos of recipes they are making, you can join here. I’m loving all the ideas everyone’s sharing! If you wish to get on the email list, you can subscribe here so you never miss a meal plan!&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div id="callout-box-block_676ad29253934f2635e272fe8b2f2a6e" class="callout-box-block callout-box-style-2"&gt;&lt;p class="callout-box-tag"&gt;&lt;h3 class="callout-box-title"&gt;&lt;span class="callout-box-icon webicon-diamond"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Ultimate Skinnytaste Meal Planner&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="callout-box-content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignleft wp-image-79975 size-full" src="" alt="Skinnytaste Ultimate Meal Planner" data-lazy-src="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Skinnytaste-UltimateMealPlanner-125.png"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignleft wp-image-79975 size-full" src="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Skinnytaste-UltimateMealPlanner-125.png" alt="Skinnytaste Ultimate Meal Planner"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get the Skinnytaste Ultimate Meal Planner! The 52 week spiral bound meal planner has weekly meal planning grids you can tear out and put on your fridge if you wish, a 12-week meal plan, 30 (15 new) recipes, and tear-out grocery lists. I love starting my week with gratitude, affirmations and intentions, so I included a space for that as well. I hope you will love this as much as I do!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;figure class="wp-block-image"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt="Skinnytaste Ultimate Meal Planner" class="wp-image-111022" data-lazy-srcset="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-scaled.jpeg 2560w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-500x375.jpeg 500w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-550x412.jpeg 550w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-1536x1152.jpeg 1536w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-2048x1536.jpeg 2048w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-600x450.jpeg 600w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-1200x900.jpeg 1200w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-150x112.jpeg 150w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" data-lazy-src="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-scaled.jpeg"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-scaled.jpeg" alt="Skinnytaste Ultimate Meal Planner" class="wp-image-111022" srcset="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-scaled.jpeg 2560w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-500x375.jpeg 500w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-550x412.jpeg 550w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-1536x1152.jpeg 1536w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-2048x1536.jpeg 2048w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-600x450.jpeg 600w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-1200x900.jpeg 1200w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-150x112.jpeg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Buy the Skinnytaste meal planner here:&lt;/h2&gt;







&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;High Protein Diet Meal Plan:&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Breakfast and lunch Monday-Friday, are designed to serve 1 while dinners and all meals on Saturday and Sunday are designed to serve a family of 4. Some recipes make enough leftovers for two nights or lunch the next day. The grocery list is comprehensive and includes everything you need to make all meals on the plan. Add some &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-protein-snacks/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;high protein snacks&lt;/a&gt; to help you reach your protein goals.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MONDAY (1/26)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;B: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-protein-zucchini-omelet-for-one/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;High Protein Zucchini Omelet for One&lt;/a&gt; with 2 chicken breakfast sausage links and 1 slice whole grain toast&lt;br&gt;L: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/tuna-and-white-bean-salad/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Tuna White Bean Salad&lt;/a&gt; and 2 tablespoons raw almonds&lt;br&gt;D: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/greek-tofu-bowl/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Greek Tofu Bowls&lt;/a&gt; (recipe x 2) with &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/roasted-cauliflower-and-chickpeas-with/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Roasted Cauliflower and Chickpeas with Minted Yogurt&lt;/a&gt; (½ recipe)&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Total Calories: 1,568* Protein: 120.5 g Fiber: 30 g&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TUESDAY (1/27)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;B: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-protein-zucchini-omelet-for-one/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;High Protein Zucchini Omelet for One&lt;/a&gt; with 2 chicken breakfast sausage links and 1 slice whole grain toast&lt;br&gt;L: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/tuna-and-white-bean-salad/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Tuna White Bean Salad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;D: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/ground-turkey-tacos/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Ground Turkey Tacos&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/quick-and-deliciouso-cuban-style-black/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Quick and Delicioso Cuban Style Black Beans&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/cilantro-lime-cauliflower-rice/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Cilantro Lime Cauliflower Rice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Total Calories: 1,477* Protein: 120 g Fiber: 34 g&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WEDNESDAY (1/28)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;B: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/carrot-banana-protein-smoothie/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Carrot Banana Protein Smoothie&lt;/a&gt; with ¼ cup low fat plain Greek yogurt&lt;br&gt;L: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/microwave-salmon-rice-bowl/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;5-Minute Microwave Salmon Rice Bowl&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;D: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/chicken-marbella/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Chicken Marbella&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/farro-with-feta-cucumbers-and-sun-dried/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Farro Salad with Feta, Cucumbers and Sun-Dried Tomatoes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;Total Calories: 1,431* Protein: 129 g Fiber: 25 g&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THURSDAY (1/29)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;B: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/carrot-banana-protein-smoothie/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Carrot Banana Protein Smoothie&lt;/a&gt; with ¼ cup low fat plain Greek yogurt&lt;br&gt;L: LEFTOVER &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/chicken-marbella/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Chicken Marbella&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/chickpea-salad/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Chickpea Salad with Cucumbers&lt;/a&gt; (1/2 recipe)&lt;br&gt;D: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/spicy-whole-wheat-linguini-with-sausage/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Spicy Whole Wheat Linguini with Sausage and Roasted Peppers&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/arugula-with-pomegranates-blue-cheese/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Arugula with Pomegranates, Blue Cheese and Pistachios&lt;/a&gt; (recipe x 2)&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Total Calories: 1,406* Protein: 131 g Fiber: 26 g&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FRIDAY (1/30)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;B: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/15-minute-protein-chia-seed-cereal/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;15-Minute Protein Chia Seed Cereal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;L: LEFTOVER &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/chicken-marbella/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Chicken Marbella&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/chickpea-salad/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Chickpea Salad with Cucumber&lt;/a&gt;s&lt;br&gt;D: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/broiled-tilapia-with-tomato-caper-sauce/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Broiled Fish with Tomato Caper Sauce&lt;/a&gt; with 1 cup whole wheat orzo and &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/roasted-broccoli-and-cauliflower/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Roasted Broccoli and Cauliflower&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Total Calories: 1,417* Protein: 122.5 g Fiber: 31 g&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SATURDAY (1/31)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;B: ⅛ &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/breakfast-casserole-with-spinach-and-sausage/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Breakfast Casserole with Sausage and Spinach&lt;/a&gt; and an orange&lt;br&gt;L: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/asian-lettuce-wrap-chicken-chopped-salad/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Asian Chicken Chopped Salad&lt;/a&gt; with ¼ cup shelled edamame&lt;br&gt;D: DINNER OUT&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Total Calories: 745* Protein: 56.5 g Fiber: 10 g&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUNDAY (2/1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;B: LEFTOVER &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/breakfast-casserole-with-spinach-and-sausage/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Breakfast Casserole with Sausage and Spinach&lt;/a&gt; and a pear&lt;br&gt;L: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/chicken-quesadillas/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Chicken Quesadilla&lt;/a&gt; with 1 ounce avocado&lt;br&gt;D: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/french-onion-pot-roast/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;French Onion Pot Roast&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/garlic-mashed-potatoes-3-ww-points/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Garlic Mashed Potatoes&lt;/a&gt; and 1 cup steamed green beans&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Total Calories: 1,452* Protein: 127 g Fiber: 33.5 g&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;*This is just a guide, women should aim for around 1500 calories per day. &lt;a href="https://www.myplate.gov/myplate-plan" target="_blank" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener"&gt;Here’s a helpful calculator to estimate your calorie needs.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt="" class="wp-image-158134" data-lazy-srcset="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249.png 802w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-500x298.png 500w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-550x328.png 550w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-800x478.png 800w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-600x358.png 600w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-150x89.png 150w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 802px) 100vw, 802px" data-lazy-src="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249.png"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249.png" alt="" class="wp-image-158134" srcset="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249.png 802w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-500x298.png 500w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-550x328.png 550w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-800x478.png 800w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-600x358.png 600w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-150x89.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 802px) 100vw, 802px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;*&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1WH_rdx5PsjY-sK9Fw4HwoyotL2pBgirH2uSTLTts5oU/edit?usp=sharing" target="_blank" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener"&gt;Google doc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="print-this-wrapper ggnoads"&gt;&lt;p class="print-this-button-wrapper"&gt;&lt;button class="print-this-button submitbutton"&gt;Print Shopping List&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="print_this_6973f42b1c86a" class="print-this-container"&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shopping List&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Produce&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 medium (ripe) banana&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;4 medium oranges (any variety)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;4 medium pears (any variety)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (6-ounce) container raspberries or blackberries&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small pomegranate (or container of seeds)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium mango&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;4 medium lemons&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;4 medium limes&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small (5-ounce) PLUS 1 medium (6-ounce) Hass avocados&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;3 medium heads garlic&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 medium shallots&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (2-inch) piece fresh ginger&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium jalapeno&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;3 small PLUS 1 medium red bell peppers&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 medium zucchini&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;4 Persian (mini) cucumbers (can sub 1 medium English, if desired)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 medium cucumbers&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium head baby bok choy&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 ½ pounds green beans&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 medium carrots&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small bag baby carrots&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium PLUS 1 large head cauliflower (can sub 1 pound pre-riced for medium head, if desired)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;¾ pound broccoli florets&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 pounds (4 medium) Yukon Gold potatoes&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small bunch scallions&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small bunch/container fresh thyme&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small bunch/container fresh dill&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small bunch/container fresh mint&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium bunch fresh cilantro&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small bunch fresh Italian parsley&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 (5-ounce) clamshell/bag baby spinach&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (1-pound) clamshell/bag baby arugula&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium head Boston or Bibb lettuce&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small head Romaine lettuce&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small head Iceberg lettuce (can sub a small bag pre-shredded, if desired)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium plum tomato&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;3 medium vine-ripened tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 dry pint cherry or grape tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small container Pico de Gallo (or &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/pico-de-gallo-salsa-0-pts/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;ingredients to make your own&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small PLUS 1 medium red onion&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small PLUS 3 medium yellow onions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meat, Poultry and Fish&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 small package chicken breakfast sausage links (can buy frozen, if desired)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;¾ pound ground turkey breakfast sausage&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 pound hot Italian chicken sausage&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 pound ground chicken&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 pound boneless, skinless chicken breasts&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 ½ pounds bone-in, skin-on chicken thighs&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 pound 93% lean ground turkey&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (6-ounce) salmon fillet&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 ½ pounds (4) tilapia, flounder or grouper fillets&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (2 ½-pound) boneless beef chuck roast&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Condiments and Spices&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extra virgin olive oil&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Canola oil&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Cooking spray&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Olive oil spray (or get a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Misto-Brushed-Aluminum-Olive-Sprayer/dp/B00004SPZV/ref=sr_1_1?s=grocery&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1515181085&amp;amp;sr=8-1&amp;amp;keywords=misto&amp;amp;th=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow sponsored external noopener" data-wpel-link="external"&gt;Misto&lt;/a&gt; oil mister)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Kosher salt (I like &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0011BPMUK/ref=as_li_qf_sp_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=1094004-20&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B0011BPMUK&amp;amp;linkId=de126591a74a25f41428f89bbb2986da&amp;amp;th=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow sponsored external noopener" data-wpel-link="external"&gt;Diamond Crystal&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Pepper grinder (or fresh peppercorns)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Turmeric&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Dijon mustard&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Sweet red chili sauce&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Sriracha sauce&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Sesame oil&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Rice vinegar&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Honey&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Hoisin sauce*&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Reduced sodium soy sauce*&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Cumin&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Garlic powder&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Oregano&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Onion powder&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Red wine vinegar&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Curry powder&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Taco seasoning (or buy paprika and chili powder and make your own with ingredients in list)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Bay leaves&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Balsamic vinegar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dairy &amp;amp; Misc. Refrigerated Items&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 (8-ounce) bottle pomegranate juice&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 (14-ounce) packages extra-firm tofu&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 18-pack large eggs&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 pint liquid egg whites&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (12-ounce) container skim milk&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 pint unsweetened almond milk&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 pint whole or reduced fat milk&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (5.3-ounce) container low fat (2%) plain Greek yogurt&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (16-ounce) container nonfat plain Greek yogurt&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small tub light sour cream&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small tub whipped butter&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (8-ounce) bag shredded reduced fat Mexican cheese blend&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (8-ounce) bag part-skim mozzarella cheese&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 block feta cheese&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package crumbled blue cheese&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium wedge fresh Parmesan cheese&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small wedge Pecorino Romano (can sub 2 tablespoons Parmesan in Spicy Linguine, if desired)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grains*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 package dry whole wheat orzo&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 package dry whole wheat linguine&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 package dry pearled farro&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 package seasoned breadcrumbs&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 package plain panko breadcrumbs&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package all-purpose flour&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small loaf slice whole grain bread (I like Dave’s Killer Bread)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 package burrito size low carb whole wheat flour tortillas (such as La Tortilla Factory)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package corn tortillas or crunchy corn shells (your choice)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Canned and Jarred&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 (3-ounce) packets tuna in water&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (8-ounce) can water chestnuts&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (15-ounce) can low sodium navy beans&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (15-ounce) can black beans&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (15-ounce) can chickpeas&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small jar pitted Spanish green olives&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 large jar capers&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (12-ounce) jar roasted peppers&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 jar sundried tomatoes in oil&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (15-ounce) can tomato sauce&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (15-ounce) can crushed tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (16-ounce) carton beef bone broth&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (32-ounce) carton low sodium chicken broth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frozen&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 small package shelled edamame&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package pre-cooked brown rice (or a single serve shelf stable package)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Misc. Dry Goods&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 single-serve package unflavored protein powder&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 single-serve package vanilla protein powder&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package ground flax (meal)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package chia seeds&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package unsalted cashews (if buying from bulk bin, you need 2 tablespoons)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package shelled pistachios (if buying from bulk bin, you need ¼ cup)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package raw almonds (if buying from bulk bin, you need 2 tablespoons)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package granulated sugar&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package brown sugar&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package pitted prunes&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 single serve bottle Pinot Grigio&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small bottle sherry wine&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (1 ¼-ounce) package dry onion soup mix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;*You can buy gluten free, if desired&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="print-this-button-wrapper"&gt;&lt;button class="print-this-button submitbutton"&gt;Print Shopping List&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


		
		
			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Skinnytaste</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:59:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxNOGc4azVWcC1KWHlJMWhLMTE1V0gxSkdtWUpWSzk2bHZhN0R5SUM4TWtvZmNhT3JjaVdfNUk4aENKUTh4UC03NmVrQkVQY0ExaHY0aVNuYjI1aHlINzlLaXRMNkVRRUJvN3M4eTAwNVMxMlg5aWVpNnNPQ2hpWk53Mw</guid></item><item><title>长寿：带状疱疹疫苗有助于减缓衰老吗？ -今日医学新闻</title><link>https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/shingles-vaccine-may-help-slow-biological-aging</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-12va8w7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="css-7j3c6j"&gt;&lt;span class="css-rwmw5v"&gt;&lt;span class="css-mjp0j9"&gt;&lt;picture class="css-16pk1is"&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2026/01/administing-Shingles-vaccine-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 1190px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2026/01/administing-Shingles-vaccine-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 990px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2026/01/administing-Shingles-vaccine-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 879w" media="(min-width: 768px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="eager" src="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2026/01/administing-Shingles-vaccine-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg" alt="older woman tightly shutting her eyes while getting vaccinated" class="css-1jytyml"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;hl-share-overlay class="css-1mqo1cs"&gt;&lt;a class="icon-hl-pinterest css-11oz8gb" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" data-event="Any Page|Image Pinterest Click|Icon Clicked" data-element-event="OPEN|CONTENTBLOCK|Any Page|Article Body|BUTTON|Image Widget Pinterest Click|" href="https://www.pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicalnewstoday.com%2Farticles%2Fshingles-vaccine-may-help-slow-biological-aging&amp;amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.post.rvohealth.io%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fsites%2F3%2F2026%2F01%2Fadministing-Shingles-vaccine-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg&amp;amp;description=Longevity%3A%20Can%20the%20shingles%20vaccine%20help%20slow%20down%20aging%3F" title="Share on Pinterest" data-pin-custom="true" data-share-url="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2026/01/administing-Shingles-vaccine-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg"&gt;&lt;span class="css-z1zfa"&gt;Share on Pinterest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-share-overlay&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;figcaption class="css-1nzy6lj css-whkgel"&gt;Can the shingles vaccine help slow biological aging? Pictured: Elizabeth Gomez, 54, of Huntington Park, right, receives a Prevnar and shingles vaccine by pharmacy manager Sandra Gonzalez at CVS in Huntington Park on August 28, 2024. Image credit: Christina House/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Over the last few years, there has been more talk about how people can slow down or improve their biological age. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scientists are currently examining a variety of medications as a way to help slow biological aging.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A new study says the shingles vaccine may help slow biological aging in older adults.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a person thinks of aging, they normally think of their chronological age and how many birthdays they’ve had so far. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the last few years, there has been more talk about how people can slow down or improve their &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/chronological-aging" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;biological age&lt;/a&gt;, which is the health and function age of their bodies on a molecular level. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People are living longer and longer, but many spend those extra years managing chronic conditions, disability, and physical and &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/cognitive-functioning" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;cognitive dysfunction&lt;/a&gt;,” &lt;a href="https://gero.usc.edu/faculty/crimmins/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Eileen M. Crimmins&lt;/a&gt;, PhD, AARP, a professor of gerontology in the Leonard Davis School of Gerontology at the University of Southern California, told &lt;em&gt;Medical News Today&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Slowing biological aging could help extend not just years of life, but years of ‘healthy life’ — the years people live with better physical and cognitive function. We have shown that the only way to improve the health of the older population and increase healthy life is to intervene early — before people have diseases and disabilities. Identifying things that slow biological aging is important for understanding how we might improve population health at older ages,” Crimmins explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists are currently examining a variety of medications as a way to help slow biological aging, such as the &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/317462" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; drug &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11561139/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;metformin&lt;/a&gt;, the immunosuppressant &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6814615/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;rapamycin&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;hl-trusted-source source="Wiley" rationale="Peer reviewed journal"&gt;&lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/acel.13774" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;rilmenidine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; prescribed for managing blood pressure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The shingles vaccine is relatively new and recommended for older adults,” &lt;a href="https://gero.usc.edu/faculty/jung-ki-kim-ph-d/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Jung Ki Kim&lt;/a&gt;, PhD, research associate professor of gerontology in the Leonard Davis School of Gerontology at the University of Southern California, and first author of this study, explained to &lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Prior studies have found lower risks of &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11485228/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt; and other age-related conditions. We wanted to understand whether it might also be associated with [the] underlying biological processes related to aging,” said Kim.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers used seven different aspects of biological aging in the body to come up with participants’ composite biological aging score: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At the study’s conclusion, scientists found that participants who had received the shingles vaccine had a slower overall biological aging on average, when compared to those who did not receive the vaccination. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This suggests that shingles vaccination may be linked not only to preventing infection and reducing its severity, but may also be more favorable to multiple biological systems, particularly inflammatory, and overall biological aging,” Crimmins said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“While this is an observational study and cannot prove cause and effect, it adds evidence that a vaccine that affects immunity also affects biological processes that underlie multiple facets of aging biology,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, shingles vaccinated-participants had much lower inflammation measurements, slower epigenetic and transcriptomic aging, and lower composite biological aging scores, than those who were not vaccinated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Inflammation and molecular aging markers have been associated with many age-related health outcomes, including cardiovascular disease and cognitive decline. Finding consistent associations across these domains suggests that shingles vaccination may be linked to slower aging at a biological level, not just differences in the immune system.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crimmins said one possible explanation as to how the shingles vaccine might help protect a person against aging and health issues that may increase biological aging is that preventing reactivation of the shingles virus may reduce chronic, low-grade inflammation, which is a key driver of aging. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Vaccination may also influence immune regulation and gene expression in ways that support healthier aging,” she added. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our study suggests that beyond its role in preventing shingles, shingles vaccination is associated with slower biological aging in older adults,” Kim said. “These findings highlight the interaction of immune system changes due to vaccine and biological aging that may have additional positive consequences.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Future research should follow people over time to better understand causality, examine whether similar patterns are seen with the newer shingles vaccine, and explore whether changes in biological aging translate into meaningful health outcomes like reduced mortality or cognitive decline,” added Kim. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; had the opportunity to speak with &lt;a href="https://www.providence.org/doctors/family-medicine/ca/santa-monica/david-cutler-1255368338" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;David Cutler&lt;/a&gt;, MD, a board-certified family medicine physician at Providence Saint John’s Health Center in Santa Monica, CA, about this study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cutler, who was not involved in this research, commented that his first reaction to the conclusions about slowing aging was one of caution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There are several important limitations that temper interpretation of the association between shingles vaccination and slower biological aging,” Cutler told us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“First, the study is observational, so it cannot establish causality; healthier individuals who choose to be vaccinated may already have slower biological aging (healthy-user bias), despite statistical adjustment. Second, residual confounding is likely, as unmeasured factors such as health-seeking behaviors, frailty trajectories, access to care, or prior immune health could influence both vaccination status and aging biomarkers,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Third, vaccination status was based on self-report, which may introduce misclassification,” Cutler continued. “Fourth, most participants received the older live-attenuated zoster vaccine (&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6150039/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Zostavax&lt;/a&gt;), limiting generalizability to the newer recombinant vaccine (&lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/drugs-shingrix" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Shingrix&lt;/a&gt;). Fifth, biological aging measures were assessed at limited time points, making it difficult to fully characterize long-term trajectories.” &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Finally,“ he added, “the cohort consisted of older U.S. adults, so results may not generalize to younger populations or other countries. Together, these limitations mean the findings are suggestive, but hypothesis-generating rather than definitive evidence that shingles vaccination slows biological aging.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cutler suggested several next research steps that would be especially useful for advancing efforts to slow biological aging, particularly in older adults, such as randomized and quasi-experimental studies, longitudinal tracking of aging trajectories, comparative studies across interventions, and studies with more diverse populations by age, race/ethnicity, socioeconomic status, and health status&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Together, these steps would help move the field from intriguing associations toward actionable, evidence-based strategies for slowing biological aging and improving health in later life,” he told us. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical News Today</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:40:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxOb2ZWVjBJR3ZLTGUzLUxTM21aYklXSlZXMkFwX2tmYVNubnhGVkFWUTNHZ0ctWDQ3R0VkdEZvZGVhY1hULVZGb2U5M1d0QWg5dHpXYVZZLW1EQkdzRHZwNXlQNFVtYmRBSmo4SFJ1SXVuZ0dKYjJKcEdTU3I2dHliX3lPX0ZCcmYyYTBkN1ctS2RfQ2c</guid></item></channel></rss>