<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>普通感冒、流感、新冠肺炎：为什么英国现在病得这么重？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c1jz608l9l4o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Cold, flu, Covid: Why is everyone sick right now?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-c4820dd1-0 cYDsPh"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-c4820dd1-11 bxdaHR"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;Nick Triggle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;Health correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 ERpRj"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251007-082128-301112d266-web-2.31.2-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d262/live/c2050750-a6bb-11f0-a356-d3fc7522eb5a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d262/live/c2050750-a6bb-11f0-a356-d3fc7522eb5a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d262/live/c2050750-a6bb-11f0-a356-d3fc7522eb5a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d262/live/c2050750-a6bb-11f0-a356-d3fc7522eb5a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d262/live/c2050750-a6bb-11f0-a356-d3fc7522eb5a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d262/live/c2050750-a6bb-11f0-a356-d3fc7522eb5a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d262/live/c2050750-a6bb-11f0-a356-d3fc7522eb5a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d262/live/c2050750-a6bb-11f0-a356-d3fc7522eb5a.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="iStock/Getty Images A woman with ginger hair and wearing a white T-shirt sneezing while pinching her nose, against a bright orange background" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;iStock/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Are you ill? If not, you probably know someone who is - or at the very least someone who has just recovered. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Coughs and colds, it seems, are rampant at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;And, if the anecdotes of people I know are anything to go by, the bug going round seems to be a particularly nasty one. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Sore throat? Tick. Streaming nose? Tick. Sinus pressure? Double tick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;What's going on?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;The perfect breeding ground&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"This is normal, it's autumn after all," says Prof Jonathan Ball, from Liverpool School of Tropical Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;He says a combination of children returning to school, adults back at work after the summer break and people spending more time indoors as the weather turns cooler creates a ripe breeding ground for respiratory viruses to flourish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Basically we have a big mixing pot of different viruses that are beginning to do the rounds. Immunity has waned and people are getting ill." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;There are actually more than 100 different viruses that cause upper and lower respiratory tract infections, plus some bacterial infections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Is there more illness than normal?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://ukhsa-dashboard.data.gov.uk/" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;Data collection from the UK Health Security Agency&lt;/a&gt; (UKHSA) shows Rhinovirus – what many of us would call the common cold – has been on the increase in recent weeks and seems to be the most common cause of illness at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Covid is also doing the rounds, driven by two new variants – XFG, called Stratus by some, and NB.1.8.1, known as Nimbus. But there is already a high degree of immunity built up in the population meaning, for most, it's a fairly mild infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;There are signs flu may be on the rise too – there has been an increase in the 15-25 age group over the past week - while RSV, which can cause serious illness in young children, also tends to take off in the autumn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"There is often, although not always, a pattern," says Dr Jamie Lopez Bernal, a consultant epidemiologist at UKHSA. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"You tend to see Rhinovirus take off first and then RSV," he explains. "Flu tends to come later in December and January. But that's not always the case – and certainly the pandemic disrupted the traditional seasonal trends. What we've seen in the last year or so is those trends return to something like normal."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;He says the levels of illnesses at the moment are not particularly high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Covid is above baseline and there's a lot of Rhinovirus around. The uptick in flu in that younger age group has perhaps come a little bit earlier than we would expect, but it is still at a low level."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Is it a cold, flu or Covid?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The most common symptoms, according to the NHS, are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;b id="colds" class="sc-d16436d-0 kPzeuB"&gt;Colds&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Symptoms appear gradually&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Mostly affect nose and throat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Early sign - pressure in your ears&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Chestier, mucus cough&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;b id="flu" class="sc-d16436d-0 kPzeuB"&gt;Flu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Comes on suddenly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Feel wiped out&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Fever, muscle aches, exhaustion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Need bed rest&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Dry cough&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;b id="covid" class="sc-d16436d-0 kPzeuB"&gt;Covid&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Typical flu symptoms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Loss of taste of smell&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Diarrhoea or tummy upset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Many of the symptoms between cold, flu and more serious viruses like Covid overlap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;How can you protect yourself?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Respiratory infections can, of course, be really dangerous for vulnerable people - in a bad winter tens of thousands of people can die of flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But there is nothing to suggest the respiratory viruses circulating now are causing more serious illness this year in otherwise healthy people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We all react in different ways – and we don't really understand why," admits Prof Ball. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Of course, age and fitness have a lot to do with it, but sometimes it is just your individual genetics or how tired and rundown you may be, or when you were last exposed to that particular virus."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In terms of protecting yourself, the most important step to take, if you are eligible, is to get vaccinatinated. Shots are being offered for &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/nhs-services/vaccination-and-booking-services/get-a-free-rsv-vaccination/" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;flu, Covid and RSV&lt;/a&gt; to protect those who are most at-risk of serious illness, which includes older people and those with certain health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;If you are ill, UKHSA says you can help protect others by washing your hands regularly, especially after coughing or sneezing, staying at home if you can and consider wearing a mask if you do have to go into public places.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Prof Ball says it is right to take precautions to try to protect vulnerable people, but adds if you are healthy and young or of working age, getting the odd respiratory illness is pretty inevitable and not necessarily a bad thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Most people will get one or two respiratory infections every year. In some ways, it's a good thing when you are a child or healthy adult.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"By getting exposed you are building up your immunity through natural infection - so when you are older you hopefully have enough immunity to not get severely ill."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:07:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1SMWdvdzItbTc5T2lXdml6VERIN25XUHR2YU92NGxNVExPSmg0cEVnMDFRcWYzOVFTYnFPQWwxaWFxUEFvM3VoS0FJOXhwTW5nNHV2eFZFRDZuQdIBX0FVX3lxTE1uTkUtSEVldXB3NTJ0WVR1MVJ4Vml2RW1HNDNUWDl4aXBYZ1NMN24zLTVEWXNfX1NEZzNaODNEQjlVQzFIcmhqWFotUVRMZDU4WDlqclZxaWRiWW5KQ0l3</guid></item><item><title>专家透露，阿尔茨海默氏症实际上可能不是脑部疾病- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-may-not-actually-be-a-brain-disease-reveals-expert</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The pursuit of a cure for  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="177204" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease is becoming an increasingly competitive and contentious quest, with recent years witnessing several important controversies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In July 2022, &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/potential-fabrication-research-images-threatens-key-theory-alzheimers-disease"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Science&lt;/em&gt; magazine&lt;/a&gt; reported that a key &lt;a href="https://doi.org/doi:10.1038/nature04533"&gt;2006 research paper, published in the prestigious journal &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which identified a subtype of brain protein called beta-amyloid as the cause of Alzheimer's, may have been based on fabricated data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One year earlier, in June 2021, the &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/drugs/postmarket-drug-safety-information-patients-and-providers/aducanumab-marketed-aduhelm-information"&gt;US Food and Drug Administration had approved aducanumab&lt;/a&gt;, an antibody-targeting beta-amyloid, as a treatment for Alzheimer's, even though the data supporting its use were incomplete and contradictory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some physicians believe aducanumab never should have been approved, while others maintain it should be given a chance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/learning-one-word-could-help-prevent-a-third-of-alzheimers-cases"&gt;Learning One Word Could Help Prevent a Third of Alzheimer's Cases&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With millions of people needing an effective treatment, why are researchers still fumbling in this quest for a cure for what is arguably one of the most important diseases confronting humankind?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_142437" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-142437" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesAmongNeurons_R_U_642-642x500.jpg" alt="Clumps of yellow forming among purple neurons" class="size-medium wp-image-142437" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesAmongNeurons_R_U_642-642x500.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesAmongNeurons_R_U_642-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesAmongNeurons_R_U_642-768x598.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesAmongNeurons_R_U_642-600x467.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesAmongNeurons_R_U_642.jpg 1204w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-142437" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Illustration of beta-amyloid plaques (yellow) amongst neurons. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MADq3tpYQR4/"&gt;Science Photo Library/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Escaping the beta-amyloid rut&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For years, scientists have been focused on trying to come up with new treatments for Alzheimer's &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ijbiomac.2020.11.192"&gt;by preventing the formation of brain-damaging clumps of this mysterious protein&lt;/a&gt; called beta-amyloid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, we scientists have arguably gotten ourselves into a bit of an intellectual rut, concentrating almost exclusively on this approach, often neglecting or even ignoring other possible explanations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regrettably, this dedication to studying the abnormal protein clumps has not translated into a useful drug or therapy. The need for a new "out-of-the-clump" way of thinking about Alzheimer's is emerging as a top priority in brain science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My laboratory at the Krembil Brain Institute, part of the University Health Network in Toronto, is devising a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/trc2.12283"&gt;new theory of Alzheimer's disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on our past 30 years of research, we no longer think of Alzheimer's as primarily a disease of the brain. Rather, we believe that Alzheimer's is principally &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.2174/1567205018666211202141650"&gt;a disorder of the immune system within the brain&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The immune system, found in every organ in the body, is a collection of cells and molecules that work in harmony to help repair injuries and protect from foreign invaders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_launch"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Launch" class="alignnone wp-image-177073 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a person trips and falls, the immune system helps to mend the damaged tissues. When someone experiences a viral or bacterial infection, the immune system helps in the fight against these microbial invaders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exact same processes are present in the brain. When there is head trauma, the brain's immune system kicks into gear to help repair. When bacteria are present in the brain, the immune system is there to fight back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_144645" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-144645" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/WhiteBloodCellsImmuneSystem642.jpg" alt="Bright green cells with orange spots in between them" class="size-full wp-image-144645" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/WhiteBloodCellsImmuneSystem642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/WhiteBloodCellsImmuneSystem642-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/WhiteBloodCellsImmuneSystem642-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-144645" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;White blood cells of the immune system, activated to fight a bacterial infection. Green shows expression of molecules on their surfaces, and orange shows synthesis of molecules inside the cells. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAC8pLP43hw/"&gt;Dlumen/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Alzheimer's as autoimmune disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We believe that beta-amyloid is not an abnormally produced protein, but rather is a normally occurring molecule that is part of the brain's immune system. It is supposed to be there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When brain trauma occurs or when bacteria are present in the brain, beta-amyloid is a key contributor to the brain's comprehensive immune response. And this is where the problem begins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because of striking similarities between the fat molecules that make up both the membranes of bacteria and the membranes of brain cells, beta-amyloid cannot tell the difference between invading bacteria and host brain cells, and mistakenly attacks the very brain cells it is supposed to be protecting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This leads to a chronic, progressive loss of brain cell function, which ultimately culminates in dementia – all because our body's immune system cannot differentiate between bacteria and brain cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When regarded as a misdirected attack by the brain's immune system on the very organ it is supposed to be defending, Alzheimer's disease emerges as an autoimmune disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are many types of autoimmune diseases, such as rheumatoid arthritis, in which autoantibodies play a crucial role in the development of the disease, and for which steroid-based therapies can be effective. But these therapies will not work against Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brain is a very special and distinctive organ, recognized as &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK234155/#"&gt;the most complex structure in the Universe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_144646" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-144646" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/OlderCoupleReadingABookTogether642.jpg" alt="A senior man and woman looking at a book together" class="size-full wp-image-144646" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/OlderCoupleReadingABookTogether642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/OlderCoupleReadingABookTogether642-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/OlderCoupleReadingABookTogether642-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-144646" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Alzheimer's is arguably one of the most important diseases confronting humankind. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAD5TsR1koQ/"&gt;Robert Kneschke/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In our model of Alzheimer's, beta-amyloid helps to protect and bolster our immune system, but unfortunately, it also plays a central role in the autoimmune process that, we believe, may lead to the development of Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though drugs conventionally used in the treatment of autoimmune diseases may not work against Alzheimer's, we strongly believe that targeting other immune-regulating pathways in the brain will lead us to new and effective treatment approaches for the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/first-of-its-kind-study-identifies-how-the-brain-could-thwart-alzheimers"&gt;First-of-Its-Kind Study Identifies How The Brain Could Thwart Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Other theories of the disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to this autoimmune theory of Alzheimer's, many other new and varied theories are beginning to appear. For example, some scientists believe that &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.mito.2022.05.001"&gt;Alzheimer's is a disease of tiny cellular structures called mitochondria&lt;/a&gt; – the energy factories in every brain cell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mitochondria convert oxygen from the air we breathe and glucose from the food we eat into the energy required for remembering and thinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some maintain that it is the end-result of a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.4103/1673-5374.339476"&gt;particular brain infection&lt;/a&gt;, with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/prd.12429"&gt;bacteria from the mouth often being suggested as the culprit&lt;/a&gt;. Still others suggest that the disease may arise from an &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/biom12050714"&gt;abnormal handling of metals within the brain&lt;/a&gt;, possibly zinc, copper, or iron.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is gratifying to see &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1136/jnnp-2021-327370"&gt;new thinking about this age-old disease&lt;/a&gt;. Dementia currently affects more than 50 million people worldwide, with a new diagnosis being made every three seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Often, people living with Alzheimer's disease are unable to recognize their own children or even their spouse of more than 50 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer's is a public health crisis in need of innovative ideas and fresh directions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_144650" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-144650" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/YoungPersonKissingASeniorLadyOnTheCheek642.jpg" alt="A young person kissing an older lady on the cheek" class="size-full wp-image-144650" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/YoungPersonKissingASeniorLadyOnTheCheek642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/YoungPersonKissingASeniorLadyOnTheCheek642-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/YoungPersonKissingASeniorLadyOnTheCheek642-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-144650" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Often, people living with Alzheimer's disease are unable to recognize their own children. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEJfNN0xD0/"&gt;akurtz/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the well-being of the people and families living with dementia, and for the socioeconomic impact on our already stressed health-care system coping with the ever-escalating costs and demands of dementia, we need a better understanding of Alzheimer's, its causes, and what we can do to treat it and to help the people and families who are living with it.&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/189047/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/donald-weaver-566502"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Donald Weaver&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, Professor of Chemistry and Director of Krembil Research Institute, University Health Network, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-toronto-1281"&gt;University of Toronto&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/alzheimers-might-not-be-primarily-a-brain-disease-a-new-theory-suggests-its-an-autoimmune-condition-189047"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in September 2022.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 20:56:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxPX1NmTV8zX0JxSzdPUmF0cjA2aTNNdmtOb0RQdDRjNEs0U2cwMWNVYXhEQmJhMmJlNmk1NDQxYnNJUnhzQ0NBeU1teEJIdUN0SVMtV2ZLZnh4WkNCNWVHeFU3MklFNWRSLTk4TnJjZ1Y2Q3VYYlU3S3hBdDYzdi00WV96X2lORnp5cDhjTjAyNTRGckVr</guid></item><item><title>我们在过去30年中对自恋心理学的了解- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/what-weve-learned-about-the-psychology-of-narcissism-over-the-past-30-years/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ve probably seen the word “narcissist” thrown around online in headlines, on dating apps or in therapy-themed TikToks. But the label that people often unthinkingly slap on toxic bosses or reality TV villains hides a much more complicated psychological picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Psychologists have studied narcissism for many years, but over time, our understanding has evolved. One of the biggest changes is that today, narcissism is no longer seen as just grandiosity, arrogance or egotism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early scientific descriptions of narcissism &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0272735807001602?via%3Dihub"&gt;focused on dominance&lt;/a&gt;, ambition and self-importance, all of which are traits associated with traditional masculine stereotypes. That meant narcissistic tendencies in women were often misread or overlooked. When those traits &lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/doiLanding?doi=10.1037%2Fa0038231"&gt;show up as emotional sensitivity&lt;/a&gt;, insecurity or relational manipulation, they sometimes still are misdiagnosed as anxiety, mood disorders or &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/psychology/articles/10.3389/fpsyg.2023.1090746/full"&gt;borderline personality disorder&lt;/a&gt; traits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most extreme and persistent forms of narcissism can sometimes be diagnosed as narcissistic personality disorder. This condition was added to the &lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2013-14907-000"&gt;Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders&lt;/a&gt;, the American Psychiatric Association’s diagnostic manual, in 1980. But most people with narcissistic tendencies won’t meet the threshold for a diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;So what does the research actually say?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Narcissism in general is &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/09637214211044109"&gt;now understood&lt;/a&gt; as a complex set of personality characteristics that can show up in different ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Psychologists had long suspected that there might be different kinds of narcissism, but it wasn’t until 1991 – when researcher Paul Wink and his colleagues &lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/doiLanding?doi=10.1037%2F0022-3514.61.4.590"&gt;presented a model&lt;/a&gt; including grandiose and vulnerable subtypes – that they were more formally recognised. Although there are other models, this remains one of the more popular approaches to understanding narcissistic tendencies in the wider population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/09637214211044109"&gt;2021 review&lt;/a&gt; by US psychologist Joshua Miller and his colleagues pulled together decades of research to offer one of the most authoritative summaries of how psychologists now understand narcissism. It explains that narcissism has a common foundation, which includes things such as self-importance and entitlement. It then branches into different forms of narcissism, such as grandiosity, antagonism and vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers now often use the terms &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0272735807001602?via%3Dihub"&gt;grandiose and vulnerable&lt;/a&gt; to describe two major forms of narcissism. One person with narcissistic traits may be bold with high levels of grandiose traits, confidence and emotional resilience. Another might be defensive, anxious and hypersensitive to criticism. Both show signs of narcissistic self-focus, but they end up looking quite different in how they experience and express emotion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S019188692100773X?via%3Dihub"&gt;2022 research paper&lt;/a&gt; I wrote with colleagues, we carried out the first meta-analysis examining how narcissistic traits relate to the ability to control one’s emotions. The results showed that vulnerable narcissism is consistently associated with greater emotional difficulty, which means these people might find it harder to keep their emotions in check.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In particular, people with high scores on vulnerable narcissism scales are more likely to rely on suppression. Suppression is a strategy that people use to hide or inhibit their emotional expressions, and has been linked to &lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/doiLanding?doi=10.1037%2F0022-3514.85.2.348"&gt;poorer wellbeing&lt;/a&gt;. On the surface, suppression might sound like self-control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some situations, it can be. For example, keeping a lid on your emotions when your boss is yelling at you. But trying to mute emotional expression without addressing the underlying emotions increases stress when it becomes our default strategy. It can worsen mental and physical health over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, grandiose narcissism wasn’t linked with emotion regulation difficulties. In fact, several of the studies included in our analysis suggest that people with higher levels of grandiose traits may not experience as much emotional distress in the first place. This challenges the popular idea among researchers that people who exhibit narcissistic tendencies are also experiencing emotional instability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Emotional intelligence and self-perception&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The differences between forms of narcissism show up in emotional intelligence research as well. In a &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/17540739211014585"&gt;2021 systematic review&lt;/a&gt; on narcissism and emotional intelligence, my colleagues and I found that people with grandiose traits often said they were good at understanding and managing emotions. For instance, how well they think they can handle anger or recognise other’s emotions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But when their skills were tested using emotion tasks (such as recognising facial expressions or identifying the best way to respond to an emotional situation), their performance didn’t always match up with how skilled they said they were. This is consistent with a &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/psychology/articles/10.3389/fpsyg.2018.01606/full"&gt;2018 study&lt;/a&gt; which also found that people with grandiose tendencies rated themselves as emotionally skilled but performed worse on skill-based emotional intelligence tasks compared to other participants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, people with vulnerable narcissistic traits tend to rate themselves lower in emotional intelligence, and seem to genuinely struggle more with managing emotions in everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;So what should we make of all this?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s time to move beyond the pop-psych trend of labelling difficult people as narcissists. Narcissism isn’t about taking too many selfies. And no, the partner who ghosted you or the colleague who dominates meetings isn’t necessarily high in narcissistic traits either – no matter how much we might like to complain about them over coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These kinds of casual diagnoses aren’t just unhelpful, they’re often wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Narcissism is a complex psychological pattern that can show up in different ways and can reflect a deeper struggle with things such as self-esteem, emotion regulation and social connection. Understanding this doesn’t excuse people’s bad behaviour – not at all. But it does help us look past the stereotypes to get a clearer picture of what narcissistic traits look like in everyday life.&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/258505/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img class="lazyload" decoding="async" src="" data-src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/258505/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/what-weve-learned-about-narcissism-over-the-past-30-years-258505"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 18:05:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxNb1BORS05T3Y1MWpCOFlqaW1ya2lDQ1VJUEF4QmplZ1haV3A4eWpkdzZoYUs1MUN2cUlabnEwNHNqeFduNEFHTnlQaE1INVlnM3JrMVNzU05uVnBWSG1CSW5Dd2phZS1PaVVYOS1vbDVfcjFFZVBvVVJ2S3o2a2FmT2w1NVppT19ONUtUaHJaUTZJZkRIM1FubFdldkxGcWJjNmc</guid></item><item><title>降雨后蚊子全力扑灭- ABC15亚利桑那州</title><link>https://www.abc15.com/news/local-news/mosquitoes-are-out-in-full-force-following-rainfall</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="RichTextArticleBody-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;PHOENIX — With Arizona getting more rainfall in recent weeks, residents have emailed ABC15 saying they’re getting bitten more often by mosquitoes. The Maricopa County Environmental Services Vector Control Division said they’ve been receiving more complaints in the last 10 days compared to all of last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Division manager John Townsend said they’ve received almost a thousand community complaints in the last week or so, bringing them up to about 3,000 for the calendar year so far. All of 2024, Townsend said, they received around 1,000 community complaints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They’ve been very small, and it’s been a lot at once. They bit me up. This is the most I've ever been bit by mosquitoes in my life,” said Phoenix resident Tayja.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;In the video player above, find out the difference between the mosquitoes you see during the day and at night and what you can do to protect yourself. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC15 Arizona</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 17:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxPSW1XVUlJOGhJTTlMSDNXV0trZzNSU0NjVVpUcVUxdlo4cUtKLWkxNFVLVWxuYjMtWDBqMUlNOTk5S3JtZVg0cExhRjlRaDlZcVpKYWktNDZlT3ppYzZtY1N3Qk1Xb1JHa1ZQYnZ5OGx1TERPNUQzemctZC11OVN0RXRhdGo1UmJrWUpvS1Q4dWNodVk</guid></item><item><title>新的大流行即将来临？日本宣布在全国范围内爆发流感，超过4000人住院治疗-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/new-pandemic-coming-japan-declares-nationwide-flu-outbreak-over-4000-hospitalised/articleshow/124484790.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the changing weather and declining immunity, flu season was expected to arrive in the coming months across the world. However, Japan has declared a nationwide flu outbreak, following a high rise in hospitalisations and school closures, leaving the public health system under pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Flu epidemic in Japan&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="Flu epidemic in Japan" msid="124485178" width="" title="Image credits: Getty Images" placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-124485178/flu-epidemic-in-japan.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;Image credits: Getty Images&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Japanese media reports, the Health Ministry has confirmed that the national average has surpassed the epidemic threshold, reaching 1.04 patients per medical institution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's surprising is that typically Japan sees a flu season from late November or December, but this year, the outbreak has arrived nearly five weeks earlier, alarming the citizens and officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Health Ministry reported that by October 3, more than 4,000 people had been hospitalised with influenza, a fourfold increase from the previous week. Twenty-eight of Japan’s 47 prefectures have reported rising cases. Particularly in Tokyo, Okinawa and Kagoshima at least 135 schools and childcare centres have been temporarily shut down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Warning of a fast-evolving virus&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="Warning of a fast-evolving virus" msid="124485226" width="" title="Image credits: Getty Images" placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-124485226/warning-of-a-fast-evolving-virus.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;Image credits: Getty Images&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to health specialists, the early and intense outbreak could signal a shift in the flu virus's behaviour. Professor Yoko Tsukamoto of the Health Sciences University of Hokkaido spoke to the Japanese media, saying, “The flu season has started really early this year, but in the changing global environment this might become a more common scenario.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tsukamoto advised common precautions like vaccination, wearing masks, washing hands regularly and avoiding spreading infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts have been urging the vulnerable population including the elderly, children and those with pre-existing conditions to get vaccinated immediately. “For most healthy individuals, the flu may be unpleasant but not dangerous. But for vulnerable groups, early vaccination is crucial,” added Tsukamoto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 17:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgJBVV95cUxNQ1Q2QkFQV1h0NmJJWnpGYUczNnNTSXN6bkNEQ1Y0bkl4RHRLaVFiN1hYbGJZWV9qUzVhdDdKb0RKOGZ5NlVDYmtTX2RYMEc2TEJMeTZLdUw5QlQ4RHZ3cVBBem9vRjJNZWprenJVeXZkM19ZSzRZUXBCeGVOSEtrOGE4MTVhZ2M2b3c0U3VfdF9laXExc0dkcGcwV3JJNFd4TDllUlVLX2hPT1JMWHhqZmI4TmZvbUNKbkVFblkzaW13MjhsdEt5dHEyZVR4WWMtWDlLdEJEZUZ0RjBQckVnTDdodi1ILXJRelRIbXVqek9vN29oSHZkQXQ3NEhRTHpHWDZ1Q1F4QjJBZzZBckHSAZMCQVVfeXFMTWdKN1c0cFVSdnpFMVlwZ3ZmcThVRy05U1ROSW4zaHk4TlBEbkJJZFpFRHQ3NmdMWF9lSmdkWE9qWVYwN1ZyRmtzTWlBQ25hV3ZncEs0MEFxYmZmcGI2cTV4cGhscnZIWV80VGhGWnF3VGE2cVpTMFdXQUFmcHJOSnM4Z0owUGVFeldtSXJHSkVhOVdQV1hXeTNyVGhCMHpJY3pVenBaOXhDMm40MjBBX3lxbU4tUUVQNkxQb1ZOT0tkSFhrU0M0NkRBZEhGb1NTSHlvQ2tjVVg3MXJYaUVMTkFlclVuWnpPR19KaW93cGFoekJETE9mZFAtTlFSb1ZNQUJJNkp5cFVvYXFsRXJ4WHg1Nkk</guid></item><item><title>25年前，果园港的人预计会得阿尔茨海默氏症。为什么不呢？ -《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/port-orchard-man-was-expected-to-get-alzheimers-25-years-ago-why-hasnt-he/</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwAFBVV95cUxNSUdCMGdOaEVFWGdDSVppbjdOYkZjZE1KdGZ2RkZUNFVQVU5zYjNUbWh5NmlMRDNrcDkwSS0zSjhBaTdHR0pZS1hJWEV1OTdCeV9fUEpuR09vV0llbXdWaXJhcV84T3kya1ZLQVZaNEVvZXRLSGlUSVZVNmNmTFJnQ3Jjd2lHV0swV1FKOHZUOVB4ZS05Wk01S2lFTGFrd3pETzU1VFJRR3pBN291UzRKQ2Z2UTZ4YWhpYU5MdVpSQ2o?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Port Orchard man was expected to get Alzheimer’s 25 years ago. Why hasn’t he?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqNggKIjBDQklTSGpvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoRUtEd2o3czZiZER4RWt1Ujg5LUVhMXdpZ0FQAQ?hl=en-US&amp;amp;gl=US&amp;amp;ceid=US:en&amp;amp;oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View Full Coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 17:00:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxNSUdCMGdOaEVFWGdDSVppbjdOYkZjZE1KdGZ2RkZUNFVQVU5zYjNUbWh5NmlMRDNrcDkwSS0zSjhBaTdHR0pZS1hJWEV1OTdCeV9fUEpuR09vV0llbXdWaXJhcV84T3kya1ZLQVZaNEVvZXRLSGlUSVZVNmNmTFJnQ3Jjd2lHV0swV1FKOHZUOVB4ZS05Wk01S2lFTGFrd3pETzU1VFJRR3pBN291UzRKQ2Z2UTZ4YWhpYU5MdVpSQ2o</guid></item><item><title>如果您被蚊子叮咬，您永远不应该做的一件事- buzzfeed.com</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/juliaries/what-to-do-mosquito-bite-sc</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-5
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="cleaning" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139482854" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Of course, not scratching isn’t the only way to speed up your recovery, and there are a few &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mosquitoes/about/about-mosquito-bites.html" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7956216" data-affiliate="true"&gt;other steps&lt;/a&gt; you want to take to prevent infection and make sure your bite gets better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The very first thing you want to do after you get bit is wash the bite out with soap and water. This will help remove &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/insect-bites-and-stings/#:~:text=Easing%20your%20symptoms,do%20to%20ease%20your%20symptoms." target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7956216" data-affiliate="true"&gt;bacteria&lt;/a&gt; near the bite that could cause an infection. A mosquito bite is technically a small wound, said Frable, and “it’s generally a good idea to wash all wounds gently with soap and water.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, you want to apply ice to the bite, ideally for about 10 minutes or so, Pritt explained. Ice can drastically reduce the itching along with inflammation, pain and swelling, according to the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/17695-mosquito-bites#:~:text=Ice:%20Ice%20can%20slow%20down,vera%20is%20a%20succulent%20plant." target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7956216" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next up: Cover the bite with an anti-itch or antihistamine cream, such as calamine lotion or hydrocortisone. &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/17695-mosquito-bites" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7956216" data-affiliate="true"&gt;These products&lt;/a&gt; can drastically reduce itchiness and, most importantly, prevent you from scratching the bite and break the scratch-itch cycle, Pritt said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you don’t have these items in your medicine cabinet or aren’t able to get to a pharmacy, you can whip up an &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/mosquito-bites/diagnosis-treatment/drc-20375314" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7956216" data-affiliate="true"&gt;anti-itch paste&lt;/a&gt; at home. Simply combine a tablespoon of baking soda with a splash of water to create a thick paste. Then, rub the mixture over the bite, wait 10 minutes, and wash it off. This DIY concoction reduces itch, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/mosquito-bites/diagnosis-treatment/drc-20375314" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7956216" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;, but, better yet, it prevents you from scratching the bite and making things even worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, you want to keep an eye on the bite and pay attention to any symptoms you develop over the next week or two. It’s fairly common to develop a fever or even swollen lymph nodes immediately after the bite, so don’t panic if you experience &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mosquitoes/about/about-mosquito-bites.html#:~:text=What%20happens%20when%20a%20mosquito,soreness,%20and%20redness%20can%20occur.&amp;amp;text=The%20body%20reacts%20to%20mosquito%20saliva%20following%20a%20blood%20meal." target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7956216" data-affiliate="true"&gt;these symptoms&lt;/a&gt; right away, Pritt said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not all mosquitoes carry disease, but some spread Zika, dengue and West Nile virus, all of which can cause severe illnesses and health complications. You can’t tell if a mosquito carried a pathogen by simply looking at the bite, according to Frable, which is why it’s crucial to pay attention to any symptoms. So, if you get a fever, a rash, severe headache, or confusion a week or two after the bite, check in with a physician. They can run diagnostics tests to determine if you contracted a mosquito-borne disease and administer supportive care to help you recover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, most mosquito bites resolve without any issues. But the less you itch and the better you take care of it, the sooner it’ll clear up … until the next mosquito comes along. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/what-to-do-mosquito-bite_l_66c4c636e4b0047d36bf6f3a" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7956216"&gt;&lt;em&gt;HuffPost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>buzzfeed.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 16:31:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE9aNjdEdTM0VmhMRTVaVHc5S3RzQnE2N3Q2T2NUZHA4ZXlVN0tDLUg1V3lNYTZnTmNGNEJtdGE5bm9oU2hFLVdsZlowLXZUMXBrQ0t2Sy1tLTVvQ0Utemhabmk5ekFwLWNYenhzdTFGaw</guid></item><item><title>保护大脑免受早发性痴呆的流行早餐食品-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15174517/breakfast-foods-protect-brain-early-onset-dementia.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Simple diet swaps could be key to preventing early-onset dementia, researchers have revealed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 7million Americans have been diagnosed with memory-robbing dementia, with that figure set to nearly double by 2050. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, one &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-13688417/factors-raise-risk-dementia-REVEALED-half-cases-avoided-people-changes-life-experts-say.html"&gt;major Lancet study&lt;/a&gt; published last year found more than a dozen of the most common risk factors for dementia are modifiable, including diet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And the results are clear. A &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14947279/doctors-reveal-simple-lifestyle-changes-prevent-dementia-study.html"&gt;landmark trial unveiled earlier this year&lt;/a&gt; found people at risk of developing dementia improved their cognitive scores after implementing diet changes, as well as exercise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now, recent studies have shown foods rich in nutrients like protein, antioxidants and carbohydrates could reduce the risk the most.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Eggs, which were &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14133867/surprising-link-eggs-dementia-risk.html"&gt;long demonized for high fat and cholesterol&lt;/a&gt;, in particular are enjoying a health renaissance for containing brain-healthy amino acids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Berries and dark, leafy greens, meanwhile are rich in antioxidants that protect brain cells responsible for memory shielded from inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And even dark chocolate may improve blood flow to the brain and boost functioning in old age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Daily Mail has revealed the best dementia-fighting foods below.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Studies have revealed the foods that are most likely to stave off dementia (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
    &lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Eggs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Eggs are a key feature in the standard American diet, with more than one in three adults claiming they have them for breakfast on a given day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One large egg contains about 150 milligrams of choline, about one-quarter of the recommended daily value. Choline is an essential nutrient also found in protein sources such as salmon and beef and chicken livers that supports memory, mood and muscle control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's thought to boost levels of the neurotransmitter acetylcholine, which controls memory and learning, and reduce levels of neurotoxins like homocysteine that damage neurons. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group floatRHS"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Eggs are rich in brain-healthy nutrients like choline, which supports memory and learning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A study in &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S002231662400289X"&gt;The Journal of Nutrition&lt;/a&gt; found that older adults who consumed more than one egg per week had a 47 percent reduced risk of dementia compared to those who had less than one egg in a week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers, from the Rush University Memory and Aging Project in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/chicago/index.html" id="mol-b7c70501-ae68-11ef-a4f6-17bf25becc42" class=""&gt;Chicago&lt;/a&gt;, noted this was likely due to the choline in the eggs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another study published last month in the journal &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/16/19/3340"&gt;Nutrients&lt;/a&gt; looked at more than 400 adults in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/china/index.html" id="mol-b7c70500-ae68-11ef-a4f6-17bf25becc42" class=""&gt;China&lt;/a&gt; over age 50, half of whom were diagnosed with dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers found that participants who ate eggs every day had a lower risk of dementia than those eating them only weekly or monthly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One large egg also contains six grams of protein, which provides amino acids needed to produce neurotransmitters like serotonin. Serotonin is crucial for cognitive function and reducing levels of toxic amyloid-beta plaques, a hallmark of Alzheimer's disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Berries&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Berries are rich in antioxidants, which reduce inflammation in the brain and prevent brain volume from shrinking (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Strawberries, blueberries and raspberries, among others, are well known for containing antioxidants, substances that protect cells from damage caused by toxic molecules called free radicals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Left unchecked, free radicals induce oxidative stress, leading to inflammation and the production of amyloid-beta.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Found in the brain's gray matter, amyloid-beta builds up and forms plaques, which attack brain cells and cause overall brain volume to shrink. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-12743301/strawberries-dementia-risk-study.html"&gt;2023 study&lt;/a&gt; out of the University of Cincinnati found that adults between 50 and 65 who ate a cup of strawberries every day for 12 weeks performed better on memory tests and had fewer symptoms of depression than those who took a placebo. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Those researchers also published a recent study in the journal &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/14/8/1619/htm"&gt;Nutrients&lt;/a&gt; that found regular consumption of blueberries reduced signs of cognitive decline.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Berries are a staple of the MIND diet, a combination of the Mediterranean and DASH (Dietary Approaches to Stopping Hypertension) diets that prioritizes anti-inflammatory foods.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Dark chocolate&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dark chocolate contains compounds called flavonoids, which increase blood flow to the brain and prevent damage (stock image) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Chocolate is generally seen as a 'guilty pleasure' and something most people should limit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But in moderation, dark chocolate has been shown to lower the risk of dementia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dark chocolate is rich in flavonoids, compounds found in plant-based foods that have antioxidant and anti-inflammatory properties, much like berries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Flavonoids also increase blood flow to the brain, preventing damage and improving overall function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A bar of dark chocolate can contain anywhere from 200 milligrams to 1,000 milligrams depending on the size, manufacturer and cacao percentage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A recent study published in &lt;a target="_blank" class="" rel="nofollow" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s43016-025-01176-1"&gt;Nature Food&lt;/a&gt; of 125,000 people found those who consumed the widest variety of flavonoids, including dark chocolate, had a 14 percent lower risk of all-cause mortality. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/your-brain-on-chocolate-2017081612179"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; found that among adults ages 50 to 69, those who took a cocoa supplement with high flavanol content for three months performed better on memory tests than those who took supplements with lower flavanol levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Whole grains and nuts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Unsalted nuts have been shown to lower dementia risk in older adults (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Like eggs, carbs have long been considered a nutritional boogeyman due to the risks of weight gain, high blood sugar and diabetes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;High glucose (blood sugar) levels can damage brain cells and blood vessels in the brain, potentially leading to dementia.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But whole grains like wheat, brown rice and oats contain complex carbohydrates, which digest slowly and provide the body with a steady, regulated flow of glucose. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Whole grains also are high in fiber, which ferments in the gut to form short-chain fatty acids that regulate inflammation in the brain.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.google.com/search?q=whole+grains+dementia+study&amp;amp;rlz=1C1GCPF_enUS1174US1174&amp;amp;oq=whole+grains+dementia+study&amp;amp;gs_lcrp=EgZjaHJvbWUyCQgAEEUYORigATIHCAEQIRigATIHCAIQIRigATIHCAMQIRigATIHCAQQIRirAjIHCAUQIRirAjIHCAYQIRiPAjIHCAcQIRiPAjIHCAgQIRiPAtIBCDM1MjdqMGo5qAIAsAIB&amp;amp;sourceid=chrome&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8"&gt;2023 study&lt;/a&gt; in the journal Neurology found participants who consumed whole grains regularly had a slower rate of memory decline with age than those who did not eat these foods. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nuts, meanwhile, are rich in omega-3 fatty acids, which may increase the volume of the brain's memory center, the hippocampus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Research &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11979034/"&gt;published earlier this year&lt;/a&gt; found eating a handful of unsalted nuts a day was enough to lower the overall risk of developing dementia.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Like berries, whole grains and nuts are both staples of the MIND diet.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 16:01:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxQWGVHM283ZGljaVgtbzRocmR6XzJrWnhwZ2tpTXd2bHlWVnZ6RVJWamFEM21WcUhlODFXZnJnaWpROHdPNE1yc3ZyVDNQLTkzRUJaWEhGZ2xDYlBiNzVEZVBabUozS1ZRWlNWZ25IRVhjNDlKX3B2eVVWMGt3bmxDbEF2TjlZbHlQeUx0d2pjaE5IZ0FNNzYyb1paMHYtZS1KdDExTkZDQi1iMDDSAbABQVVfeXFMT1Z5S0Vra1plNGEyYnppcXBXQlZxNExka1RBOTVDLVJORDkyem1pSDJmYmE0OEdyZEZKa3kwMnozQ0w1MlpiNHdNcDF6Ty1FRVpZSUtZaXpOWFFMT2Jld2UxRzJDY2dheW9ObUw3UWVXZk1vcy05dXpJaFhHbWNkcFJrUWhxNXdTdTNyQUdqR3JrMm41RDgwX2pxM0F1T2YzOTJPRjFMODZ6R2dxaWdoaEs</guid></item><item><title>保护大脑免受早发性痴呆的流行早餐食品-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15174517/breakfast-foods-protect-brain-early-onset-dementia.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Simple diet swaps could be key to preventing early-onset dementia, researchers have revealed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 7million Americans have been diagnosed with memory-robbing dementia, with that figure set to nearly double by 2050. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, one &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-13688417/factors-raise-risk-dementia-REVEALED-half-cases-avoided-people-changes-life-experts-say.html"&gt;major Lancet study&lt;/a&gt; published last year found more than a dozen of the most common risk factors for dementia are modifiable, including diet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And the results are clear. A &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14947279/doctors-reveal-simple-lifestyle-changes-prevent-dementia-study.html"&gt;landmark trial unveiled earlier this year&lt;/a&gt; found people at risk of developing dementia improved their cognitive scores after implementing diet changes, as well as exercise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now, recent studies have shown foods rich in nutrients like protein, antioxidants and carbohydrates could reduce the risk the most.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Eggs, which were &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14133867/surprising-link-eggs-dementia-risk.html"&gt;long demonized for high fat and cholesterol&lt;/a&gt;, in particular are enjoying a health renaissance for containing brain-healthy amino acids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Berries and dark, leafy greens, meanwhile are rich in antioxidants that protect brain cells responsible for memory shielded from inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And even dark chocolate may improve blood flow to the brain and boost functioning in old age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Daily Mail has revealed the best dementia-fighting foods below.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Studies have revealed the foods that are most likely to stave off dementia (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
    &lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Eggs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Eggs are a key feature in the standard American diet, with more than one in three adults claiming they have them for breakfast on a given day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One large egg contains about 150 milligrams of choline, about one-quarter of the recommended daily value. Choline is an essential nutrient also found in protein sources such as salmon and beef and chicken livers that supports memory, mood and muscle control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's thought to boost levels of the neurotransmitter acetylcholine, which controls memory and learning, and reduce levels of neurotoxins like homocysteine that damage neurons. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group floatRHS"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Eggs are rich in brain-healthy nutrients like choline, which supports memory and learning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A study in &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S002231662400289X"&gt;The Journal of Nutrition&lt;/a&gt; found that older adults who consumed more than one egg per week had a 47 percent reduced risk of dementia compared to those who had less than one egg in a week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers, from the Rush University Memory and Aging Project in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/chicago/index.html" id="mol-b7c70501-ae68-11ef-a4f6-17bf25becc42" class=""&gt;Chicago&lt;/a&gt;, noted this was likely due to the choline in the eggs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another study published last month in the journal &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/16/19/3340"&gt;Nutrients&lt;/a&gt; looked at more than 400 adults in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/china/index.html" id="mol-b7c70500-ae68-11ef-a4f6-17bf25becc42" class=""&gt;China&lt;/a&gt; over age 50, half of whom were diagnosed with dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers found that participants who ate eggs every day had a lower risk of dementia than those eating them only weekly or monthly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One large egg also contains six grams of protein, which provides amino acids needed to produce neurotransmitters like serotonin. Serotonin is crucial for cognitive function and reducing levels of toxic amyloid-beta plaques, a hallmark of Alzheimer's disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Berries&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Berries are rich in antioxidants, which reduce inflammation in the brain and prevent brain volume from shrinking (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Strawberries, blueberries and raspberries, among others, are well known for containing antioxidants, substances that protect cells from damage caused by toxic molecules called free radicals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Left unchecked, free radicals induce oxidative stress, leading to inflammation and the production of amyloid-beta.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Found in the brain's gray matter, amyloid-beta builds up and forms plaques, which attack brain cells and cause overall brain volume to shrink. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-12743301/strawberries-dementia-risk-study.html"&gt;2023 study&lt;/a&gt; out of the University of Cincinnati found that adults between 50 and 65 who ate a cup of strawberries every day for 12 weeks performed better on memory tests and had fewer symptoms of depression than those who took a placebo. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Those researchers also published a recent study in the journal &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/14/8/1619/htm"&gt;Nutrients&lt;/a&gt; that found regular consumption of blueberries reduced signs of cognitive decline.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Berries are a staple of the MIND diet, a combination of the Mediterranean and DASH (Dietary Approaches to Stopping Hypertension) diets that prioritizes anti-inflammatory foods.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Dark chocolate&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dark chocolate contains compounds called flavonoids, which increase blood flow to the brain and prevent damage (stock image) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Chocolate is generally seen as a 'guilty pleasure' and something most people should limit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But in moderation, dark chocolate has been shown to lower the risk of dementia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dark chocolate is rich in flavonoids, compounds found in plant-based foods that have antioxidant and anti-inflammatory properties, much like berries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Flavonoids also increase blood flow to the brain, preventing damage and improving overall function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A bar of dark chocolate can contain anywhere from 200 milligrams to 1,000 milligrams depending on the size, manufacturer and cacao percentage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A recent study published in &lt;a target="_blank" class="" rel="nofollow" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s43016-025-01176-1"&gt;Nature Food&lt;/a&gt; of 125,000 people found those who consumed the widest variety of flavonoids, including dark chocolate, had a 14 percent lower risk of all-cause mortality. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/your-brain-on-chocolate-2017081612179"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; found that among adults ages 50 to 69, those who took a cocoa supplement with high flavanol content for three months performed better on memory tests than those who took supplements with lower flavanol levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Whole grains and nuts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Unsalted nuts have been shown to lower dementia risk in older adults (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Like eggs, carbs have long been considered a nutritional boogeyman due to the risks of weight gain, high blood sugar and diabetes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;High glucose (blood sugar) levels can damage brain cells and blood vessels in the brain, potentially leading to dementia.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But whole grains like wheat, brown rice and oats contain complex carbohydrates, which digest slowly and provide the body with a steady, regulated flow of glucose. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Whole grains also are high in fiber, which ferments in the gut to form short-chain fatty acids that regulate inflammation in the brain.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.google.com/search?q=whole+grains+dementia+study&amp;amp;rlz=1C1GCPF_enUS1174US1174&amp;amp;oq=whole+grains+dementia+study&amp;amp;gs_lcrp=EgZjaHJvbWUyCQgAEEUYORigATIHCAEQIRigATIHCAIQIRigATIHCAMQIRigATIHCAQQIRirAjIHCAUQIRirAjIHCAYQIRiPAjIHCAcQIRiPAjIHCAgQIRiPAtIBCDM1MjdqMGo5qAIAsAIB&amp;amp;sourceid=chrome&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8"&gt;2023 study&lt;/a&gt; in the journal Neurology found participants who consumed whole grains regularly had a slower rate of memory decline with age than those who did not eat these foods. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nuts, meanwhile, are rich in omega-3 fatty acids, which may increase the volume of the brain's memory center, the hippocampus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Research &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11979034/"&gt;published earlier this year&lt;/a&gt; found eating a handful of unsalted nuts a day was enough to lower the overall risk of developing dementia.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Like berries, whole grains and nuts are both staples of the MIND diet.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 16:01:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxQWGVHM283ZGljaVgtbzRocmR6XzJrWnhwZ2tpTXd2bHlWVnZ6RVJWamFEM21WcUhlODFXZnJnaWpROHdPNE1yc3ZyVDNQLTkzRUJaWEhGZ2xDYlBiNzVEZVBabUozS1ZRWlNWZ25IRVhjNDlKX3B2eVVWMGt3bmxDbEF2TjlZbHlQeUx0d2pjaE5IZ0FNNzYyb1paMHYtZS1KdDExTkZDQi1iMDA</guid></item><item><title>他汀类药物，解释：每个男人都需要了解的他汀类药物- GQ</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/stains-explained-1</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The drugs can reduce a patient's LDL cholesterol by around thirty—sometimes even fifty—percent &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.heartuk.org.uk/getting-treatment/statins#:~:text=Statins%20are%20a%20type%20of,even%2050%25%20with%20high%20doses." class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.heartuk.org.uk/getting-treatment/statins#:~:text=Statins%20are%20a%20type%20of,even%2050%25%20with%20high%20doses."}' href="https://www.heartuk.org.uk/getting-treatment/statins#:~:text=Statins%20are%20a%20type%20of,even%2050%25%20with%20high%20doses." rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;with high doses&lt;/a&gt;. A meta-analysis of 27 randomized trials, showed that statin therapy helped reduce adverse cardiovascular events &lt;a href="https://www.acc.org/latest-in-cardiology/articles/2016/11/17/09/03/summarizing-the-current-state-and-evidence-on-efficacy-and-safety-of-statin-therapy#:~:text=In%20a%20meta-analysis%20of,mortality%20is%20reduced%20by%2010%25."&gt;by twenty to twenty-five percent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p role="heading" aria-level="3" class="heading-h3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are statins right for me?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reason statins are so widely prescribed is because they work. They’re often prescribed as the first level of defense. This isn't to say that they’re the only way to get your cholesterol levels down. Dropping weight, moving more, and changing your diet can also make big shifts. Still, sometimes lifestyle changes alone are not enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“​​Diet can lower LDL by about ten to fifteen percent which may be sufficient for some people to achieve their LDL goal level,” said McGowan. “However, there are many people for whom diet is insufficient either because they already have cardiovascular disease or because they have genetic conditions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Depending on what your doctor advises, a combination of lifestyle changes and medications might be necessary. People more prone to heart disease or stroke, including &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/cholesterol/treating_cholesterol.htm#:~:text=Statin%20drugs%20lower%20LDL%20cholesterol,is%20already%20in%20the%20blood."&gt;men over forty&lt;/a&gt;, should also think more seriously about medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p role="heading" aria-level="3" class="heading-h3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the side effects of statins?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Statins come with a number of potential side effects. Some of these can be relatively minor like dizziness, constipation, or flatulence. They can also include things like muscle pain. More rarely, statins have been associated with things like memory loss, liver inflammation, and an increase in diabetes. Board-certified cardiologist R. Todd Hurst found that in his clinical experience side effects impacted about &lt;a data-offer-url="https://blogs.webmd.com/heart-health/20210121/considering-statins-what-a-cardiologist-wants-you-to-know" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://blogs.webmd.com/heart-health/20210121/considering-statins-what-a-cardiologist-wants-you-to-know"}' href="https://blogs.webmd.com/heart-health/20210121/considering-statins-what-a-cardiologist-wants-you-to-know" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;ten percent of people&lt;/a&gt;, which was similar to the numbers found in research trials, with the most-common side effect being sore muscles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p role="heading" aria-level="3" class="heading-h3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ideally, statins are paired with a healthy lifestyle&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For many experts, lifestyle changes take center stage, especially as preventative measures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Many people prefer to avoid taking medications and try to lower their cholesterol, as statins have been shown to increase cortisol, which in turn trigger a chain reaction with your body’s natural hormone production,” said Dr. Darren Clair, Chief Medical Officer at &lt;a data-offer-url="https://rebalancehealth.com/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://rebalancehealth.com/"}' href="https://rebalancehealth.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Rebalance Health&lt;/a&gt;. “Eating a whole food plant-based diet, as well as managing stress, getting enough quality sleep, and maintaining natural, healthy hormone levels in a comprehensive manner is the best way to achieve optimal health and minimize your risk of all chronic health conditions including heart disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the best course of action for figuring out whether or not you should be using statins is always going to be talking things through with a medical professional and chatting about the potential cost/benefits. But if you're a person who is at higher risk for a cardiovascular event—again looking at men over forty and overweight folks—then that might be a conversation you want to be having sooner rather than later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div class="ExternalLinkEmbedWrapper-hyhwEF gAlnVg" data-testid="external-link-embed--inline"&gt;&lt;div class="ExternalLinkEmbedText-gqUJZT bQrYnp"&gt;&lt;p class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE ExternalLinkEmbedRubric-hJfSsX bLcSov cpCFUv"&gt;Read More&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a attributes="[object Object]" class="external-link-embed__hed-link button" href="/story/cholesterol-explained"&gt;&lt;span class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE ExternalLinkEmbedHed-dDmZdb deqABF fHNWjh jMVqeX"&gt;The Good and the Bad of Cholesterol&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE ExternalLinkEmbedDek-bINJOE deqABF eKqexI pjXVm"&gt;Cholesterol isn't straightforward. It's "good" and it's "bad." It's in eggs and fatty food—but most of it is produced inside your body. But understanding how it relates to you and your diets starts with a simple checkup at the doctor.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a attributes="[object Object]" class="external-link-embed__image-link" href="/story/cholesterol-explained"&gt;&lt;picture class="ResponsiveImagePicture-cGZhnX jwYQWO ExternalLinkEmbedResponsiveImage-iLQTTl fltlts responsive-image"&gt;&lt;img alt="Image may contain: Graphics, Art, and Text" loading="lazy" class="ResponsiveImageContainer-eNxvmU cfBbTk responsive-image__image" srcset="https://media.gq.com/photos/620e9bef6db16e3382d49bf4/1:1/w_120,c_limit/cholesterol.jpg 120w, https://media.gq.com/photos/620e9bef6db16e3382d49bf4/1:1/w_240,c_limit/cholesterol.jpg 240w, https://media.gq.com/photos/620e9bef6db16e3382d49bf4/1:1/w_320,c_limit/cholesterol.jpg 320w, https://media.gq.com/photos/620e9bef6db16e3382d49bf4/1:1/w_640,c_limit/cholesterol.jpg 640w" sizes="100vw" src="https://media.gq.com/photos/620e9bef6db16e3382d49bf4/1:1/w_775%2Cc_limit/cholesterol.jpg"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>GQ</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 15:51:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiVkFVX3lxTE1nN0pIZlhEWWl4UXZLZzFvbGdNcGlfUW00OWtHUGxidVNGM011azhSTVlKY0xLWXBMWDJ2aVFleFNMTG1nQUhoQkdMZk5mTXlGNmJPc0dR</guid></item><item><title>麻省理工学院的科学家发现使肠道恢复活力的氨基酸- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/mit-scientists-discover-amino-acid-that-rejuvenates-the-gut/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 15:32:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNYlExSTVGdnlZMjZDYUZiUDNCWjZyaTlvMjR0OWJ4aHB1aUQwOWM0TnByUmVMU2RDQ2xWYmlRbkEtR1RfTnh5dUFORVBacTd4SUlPV21vdi0wWFo2c1RKN1ZLU0dRTHczMEpLVVl3aFhJLThMT3F4dlJoeGxyMkRQenZpN0VydEJKYnJYM1N3</guid></item><item><title>心理学家说， 8种奇怪的具体爱好比正念更能减少焦虑- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/things-to-do/z-8-weirdly-specific-hobbies-psychologists-say-reduce-anxiety-better-than-mindfulness/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p data-start="371" data-end="579"&gt;We’ve all been told that mindfulness is the holy grail for managing anxiety. And sure—it helps. Sitting still, focusing on your breath, observing your thoughts without judgment… it sounds great in theory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="581" data-end="719"&gt;But if you’ve ever tried to meditate with a racing mind, you know the struggle. Sometimes, stillness actually makes your anxiety louder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="721" data-end="947"&gt;The truth is, mindfulness isn’t for everyone. Some of us need movement, texture, and engagement to calm our minds. And psychologists are increasingly recognizing that anxiety relief often comes from &lt;em data-start="920" data-end="927"&gt;doing&lt;/em&gt;—not just &lt;em data-start="937" data-end="945"&gt;being.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="949" data-end="1144"&gt;That’s where these “weirdly specific” hobbies come in. They don’t just distract you; they regulate your nervous system in ways that mirror mindfulness—but often feel more natural and enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1146" data-end="1286"&gt;So, if sitting in silence isn’t your thing, here are eight activities that can ground you just as deeply (and sometimes more effectively).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="1293" data-end="1308"&gt;1) Pottery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1310" data-end="1501"&gt;There’s something deeply grounding about working with clay. It’s sensory, messy, and fully in the moment—everything mindfulness &lt;em data-start="1438" data-end="1445"&gt;tries&lt;/em&gt; to be, but without the pressure to “clear your mind.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1503" data-end="1801"&gt;Dr. Cathy Malchiodi, a psychologist and expressive arts therapist, explains that tactile art forms like pottery help &lt;a href="https://www.cathymalchiodi.com/resources/expressive-art-therapy-articles-links?.com"&gt;discharge emotional tension&lt;/a&gt; through the body. The rhythmic motion of shaping and smoothing activates the parasympathetic nervous system—the part responsible for rest and recovery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1803" data-end="1999"&gt;When your hands are busy centering clay on a wheel, your brain naturally settles into a calm, focused rhythm. You’re not &lt;em data-start="1924" data-end="1934"&gt;thinking&lt;/em&gt; your way out of anxiety; you’re &lt;em data-start="1967" data-end="1976"&gt;feeling&lt;/em&gt; your way through it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2001" data-end="2294"&gt;I took a pottery class a few years back after a stressful job transition. I wasn’t great at it—half my bowls collapsed like deflated soufflés—but I didn’t care. My mind was quiet for the first time in months. There’s something humbling about creating something imperfect with your own hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2296" data-end="2464"&gt;That’s the secret: pottery teaches you to release control and embrace imperfection. You don’t need to make something beautiful—you just need to make something &lt;em data-start="2455" data-end="2462"&gt;real.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="2471" data-end="2487"&gt;2) Foraging&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2489" data-end="2550"&gt;Foraging is part mindfulness, part adventure, part therapy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2552" data-end="2781"&gt;When you’re wandering through the woods searching for edible mushrooms or wild herbs, your mind can’t afford to spiral. It’s fully absorbed in observation—the color of a cap, the smell of damp soil, the sound of birds overhead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2783" data-end="3036"&gt;Psychologists refer to this as &lt;a href="https://positivepsychology.com/attention-restoration-theory/?.com"&gt;attention restoration theory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em data-start="2814" data-end="2845"&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; It suggests that time spent in natural, lightly engaging environments helps your prefrontal cortex recover from overstimulation. In plain English: nature resets your brain’s stress levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3038" data-end="3182"&gt;There’s also something primal and grounding about foraging—it reconnects you to a sense of agency and survival that modern life tends to dull.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3184" data-end="3531"&gt;I joined a local foraging group last spring. I’ll be honest, I was mostly in it for the excuse to get outside and meet people. But after a few hikes, I noticed something unexpected: I was sleeping better, thinking clearer, and feeling calmer during the week. My therapist later said, “That’s your nervous system responding to rhythm and nature.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3533" data-end="3619"&gt;Turns out, you don’t have to meditate under a tree—you just have to walk among them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="3626" data-end="3646"&gt;3) Birdwatching&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3648" data-end="3809"&gt;Birdwatching might sound like a hobby for retirees with binoculars and floppy hats—but it’s quietly one of the most effective anti-anxiety practices out there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3811" data-end="4067"&gt;A 2022 study published in &lt;em data-start="189" data-end="209"&gt;Scientific Reports&lt;/em&gt; found that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/10/221027093319.htm?.com"&gt;seeing or hearing birds&lt;/a&gt; was associated with noticeable boosts in mental well-being lasting up to eight hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4069" data-end="4305"&gt;Here’s why: birding trains your brain to shift from rumination to observation. Instead of looping on anxious thoughts, you’re scanning for movement, listening for calls, noticing details. It’s mindfulness that comes with a soundtrack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4307" data-end="4490"&gt;There’s also a subtle joy in delayed gratification. You wait, you watch, and suddenly—there it is. A flash of red, a flutter of wings, a moment that pulls you entirely into the now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4492" data-end="4701"&gt;A friend of mine started birdwatching after her therapist suggested it for social anxiety. She said, “It’s the first time I can stand in silence and not feel awkward.” That line has stuck with me ever since.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="4708" data-end="4730"&gt;4) Jigsaw puzzles&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4732" data-end="4837"&gt;Mindfulness tells you to “focus on one thing at a time.” Jigsaw puzzles make that happen automatically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4839" data-end="5165"&gt;The repetitive motion of sorting pieces and fitting them together triggers a state psychologists call “flow”—the same deep focus artists and athletes experience when they’re completely immersed in an activity. In this state, your brain releases dopamine, which improves mood and concentration while lowering stress hormones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5167" data-end="5443"&gt;A longitudinal trial called PACE (Jigsaw Puzzles As Cognitive Enrichment) showed that solving jigsaw puzzles strongly &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/aging-neuroscience/articles/10.3389/fnagi.2018.00299/full?.com"&gt;engages a variety of cognitive skills&lt;/a&gt; (spatial perception, mental rotation, working memory, flexibility, reasoning) and is correlated with better visuospatial cognition—especially in older adults.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5445" data-end="5648"&gt;During lockdown, I rediscovered puzzles as a way to decompress. What started as “something to do” became my evening ritual. I noticed I was calmer, sleeping better, and far less tempted to doom-scroll.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5650" data-end="5852"&gt;There’s a sense of progress in puzzles that’s hard to find in daily life. Piece by piece, you remind yourself that order can emerge from chaos—and that’s a comforting metaphor for anyone with anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="5859" data-end="5876"&gt;5) Gardening&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5878" data-end="6004"&gt;As someone who spends her weekends elbow-deep in soil, I can say with confidence: gardening is therapy disguised as a chore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6006" data-end="6146"&gt;You dig, plant, water, prune. You get sun on your face and dirt under your nails. It’s tactile and sensory—two things anxious minds crave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6148" data-end="6403"&gt;Researchers at the University of Florida found that gardening activities &lt;a href="https://biotech.ufl.edu/gardening-can-cultivate-better-mental-health/?.com"&gt;significantly reduced stress&lt;/a&gt;, anxiety, and depression in participants, even for healthy people who’d never gardened before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6405" data-end="6641"&gt;And here’s the fun part: soil contains &lt;em data-start="6444" data-end="6466"&gt;Mycobacterium vaccae&lt;/em&gt;, a natural microbe shown to boost serotonin levels—the same neurotransmitter targeted by antidepressants. So, yes, you can literally cultivate happiness from the ground up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6643" data-end="6935"&gt;One of my favorite moments each week is checking on my tomato plants at sunrise. The stillness, the smell of earth, the faint sound of bees—everything slows down. It’s not about productivity or results. It’s about remembering you’re part of something bigger and steadier than your thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="6942" data-end="6963"&gt;6) Improv comedy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6965" data-end="7112"&gt;At first glance, improv sounds like the last thing someone with anxiety should do. Standing in front of strangers with no script? Nightmare fuel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7114" data-end="7321"&gt;But psychologists are starting to use improv principles in therapy for exactly that reason. It’s controlled unpredictability. You learn to adapt, think on your feet, and—most importantly—laugh at yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7523" data-end="7757"&gt;Every time you say “yes, and…” you’re reinforcing flexibility and presence. There’s no time to overthink. You have to respond instinctively, which trains your brain to handle anxiety-provoking situations with humor instead of panic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7759" data-end="8024"&gt;I tried an improv class once at a friend’s urging. I was nervous beyond belief, but halfway through, something shifted. Everyone was laughing at themselves, failing cheerfully, and cheering each other on. It was liberating. I left lighter than I’d felt in months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8026" data-end="8132"&gt;It reminded me that joy isn’t the absence of anxiety—it’s the ability to hold it loosely and still play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="8139" data-end="8161"&gt;7) Model building&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8163" data-end="8301"&gt;Whether it’s assembling a miniature train set, crafting tiny houses, or designing scale models, this hobby has a strangely calming pull.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8303" data-end="8592"&gt;Model building demands attention to detail, but not perfection. You measure, glue, paint, and adjust, entering what psychologist Mihály Csíkszentmihályi famously called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flow_%28psychology%29?.com"&gt;“the flow state.”&lt;/a&gt; In this zone, time blurs, and your sense of self quiets down—a physiological parallel to meditation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8594" data-end="8795"&gt;For people with anxiety, this kind of structured engagement provides safety and predictability. You control small, manageable outcomes, which helps restore a sense of mastery when life feels chaotic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8797" data-end="9102"&gt;A retired engineer once told me that model shipbuilding “stills the noise.” I didn’t get it until I tried building a wooden miniature greenhouse last winter. The process was slow, precise, and oddly absorbing. When I finally snapped the roof into place, I felt a calm I hadn’t realized I’d been missing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="9104" data-end="9189"&gt;Sometimes what we need isn’t less stimulation—it’s the &lt;em data-start="9159" data-end="9171"&gt;right kind&lt;/em&gt; of stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="9196" data-end="9217"&gt;8) Trail running&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="9219" data-end="9342"&gt;I might be biased here—I’ve been a trail runner for years—but it’s the single most reliable thing I’ve found for anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="9344" data-end="9560"&gt;Unlike road running, trail running forces full-body awareness. You’re scanning roots, adjusting pace, balancing on uneven terrain. There’s no space for mental chatter because your brain is busy keeping you upright.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="9562" data-end="9881"&gt;Psychologists call this embodied mindfulness — a form of movement-based presence. In fact, a systematic review of rhythmic physical activity (dance, walking, etc.) showed &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2077-0383/12/22/7084?.com"&gt;meaningful reductions in anxiety&lt;/a&gt; and improvements in quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="9883" data-end="10066"&gt;I’ve had moments mid-run where I feel so in sync with my body and surroundings that everything else fades away—the deadlines, the worries, the what-ifs. Just breath, ground, rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="10068" data-end="10190"&gt;And honestly, that’s what mindfulness aims for anyway: the freedom of presence. Trail running just gets me there faster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="10197" data-end="10216"&gt;Final thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="10218" data-end="10381"&gt;Here’s the truth: mindfulness isn’t a one-size-fits-all solution. For some of us, the quiet feels claustrophobic. For others, the stillness invites overthinking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="10383" data-end="10475"&gt;But that doesn’t mean we can’t experience its benefits—we just need different doorways in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="10477" data-end="10677"&gt;Pottery, puzzles, foraging, gardening, even improv—they’re all mindfulness in disguise. They give your hands something to do, your senses something to engage with, and your mind a break from itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="10679" data-end="10783"&gt;If sitting in silence doesn’t soothe you, stop forcing it. There’s no single “right” way to find calm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="10785" data-end="10913"&gt;Because sometimes the best way to quiet the mind is to give it something joyful to do—something beautifully, weirdly specific.&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:31:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxOLWt5Q0RYa0dDcXRzVE9lS3VIQTF0STNJRlB2OFpHTzZuN0MxNUN1LTVMLXc0TGNlU2pXeFBwMUhoQ1h2SHpwQU1WV1hydGZVZW02SkdEc0hqVjA5WFFzVlIyRUxjMjVUYkJRb1RKcG5GV2JiNFJXOWRhdmN1RW5fM2Z1aUpSNXVSbUJBNnpBTHdnOFNna0RUdURPd054MXJrVGRyQTZQZGp0V2w3Umk2d0tYUWR2b3EzVGwtNkh3</guid></item><item><title>久坐会导致严重的健康问题，以下是科学家推荐的答案- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/too-much-sitting-causes-significant-health-issues-counteract-with-exercise/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We sit a lot. School, work, screens – all of those hours on your backside add up, and our bodies don’t appreciate it one bit. A new study warns that long hours sitting causes significant health issues – even for young, active adults – raising the odds of heart disease and obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As if that news wasn’t bad enough, researchers also argue that today’s federal exercise recommendations don’t fully counteract the harm caused by excessive sitting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike many aging studies that focus on people in their 60s, this project zeroed in on younger adults. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists from &lt;a href="https://www.ucr.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;UC Riverside&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://www.colorado.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;University of Colorado Boulder&lt;/a&gt; analyzed health data from more than 1,000 Colorado residents, with an average age of 33.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-health-risks-from-prolonged-sitting"&gt;Health risks from prolonged sitting&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study reports that logging eight or more seated hours a day pushes two early warning signs in the wrong direction – &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/just-one-handful-of-pecan-nuts-each-day-can-lower-cholesterol-heart-health/"&gt;cholesterol ratio&lt;/a&gt; and body mass index (&lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/9464-body-mass-index-bmi" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;BMI&lt;/a&gt;) – even for people who work out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cholesterol ratio, which blends triglyceride and cholesterol levels to flag cardiovascular risk, and BMI, an estimate of body fat, both climbed with prolonged sitting, signaling potential trouble ahead if habits don’t change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Though unhealthy diet and smoking play a major role in increasing BMI, the full-point jump we saw in the data was just due to sitting alone,” said Ryan Bruellman, lead researcher and doctoral candidate in UCR’s Department of &lt;a href="https://genetics.ucr.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Genetics, Genomics and Bioinformatics&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-twin-driven-analysis"&gt;Twin-driven analysis&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A large twin-and-sibling project examined how sitting time and exercise intensity relate to these “aging” &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/100-year-old-people-all-share-these-crucial-blood-biomarkers-that-short-lived-people-dont-have/"&gt;biomarkers&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sample included over a thousand adults, ages 28 to 49, with an average age in the early thirties. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group mixed adopted siblings, non-adopted siblings, and both identical and fraternal twins to help separate lifestyle effects from genetics and shared upbringing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On average, participants reported about 60 hours of sitting each week – roughly 8.6 hours per day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Men tended to report more vigorous activity and also showed higher BMI and TC/HDL cholesterol levels than women. Sitting time was roughly normally distributed across the group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-the-study-was-done"&gt;How the study was done&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team modeled how BMI and TC/HDL change with age while accounting for sitting time and physical activity intensity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They made a clear distinction between “moderate” activity and “vigorous” activity because a brisk walk does not stress the body like hard running or fast cycling. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They also used a “co-twin control” approach: comparing one twin directly to their co-twin to reduce genetic and family-environment noise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In plain terms, if an identical twin who moves harder and sits less shows better biomarker values than their genetically matched twin, behavior is a plausible contributor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-sitting-and-health-hard-data"&gt;Sitting and health – hard data&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;More sitting tracked with a drift in the wrong direction over the thirties and forties: higher BMI and a higher TC/HDL ratio. &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/exercising-more-than-recommended-may-greatly-reduce-health-risk-of-early-death-from-any-cause/"&gt;Vigorous activity&lt;/a&gt; was shown to push those levels back to normal ranges. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When models accounted for sitting time, people who did around 30 minutes of vigorous exercise per day showed BMI and TC/HDL values similar to those of &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/just-one-minute-of-short-energy-burst-exercise-every-day-can-add-years-to-your-life/"&gt;sedentary people&lt;/a&gt; who were five to ten years younger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twin comparisons reinforced this pattern. In identical and fraternal pairs, the twin who sat less and did more vigorous activity tended to show better TC/HDL. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A focused test looked at identical twins who were “discordant,” meaning they differed enough in overall health, sitting times, and vigorous exercise for a fair comparison. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pairs were sorted into two styles: “Active Replacers,” who swapped some sitting time for vigorous exercise; and “Active Compensators,” who sat a lot but tried to offset it with more vigorous exercise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The math defined an “exchange” as replacing each extra hour of weekly sitting with about six minutes of vigorous exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-law-of-diminishing-returns"&gt;Law of diminishing returns&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study showed a very clear correlation: less sitting and more vigorous movement was directly linked to a healthier TC/HDL profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Benefits from vigorous activity showed diminishing returns. Moving from almost none to a reasonable &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/small-doses-of-exercise-can-greatly-reduce-dementia-risk/"&gt;daily dose&lt;/a&gt; mattered a lot. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, adding more and more did not keep producing the same improvement in TC/HDL. Vigorous work can compensate for sitting to a point, yet reducing sitting still looked “paramount.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public health guidance offers simple guardrails: 150 minutes of moderate exercise or 75 minutes of vigorous exercise per week. Intensity definitely matters for certain outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For lipids and metabolic risk, &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/six-minutes-of-vigorous-exercise-helps-protect-the-brain-from-aging/"&gt;vigorous minutes&lt;/a&gt; often deliver extra value. Moderate activity still counts; this result highlights where vigorous work seems especially potent for these early biomarkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-limitations-of-biomarkers"&gt;Limitations of biomarkers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As with all studies, this one had limitations. BMI and TC/HDL are informative, not definitive. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The participants were relatively young adults, so we are looking at early warning signs, not clinical disease. This was not a randomized trial; no one assigned people to sit or sprint. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The twin design, including the “co-twin control” comparison, adds strength beyond typical observational studies, but it cannot prove causation the way a trial can.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Self-reported sitting time can be fuzzy. Wearable devices could sharpen future estimates and help test whether replacing specific chunks of sitting with short, vigorous bouts delivers consistent shifts in TC/HDL.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-vigorous-exercise-and-prolonged-sitting"&gt;Vigorous exercise and prolonged sitting&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To sum it all up, prolonged sitting is much more damaging to human health than scientists had ever imagined, particularly in younger people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This twin-and-sibling study suggests that how much we sit and how hard we move shows up in early risk markers for heart and &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/sleep-quality-could-be-the-key-to-better-metabolic-health/"&gt;metabolic health&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across adults in their late 20s to late 40s, more sitting was linked to higher BMI and a higher total cholesterol-to-HDL ratio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversely, regular vigorous activity pushed those numbers in a healthier direction, with roughly 30 minutes a day associated with profiles similar to sedentary people 5-10 years younger. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This study makes it clear: if you sit for long periods, the standard exercise recommendations are not enough,” Bruellman concluded. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“All adults, even the younger ones, need to move more, and exercise harder, to counteract the impact of sitting.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Break up long sitting spells. Stand more during tasks. Add walking between activities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Build a routine that includes some vigorous minutes most days – enough to push breathing and heart rate safely for your fitness level. Reducing sitting and adding vigorous movement worked best together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The full study was published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0308660#sec017" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;PLOS One&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:23:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxORERoZy1GZFRyMHlLbTVvT0c1OFE1ZDYtbzFDNU5zMTRiNUZFOEoyVXhTWFNTZUFlbVBOSmhYTThuZTlkbHBjM3ROSWlQRzgtWWxMZFNDOTd3THFWSlFkRm05MXMtWTNmS29VaGpjWkttYjd2dnZJTVFLYkdfdF8wS1MwekNyUEo5anlUY0Q5cEFXR2pDU0VuTXREVm8zNC1kNlJ3cw</guid></item><item><title>99%的中风是可以预防的：研究显示，几乎所有心脏病患者都有这4个警告信号之一-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/99-strokes-are-preventable-study-reveals-almost-all-heart-attack-victims-have-one-of-these-4-warning-signs/photostory/124472545.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;No matter how many diseases we come across, heart attacks remain one of the scariest diseases one could encounter in their lifetime. Cardiovascular diseases (CVDs) – the wide umbrella of heart diseases, heart attack is a part of – are the leading cause of death globally. In fact, a 2025 American Heart Association report, which uses global data, estimates that the global prevalence of CVD was 612.06 million in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But here’s the thing: Heart attacks don’t always strike with sudden, dramatic chest pain. Often, your body sends quiet, everyday signals, well before a heart crisis hits. In fact, a recent American Heart Association guide lists key symptoms like chest discomfort, upper-body pain, breathlessness, cold sweating, nausea, rapid heartbeat, and lightheadedness – symptoms that may appear gradually or without the classic chest pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, a new study has revealed that nearly 99% of heart attacks, strokes, or major cardiovascular events that occur in people who already had warning signs – often silent, untreated, or dismissed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These “red flags” show up years before a crisis, which means that most incidents are not sudden or unpredictable but build up over time. In other words, almost no one’s cardiovascular event is truly “out of the blue.” Researchers found that virtually all patients showed early red flags – particularly 4 warning signs – years before their first major incident.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgJBVV95cUxOV0RCSHlfZzFKcGtpemFYQXNiaUZRSV9LOUFTODJnSXRRQkpMa01hOVc2dlhUakhxTHd4WU5FdDZzSXAzbHdTSV9GMGQ1WkxRLV9uNFprTy1yek9qZ0h2ZUptUnBLc2d1ckZ4WmdIQ1hVWDNwei1OYk01Q2hfWnVRRGJ2UmtXTnZ0OFQ2a0doNmVOcm1QcEZjeFFxRjR0eUNHNjJ0SWdXRjh2QnZjY19UN2hGc1A0RVQwa2x0VnppbjYyZXllX2pxQXliVFBZRDh6Ni1sOEdxcmx6QnZoSktZZ0FRWkxjZDRMR01yUklJRHhkOUJqWFNGTEU2UnRaeHpWR0xfWS1rTFZGQVpqTDZKalViX21xUkJkZzljaUZUck1jd1dwVHpjbGZmOGRJZ9IBtgJBVV95cUxQS19TR2xvNlB2bS11c0pVWkdnakhESUN5dUgtaksyLVhkMHFwZFBVYjdJOGlhWmN2MGpaMEJibEQtNFhSdFR0V0FoRUlmSkxiWWVlS2Ewby1wdy0wLVJ6NTM4UnQ2eHUxaW5Va212NWc1M3lnN0VOazBRMEVhaThIT09IS1JKWXF2MEUtOU9ILTRhOWpIbnREQ1FlaFFKbnZPelBtcXRRQUpnVDFkV2M4M3h4NW95ZFVCbWpEdmNwSnVQdFNBclJBTWp4Q2RzUlVhaWpqTTlqSndLbnRMdjF6YWNCTVROdEpaRER4S3R6N2ZoSTJiMEdDeS1KbXdEb3hkTmxaOWUzejBoUFdyZjM5V1dWSnloV28wcm5NR0pfOEpuZ1A1TC1sdXhwa21hRWMxT0QzYUhB</guid></item><item><title>麻疹病例在明尼苏达州攀升，这是自2000年以来美国最大规模疫情的一部分- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/measles-cases-climb-minnesota-part-130538604.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minnesota is seeing an increase in measles cases, with Dakota County reporting three new infections, bringing the state total to 20.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;State health officials say the latest cases involve unvaccinated children who likely contracted the virus from an unvaccinated adult.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC reports an average of 27 new measles cases each week nationwide since late August, with more than 1,500 cases so far this year — the highest annual total since measles was declared eliminated in the U.S. in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cases have been reported in 41 states and the District of Columbia. The cases have resulted in the deaths of at least three people and have left 193 hospitalized. An alarming 92% of the cases were found in unvaccinated individuals, according to the &lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials continue to advocate for the MMR vaccine as the most effective means to combat the deadly and highly contagious virus. The shots are reported to be 97% effective, preventing illness and further spread of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC reported that only 8% of those with confirmed cases had a known measles vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;RELATED STORY | &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.scrippsnews.com/health/as-measles-spreads-to-another-state-how-early-can-babies-be-vaccinated" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:As measles spreads to another state, how early can babies be vaccinated?;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;&lt;b&gt;As measles spreads to another state, how early can babies be vaccinated?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children are routinely vaccinated for measles at 12 to 15 months and again at 4 to 6 years of age — before going to kindergarten — but children as young as 6 months old can receive the measles vaccine if they are at risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the CDC, measles causes the following symptoms:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The World Health Organization says that herd immunity against measles can be reached when a community achieves a 95% vaccination rate. U.S. health officials estimate that 92.7% of kindergarten students were vaccinated last school year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;RELATED STORY | &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.scrippsnews.com/health/erosion-of-trust-in-science-fuels-measles-resurgence-experts-warn" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Measles cases surge past 1,300; experts blame erosion of trust in science;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Measles cases surge past 1,300; experts blame erosion of trust in science&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:14:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQVjRBdFFobTJqTWU4Vy10aFp6aVlPUUZLUXRJaFJpZUJVRVdhaUdvUE9mZ09pMF9fc25FUTJqM2pFM0N2aXZfUGVHMkhPT2FDZ1JqNkJ5a1dvX000SjRCa3BFVGYyM2hTTUxpYWdISDdEV1FsT0JZLVl0T0U1TjZSbWlJdko</guid></item><item><title>我每天吃鸡蛋2周—这是我感觉到的最大变化- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/ate-eggs-every-day-2-102300851.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;I Ate Eggs Every Day for 2 Weeks&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;Thai Liang Lim - Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve never been much of a breakfast person — I don’t like to eat too soon after waking up, and I haven’t been a huge fan of traditional breakfast foods, like eggs. I was also a vegan until a year and a half ago, when I learned I had a vitamin &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6543499/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:B12 deficiency;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;B12 deficiency&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (I was unusually tired and had tingling in my hands and feet).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I tried giving myself B12 shots, but that wasn’t for me, so I started changing my diet a little bit. That has included the occasional egg (now, I eat fish and meat sometimes, too). Although I’ve learned to like eggs, I don’t typically eat them every day. So when my editor asked me to try a daily egg for two weeks, I thought it would be a fun experiment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every day, &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK615377/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:27% of Americans;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;27% of Americans&lt;/a&gt; eat eggs on their own, in an omelette, or as part of a sandwich. Over the course of a year, it's estimated that we each eat &lt;a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/183678/per-capita-consumption-of-eggs-in-the-us-since-2000/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:more than 280 eggs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;more than 280 eggs&lt;/a&gt;. That's good news because experts say eggs are incredibly good for you when they're part of a balanced diet: “Despite being small, they deliver a powerful nutrient package,” says &lt;a href="https://health.usf.edu/publichealth/overviewcoph/faculty/lywright" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Lauri Wright;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Lauri Wright&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Ph.D., R.D.N., director of nutrition programs and associate professor at the &lt;a href="https://health.usf.edu/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:University of South Florida;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;University of South Florida&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Eggs are often called ‘nature’s multivitamin’ for good reason,” she says. “They’re packed with high-quality protein, which supports muscle repair and satiety, and they contain nutrients many people fall short on, like vitamin D, choline, and lutein.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But is it healthy to eat them every day? And what happens to your body when you eat an egg every day? I was intrigued to find out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Egg nutrition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;One &lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/748967/nutrients" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:egg;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;egg&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; contains:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calories: 71&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Total fat: 5 g&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protein: 6.24 g&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin B12: 0.5 mcg&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin D: 1.24 mcg&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calcium: 24 mg&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choline: 169 mg&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What are the health benefits of eating eggs?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For years, eggs got a bad rap. That’s mostly because they contain saturated fat and cholesterol, and people worried about their health effects. However, recent &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11161868/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:studies;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;studies&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; have debunked the myth that eggs are linked to cardiovascular disease and eggs now appear to be neutral or slightly beneficial for lipid profiles in most healthy adults. “The old philosophy that eggs raise cholesterol has been found to be outdated,” Berjis says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the main nutrient benefits of eggs include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protein: &lt;/strong&gt;Eggs are packed with &lt;a href="https://www.goodhousekeeping.com/health/diet-nutrition/a64853473/how-much-protein-do-we-need/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:protein;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;protein&lt;/a&gt;, which can slow digestion and curb cravings, Wright says. “Over time, that can help with appetite regulation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin D:&lt;/strong&gt; Eggs are one of just a few foods that naturally contain &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminD-HealthProfessional/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:vitamin D;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;vitamin D&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which helps you absorb calcium. The vitamin is essential for bone health, mental health, and mood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choline:&lt;/strong&gt; This is “great for brain health,” Berjis says. &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Choline-Consumer/#:~:text=professional" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Choline;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Choline&lt;/a&gt; also supports your nervous system and cell health. Most adults do not meet the recommended intake for choline, making eggs a convenient way to help reach targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin B12:&lt;/strong&gt; Two eggs give you a third of your necessary &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminB12-HealthProfessional/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:B12;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;B12&lt;/a&gt; for the day, Wright says. The vitamin is “essential for making red blood cells, keeping nerves healthy, and supporting energy metabolism,” she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Antioxidants: &lt;/strong&gt;For example, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4632414/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:the antioxidants;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;the antioxidants&lt;/a&gt; lutein and zeaxanthin support eye health, Berjis says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;AlexPro9500 - Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What happened when I ate eggs every day&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting off, I made egg bites packed with spinach and other vegetables. I’d made them before and knew they freeze well, so I thought it would be convenient to have these on hand for when I felt too lazy to cook. &lt;strong&gt;I ate the egg bites a few times over the two-week period, usually with a slice of whole-wheat toast or a whole-wheat frozen waffle. This was a very filling combo—I never felt snacky until the next mealtime. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same goes for a couple of other meals I enjoyed: arugula salad with a hard-boiled egg and scrambled eggs with toast. This kept me full for hours. On other days, I ate a hard-boiled egg or two as a snack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Along with feeling fuller after meals and snacks, I seemed to have more energy. &lt;strong&gt;I noticed that I stopped reaching for my usual afternoon coffee. Experts say this is common when you eat eggs. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Most people notice they stay fuller for longer thanks to the protein and healthy fats,” says &lt;a href="https://innerhealthwellness.com/about/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Sahar Berjis;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Sahar Berjis&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, R.D., a registered dietitian and founder of &lt;a href="https://innerhealthwellness.com/about/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Inner Health and Wellness;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Inner Health and Wellness&lt;/a&gt;. “Some report more steady energy throughout the day.” The stabilized energy is likely due to the B vitamins, as well as choline, which is crucial for mood, memory, and brain and nervous system function, Wright says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is it a good idea to eat eggs every day?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I love the idea of eating eggs every day,” says Berjis, who recommends choosing organic and cage-free eggs. “For most healthy individuals, eggs can absolutely be part of a daily routine.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One egg per day is a “solid guideline for the general population,” Wright says. Two a day may be recommended for older people, active individuals, and those with higher protein needs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;, but one's risk of heart disease should be considered as well.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Eating more than that occasionally isn’t harmful for most, but consistently eating four or more a day may not be ideal for those with diabetes, high cholesterol, or a family history of heart disease,” she explains. Most recent guidelines do not strictly limit egg intake for these groups, but individual context matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, don’t rely on eggs alone as your only protein source. Wright suggests balancing your intake with other proteins, such as fish, beans, or nuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some people may notice bloating and stomach discomfort when they eat eggs too frequently, which could be a sign of an egg sensitivity, Berjis says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to eat more eggs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond health, Berjis says eggs are “quick, budget-friendly, and incredibly versatile.” She says she loves a “veggie-packed scramble” — eggs with sautéed spinach, tomatoes, and onions, and topped with avocado. “It’s fast, colorful, and makes you feel like you’ve already checked the ‘eat your veggies’ box by breakfast.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Incorporating veggies adds “extra fiber, vitamins, and minerals to the protein-rich base of eggs,” says Wright, who also recommends snacking on hard-boiled eggs sprinkled with everything-bagel seasoning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other easy ways to incorporate eggs include tossing them into salads, whipping up a frittata, or simply scrambling them, she suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I enjoyed eating eggs daily and felt that pairing them with whole grains and greens made me feel fuller and more energetic.&lt;/strong&gt; However, I did get a little sick of eggs by the end of the two weeks. While I do plan to incorporate them into my routine, I’m not sure I’ll stick to eating an egg a day. However, dietitians do say eating eggs daily is a healthy option that offers protein and other essential nutrients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 12:46:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZkFVX3lxTE5yamRLel9pTnBhYktPUGJGdXpFdXlSOFlORVlhWFVxTHV4UEdsbUJhd2VXYWZDMk1kLWdpajBrZVp6TE90QUNURkRsdkhONE1MVEZ6ejJlV0RfOGZEMHlvalhUQmowZw</guid></item><item><title>她的分娩是正常的，然后她的心脏停止了跳动。新妈妈在罕见并发症后康复的斗争- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/amniotic-fluid-embolism-birth-delivery-labor-university-of-maryland-baltimore/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Jennifer Choate's pregnancy was uncomplicated — until it wasn't. Two and a half weeks before her March 6, 2025 due date, the 27-year-old went to the emergency room at the University of Maryland Baltimore Washington Medical Center after experiencing headaches and high blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors thought Choate might be suffering from preeclampsia and induced labor. Her fiancée rushed to her side. Choate chatted with him and her care team as her labor progressed normally. Suddenly, she was struck with an excruciating pressure in her chest and head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It was not painful but it felt like someone was squeezing me as hard as they possibly could. I felt like my head was going to explode," Choate said. She turned to Arianna Bortle, the labor and delivery nurse at her side. "I said, 'Something has gone wrong. I don't feel good.'" &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bortle had only been a nurse for 18 months but Choate's statements made her hair stand on end. She immediately ran to get her superiors. As they re-entered the room, Choate's heart stopped.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She was talking to me, and then she wasn't," Bortle said. "She didn't have a pulse." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/03/fa8ddf0a-100d-4991-bf61-efd9cd23d952/thumbnail/620x465/83be26c8df031f8f25bb8e9104c77c66/jennifer-and-caleb-prior-to-delivery.jpg#" alt="jennifer-and-caleb-prior-to-delivery.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/03/fa8ddf0a-100d-4991-bf61-efd9cd23d952/thumbnail/620x465/83be26c8df031f8f25bb8e9104c77c66/jennifer-and-caleb-prior-to-delivery.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/03/fa8ddf0a-100d-4991-bf61-efd9cd23d952/thumbnail/1240x930/81346b75a755680e4741425fc12a2d85/jennifer-and-caleb-prior-to-delivery.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Jennifer Choate and her fiance before her delivery. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Jennifer Choate

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What is an amniotic fluid embolism? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;What Choate had experienced was an amniotic fluid embolism, doctors said. The condition is a "super rare obstetric event" when amniotic fluid enters a person's bloodstream and "sets off a cascade of events" that causes "essentially all major organs of the mom's body to shut down," said Dr. Nicole Scott, an associate professor of clinical obstetrics &amp;amp; gynecology at Indiana University's School of Medicine. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doctors don't know what causes the "life-threatening event," Scott said. It occurs in about 1 in 40,000 U.S. births, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/15463-amniotic-fluid-embolism" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;according to the Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. They usually happen shortly after a person's water breaks, and have no warning signs, Scott said. Patients quickly decompensate, with the heart failing and other organs shutting down. The body's clotting process malfunctions, causing intense bleeding. People may experience strokes and &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/minnesota/news/mom-survives-rare-amniotic-fluid-embolism-while-giving-birth/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;seizures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About half of the women who have an amniotic fluid embolism die, according to Scott. The mortality rate for their babies varies depending on the stage of labor a person is in when the embolism occurs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Survivors usually suffer lifelong complications, according to Scott. A lack of blood to the brain may leave a patient with long-lasting neurological issues, and blood clots can cause musculoskeletal issues. &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/minnesota/news/amniotic-fluid-embolism-annie-sterle/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Some people are paralyzed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Doctors may need to perform a hysterectomy. Survivors also "have a significant amount of trauma," Scott said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/03/da3b34be-0f06-43b8-9c58-cad89ba6751d/thumbnail/620x465/3544d839dd190923eb2d809f17873641/img-4560-1.jpg#" alt="img-4560-1.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/03/da3b34be-0f06-43b8-9c58-cad89ba6751d/thumbnail/620x465/3544d839dd190923eb2d809f17873641/img-4560-1.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/03/da3b34be-0f06-43b8-9c58-cad89ba6751d/thumbnail/1240x930/ecd54957a580dda72b0cd54b4a1e10d6/img-4560-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Jennifer Choate on a respirator after emergency surgery. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Jennifer Choate

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;A fight to recover &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choate was resuscitated, and her daughter was successfully delivered via cesarean section. Doctors used blood transfusions, clamps and a uterine tamponade to control Choate's blood loss and stabilize her, said Dr. Pablo Argeles, the chair of obstetrics and gynecology at UM BWMC. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Medical professionals from multiple disciplines collaborated on how to keep Choate alive, Argeles said. She was placed on a ventilator and transferred to the University of Maryland Medical Center for advanced intensive care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Choate woke up, she had no idea what had happened or where her baby was. She assumed the worst. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was like, 'If I have a tube in my throat, there's no way she survived whatever happened ... there's no way that a baby that is measuring 7 or 8 pounds is alive right now,'" Choate said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After an agonizing wait, Choate was told that her baby was alive and well. After a doctor explained what had happened, Choate understood that she was lucky: Both she and her daughter had survived, and she would not have long-term medical complications. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/03/639e448b-6300-4630-882e-2876a088b810/thumbnail/620x1102/04258a03b817e276ec11f02eed111c93/img-1882-1.jpg#" alt="img-1882-1.jpg " srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/03/639e448b-6300-4630-882e-2876a088b810/thumbnail/620x1102/04258a03b817e276ec11f02eed111c93/img-1882-1.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/03/639e448b-6300-4630-882e-2876a088b810/thumbnail/1240x2204/dc543adc3c2861934b9a4277d9882eb0/img-1882-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Jennifer Choate meets her baby.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Jennifer Choate

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Choate recovered, she was haunted by her ordeal. She Googled amniotic fluid embolisms and said she was horrified by the statistics she found. She was able to briefly see her baby but was distraught about missing so much time with her. Being apart hurt more than her recovery, she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was like, 'I need to go home. I have to go home right now. I need to be a mom,'" Choate said. "They kept telling me I was a miracle. I was like, 'I don't care about being a miracle. I want to be a mom.'" &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As staff weaned her off medications and machines, Choate began to push herself. She practiced how she would maneuver her way into the bathtub or stand up from a couch. She wheeled her baby's bassinet around the recovery floor to show she was ready to leave. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It was hard. It was the hardest thing I've ever done. It was painful, and I was crying. I was in so much pain. But when you have a baby, all of that pain just gets pushed to the side. My pain level was 1000 over 10, and I did not care," Choate said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/03/db3bf515-aed0-4d9e-adc8-41260223ebac/thumbnail/620x1013/f1300f2a1f5fe3c6f2f7d10f3e7004a0/screenshot-2025-10-03-at-9-54-03-am.png#" alt="screenshot-2025-10-03-at-9-54-03-am.png " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/03/db3bf515-aed0-4d9e-adc8-41260223ebac/thumbnail/620x1013/f1300f2a1f5fe3c6f2f7d10f3e7004a0/screenshot-2025-10-03-at-9-54-03-am.png 1x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Jennifer Choate pushes her baby in a bassinet while recovering.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Jennifer Choate

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The display worked. Choate was discharged after nine days in the hospital. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;"The one most important thing" &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Choate arrived home, the house was covered in so many cards, posters and baby gifts that she could barely recognize it. Her family offered support. Bortle, the nurse who realized something was wrong, came to visit. Her daughter, now seven months old, is on her best behavior, Choate joked, and practicing skills like rolling and sitting up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She doesn't cry about literally anything. I say 'She knows what I've been through, so she's taking it easy," Choate teased. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even as life continues on, Choate said she thinks about her ordeal "every single day." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I've never taken my life for granted, but it is scary to think that anything can happen," Choate said. "Sometimes I wonder, like, did this actually happen to me? I almost feel like I'm living in a different universe." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/03/37a94b5d-9108-49df-a478-961830883c5a/thumbnail/620x827/a8d2cefccfad0a3e441ea0c9ced53320/caleb-jennifer-and-teagan.jpg#" alt="caleb-jennifer-and-teagan.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/03/37a94b5d-9108-49df-a478-961830883c5a/thumbnail/620x827/a8d2cefccfad0a3e441ea0c9ced53320/caleb-jennifer-and-teagan.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/03/37a94b5d-9108-49df-a478-961830883c5a/thumbnail/1240x1654/1bc04ea3e8e09bb5b0f20063c700e820/caleb-jennifer-and-teagan.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Jennifer Choate, her fiance and their baby.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Jennifer Choate

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Love for her daughter washes away those troubled thoughts quickly. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc5" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",5]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I got the one most important thing out of my birth and labor," Choate said. "My child is alive." &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/section&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 12:00:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxPblI3bFFfNXhEYmYwejJ6QURRUW9ZdDh6RXBhLUdPQWl4dkN3YW1ETjd6cVFtUHVsQUtTcEgzeURnOVRsUmVTdXNJQXBkVGhjc3hwNFFaNFpuMDc0ZmxiSEloVWJ5ZGRSSzZNZF9NUEQ4UEh3Z0lzWWFILVFpUllEa3UzUzZXQjNIXzNya1BQLW1UNHJFV2pFOFdyQURfOGtfT3RzSk1GRXY2OWvSAbABQVVfeXFMTTBQTmlVZ2VwZ2Z0WEpjNHVKNDBmcXhiRkt6cllTd0t5LWt1UmFVZnR2SmVTNlJHVzhEMC1sZ2V0bmx3bzY4TkNfa2hhLVB2MTdrb0hpSktlaFhZYXg2QVhGX25pdXZYRkNjaEFFcWg5dHpSdHh4bUFTd0lPckVZVlN0c2dBdF9RV0NPQ3dKRGwwc091UUx1S3Z1Qk5XVDBJRzlYUXlHZHFkQkRrVF85OUs</guid></item><item><title>救命！我女朋友拒绝碰我，除非我做一些会让我生病的事情。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/10/dear-prudence-girlfriend-refusing-touch-sick.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="8" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv2rkr0020tzm70p361rtb@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dear Prudence is Slate’s advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSd_tjeEx47o2lIrDSg1Ioh_9shU0REmIAAtvoVHZj_FWz76AA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Submit questions here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4u8b0021357827t9gg0r@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Prudence,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="96" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4uax00243578zrkpr5n9@published"&gt;I have a skin condition where my mouth and chin are covered in painful bleeding sores. Recently, I’ve run out of medication to treat it, and for the first time in my two-year relationship, my girlfriend has seen the worst of it. She’s almost outright stopped talking to me since the sores have come back, and physical contact has been literally nonexistent. I know that the sores are uncomfortable to look at, but I can’t stand being walled off from my girlfriend until my medicine arrives. Well, yesterday, she came to me with a frightening ultimatum.&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="102" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4ugm002735780179sr9g@published"&gt;The only way she says she’ll engage with me is if I grow a beard to cover the sores. I’ve tried before, but it only makes them more painful, and it’s easier for them to get infected. I’ve told her this, but she won’t listen, and gives me the cold shoulder any time I’m near her. She’s a wonderful human being, and probably the woman I want to marry, and I can’t stand being apart from her. What should I do—grow a beard and worsen the sores, or not grow a beard and face the fact that she won’t talk to me?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="6" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4uin002835783pu03qrp@published"&gt;—To Beard of Not to Beard&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4ukm00293578lu3mx0zh@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear to Beard,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="97" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4ump002a35789257ru3m@published"&gt;Wait a minute, how long is it going to be until you get your medication? Longer than it takes to grow a beard? This isn’t just a cosmetic issue—you’re in pain! And I doubt the medication is a controlled substance. Can you ask your doctor for an early refill? Or an emergency supply so this doesn’t happen again? Is there a Facebook or Reddit community made of people with your skin condition, where you could ask if anyone local to you has an extra tube? It just doesn’t seem right that you’re having to suffer through this.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="102" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4upb002b3578mnln89vi@published"&gt;But you didn’t ask for medical advice and that’s not my area of expertise, so let’s move on to your girlfriend: You say she’s a wonderful human being, but how does withholding attention until you do something that will cause pain and infection fit into that? I think it disqualifies her from “wonderful” status. And I can’t say enough that it’s really, really important that the person you marry cares about your feelings and wants the best for you, or can at least be kind to you when the best thing for you and the best thing for her are in conflict.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="150" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4ur7002c35784qfef59c@published"&gt;I understand that you’re not going to break up with her just because I said that. I know. But I just ask that you refuse to grow the beard, observe her reaction, and pay close attention to whether this is a person who treats you in the way you want to be treated for the rest of your life. Yes, you’re extremely attached to her and find it hard to be away from her, but that’s not what I’m talking about. I want you to think about the quality of the time you have with her and how it makes you feel, especially when one or both of you has something difficult to deal with. Metaphorically speaking, life has a lot of painful open sores. When they inevitably flare up, do you want to be married to someone who makes the situation more agonizing, or someone who helps you heal?&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmgjv4u8g00233578dldu93o7@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class="prudie-google-form" data-form-response-uri="https://docs.google.com/forms/u/0/d/e/1FAIpQLSd_tjeEx47o2lIrDSg1Ioh_9shU0REmIAAtvoVHZj_FWz76AA/formResponse" data-uri="slate.com/_components/prudie-google-form/instances/cmgjv5j7700333578ywd0qcuy@published"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="prudie-google-form__disclaimer"&gt;
      Please keep questions short (&amp;lt;150 words), and don‘t submit the same question to multiple columns. We are unable to edit or remove questions after publication. Use pseudonyms to maintain anonymity. Your submission may be used in other Slate advice columns and may be edited for publication.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="slate-notification--success js-success-message" hidden&gt;Thanks! Your question has been submitted.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmgjv4ub1002535788xdiujmk@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4uxm002e3578u7nm96il@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Prudence,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="54" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4v48002f3578xny0xunj@published"&gt;My husband’s aunt passed away last week, and I am wondering if it would be appropriate to bring our 16-month-old son to the funeral, as he tends not to do well with sitters. In general, he is not prone to crying fits, but he is a baby, so there isn’t a non-zero chance. Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="6" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4v6c002g35780bi8p3en@published"&gt;—Roll the Dice on Keeping Quiet&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4vaf002h35784ebkw7cu@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Keeping Quiet,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="116" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4vfk002i3578qb022i6m@published"&gt;A funeral is a perfect time to reflect on the entire cycle of life and how precious each part of it is, including the part that includes a lot of screaming. Bring your son. His presence will bring joy to everyone as you mingle before and after the main event. I’m guessing this might be an opportunity for him to meet a lot of relatives. Sadly, weddings and funerals are often the only times these introductions occur. At the end of the day, it’s the togetherness, not the official funeral program that is important. If you have to step out during the service (which you should plan to do if he gets loud), so be it.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmgjv54sv002w3578wx98mxgw@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4vk5002k3578dldlq636@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Prudence,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4vm9002l3578des7oacf@published"&gt;My partner lost his wife five years ago. They have a 25-year-old son and a 20-year-old daughter, “Hannah.”&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="93" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4voo002m3578icyuwr19@published"&gt;Hannah disproves of her dad dating anyone, but especially me. I am very much the opposite of her mom: White, career-oriented, and non-religious. I have tried by best to build a bridge here, but Hannah can barely contain her disdain for me. I can’t even have a civil conversation about the weather without Hannah having to get her jabs in. If her father defends me and tells Hannah to cut it out, she will have a meltdown and cause a scene. We actually were asked to leave a restaurant because of her behavior.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="47" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4vr9002n3578jgiapenp@published"&gt;Hannah refuses to go to therapy. She currently isn’t talking to either her father or brother. My partner and I have talked about getting more serious and moving in together, but I could never live with someone as hostile as Hannah is. Is there any hope here?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4vtc002o35788s7z4nlm@published"&gt;—Home and Hannah&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4vvg002p3578k281n635@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Home, &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="179" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4vzy002q3578sdbiuy9g@published"&gt;Not much! So I’m happy you’re thinking about all this before moving in together. It sounds like Hannah has some pretty serious issues, separate from her relationship with you. And there’s absolutely no plan to address them. Tell your partner you want to put the brakes on and pause any conversations about cohabitation until your presence doesn’t trigger a tantrum. It’s really important that you look at things clearly in this moment, when disentangling your life doesn’t involve major financial or real estate decisions. Hannah is always going to be your partner’s daughter. He’s always going to love her—and perhaps even give her some extra leeway because of the devastating loss of her mom. Combine that with the fact that it is nearly impossible to force an adult into therapy, and I can see a future in which an angry woman lives under your roof and makes your life miserable, you have absolutely no power to address it, and your end up resenting your partner over a dynamic that’s just as hard on him as it is on you.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="47" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4w23002r35789zfiptdb@published"&gt;Don’t let that happen! Stay in your home. Go on dates. And decide what you’d need to see from Hannah to start thinking about moving in again. My suggestion: Six months straight of civil behavior and an unprompted apology for how she treated you in the &lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;past.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="6" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4w4c002s3578w5zcwjmo@published"&gt;&lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/dear-prudence"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Catch up on this week’s Prudie.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmgjv4u8b00223578pycmj94h@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="141" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgjv4w89002t3578pwsmd0y1@published"&gt;A few years ago, my little brother had an affair. He was eventually found out and filed for a divorce, which my sister-in-law fought tooth and nail. My brother is still involved in a relationship with “the other woman” and they are planning to take the next step. To be honest, I never liked his ex-wife. The “other woman” and I have a lot in common, and had we met in other circumstances, I am certain that we would be friends. My mother absolutely refuses to entertain the idea of inviting her to family functions, and as a result, one round of Christmas and Thanksgiving have already been destroyed. I would really like to put the past behind us and move on—with the other woman—but my mom feels that there is &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2017/03/dear-prudence-my-mother-wont-accept-the-woman-my-brother-left-his-wife-for.html"&gt;a moral red line against ever including her in our lives&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Dear Prudence" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmgjv2rkr0023tzm7bclpxnku@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Don't miss what's new from Prudie&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get advice on manners and morals in your inbox three times a week.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQd284VFJtWXNFR1psNW9ib3FmMTktTjVXeXVuOWR2RE5HOXBDQ1h6MG0yaWs2OTc5cFNSSjdCcWJxLVRyZnYyYmZGZ2tsNXdKLXNkQm9Ycm5FUVl4bDlDVkxmMjdzX29pQmpxOVFRU3VNWmQ0TTJBSkNIaldjei1kMW12VmRlbWRLUWc</guid></item><item><title>本周科学：一只奇异的鸟，宇宙的终结等等！ - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/this-week-in-science-a-bizarre-bird-the-end-of-the-universe-and-more</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;This week in science: &lt;span&gt;A strange hybrid bird; the cancer clues hidden in your toenails; a reverse Big Bang; and much more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="text-h2 sm:text-h1 font-source-sans font-semibold text-legibility block mb-4"&gt;Huge Study Links 99% of Heart Attacks And Strokes With 4 Risk Factors&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_146819" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-146819" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/HeartOnBackground-642x260.jpg" alt="Heart On Background" class="wp-image-146819 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/HeartOnBackground-642x260.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/HeartOnBackground-768x311.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/HeartOnBackground-600x243.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/HeartOnBackground.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-146819" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;(zf L/Moment/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="a_GcMg font-feature-liga-off font-feature-clig-off font-feature-calt-off text-decoration-none text-strikethrough-none"&gt;A huge study has linked 99 percent of all heart attacks and strokes to four risk factors: high blood pressure, high cholesterol, high blood sugar, and smoking.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High blood pressure&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;was the factor most commonly tied to cardiovascular events. In both the US and South Korea, more than 93 percent of individuals who experienced a heart attack, stroke, or heart failure had hypertension beforehand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Managing this risk factor could be key to preventing serious cardiovascular disease down the road.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Read the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/huge-study-links-99-of-heart-attacks-and-strokes-with-four-risk-factors"&gt;full story here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="text-h2 sm:text-h1 font-source-sans font-semibold text-legibility block mb-4"&gt;The 2025 Nobel Prizes Were Awarded This Week, Celebrating Major Scientific Breakthroughs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177187" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177187" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Nobel-prize-642x260.jpg" alt="This Week in Science: a Bizarre Bird, The End of The Universe, And More!" class="wp-image-177187 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Nobel-prize-642x260.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Nobel-prize-768x311.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Nobel-prize-600x243.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Nobel-prize.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177187" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;(&lt;a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Nobel_prize_medal_for_medicine,_Sweden,_1945,_to_Sir_Alexander_Fleming_(1881-1955)_who_discovered_Penicillin._On_display_at_the_National_Museum_of_Scotland.jpg"&gt;Osama Shukir Muhammed Amin FRCP(Glasg)&lt;/a&gt;/&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/deed.en"&gt;CC BY SA 4.0&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This year, the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine was awarded to Shimon Sakaguchi from Osaka University in Japan, Mary E. Brunkow from the Institute for System Biology and Fred Ramsdell from Sonoma Biotherapeutics, both in the US, for discovering how the body stops its own immune system from turning against itself.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Read the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/surprising-immune-cell-discovery-wins-2025-nobel-prize-heres-the-science"&gt;full story here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Nobel Prize in Physics went to &lt;span&gt;Briton John Clarke, Frenchman Michel Devoret, and American John Martinis for putting quantum mechanics into action and enabling the development of all kinds of digital technology from cellphones to a new generation of computers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Read the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/quantum-tunneling-experiments-earn-team-the-nobel-prize-in-physics"&gt;full story here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And the Nobel Prize in Chemistry was awarded to &lt;a href="https://www.icems.kyoto-u.ac.jp/en/people/1422/"&gt;Susumu K&lt;/a&gt;i&lt;a href="https://www.icems.kyoto-u.ac.jp/en/people/1422/"&gt;tagawa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;from Kyoto University, Japan,&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Richard Robson&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;from the University of Melbourne, Australia, and&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Omar M. Yaghi&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;from the University of California, Berkeley, for discovering a new form of molecular architecture: crystals that contain large cavities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Read the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/2025-nobel-prize-for-chemistry-awarded-for-a-whole-lot-of-nothing"&gt;full story here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_astro"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Astro" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="text-h2 sm:text-h1 font-source-sans font-semibold text-legibility block mb-4"&gt;There Are 5 Profiles of Sleep – Here's What Yours Says About Your Health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_164906" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-164906" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/sleep-apnea-642x260.jpg" alt="Risk of Sleep Breathing Disorder Set to Rise 45% by End of Century" class="wp-image-164906 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/sleep-apnea-642x260.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/sleep-apnea-768x311.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/sleep-apnea-600x243.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/sleep-apnea.jpg 1024w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-164906" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;(urbazon/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176113" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176113" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;span class="a_GcMg font-feature-liga-off font-feature-clig-off font-feature-calt-off text-decoration-none text-strikethrough-none"&gt;Scientists have identified five sleep profiles that link the quality of a person's shut-eye with their physical and mental health in various ways.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"The different sleep profiles were also supported by unique patterns of brain function measured with &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/magnetic-resonance-imaging" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73063" data-postid="177178" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;MRI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, suggesting that sleep experiences are reflected not just in health and behavior, but also in the brain's wiring and activity," &lt;/span&gt;says&lt;span&gt; Aurore Perrault, neuroscientist at Concordia University in Canada.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Read the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/there-are-5-profiles-of-sleep-heres-what-yours-says-about-your-health"&gt;full story here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="text-h2 sm:text-h1 font-source-sans font-semibold text-legibility block mb-4"&gt;'Grue Jay' Spotted in a Texas Backyard Is First-of-Its-Kind Hybrid&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_175870" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-175870" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/closeupofgruejayhybrid-642x260.jpg" alt="'Grue Jay' Spotted in a Texas Backyard Is First-of-Its-Kind Hybrid" class="wp-image-175870 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/closeupofgruejayhybrid-642x260.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/closeupofgruejayhybrid-768x311.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/closeupofgruejayhybrid-600x243.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/closeupofgruejayhybrid.jpg 1024w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-175870" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Grue jay hybrid. (&lt;a href="https://cns.utexas.edu/news/research/so-what-should-we-call-grue-jay"&gt;Brian Stokes/University of Texas at Austin&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176113" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176113" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;span class="a_GcMg font-feature-liga-off font-feature-clig-off font-feature-calt-off text-decoration-none text-strikethrough-none"&gt;A strange bird found in a Texas backyard turned out to be a "grue jay", the first documented wild hybrid of a blue jay and a green jay.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"We think it's the first observed vertebrate that's hybridized as a result of two species both expanding their ranges due, at least in part, to climate change," &lt;/span&gt;says&lt;span&gt; ecologist Brian Stokes of the University of Texas at Austin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Read the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/grue-jay-spotted-in-a-texas-backyard-is-first-of-its-kind-hybrid"&gt;full story here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="text-h2 sm:text-h1 font-source-sans font-semibold text-legibility block mb-4"&gt;Your Toenails Can Reveal if You've Been Exposed to an Invisible Lung Cancer Cause&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176972" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176972" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/toenail-clippings-cover-642x260.jpg" alt="Your Toenails Can Reveal if You've Been Exposed to an Invisible Lung Cancer Cause" class="wp-image-176972 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/toenail-clippings-cover-642x260.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/toenail-clippings-cover-768x311.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/toenail-clippings-cover-600x243.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/toenail-clippings-cover.jpg 1024w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-176972" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;(nito100/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176113" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176113" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;span class="a_GcMg font-feature-liga-off font-feature-clig-off font-feature-calt-off text-decoration-none text-strikethrough-none"&gt;Your toenails store an 'archive' of your exposure to hazards like radon gas, which could help doctors identify patients at risk of lung cancer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"The data will form the evidence that could lead to the inclusion of more patients, whose lung cancer is not caused by &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;tobacco smoke&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;, in potentially life-saving early screening and diagnosis," says biochemist Aaron Goodarzi at the University of Calgary in Canada.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Read the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-toenails-can-reveal-if-youve-been-exposed-to-an-invisible-lung-cancer-cause"&gt;full story here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="text-h2 sm:text-h1 font-source-sans font-semibold text-legibility block mb-4"&gt;Physicists Predict When The Universe Will End in a Reverse Big Bang&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176236" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176236" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/unverse-plop-642x260.jpg" alt="Physicists Predict When The Universe Will End in a Reverse Big Bang" class="wp-image-176236 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/unverse-plop-642x260.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/unverse-plop-768x311.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/unverse-plop-600x243.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/unverse-plop.jpg 1024w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-176236" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;(Daniel Rocal - PHOTOGRAPHY/Moment/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176113" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176113" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;span class="a_GcMg font-feature-liga-off font-feature-clig-off font-feature-calt-off text-decoration-none text-strikethrough-none"&gt;A new model predicts that in about 11 billion years, the Universe will begin to contract, ending in a reverse Big Bang 20 billion years from now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"For any life, you want to know how life begins and how life ends – the end points,"&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;says astrophysicist &lt;span&gt;Henry Tye of Cornell University in the US&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"For our Universe, it's also interesting to know, does it have a beginning? In the 1960s, we learned that it has a beginning. Then the next question is, 'Does it have an end?' For many years, many people thought it would just go on forever. It's good to know that, if the data holds up, the Universe will have an end."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Read the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/physicists-predict-when-the-universe-will-end-in-a-reverse-big-bang"&gt;full story here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:52:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQdTJCZGVnTXhMX1FUZnpabHkxVkVrTjc1MEFOTTVUVHhLLVd6VU5LTF9pYXdVbGhDY20xd1pOMVROQmliRlJhaWZtQzlrRXBaNDJTdWhOT2NFRmxoczJVU3drMzV4WE1oVFIwNTB0SHA0MVdOQjBzNjlYRjZGbWF2dWZIdUgwNS03azNfZTJqY05CMFh5VloyU3VLdHhmQQ</guid></item><item><title>根据长寿专家的说法， 5种饮料可以帮助您活到100岁-非常简单</title><link>https://www.realsimple.com/drinks-that-help-you-live-to-100-11826483</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-article-intro_1-0" class="comp mntl-article-intro mntl-block article-content__description"&gt;&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For most people, &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/how-to-live-to-100-8734564" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;living to 100&lt;/a&gt; may feel out of reach. Yet what seems unachievable to many is actually a reality for the 101,000 centenarians who’ve made it to 2024, likely due to years of making healthy decisions, like &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-centenarians-rarely-eat-8737190" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;avoiding certain foods&lt;/a&gt; and habits, in order to extend their lives. Besides the foods we eat, the drinks we consume also play a role in the quality and length of our lives, according to Dr. Michaela Robbins, nurse practitioner. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Certain drinks not only provide water and hydration to allow our body to function, but also provide things like bioactive compounds, electrolytes, and antioxidants while also getting rid of the bad stuff,” she explains. “Antioxidants, for example, help us detoxify free radicals and reduce inflammation, which is one of the biggest drivers of aging, and help you feel your best for longer.” The link between drinks and longevity is much more important than we might realize—that’s why we asked longevity experts for more information on which drinks can help us live our longest, healthiest, and best lives.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--meetourexpert mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--meetourexpert mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-meetourexpert callout--bordered" data-text="Meet the Expert" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/michaela-robbins-dnp-72110919" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Michaela Robbins&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, NP, is a nurse practitioner and hormone and longevity expert&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/erin-barrett-7968a82" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Erin Barrett&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, PhD, is the senior director of product innovation and scientific affairs at Shaklee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-whats-the-link-between-drinks-and-longevity"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What’s the Link Between Drinks and Longevity? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “The goal of longevity isn’t just to add years to life; it’s about living those years well—achieving a longer health span,” explains Dr. Erin Barrett, senior director of product innovation and scientific affairs at Shaklee. “Staying properly hydrated supports cellular health and organ function (especially the kidneys), aids in nutrient absorption, and helps maintain energy levels.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Antioxidants are the number one priority when it comes to drinks that can support healthy aging. These properties can reduce the risk of chronic disease, support brain and eye function, and even improve mental health. Make sure you’re looking for these specific properties and ingredients while browsing through your local grocery store’s drink aisle.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-5-drinks-thatll-help-you-live-to-100"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 5 Drinks That’ll Help You Live to 100 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc__content_1-0" class="comp list-sc__content realsimple-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 3, 6, 9, 12, 15, 18]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="list-sc-item_1-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-berry-smoothies"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Berry Smoothies &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/easy-fruit-smoothie-recipes-7375286" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Berry smoothies&lt;/a&gt;—especially those made with blueberries, raspberries, and strawberries—contain anti-inflammatory properties to promote healthy aging. “These fruits are packed with antioxidants that combat free radicals and reduce oxidative stress, which is essential for maintaining cell health,” Dr. Barrett explains. Similarly, Dr. Robbins recommends starting your day with a berry smoothie, suggesting to “blend it with almond milk for bone health and nut butter for protein, and you have a perfect longevity breakfast.”&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@7a7535fb" data-item-index="1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_2-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-green-and-black-tea"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Green and Black Tea &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It often feels like the &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/types-of-tea-7152305" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;benefits of drinking tea&lt;/a&gt; are limitless. Green and black tea are rich in powerful antioxidants, such as catechins, according to Dr. Barrett. “These compounds help neutralize free radicals and minimize oxidative stress, promoting cellular health,” she explains. “&lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/tea-for-longevity-11695788" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Regular consumption of these teas&lt;/a&gt; can be a simple yet effective way to support your health span.”&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@7c27affa" data-item-index="2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_3-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-black-coffee"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Black Coffee &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Black coffee can get a bad rap when overconsumed, but it’s not just good for a morning pick-me-up. “Studies have indicated that long-term consumption of coffee can cut your risk of premature death by up to 30%, regardless of whether it is caffeinated or decaffeinated,” Dr. Robbins explains. “Coffee also stimulates neurotransmitters dopamine and serotonin, which can elevate mood, and happiness is linked to longer lives.”&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@18d8b776" data-item-index="3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_4-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-hydrogen-rich-water"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Hydrogen-rich Water &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Of course, &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/how-to-drink-more-water-7495589" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;water is a go-to&lt;/a&gt; when it comes to hydration and healthy living, but there are a variety of packaged water that can do even more. For example, hydrogen-rich water adds extra molecular hydrogen gas to enhance its antioxidant and anti-inflammatory properties, along with reducing the risk of high cholesterol and improving kidney function. While plain water is perfectly fine, enhanced water can boost its benefits.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@5158a889" data-item-index="4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_5-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-red-wine"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Red Wine &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; We can’t stress this enough: there’s no amount of alcohol that is &lt;em&gt;good &lt;/em&gt;for you. In fact, maintaining an alcohol-free lifestyle is a foolproof way to feel and be healthier; however, that’s not always an attainable goal for people living in today’s world, and in that case, &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/red-wine-health-benefits" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;red wine&lt;/a&gt; is the best option. “When consumed in moderation, red wine is a rich source of resveratrol, a potent antioxidant associated with numerous health benefits,” Dr. Barrett explains. “Resveratrol is known for its anti-inflammatory properties and potential to promote heart health, making it a positive addition to a balanced diet aimed at supporting quality of life.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@2d195b4" data-item-index="5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Real Simple</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTFBaYjlFNjNweFBCcTdkYzBkMUZVMmF6aTBaOF9PY0ROZDBldTZSN3pqaGFoT0V3MUhzYXJvMkxTQ2JZWjhDS2ZTZXR4bUwyNWZqWDNSS1JlbU9aY3NGNm5McGJLdWxWT2luYTM5LV9tMll0d0pkbGhj</guid></item><item><title>极右和极左的人表现出惊人的相似的大脑反应- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/people-on-the-far-right-and-far-left-exhibit-strikingly-similar-brain-responses/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study suggests that people with strongly held political beliefs, whether liberal or conservative, tend to process political content in strikingly similar ways at a neurological level. The findings, published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2026-54527-001?doi=1" target="_blank"&gt;Journal of Personality and Social Psychology: Attitudes and Social Cognition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, indicate that emotional reactions may play a central role in driving ideological extremity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers set out to better understand what might fuel increasingly polarized and extreme political attitudes in the United States. While disagreement and debate are foundational to democratic systems, the political landscape has become more divided in recent years, with a growing number of Americans identifying with viewpoints further from the political center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prior research has pointed to several contributors to this trend, including psychological tendencies like intolerance of uncertainty or a preference for black-and-white thinking. But many scholars have also proposed that emotion—especially negative emotion such as fear or anger—plays a powerful role. Emotional reactions can shape how people interpret news, view political opponents, and form alliances. In this study, the researchers asked whether people on the far left and far right not only hold strong beliefs but also experience political information in similarly emotional ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They also aimed to test a concept sometimes referred to as the “horseshoe theory,” which suggests that political extremes may resemble each other more than they do moderates. If true, then individuals on opposite ideological ends could be more psychologically alike than different, at least in how they respond to political content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This research was inspired by the growing political polarization and ideological extremism observed around us. Recent political crises such as the COVID-19 pandemic and the war between Israel and Gaza have intensified extreme views across both ends of the political spectrum, which motivated us to look beyond left-right differences,” said study author Daantje de Bruin, a PhD student at Brown University and member of &lt;a href="https://www.feldmanhalllab.com/" target="_blank"&gt;the FeldmanHall lab&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Instead, we asked whether there might be common neurophysiological mechanisms underlying political extremism, regardless of ideological content. This idea aligns with the ‘horseshoe theory’ of politics, which suggests that the far left and far right, despite opposing beliefs, often resemble each other in psychological and behavioral ways.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To explore these questions, the team recruited 44 participants from across the political spectrum, with a particular focus on those at the ideological extremes. Participants were identified based on how far they leaned from the political center on a 100-point scale, ranging from extremely liberal to extremely conservative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The participants watched a politically charged segment of the 2016 vice-presidential debate between Tim Kaine and Mike Pence while undergoing brain scans in a magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) machine. At the same time, the researchers recorded physiological responses—specifically, galvanic skin conductance, which measures emotional arousal through changes in sweat gland activity. Eye-tracking was also used to assess where participants focused their attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analysis of the brain imaging data revealed a consistent pattern: participants with stronger political beliefs, regardless of whether they were liberal or conservative, showed increased activity in brain areas associated with emotion and threat detection. These included the amygdala, known for processing fear; the periaqueductal gray, which is involved in defensive behaviors; and the posterior superior temporal sulcus, a region linked to interpreting social cues and understanding others’ intentions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our findings were in line with our hypothesis that holding extreme views (regardless of the content of those views) means that individuals share, at least on some dimensions, similar processing of the world around them,” de Bruin told PsyPost. “This helps explain how the language or actions of die-hard liberals or conservatives can appear eerily similar to the language and actions of those on the other side.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This finding suggests that extreme political views may be tied to stronger emotional reactions to political material. In other words, the more ideologically extreme a person was, the more emotionally charged their brain response appeared to be when watching political content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also analyzed how similarly participants’ brains responded to the debate. By comparing moment-to-moment brain activity across pairs of participants, they found that those who both held extreme views—even if one was very liberal and the other very conservative—showed more synchronized brain responses than moderates did. This synchronization was especially pronounced in areas of the brain involved in understanding others’ perspectives and emotions, such as the temporoparietal junction and adjacent regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, this effect was not merely the result of shared ideology. Participants with very different political beliefs still showed similar patterns of brain activity if both were high in extremity. This provides evidence that the way people process political content may be shaped more by the intensity of their beliefs than by the direction of those beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another layer of the study looked at the role of language. The researchers used a machine learning tool to evaluate the level of extreme language in the debate video. They found that parts of the video containing more extreme or provocative language tended to strengthen the brain synchrony effect among extreme individuals. In other words, the most emotionally intense parts of the political content seemed to draw extreme viewers into an even more aligned neurological state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, the researchers examined physiological arousal. While they did not find that more extreme individuals had higher average arousal levels overall, they did find that shared physiological responses between pairs—specifically synchronized spikes in skin conductance—correlated with greater neural synchrony. This relationship held especially true for participants with the most extreme beliefs. In other words, when extreme individuals not only shared strong views but also experienced similar emotional reactions in their bodies, their brains tended to process political content in more closely aligned ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We find that people with more extreme political views, on either end of the political spectrum, show stronger brain responses to the political content in areas involved in emotions, such as fear, threat detection, and understanding the perspective of others,” de Bruin explained. “We also find that more extreme individuals, regardless of their political ideology, show more similar neural responses to political content.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Despite stark differences in political beliefs, extreme individuals on opposite sides of the political spectrum thus process political content in similar ways, providing neurophysiological support for the horseshoe theory of politics. This suggests that ideological opposites may be more alike in how they process politics than they realize. Recognizing this shared experience could foster greater empathy and reduce dehumanization across the political divide.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study provides evidence that emotion plays a central role in shaping how people with extreme beliefs experience political content, but it also comes with some limitations. First, the political material used covered only a narrow set of topics, specifically immigration and policing. It is not clear whether similar results would emerge with different political subjects or more recent content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, the research was conducted entirely within the United States and may not generalize to other countries or political systems. Cultures with different norms, levels of polarization, or media environments might show different patterns of emotional and neurological responses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these limitations, the study provides new insight into how emotion and social perception influence political extremity. The fact that people with opposing ideologies can show similar patterns of brain activity suggests that emotional experience may be a shared thread connecting those on both sides of the political divide. Recognizing this shared experience might help reduce hostility and open the door to more understanding, even in a time of rising polarization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our findings support the theorized link between extremism and affective processing, highlighting the importance of understanding polarization and radicalization as not just a cognitive or ideological process, but also one that considers emotion,” de Bruin said. “In future work, we aim to further investigate how affective processing might be altered in more extreme individuals, and why their responses may differ from moderates. Ultimately, we aim to use these insights to inform approaches that reduce polarization and help people engage with political information more thoughtfully.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2026-54527-001?doi=1" target="_blank"&gt;Politically Extreme Individuals Exhibit Similar Neural Processing Despite Ideological Differences&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Daantje de Bruin and Oriel FeldmanHall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:03:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxPVjhYUmFZZUl0NXMyZ0JQcjc2dmdWOTVTa3NqbTVuaTJNYkN0VExfT012akhLWGtFcUV6MzlfWTFOQUFYbkhlMW9YRC05ak84U3dlSFlHSkJtTGVhZEdNWXMxanNPVmRvYUVlUDA5a3hVTXBBaHhxT3pQNmVhYVhyVXdWSXZZdk13bTZkR2tVNUlSclF1ekdCeFJjVzY4bV9SRGNJZHJJOA</guid></item><item><title>新的阿尔茨海默氏症治疗和研究正在激发人们的希望-《波士顿环球报》</title><link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/10/11/metro/alzheimers-treatments-lithium/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body | gutter_16--desktop gutter_16--tablet paywalled_content
              "&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Rick is helping to answer a question central to the future of Alzheimer’s care: Can the disease be stopped, or delayed, before it has noticeable effects? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Doctors now believe the seeds of Alzheimer’s are planted decades before symptoms emerge, and the best hope for combating the illness will be treating people when they’re feeling just fine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Rick is participating in &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://www.aheadstudy.org/__;!!BspMT6SJLSDJ!Nbg8etTEA7UXfqbxewlRMjs7_8ObNJcDixLNIvEofWHZ6TbsPo9Vrn_MDembfrLVyhxXusKufzvFN03yde4YmA$" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;the AHEAD study&lt;/a&gt;, one of &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://www.alzheimers.gov/clinical-trials/donanemab-prevention-alzheimers-disease__;!!BspMT6SJLSDJ!Nbg8etTEA7UXfqbxewlRMjs7_8ObNJcDixLNIvEofWHZ6TbsPo9Vrn_MDembfrLVyhxXusKufzvFN03LmQgQvA$" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;two&lt;/a&gt; nationwide studies in which people with no symptoms are given a drug that is otherwise provided only to those already experiencing signs of Alzheimer’s disease. (Rick doesn’t know whether he’s receiving the drug or an inactive placebo.) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Within a few years, the study may show whether the drugs can prevent the disease from developing in the first place.&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;If the answer is yes, “that would be revolutionary,” said Dr. Daniel Z. Press, chief of the Division of Cognitive Neurology at Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center, who is not involved with that research. “We would then be for the first time trying to prevent Alzheimer’s disease rather than treating it.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;That’s only one piece of the sprawling puzzle of Alzheimer’s research. Also under study are dozens of other drugs that work on different aspects of the biology of the disease. At the same time, there’s growing evidence people can lower their risk of dementia with a healthy lifestyle. And a new emphasis on learning how to live with dementia is shifting the grim paradigm that for so long has defined the illness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“I’m feeling quite optimistic,” said Susan Antkowiak, vice president of programs and services at the Alzheimer’s Association of Massachusetts and New Hampshire.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Such optimism marks a shift in the fraught and often disappointing history of Alzheimer’s research, which critics say had focused too narrowly on the role of amyloid and has been tainted by &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2022/07/25/business/key-elements-influential-alzheimers-study-may-have-been-fabricated-report-says/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;allegations of fraud&lt;/a&gt;. The drug Aduhelm, which could slightly slow the progress of Alzheimer’s but had major risks, was &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2024/01/31/business/biogen-adhuhlem-fda-lequembi/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;pulled off the market&lt;/a&gt; in 2024 after skeptical doctors shunned it and insurers and Medicare restricted coverage.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The enthusiasm is also tempered by fears that reductions in federal research funding could stall the most promising work. President Trump has asked Congress to cut the National Institutes of Health budget by 40 percent. But appropriations committees in both the Senate and the House &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://www.alz.org/news/2025/house-appropriations-committee-15-million-increase-alzheimers-research__;!!BspMT6SJLSDJ!KfxNhNa3CQq5idGt7H_0MbjPlKtE5APzJ4buNlYhqNfXZ38a4czGJj0wkKp5FK1U9m0ozkx8ZXl-TTrp0Q08c54$" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;have voted to increase&lt;/a&gt; funding for Alzheimer’s research. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“As we’re making this progress, we cannot back up,” Antkowiak said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The current leading hypothesis is that Alzheimer’s disease is driven by two types of malformed proteins — amyloid plaques and tau tangles — which interfere with brain function, gradually diminishing the ability to think and remember.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Tau helps the neurons in healthy brains function. But it becomes a problem when it twists into sticky tangles that accumulate in the brain. How tau and amyloid interact is not fully understood, but tau tangles seem to play a greater role in imminent cognitive decline, said Dr. Reisa Sperling, director of the Center for Alzheimer’s Research and Treatment at Mass General Brigham and a leader of the AHEAD study that Rick is participating in. When tau tangles start spreading, it “almost always occurs in the setting of pretty high amyloid,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Participants in the AHEAD study receive infusions of Leqembi (lecanemab), one of two drugs that have been approved to treat people who already have symptoms. Leqembi and the other drug, Kisunla (donanemab), remove amyloid and slow the illness, but do not stop it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;&lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://www.eisai.com/news/2025/news202554.html__;!!BspMT6SJLSDJ!Nbg8etTEA7UXfqbxewlRMjs7_8ObNJcDixLNIvEofWHZ6TbsPo9Vrn_MDembfrLVyhxXusKufzvFN027r0DB2w$" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;A new study&lt;/a&gt; showed that many symptomatic participants who had low levels of malformed tau when they started taking Leqembi either got better or maintained the same level of function after four years. This has bolstered hopes that providing the medication even earlier in the process, to people at risk but still without symptoms, can prevent tau tangles from spreading.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;These drugs have serious downsides, however. They require trips to the hospital, or a visit from a home nurse, to get infusions, although &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://pharmatimes.com/news/fda-approves-leqembi-iqlik-for-maintenance-dosing-in-early-alzheimers-disease/__;!!BspMT6SJLSDJ!KfxNhNa3CQq5idGt7H_0MbjPlKtE5APzJ4buNlYhqNfXZ38a4czGJj0wkKp5FK1U9m0ozkx8ZXl-TTrp-Q1hHbI$" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;a new injectable version&lt;/a&gt; that can be self-administered may soon be available. Also,&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;up to 14 percent of patients experience inflammation or bleeding in the brain, necessitating regular brain scans to check for this side effect.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;A Massachusetts General Hospital research team has identified a substance that, instead of clearing out amyloid, may short-circuit its formation in the first place, based on laboratory results. Rudolph E. Tanzi, director of Mass. General’s Henry and Allison McCance Center for Brain Health, said this drug, known as GSM, for gamma secretase modulator, would come in the form of a pill and would be less expensive. He hopes to start testing its safety in humans in the fall.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;If it’s proven safe and effective, Tanzi envisions GSM someday being offered to people at risk of Alzheimer’s in the same way statins are prescribed for people at risk of heart disease. “We’re going to nip it in the bud,” he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;All told, said Antkowiak, of the Alzheimer’s Association, more than 140 unique therapies are being tested in clinical trials, targeting amyloid and tau but also inflammation and the health of blood vessels — all believed to be involved in the development of Alzheimer’s.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/08/06/metro/alzheimers-treatment-harvard-lithium-deficiency-plaques/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;One study published in August&lt;/a&gt; stirred excitement when it showed that the metal &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/08/06/metro/alzheimers-treatment-harvard-lithium-deficiency-plaques/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;lithium, used to treat psychiatric illnesses&lt;/a&gt;, plays a role in brain function and might protect against Alzheimer’s. The study found lithium was depleted in the brains of people in the earliest stages of memory loss during aging, as amyloid began forming. Amyloid bound to the lithium, apparently depriving cells of its protective function. The study also found that feeding tiny amounts of lithium to mice with signs of dementia restored their memory.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;But those who are worried about Alzheimer’s don’t need to wait for new drugs to improve their prospects. Ample and growing evidence shows that lifestyle changes can reduce the risk of developing dementia. In the &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2837046__;!!BspMT6SJLSDJ!Nbg8etTEA7UXfqbxewlRMjs7_8ObNJcDixLNIvEofWHZ6TbsPo9Vrn_MDembfrLVyhxXusKufzvFN01yd_YVBQ$" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;largest such randomized trial&lt;/a&gt;, published in July, older people at risk of cognitive decline who followed a program of diet, exercise, and brain training saw, on average, their performance on cognitive tests improve. Another &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-025-03891-5__;!!BspMT6SJLSDJ!KfxNhNa3CQq5idGt7H_0MbjPlKtE5APzJ4buNlYhqNfXZ38a4czGJj0wkKp5FK1U9m0ozkx8ZXl-TTrpUmi94-c$" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; of people with a strong genetic risk for Alzheimer’s found those following a Mediterranean diet full of fruits, vegetables, nuts, whole grains, fish, and olive oil were significantly less likely to develop dementia.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;For guidance on where to start on lifestyle changes, the &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://www.massgeneral.org/neurology/mccance-center/about/brain-care-score__;!!BspMT6SJLSDJ!Nbg8etTEA7UXfqbxewlRMjs7_8ObNJcDixLNIvEofWHZ6TbsPo9Vrn_MDembfrLVyhxXusKufzvFN03LkVT4xw$" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;McCance Brain Care Score&lt;/a&gt; helps pinpoint which aspects are most important to tackle. Tanzi, of the MGH brain center, has developed a regime called &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://www.massgeneral.org/neurology/mccance-center/about/shield__;!!BspMT6SJLSDJ!Nbg8etTEA7UXfqbxewlRMjs7_8ObNJcDixLNIvEofWHZ6TbsPo9Vrn_MDembfrLVyhxXusKufzvFN02QiXREjw$" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;SHIELD,&lt;/a&gt; for Sleep, Handling stress, Interaction with friends, Exercise (150 minutes per week), Learning new things, and Diet (lots of vegetables, fruits, whole grains, nuts and seeds).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Meanwhile, another, quieter revolution may be occurring: the notion of &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://people.com/couple-refuses-to-stop-traveling-despite-husbands-early-onset-alzheimers-exclusive-11786909__;!!BspMT6SJLSDJ!Nbg8etTEA7UXfqbxewlRMjs7_8ObNJcDixLNIvEofWHZ6TbsPo9Vrn_MDembfrLVyhxXusKufzvFN02cbAY7Bw$" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;living well with dementia&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;That might seem inconceivable. But Kerry Dennis said a rewarding&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;life is possible even when the diagnosis comes at an early age. Dennis, who is 60 and lives in Auburn, N.H., spent three years trying to find out why, in her mid-50s, she could no longer perform routine tasks at her high-powered job with a financial services company. Eventually a Mass. General neurologist diagnosed her with mild cognitive impairment, likely due to brain changes that typically lead to Alzheimer’s.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="" class="image | relative margin_bottom_16
          margin_top width_full
          false
          false
          "&gt;&lt;figure class="font_primary false
               false
              false
            " id="img-6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM"&gt;&lt;img id="img-6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM-image" alt="Kerry Dennis from Auburn, N.H., was diagnosed her with mild cognitive impairment." class="height_a width_full invisible width_full--mobile width_full--tablet-only" data-src="https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440" data-srcset="https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440 1440w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440 1280w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440 1024w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440 820w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440 600w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440 420w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440 240w" src="https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440" srcset="https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440 1440w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440 1280w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440 1024w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440 820w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440 600w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440 420w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/6SSGWLYL42NDFKUFKCOUFZKSDM.jpg?auth=54495d41a0e557b715ad6371d39103bdeeb7b8190636d725bda7f59e039df3fe&amp;amp;width=1440 240w" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption class=" img_caption | margin_horizontal_0--mobile margin_horizontal_0--tablet
        "&gt;&lt;span class="caption | margin_right_half"&gt;Kerry Dennis from Auburn, N.H., was diagnosed her with mild cognitive impairment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit uppercase"&gt;John Tlumacki/Globe Staff&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Her “overwhelming relief” at learning what was wrong quickly gave way to dark thoughts. Her mother and grandmother had died of Alzheimer’s, and her uncle is living with the disease. “All I could think about was what I was going to put my family through,” Dennis said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;With time, though, she accepted her diagnosis and realized she had plenty more life to live.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Through the Alzheimer’s Association, she joined a support group and got engaged with advocacy, which gave her a sense of purpose. Dennis speaks about the importance of early diagnosis at association events. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Of course there are losses. She left her job, can no longer knit or quilt, and relies on AI to compose her emails. But with her husband, Dennis stays active and eats healthfully. “I am living a beautiful life,” she said, “that I am more appreciative of because of my diagnosis.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Boston Globe</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:01:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxOa0t5ZzBzR2xqVXNxMzNIWDJlOVEwbEs3Z1Fja2dWb3BOVDU1TVMyQ1FMTkMwM3BLR3RWd01saTFJX0xPZEFHLUdRN0gyT1IxeGFKYVNkN1JIZTA3WkUxQ0JFM0hIZFJjejY0cDdNQmE2Z0E2VkE3b0JsZVZXUmlYMQ</guid></item><item><title>麻疹并不是SC儿童面临的唯一日益严重的威胁。这些疾病的病例也在上升-国家</title><link>https://www.thestate.com/news/state/south-carolina/article312458991.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="primary-content" class="paper story-body"&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div class="lead-item "&gt;
        
                








    
        
    

            
        

                 
                
                    
                        &lt;figcaption&gt;
                            
    
        A nurse prepares a dose of the measles, mumps and rubella virus vaccine at a pop-up clinic at the Carrollton-Farmers Branch ISD Administration Building in Carrollton, Texas, on Friday, March 7, 2025. (Liz Rymarev/The Dallas Morning News/TNS)
    
    
        
            &lt;span class="byline"&gt;
                Liz Rymarev
            &lt;/span&gt;
        
        
            &lt;span class="credit"&gt;TNS&lt;/span&gt;
        
    

                        &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                    
                
        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="trinityAudioPlaceholder trinity-player-iframe-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles is not the only disease that has increased as the number of childhood vaccinations have decreased in South Carolina over the past several years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cases of whooping cough and chicken pox have been reported to the South Carolina Department of Public Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like the recent measles outbreak, most of the cases in the state have been in the Upstate although Lexington and Richland residents have become ill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-101" class="zone zone-el" index="2" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The health department says 91% of students statewide have received the vaccines that guard against diphtheria, tetanus and &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://dph.sc.gov/diseases-conditions/infectious-diseases/bacterial-diseases/whooping-cough-pertussis"&gt;whooping cough.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Declining vaccination rates mean a rise in rates of the potentially preventable diseases they protect against, like measles, and the possible complications, from minor to severe, that they can cause,” Louis Eubank, director of Department of Public Health’s Bureau of Emergency Preparation and Response. “This is true not just for the unvaccinated individual who contracts a vaccine-preventable disease but also for anyone else who they expose who may also be unvaccinated or have a compromised immune system.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of exemptions from the state’s requirement for vaccination to attend school have not recovered since a major decline in 2020-21 during the COVID pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to state health data Fairfield, Spartanburg and Richland counties have the lowest vaccination rates in the state, right around 90%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials say 95% is optimum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The highest rates are Allendale, Dillon and Clarendon at 98%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week, health officials reported a measles outbreak in Upstate South Carolina, including in two Spartanburg County schools. One case was reported in Greenville County. Dr. Linda Bell, state epidemiologist with the Department of Public Health, said Thursday &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.thestate.com/news/state/south-carolina/article312444330.html"&gt;11 cases had been reported&lt;/a&gt; in the state this year and all those infected were not vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some cases are travel-related exposures or close contacts of known cases but the source of other cases could not be identified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This means the disease is spreading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She said 90% of unvaccinated people exposed to the measles virus will develop the disease, which is characterized initially by high fever, cough and runny nose before a red rash on the face occurs, usually within four days. The rash then spreads to the rest of the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-106" class="zone zone-el" index="12" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Spartanburg County schools are Global Academy of South Carolina, a public charter school, with one case and Fairforest Elementary, in Spartanburg School District 6 with three cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Students who have been exposed have been excluded from school, Bell said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, Wellford Academy of Science and Technology in Spartanburg County reported a &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://dph.sc.gov/diseases-conditions/infectious-diseases/viruses-parasites-bacterial-infections/varicella-chicken"&gt;chickenpox&lt;/a&gt; outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-107" class="zone zone-el" index="15" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Melissa Robinette, director of public relations at Spartanburg District Five Schools, said at least four students have been diagnosed. The students were excluded from school for a month..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Carolina cases of whooping cough increased as well, with the majority of cases being in Spartanburg County. In all, 45 of 183 cases confirmed between Jan. 1 and July 30, 2025 were in the Upstate county.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year during the came period there were 147 cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-108" class="zone zone-el" index="18" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whooping cough of pertussis, a highly contagious disease caused by bacteria, once was among the most common causes of childhood deaths prior to the availability of a vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms are similar to those of a cold but the cough worsens over a week or two and coughing becomes the characteristic whoop at the end of an attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chicken pox causes blister-like lesions and can spread over the entire body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-109" class="zone zone-el" index="21" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One in 10 children develops complications such as infections, dehydration from vomiting or diarrhea, attack of asthma, or pneumonia. Most cases of chickenpox occur in persons less than 15 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles, whooping cough and chickenpox are spread through the air from coughing or sneezing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="zone grid"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-16" class="zone-el"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The State</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE1nVWlLb2oyUzItOFpwZ3NLdUVvU2dwNGNSX05TYkVDRGduZzExRHQyUkI4b0x4RHU5cTl2VU9GMS01d20tUDE0QXMzZnJqUDJwcmpqTDA4aVgxVGNSVnY0X05PWDVOdFJRT2xKLTFaX3lfMzlrVzV1akdLX0zSAXxBVV95cUxOVEdaRWdfd0k0cWhMWXNTbi1sSU9JS1hhTmFLaDlfNlJEYTltTmhQMlBYcGdLYnFCVDZXTXVFeEp2dnVsTzRzR00zU09rZkNXNDRmRXByeGdjVzJ6VWUyVk9wakFIV1kwMGdvUXdZNXhURkw1NWFqUUJzUU9q</guid></item><item><title>麻省理工学院的“隐身”免疫细胞可能永远改变癌症治疗- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/10/251011043535.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Scientists have created a new and more advanced form of immune-based cancer therapy using engineered cells known as CAR-NK (natural killer) cells. Like CAR-T cells, these modified immune cells can be programmed to recognize and attack cancer, but they rely on a different type of immune cell that naturally targets abnormal or infected cells.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team from MIT and Harvard Medical School has now developed a more effective way to engineer CAR-NK cells that dramatically reduces the chance of the body’s immune system rejecting them. Immune rejection has been one of the biggest limitations of cell-based therapies, often weakening their effectiveness.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This innovation could also make it possible to produce “off-the-shelf” CAR-NK treatments that are available immediately after diagnosis, rather than waiting weeks for custom-engineered cells. Traditional CAR-NK and CAR-T manufacturing methods typically require several weeks to complete before patients can begin treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This enables us to do one-step engineering of CAR-NK cells that can avoid rejection by host T cells and other immune cells. And, they kill cancer cells better and they’re safer,” says Jianzhu Chen, an MIT professor of biology, a member of the Koch Institute for Integrative Cancer Research, and one of the senior authors of the study. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In tests using mice with humanized immune systems, the newly engineered cells successfully destroyed most cancer cells while avoiding attack from the host’s own immune defenses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rizwan Romee, an associate professor of medicine at Harvard Medical School and Dana-Farber Cancer Institute, is also a senior author of the paper, which was published in &lt;em&gt;Nature Communications&lt;/em&gt;. The study’s lead author is Fuguo Liu, a postdoctoral researcher at the Koch Institute and a research fellow at Dana-Farber.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evading the immune system&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Natural killer (NK) cells are a vital part of the body’s built-in immune defense, responsible for identifying and destroying cancerous and virus-infected cells. They eliminate these threats through a process called degranulation, which releases a protein known as perforin. This protein punctures the membrane of target cells, leading to their death.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To produce CAR-NK cells for treatment, doctors typically collect a blood sample from the patient. NK cells are then extracted and engineered to express a specialized protein called a chimeric antigen receptor (CAR), which is designed to target specific markers found on cancer cells.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once modified, the cells must multiply in the lab for several weeks before there are enough to be infused back into the patient. The same general process is used for CAR-T cell therapies, some of which have already been approved to treat blood cancers like lymphoma and leukemia. CAR-NK therapies, however, are still being tested in clinical trials.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because growing enough personalized CAR-NK cells takes time and the patient’s cells may not always be healthy enough for reliable use, scientists have been exploring an alternative: creating NK cells from healthy donors. These donor-derived cells could be mass-produced and stored for rapid use. The challenge, however, is that the recipient’s immune system often identifies donor cells as foreign and destroys them before they can attack the cancer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In their latest research, the MIT team aimed to solve this problem by helping NK cells “hide” from immune detection. Their experiments showed that removing surface proteins known as HLA class 1 molecules allowed NK cells to avoid attack from T cells in the host’s immune system. These proteins normally act as identity markers that tell the immune system whether a cell belongs to the body.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To make use of this insight, the researchers added a sequence of siRNA (short interfering RNA) that silences the genes responsible for producing HLA class 1 proteins. Along with this genetic tweak, they introduced the CAR gene itself and another gene that encodes either PD-L1 or single-chain HLA-E (SCE), both of which help strengthen the NK cells’ cancer-fighting abilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All of these genetic components were combined into a single DNA construct, which allowed the team to efficiently convert donor NK cells into immune-evasive CAR-NK cells. Using this method, they engineered cells that target CD-19, a protein commonly found on malignant B cells in lymphoma patients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NK cells unleashed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers tested these CAR-NK cells in mice with a human-like immune system. These mice were also injected with lymphoma cells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mice that received CAR-NK cells with the new construct maintained the NK cell population for at least three weeks, and the NK cells were able to nearly eliminate cancer in those mice. In mice that received either NK cells with no genetic modifications or NK cells with only the CAR gene, the host immune cells attacked the donor NK cells. In these mice, the NK cells died out within two weeks, and the cancer spread unchecked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers also found that these engineered CAR-NK cells were much less likely to induce cytokine release syndrome — a common side effect of immunotherapy treatments, which can cause life-threatening complications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because of CAR-NK cells’ potentially better safety profile, Chen anticipates that they could eventually be used in place of CAR-T cells. For any CAR-NK cells that are now in development to target lymphoma or other types of cancer, it should be possible to adapt them by adding the construct developed in this study, he says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers now hope to run a clinical trial of this approach, working with colleagues at Dana-Farber. They are also working with a local biotech company to test CAR-NK cells to treat lupus, an autoimmune disorder that causes the immune system to attack healthy tissues and organs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research was funded, in part, by Skyline Therapeutics, the Koch Institute Frontier Research Program through the Kathy and Curt Marble Cancer Research Fund and the Elisa Rah Memorial Fund, the Claudia Adams Barr Foundation, and the Koch Institute Support (core) Grant from the National Cancer Institute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:25:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFB1UUlScDBSUEJNU3pKMWZMMkVsUjZ6UmdOMF96c3gyWkVBenhVcFNndHptTDdvSm9TOW9WVm5uOUJoUWhmSmVyQ3VjZEJLRkhXay1FbWRwZlJ5WnAxRFBUdXZhOEJHSmtoeWVPamxnOA</guid></item><item><title>COVID-19导致精子发生变化，导致后代焦虑增加- medianet.com.au</title><link>https://newshub.medianet.com.au/2025/10/covid-19-causes-changes-in-sperm-that-lead-to-increased-anxiety-in-offspring/122805/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Florey researchers have shown that a father’s SARS-CoV-2 viral infection before conception can alter their offspring's brain development and behaviour, through changes in sperm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lead researcher Professor Anthony Hannan said the study in mice suggested that the COVID-19 could have long-lasting effects on future generations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We already knew that when male mice were exposed to specific environmental and lifestyle factors, like poor diet before mating, it could change brain development and behaviour in offspring,” Professor Hannan said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This is because the father's experiences can alter the information carried in sperm, including specific RNA molecules, which transmit instructions for offspring development."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with co-authors Dr Elizabeth Kleeman, Dr Carolina Gubert and others, the team wanted to see whether the COVID-19 virus would similarly affect sperm RNA and resulting offspring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study’s first author Dr Elizabeth Kleeman said: "We let male mice recover from SARS-CoV-2 infection for a few weeks before they mated with healthy females. We found that the resulting offspring showed more anxious behaviours compared to offspring from uninfected fathers."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All offspring from COVID-19-affected fathers displayed increased anxiety-like behaviours. Female offspring also had significant changes in specific gene activity in their brain's hippocampus region, which is important for anxiety, depression and other affective behaviours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Co-senior author Dr Carolina Gubert said: “These kinds of changes in the hippocampus, as well as other brain regions, may contribute to the increased anxiety we observed in offspring, via epigenetic inheritance and altered brain development”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Analysis of the RNA from the infected fathers’ sperm showed that COVID-19 had altered various molecules, including some involved in the regulation of genes that are known to be important in brain development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professor Hannan said the study is the first to show that a father's SARS-CoV-2 infection before conception can impact their offspring's behaviour and brain development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“While more research is needed, particularly in the sperm and offspring of humans infected with the SARS-CoV-2 virus, these findings suggest that the COVID-19 pandemic could have long-lasting effects on future generations. Our discoveries highlight the importance of understanding the impacts of this virus and infectious disease, not only on those directly infected, but also on their children who may be affected by their parent’s experience with COVID-19.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If our findings translate to humans, this could impact millions of children worldwide, and their families, with major implications for public health.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>medianet.com.au</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:03:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPQVFrQ0JmY1NBRXJNYURuZGNSZXQ0eHlLT2otYkhmaVY4aXZmdmk4OFg0R3hQSHJaSVh4MGl6M2ZQZFRJV1JsMWlxVHc2aUZRMmNyeUt0LTl0akdwcmdnRklSZGRrdzdYbXMzeVFUTzhBZkd0UUNZa0hJR2dZRE9McjBmT0RrdmFhRk9MbzlTLXlONFR2allJd1BVcDZUYjhOWW5yUVNKbkx6VVFkSTg2aTduMWRNbjdtS0pXb3Z3SjBlUQ</guid></item><item><title>我问了2位医生如何“增强”你的免疫系统，他们都说了同样的话- HuffPost UK</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/how-to-boost-immune-system-naturally_uk_68e393aae4b0b59bd0ef0326</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though the NHS recommends most adults consider &lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/nhs-vitamin-advice-winter_uk_66deb37ce4b05e7aac7c431a" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="taking vitamin D until around March" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e393aae4b0b59bd0ef0326" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="66deb37ce4b05e7aac7c431a" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;taking vitamin D until around March&lt;/a&gt; as daylight hours shrink, &lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/do-supplements-work-immune-system-colds_uk_6718c9eae4b0ede6b2bfafe8" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="the service also noted" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e393aae4b0b59bd0ef0326" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="6718c9eae4b0ede6b2bfafe8" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;the service also noted&lt;/a&gt;: “There’s little evidence that supplements such as vitamin C, echinacea or garlic prevent colds or help you get better more quickly.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s not to say that eating a balanced diet, &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/nutrition/myths-and-truths-about-vitamin-c" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="including getting enough vitamin C" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e393aae4b0b59bd0ef0326" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.health.harvard.edu/nutrition/myths-and-truths-about-vitamin-c" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;including getting enough vitamin C&lt;/a&gt;, isn’t key to &lt;em&gt;supporting&lt;/em&gt; your immune system: it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s just &lt;a href="https://www.livescience.com/coronavirus-vitamin-c-myth.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="unlikely to provide the short-term" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e393aae4b0b59bd0ef0326" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.livescience.com/coronavirus-vitamin-c-myth.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;unlikely to provide the short-term&lt;em&gt; “boost”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; many people who begin taking the supplement in autumn hope it will.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what does help to build a strong immune system? I asked two doctors whose answers had a surprising amount in common.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ditch the idea of short-term immune “boosts” &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking to HuffPost UK,&lt;a href="https://onlinedoctor.asda.com/uk/dr-crystal-wyllie.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name=" Dr Crystal Wyllie at Asda Online Doctor" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e393aae4b0b59bd0ef0326" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://onlinedoctor.asda.com/uk/dr-crystal-wyllie.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt; Dr Crystal Wyllie at Asda Online Doctor&lt;/a&gt; said there’s no one-stop, quick-fix way to “supercharge” your immune system. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;And &lt;a href="https://click2pharmacy.co.uk/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr Hussain Ahmad" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e393aae4b0b59bd0ef0326" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://click2pharmacy.co.uk/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;Dr Hussain Ahmad&lt;/a&gt;, a hospital doctor, said: “I don’t really like the word boost when we talk about the immune system. It gives the idea that you can switch it on or make it stronger with tablets or drinks, but that’s not how it works... taking lots of vitamin C or other supplements doesn’t make it work any better for most people.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, Dr Wyllie said: “The easiest way to help boost your immune system is to choose a healthy lifestyle. Maintaining a healthy weight, eating a balanced diet high in fruit and vegetables, and exercising regularly are all natural steps you can take to help your immune system function normally.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, though all doctors recommended doing what Dr Ahmad called “simple stuff” over a long period of time, Dr Wyllie said that some changes really can make a significant change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Quitting smoking is hugely beneficial for your overall health, but also helps the health of your immune system,” she revealed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s partly because “your adaptive immune system, the part responsible for remembering and responding to threats, can be negatively impacted by smoking,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It can take years for your immune system to recover after quitting smoking, so the sooner you decide to stop, the better.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, you might be surprised by how much changing your pace of life helps. “Stress and tiredness can make you more likely to catch things, so slowing down when you can really helps,” Dr Ahmad advised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are there any genuine “immune boosts”?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes(ish). There is one exception to the “slow-burn, lifestyle change” rule: vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;These “are the only proven ways to prepare your immune system for specific infections,” Dr Ahmad advised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;And Dr Wyllie shared “It is much safer and easier for your immune system to build its defences through vaccinations than by catching the disease”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is not to say that nobody should take supplements or that they’re useless – this is not the case, especially if you have nutrient deficiencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;But, as Dr Ahmad put it, the best place for most of us to start is by trying our best to “eat proper meals with some fruit and veg in there, move your body every day, and make sure you’re getting enough rest”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;That, along with keeping up with any vaccines we’re eligible for, is as close to an “immune system boost” as we’re likely to get.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost UK</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxOQl9VamFkYXdobFpyQVBobGxuOUh5c2lCa21wcnpRVHBQdnJZQWt5a0pRWXFSc2phdDVrUWVQQl8zMlMtYkFFdVU1cTl4M0tlYV9lZk9zMmhZcWJDd1BiNnN6S05BZ1VjeVFXNmFTMFRRcGhPaDRVak0wTkJzbnRrSkJ0eTF6RGJrbVdubWlvRl95QXA5eEtDcFZYUVlmVjRULVpUSmt30gGsAUFVX3lxTE9uSjlDQ2w2cU96dVhoVEx4Q2FxWGUzeVJ4ZmVjTnVmcENnZElSZkdqQnFzN0NtdENXOENyMWR0ZHpJRm1GTzZBQzBidnBLTWJFUzVPRHBfcE5pUkp5M21RVlRUcUZjQWs4ZThFTzh4MzFwZWx2VzJjWHJnS1lCcnllVS03UEFYSzhoRjdkT1B1OU5hVlhKS040S1UxMTg0WkFDcDhhUzBQdzFUWnI</guid></item><item><title>楼梯对老年人有危险吗？他们可以，但他们也有健康益处。- Barron's</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stairs-dangers-health-benefits-home-469802ee</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Barron's</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQZFpRMFNtRHBYUVcxMHU3OFI5T0ZVcXdKYzNEOFVwTTYtdUNfaEE2YTlNZjRQQ1hiS19MbEg2ZE1SM21EOUUtSnoxVnFFY1lEeDZFVDZrV0RCTzhZUlNpM1dLLTF3TWRDZXBiSE53clV2UWQzTklRUWxscXFmOGtsMFpBWQ</guid></item><item><title>专家分享了从小说中分辨肠道健康的5个技巧- Euronews.com</title><link>https://www.euronews.com/health/2025/10/11/gut-health-is-all-the-rage-experts-share-5-tips-to-sort-fact-from-fiction</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="c-article-content c-article-content--health js-article-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="c-ad u-show-for-mobile-only"&gt;
        &lt;p data-ad-id="adzone-position" class="c-ad__adzone advertising optidigital-mobile-content-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class="c-ad__placeholder"&gt;
          &lt;img class="c-ad__placeholder__logo" src="https://static.euronews.com/website/images/logos/logo-euronews-stacked-outlined-72x72-grey-9.svg" alt="" loading="lazy"&gt;
          &lt;span&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

            

&lt;p&gt;More and more, it may seem that the answer to common health quandaries leads to a single culprit: our guts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The gut microbiome – the ecosystem of bacteria and other tiny organisms that live in our digestive tracts – has in recent years been linked to a wide range of health issues, including &lt;a href="https://www.euronews.com/health/2025/07/07/common-bacteria-found-in-the-stomach-has-no-symptoms-but-could-cause-12-million-cancers-st"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;cancer,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.euronews.com/health/2025/08/13/cant-sleep-your-gut-health-may-be-partly-to-blame-study-finds"&gt;insomnia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, heart disease, type 2 diabetes, &lt;a href="https://www.euronews.com/health/2025/09/11/how-womens-gut-health-could-affect-their-risk-of-preterm-birth"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;preterm birth&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and more.&lt;/p&gt;        

&lt;p&gt;That’s prompted a lot of excitement among doctors and scientists seeking to improve people’s wellbeing – but in most cases, there are still more questions than answers. In the absence of strong evidence, grifters, half-baked trends, and misinformation often fill the void.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Euronews Health spoke with gut health experts to set the record straight. They said there’s no model for a perfectly healthy gut because our microbiomes are all unique, and changes to them aren’t necessarily bad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“With the microbiome, it's very rare that you can give a straight, 100 per cent answer that applies to everyone, because everyone is so different. Simple stories really don't exist,” Alan Walker, a microbiologist at the University of Aberdeen, told Euronews Health.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Here are five expert tips to sort fact from fiction when it comes to gut health.&lt;/p&gt;  

&lt;h2&gt;At-home tests don’t have all the answers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many diagnostic tests for gut health are sold over the counter or through expensive private laboratories, and claim they can use a stool sample to identify whether specific foods are good or bad for the buyer. The results are often presented on a scale or colour-coded from green to red.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But “simple indices and indicators are always very misleading,” said Dr Lucas Wauters, a gastroenterologist at University Hospitals Leuven (UZ Leuven) in Belgium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wauters told Euronews Health that these tests often have some basis in science, focusing on things such as food intolerance or leaky gut, formally called intestinal permeability. Others can be genuinely useful, such as tests that look for specific bacteria in stool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, Wauters said scientists are still studying these concepts in laboratory settings, so at-home tests may rely on thin evidence to make outsized health claims.&lt;/p&gt;  



&lt;p&gt;A major red flag, he said, is test results that come with recommendations for – or even links to purchase – supplements or other products that claim they will “cure” the gut malady.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If the claims are put too simply [or are] automatically coupled to a treatment, like a supplement or whatever, then you can call it, or be close to calling it, a scam,” Wauters said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;When it comes to quick fixes, buyer beware&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s no shortage of supplements, juices, powders, and detoxes that suggest they’ll boost gut health. Before buying, Walker recommends checking whether any of these products have been tested in people and have the evidence to back up their health claims. Most don’t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If the proof isn't there, it doesn't mean it won't work, but it’s a leap of faith,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Probiotics are more complex than they seem&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Probiotics are the “good” microbes that can support certain aspects of our health, while prebiotics are parts of food that we don’t digest. Instead, they feed the beneficial bacteria in the gut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Probiotics are thought to restore the natural balance of bacteria in the gut, and are found in fermented foods such as yoghurt, kefir, cottage cheese, kimchi, and kombucha.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;But there are thousands of different probiotic bacteria and yeasts – so simply adding probiotic supplements or shakes to your diet may not do much for your gut health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walker said he would like to see more rigorous research testing different types of probiotics at various doses and durations to treat specific health issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, “if we're being honest and we look at the level of evidence that those things actually work, overall it's very patchy,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Stay away from DIYs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Faecal transplants – when a healthy person’s stool is placed into a patient’s colon – have shown promise to treat recurring infections with bacteria known as Clostridium difficile. That’s prompted research into whether these transplants can be used to treat other medical problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it’s also led to a raft of people trying to do their own faecal transplants at home to treat everything from mental health issues to Lyme disease.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Walker warned that people should leave this procedure to the professionals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“People can be harmed, and we don't understand the long-term consequences,” he said. “This should never be done outside of clinical recommendations”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;When in doubt, stick with the tried and true&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, a healthy, balanced diet is one of the best things we can do for our gut health, Wauters and Walker said. Drink lots of water, limit soda and alcohol consumption, and get enough fruits and vegetables.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They both recommended eating foods rich in fibre, such as beans, kiwis, and oats – but they noted that people’s tolerances vary. If you experience symptoms such as bloating, gas, or constipation after &lt;a href="https://www.euronews.com/health/2025/07/14/fibremaxxing-why-nutrition-experts-can-actually-get-behind-tiktoks-latest-wellness-trend"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;upping your fibre intake&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, try cutting down a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wauters also recommended that people with irritable bowel syndrome (IBS) or gut pain get at least 30 minutes of moderate exercise three to five days per week to keep their digestive system moving and relieve constipation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, when it comes to more expensive or high-tech solutions, the experts urged caution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There's lots of promise [in gut microbiome research], but at this point in time we need better quality evidence for most interventions,” Walker said.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;

                          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Euronews.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 06:00:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxOYWppZGZyUzJWLVpMYllhN042NjA4VElzMlF3UmlrdjBNXzdDZ2c1YmV1anR1S1FUc3Q4Q2N1dG85VVI4Tlo1WW5GM0lFYkRULVhBV0prTnpCM2dEZS16RERQYjN0R3l1cWtvYnlEVEplakdid0ZEZTJVYl9sdDJraEJvdC1oeXhkV0RvN2duSnZ2b2E4cEFRSkNsbUpKZnA3ZFJFdWx3OTRFb1BhTjlUXzRBZl9hV3M</guid></item><item><title>科学家首次发现与抑郁症相关的脑细胞- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/10/251010091559.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Scientists at McGill University and the Douglas Institute have discovered that two distinct types of brain cells show changes in people experiencing depression.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Published in &lt;em&gt;Nature Genetics&lt;/em&gt;, the research provides new clues that could guide the creation of treatments focused on these specific cells. It also enhances scientific understanding of depression, a condition that affects more than 264 million people globally and is one of the leading causes of disability.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This is the first time we've been able to identify what specific brain cell types are affected in depression by mapping gene activity together with mechanisms that regulate the DNA code," said senior author Dr. Gustavo Turecki, a professor at McGill, clinician-scientist at the Douglas Institute and Canada Research Chair in Major Depressive Disorder and Suicide. "It gives us a much clearer picture of where disruptions are happening, and which cells are involved."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rare brain bank enables breakthrough&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team conducted their work using post-mortem brain tissue from the Douglas-Bell Canada Brain Bank, one of the few collections worldwide that includes donations from people with psychiatric conditions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Through advanced single-cell genomic analysis, the researchers examined RNA and DNA from thousands of individual brain cells to determine which ones behaved differently in people with depression and which DNA sequences might explain these variations. The study analyzed tissue from 59 individuals who had depression and 41 who did not.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They discovered that gene activity was altered in two types of brain cells: a class of excitatory neurons responsible for mood and stress regulation, and a subtype of microglia, the immune cells that manage inflammation in the brain. In both cell types, many genes were expressed differently in people with depression, pointing to possible disruptions in vital neural systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By identifying the specific cells affected, the research deepens understanding of the biological foundation of depression and helps dispel outdated views of the condition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This research reinforces what neuroscience has been telling us for years," Turecki said. "Depression isn't just emotional, it reflects real, measurable changes in the brain."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, the scientists intend to explore how these cellular changes influence brain function and whether targeting them could lead to more effective treatments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the study&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Single-nucleus chromatin accessibility profiling identifies cell types and functional variants contributing to major depression" by Anjali Chawla and Gustavo Turecki et al., was published in &lt;em&gt;Nature Genetics.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study was funded by Canadian Institutes of Health Research, Brain Canada Foundation, Fonds de recherche du Québec - Santé and Healthy Brains, Healthy Lives initiative at McGill University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 05:58:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE85RnhaNjdGel9fRlFwaV9rNzdpSXkxSEY2d0lfVXVvQ0VHOUlDMGJfZl9ndzVCS1NIbkVudk1UQldyRWp1UE05TGhoMFNDM2VCTFRNbXJsVkZlT014Y3BFd2hwRGh2bVFOMmNhMndKWQ</guid></item><item><title>新疗法“修复”与脑部疾病有关的基因……逆转数百万人患有衰弱性疾病的症状-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15177439/autism-epilepsy-gene-therapy-syngap1.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists may be one step closer to a new therapy that could 'fix' the faulty genes at play in people with brain disorders such as autism and epilepsy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About a million people worldwide are thought to have a SYNGAP1-related disorder (SRD). This is a group of brain disorders that disrupt normal brain development and can lead to intellectual disability, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15148925/epilepsy-cure-childrens-brains.html"&gt;epilepsy&lt;/a&gt;, movement problems and impulsive behavior, as well as symptoms associated with autism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In most cases, the conditions are caused when someone only has one functional copy of the SYNGAP1 gene instead of the usual two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now, scientists in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/washington-state/index.html" id="mol-076e8d60-a514-11f0-9292-7b50e0f25ff3"&gt;Washington state&lt;/a&gt; say they have found a way to repair the damaged gene and potentially help patients function better in daily life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a new study, researchers administered juvenile mice suffering from the brain disorder with an altered adenovirus, or a cold virus, that carried a healthy copy of the SYNGAP1 gene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The virus successfully delivered the gene to brain cells, with the rodents then experiencing broad improvements in their behavior up to two weeks later, including the near elimination of epilepsy, a neurological disorder where patients suffer from recurrent and unprovoked seizures, and a reduction in hyperactive and risky behavior.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The mice also saw a substantial shift in their brain wave patterns, or electrical pulses generated by the brain, from abnormal to much closer to normal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Boaz Levy, a biochemist at the Allen Institute for Brain Science who led the study, said: '[This study] is an important milestone for the field that provides hope for those who suffer from this class of severe neurological diseases.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Scientists say they have found a potential new therapy for a brain disorder that can cause autism symptoms in children (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He added: 'Gene supplementation is providing a functional new copy of a defective gene, a strategy that has great potential for correcting diseases where a gene is completely missing or where a single copy of a gene is lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This [study] provides a clear demonstration that SYNGAP1-related disorders can be treated with a neuron-specific gene supplementation strategy.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The research is in the early stages and was only carried out in mice, with researchers saying clinical trials still need to be done in humans to confirm that the therapy works.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But scientists heralded the results as a positive step towards developing a treatment for the condition. It was particularly notable that the study was successful in juvenile mice, which is around the same age at which humans are diagnosed with SRDs and could, therefore, receive treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 1,500 Americans have been diagnosed with a SYNGAP1-related brain disorder, activists say, although estimates suggest many cases have been missed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Not all autism and epilepsy cases are caused by SYNGAP1-related disorders, although patients with SRDs may be diagnosed with these conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The disorders are considered to be a spectrum because the faulty genes often do not affect the brain in exactly the same way or to the same level of severity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There is currently no specific treatment or cure for the condition, but doctors say they can help patients to manage symptoms using antiseizure medications or implanting devices into the body that can help to control nerve activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About one to two percent of all intellectual disability cases, including autism spectrum disorder and epilepsy, are estimated to be caused by SRD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;In the therapy, a healthy copy of the faulty gene is delivered to brain cells by an adenovirus, or cold virus. It was successful at improving symptoms in juvenile mice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About one in 31 children in the US has autism, a surge on the one in 150 estimated to have the condition in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some research has suggested that about 80 percent of autism cases are linked to inherited genetic mutations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But Robert F Kennedy Jr, the Health and Human Services Secretary, is among those who have argued that the surge in cases cannot be blamed on genetics alone and is likely also down to unidentified environmental factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 470,000 children in the US have epilepsy, with experts also suggesting that the condition is caused by both genetic and lifestyle factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Epilepsy is a common symptom in patients with SYNGAP1-related brain disorders, with more than 80 percent of sufferers also diagnosed with this condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For the research, published in the journal &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.cell.com/molecular-therapy-family/molecular-therapy/pdf/S1525-0016(25)00759-2.pdf?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS1525001625007592%3Fshowall%3Dtrue"&gt;Molecular Therapy&lt;/a&gt;, scientists injected the altered adenoviruses into the mice's cerebral ventricles, the fluid-filled cavities in the center of the organ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The injection was carried out by inserting a needle past the eye and into the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Shown above is Dr Boaz Levy, left, who led the research, and associate investigator Dr Rong Guo and scientist Dr Meagan Quinlan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above is the cross section of the brain of a mouse in the study. The highlighted areas represent locations where the adenovirus delivered the treatment to the brain&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One to two weeks later the rodents were put through a battery of tests to measure the impact of the therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Tests included tracking the movements of mice in a 7.8inch by 7.8inch arena, to check for erratic behavior, and placing them in an elevated maze and monitoring their behavior to estimate anxiety and risk-taking behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team concluded: 'Our findings provide the first evidence that... gene therapy can restore SYNGAP1 function and reverse key [symptoms], supporting its potential as a transformative therapeutic for patients.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 04:46:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPOVAtaEFWeEJyenhqQ0M5TDZRbVNSZXBqc24yTjhpX241bC16VzAzU1g1eW1BYnZ3QnkwSVZWQkVMeTJkLWg5QnE2Zi1tZ054MzZqTkJmeExsaG4wckxnc2hzU2FtVU9JejFuajJCeHl2MzdabTBrbXUtSjY0NERwM0Fta0VtSTJ0enRESV9JQXB6WWFuVGZZTtIBngFBVV95cUxONjlrRFNkeDRMa19mSDVYQW1ZT09NMUpFUkptUXI3UTNvMVp5amlteWlOWUtQcVctbHpTbURJdzB6UEZXZnQzeTJvZDhzVGpJX01KQUlwTzBIRWpRNGprYjV1QWM3N3p5Z3lQZ0dRcTFjUTdHak1uMVp3QVc4RE16QTQ4UTM4U1RyUjA5YW9UVFZJN2RQT2NWd2Flb2owdw</guid></item></channel></rss>