<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>使用ChatGPT后，男性将盐换成溴化钠并患上精神病- Ars Technica</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwFBVV95cUxNU3lPeVJYOXNVMjRSM2d3cmE4NWNrckdMOWlIdzA0MDJHeUE1NzR6SFRqa3hyWlVUY2xJMXVkX1V2dWE3eU1IaFpaY2pVbjBRSS1YVW9pZjVaQjd0a1dVckhCR240aHRETzB5RG0xejBQWUFTM1ROcWd5MU1kVDI1bW0xdGxnN3BHNUJ1RWFTRTFXYkFCMm5XVXRUMHRFZW9zNXZrczVDbGx1dVMzQWc1eC02ZXFDVmk5MmFJ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
          
          
&lt;p&gt;Bromide sedatives vanished from the US market by 1989, after the Food and Drug Administration banned them, and "bromism" as a syndrome is today unfamiliar to many Americans. (Though you can still get it by &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.3109/15563659709001219"&gt;drinking, as one poor guy did, two to four liters of cola daily [!],&lt;/a&gt; if that cola contains "brominated vegetable oil." Fortunately, the FDA &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/food/hfp-constituent-updates/fda-revokes-regulation-allowing-use-brominated-vegetable-oil-bvo-food"&gt;removed brominated vegetable oil&lt;/a&gt; from US food products in 2024.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this case, over the man's first day at the hospital, he grew worse and showed "increasing paranoia and auditory and visual hallucinations." He then attempted to escape the facility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the escape attempt, the man was given an involuntary psychiatric hold and an anti-psychosis drug. He was administered large amounts of fluids and electrolytes, as the best way to beat bromism is "aggressive saline diuresis"—that is, to load someone up with liquids and let them pee out all the bromide in their system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This took time, as the man's bromide level was eventually measured at a whopping 1,700 mg/L, while the "reference range" for healthy people is 0.9 to 7.3 mg/L.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, the man suffered from a terrifying psychosis and was kept in the hospital for &lt;em&gt;three full weeks&lt;/em&gt; over an entirely preventable condition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How it all began&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was during his stay, once doctors had his psychosis under control, that the man began telling them how it all began. He had read about the problems with too much table salt, which led him to rid his diet of sodium chloride, which led him to ChatGPT, which led him to believe that he could use sodium bromide instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The doctors who &lt;a href="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/aimcc.2024.1260"&gt;wrote up this case study for Annals of Internal Medicine: Clinical Cases&lt;/a&gt; note that they never got access to the man's actual ChatGPT logs. He likely used ChatGPT 3.5 or 4.0, they say, but it's not clear that the man was actually told by the chatbot to do what he did. Bromide salts &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; be substituted for table salt—just not in the human body. They are used in various cleaning products and pool treatments, however.&lt;/p&gt;

          
                  &lt;/div&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:20:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxNU3lPeVJYOXNVMjRSM2d3cmE4NWNrckdMOWlIdzA0MDJHeUE1NzR6SFRqa3hyWlVUY2xJMXVkX1V2dWE3eU1IaFpaY2pVbjBRSS1YVW9pZjVaQjd0a1dVckhCR240aHRETzB5RG0xejBQWUFTM1ROcWd5MU1kVDI1bW0xdGxnN3BHNUJ1RWFTRTFXYkFCMm5XVXRUMHRFZW9zNXZrczVDbGx1dVMzQWc1eC02ZXFDVmk5MmFJ</guid></item><item><title>现在与Lou Gehrig病有关的最富有的美国人喜爱的“健康”食品- dailymail.co.uk</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixAFBVV95cUxOTUk3ZjlBZFo0WlVmU3hjYk5LS2JyRXFWMVVoanNFUjJtQVZoWm1oeE80dDNJa0xIcmtId1JtLURMSzl1Q0xVbFdEV3NfaHdUd1lzUmtwUVlhZzBGN1R4MFVhdUp0c0UzdTJLallrT0c0ejlLQTM0RUE4SjRZWVNidXU1MUVWOW1ENTd5R25UVUhWY0Jtemk4Sk1QY3VSUG0xdTJ3LWN5ZFJRcVNyWG1XNjh1SHM3OGxCZzAxa18wcl9nQlEw0gHKAUFVX3lxTE9mbDVnQ29LZF9YdGZMMi1vYVhiQURyYkliR3ZuUUdxNEI1aFBRb0xkaFBtSzV3cDV0ZnFGdVhxSVFRSW96NlltQ0pheGZqMUljdGp4YTE4S2ljVE5qVjl5Rk9xOUJ3M1ZHT090UTF3ZTZrMndTRm5aZGlFSGlGU2xueWZGNVRWS1JadGRkY0NEUy1sYWY4a21weWttU1ptQ28wVWZPQzM1NWJTTWNiVDVLOFlYNDc1WWxUdWZ3SklkWlV3ZkFRd1llS2c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The toxic cousin of a gourmet delicacy could put foodies at risk of a devastating and irreversible neurological disorder. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A true morel is one of the most luxurious and sought-after &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/sciencetech/article-13210479/deadly-morel-mushroom-CDC-Montana.html"&gt;wild mushrooms&lt;/a&gt;, often featured in high-end cuisine from risotto to a cream sauce over steak due to its earthy, nutty flavor and exclusive seasonal availability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Morels are coveted in the culinary world, but they have deceptive, poisonous lookalikes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;False morels have tricked amateur foragers and garnered true fans in a town called Montchavin, a village in the French Alps, for their 'rejuvenating' properties. Despite their name, though, they belong to an entirely different family of fungi, the Gyromitra.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;False morels contain compounds called hydrazines that are toxic to the nervous system. While eating one may cause abdominal pain and diarrhea, in severe cases, a false morel can cause seizures and multi-organ failure. Gyromitrin, the main toxin in the mushroom, is also a carcinogen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Recently, scientists believe they've found a link between false morels and &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14606543/footage-impact-motor-neurone-disease-healthy-woman.html"&gt;Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis&lt;/a&gt; (ALS) in Montchavin, as a mysterious cluster of cases has developed over the last decade. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Also known as Lou Gehrig's disease, and, in some parts of the world, motor neurone disease, ALS is a fatal neurological disorder that progressively paralyzes patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Montchavin has a permanent population of about 200 people, and the average global diagnosis rate of ALS is two to three diagnoses per 100,000 people annually. Yet in the last decade, there have been 16 cases reported in Montchavin, far more than what would be expected.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" aria-label="To enrich screen reader interactions, please activate Accessibility in Grammarly extension settings"&gt;Over a period of about 10 years, 16 residents of a ski village in the French Alps, out of a population of 200, had ALS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If made comparable to a rate in 100,000 people per year, Montchavin's rate would be 800 cases per 100,000 residents per year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The search for answers was led by Dr Emmeline Lagrange, a neurologist practicing at Grenoble University Hospital, 84 miles southwest of the village. A resident of Montchavin who had been experiencing neurological issues had been referred to Lagrange, who diagnosed them with ALS. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She would later learn on a call with the patient’s referring physician in Montchavin that this was one of several ALS cases in the small mountain village.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;None of the patients had a gene mutation making them more susceptible to ALS or a family history of the disease, which causes continuously worsening paralysis over time, leading to death after two to five years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists are still investigating the cause of ALS, which affects roughly 33,000 Americans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Genetics are behind between 10 and 15 percent of cases, while the rest could be tied to environmental exposures, including toxic pollution, smoking, exposure to heavy metals like lead and mercury, and a history of head injuries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lagrange published an abstract summarizing her investigation into the unusual ALS cluster, which caught the eye of environmental neuroscientist Dr Peter Spencer of the Oregon Health &amp;amp; Science University in Portland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Spencer is the leading proponent of a separate theory linking food to the degenerative disease.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;His theory was that toxins in cycad seeds, once a staple of Guam’s Chamorro people, triggered an epidemic of Western Pacific ALS-Parkinsonism dementia (ALS-PDC). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At its peak, ALS-PDC was 50 to 100 times more common in Guam than ALS rates worldwide. In the 1950s, incidence rates reached about 200 per 100,000 among Chamorro adults. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He has investigated the link for over four decades, arguing that a compound in cycad seeds called cycasin metabolizes into a neurotoxic DNA-damaging byproduct called methylazoxymethanol (MAM).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;MAM is also formed when the body metabolizes hydrazine, a volatile chemical used in rocket fuels and also found in false morels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" aria-label="To enrich screen reader interactions, please activate Accessibility in Grammarly extension settings"&gt;A true morel is a gourmet delicacy, though it must be properly cooked or could be poisonous. True morels are often featured in Michelin-starred restaurants and in high-end cuisine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The false morel [shown] is often reddish-brown, whereas true morels are typically green or gray. False morels are also a different shape and has brain-like folds and ridges&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When Spencer saw a presentation of Lagrange’s abstract, his mind lingered on one line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He told &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://knowablemagazine.org/content/article/health-disease/2024/did-eating-false-mushrooms-cause-als-french-village"&gt;Knowable Magazine&lt;/a&gt;: ‘I noted that among the foodstuffs they reported were mushrooms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘And I asked them what type of mushrooms, because one particular type contains poisons associated with the Guam problem.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They began collaborating on a study. Lagrange had learned that the ALS patients in Montchavin had been purposely seeking out false morels, believing they had rejuvenating properties, despite their illegal status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A villager told Lagrange: ‘They are always in a group, a secret group, a social network, and they eat the mushrooms. And they all knew that it’s forbidden.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers included those patients in their study, as well as 48 villagers without the disease who ate wild mushrooms, but not false morels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some ALS patients had a history of collecting up to six pounds of the poisonous fungi during the spring and summer and eating them throughout the year. People who had been diagnosed with ALS had been eating the mushrooms for as long as 20 years before ALS symptoms arose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘All ALS cases but none of the controls had a history of consuming acutely poisonous False Morels, notably the Snow Morel Gyromitra gigas,’ Lagrange &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.jns-journal.com/article/S0022-510X(21)00252-5/fulltext"&gt;concluded&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" aria-label="To enrich screen reader interactions, please activate Accessibility in Grammarly extension settings"&gt;Neuroscientist Emmeline Lagrange spearheaded the investigation into the ALS cluster in the French Alps, determining from a lengthy investigation that ALS patients shared something in common: their love for false morels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Since no other significant chemical or physical exposure was found, the primary risk factor for ALS in this community appears to be repeated ingestion of these neurotoxic fungi.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Despite the false morel’s toxicity, it is a delicacy in parts of Scandinavia, where Michelin-starred restaurants incorporate it on seasonal menus for its tang and nuttiness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Finns are such big fans that the species was featured on a 1974 postage stamp. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;False morels are also endorsed by the Finnish Food Authority, which advises people to repeatedly boil and rinse fresh or dried specimens before eating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Despite their differences in appearance, amateur foragers often confuse true morels with false ones, which resemble a reddish brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A June 2024 Toxicon study identified &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0041010124003970?via%3Dihub"&gt;118 false morel poisonings&lt;/a&gt; in Michigan between 2002 and 2020. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Most of the patients suffered from vomiting, diarrhea, and abdominal pain, while over a dozen developed liver damage. One sustained a kidney injury, and others reported neurological effects such as headaches and dizziness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>dailymail.co.uk</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:25:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixAFBVV95cUxOTUk3ZjlBZFo0WlVmU3hjYk5LS2JyRXFWMVVoanNFUjJtQVZoWm1oeE80dDNJa0xIcmtId1JtLURMSzl1Q0xVbFdEV3NfaHdUd1lzUmtwUVlhZzBGN1R4MFVhdUp0c0UzdTJLallrT0c0ejlLQTM0RUE4SjRZWVNidXU1MUVWOW1ENTd5R25UVUhWY0Jtemk4Sk1QY3VSUG0xdTJ3LWN5ZFJRcVNyWG1XNjh1SHM3OGxCZzAxa18wcl9nQlEw0gHKAUFVX3lxTE9mbDVnQ29LZF9YdGZMMi1vYVhiQURyYkliR3ZuUUdxNEI1aFBRb0xkaFBtSzV3cDV0ZnFGdVhxSVFRSW96NlltQ0pheGZqMUljdGp4YTE4S2ljVE5qVjl5Rk9xOUJ3M1ZHT090UTF3ZTZrMndTRm5aZGlFSGlGU2xueWZGNVRWS1JadGRkY0NEUy1sYWY4a21weWttU1ptQ28wVWZPQzM1NWJTTWNiVDVLOFlYNDc1WWxUdWZ3SklkWlV3ZkFRd1llS2c</guid></item><item><title>宠物猫死于瘟疫后发出健康警告-《独立报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxPbVFQeHFlLXNUR0llbkNTZnNqWmg4NW16MkpFZDl4LW5jTjZpMGJVQVJHYTNqZENUa0hueEtkWS1zUFdpMG5PZFVoU0t2TGd3ZS1RaVhZUXJGTWdMdEFaX3pTOTc1M2M2RjViZXAtdmdIUkVJYllCUlpHWGw1SUNsc3QzSzJMc1JfVTQxTS1wWmVwWFZrU0E?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-1d79dbf-0 hpUznh"&gt;&lt;h3 class="sc-erjdy9-0 hKUIcv"&gt;Thank you for registering&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1ty8yds-2 uWTBa"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1ty8yds-0 bbjlNt"&gt;Please refresh the page or navigate to another page on the site to be automatically logged in&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1ty8yds-1 SkKtY"&gt;Please refresh your browser to be logged in&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPbVFQeHFlLXNUR0llbkNTZnNqWmg4NW16MkpFZDl4LW5jTjZpMGJVQVJHYTNqZENUa0hueEtkWS1zUFdpMG5PZFVoU0t2TGd3ZS1RaVhZUXJGTWdMdEFaX3pTOTc1M2M2RjViZXAtdmdIUkVJYllCUlpHWGw1SUNsc3QzSzJMc1JfVTQxTS1wWmVwWFZrU0E</guid></item><item><title>关于表明锂可以帮助预防阿尔茨海默病的新研究的须知事项-《波士顿环球报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimAFBVV95cUxOZnJTdVA5bEFJYk5faUM3MVNnQV9XVUNFd25zS1JVZFk2UGZ0QjAwN1dfbzdqTkpOcjRqRFNIQV9fWU9rcWkxcjMwajhPVVc5NUxwYVRucENfd2QwZXY3RTBudkdkci1OclAyQVBTN0ZLMnNEUW1kLUpUUlZIVFBQbFJmbG9XZlZQOVhsSURkVVNKSUl0Y1Naaw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body | gutter_16--desktop gutter_16--tablet paywalled_content
              "&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The researchers studied brain tissue of about 400 people post mortem, as well as blood samples and a battery of memory tests performed yearly before their death. The scientists found higher levels of lithium in cognitively healthy people. But as sticky clumps of protein, known as amyloid plaques, began forming in their brains in the early stages of dementia, the amyloid trapped the lithium, restraining it and reducing its availability to surrounding brain cells. That depleted the lithium even in parts of the brain that were amyloid-free, essentially reducing lithium’s protective function.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The researchers also fed healthy mice a lithium-restricted diet, spurring memory problems: they had trouble performing several laboratory memory tests. And finally, the researchers were also able to reverse disease-related damage and restore memory function, even in older mice with advanced disease, by returning lithium to their diet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="flex align_items_base justify_space_between heading-container"&gt;&lt;h3 id="what_kind_of_lithium_was_used_in" class="heading | bold font_secondary gutter_20_0--mobile 
             padding_top_24"&gt;What kind of lithium was used in the study?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The researchers used a different form of lithium than is typically used to treat psychiatric disorders, such as bipolar disorder. They used &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11954165/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11954165/"&gt;lithium orotate,&lt;/a&gt; which is a compound that is able to evade the sticky amyloid plaques in our brains. The type of lithium used to treat psychiatric disorders is lithium carbonate, but it can be &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5537577/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5537577/"&gt;hard on people’s kidneys&lt;/a&gt; and toxic to elderly patients. The amount of lithium orotate used by the Harvard team was one-thousandth the level, essentially mimicking the amount naturally found in the brain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="flex align_items_base justify_space_between heading-container"&gt;&lt;h3 id="should_you_buy_lithium_online_or_in" class="heading | bold font_secondary gutter_20_0--mobile 
             padding_top_24"&gt;Should you buy lithium online or in stores and start taking it?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Lithium, like other supplements or vitamins sold online or in stores, is &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/food/information-consumers-using-dietary-supplements/questions-and-answers-dietary-supplements" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.fda.gov/food/information-consumers-using-dietary-supplements/questions-and-answers-dietary-supplements"&gt;not subject to review or testing by &lt;/a&gt;federal regulators the way prescription medicines are. So there’s no way to tell whether the substance actually contains lithium and, if so, in what amounts, or whether it contains contaminants. Generally, a firm does not have to provide the FDA with the evidence it relies on to substantiate safety before or after it markets its products.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="flex align_items_base justify_space_between heading-container"&gt;&lt;h3 id="how_else_should_i_get_lithium_in" class="heading | bold font_secondary gutter_20_0--mobile 
             padding_top_24"&gt;How else should I get lithium in my diet?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Many foods already touted for their health benefits naturally contain higher amounts of lithium —&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6443601/#CR44" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;seafood, grains,&lt;/a&gt; nuts, some vegetables, and mineral water.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="flex align_items_base justify_space_between heading-container"&gt;&lt;h3 id="what_else_can_i_do_to_lower" class="heading | bold font_secondary gutter_20_0--mobile 
             padding_top_24"&gt;What else can I do to lower my risk of Alzheimer’s disease?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Another &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/07/29/metro/study-alzheimers-lifestyle-interventions-protect-brain-health-ri-butler-hospital/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/07/29/metro/study-alzheimers-lifestyle-interventions-protect-brain-health-ri-butler-hospital/"&gt;new study released late last month, &lt;/a&gt;called US POINTER, found that simple lifestyle changes, including improved nutrition, increased physical activity, and more time with friends, led to improved cognition. It studied more than 2,000 adults between the ages of 60 and 79 who were at risk for cognitive decline and dementia. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Scientists say the new lithium findings are exciting, but urge people not to rush out and buy supplements before researchers can test lithium orotate in a large clinical trial with one group of participants receiving small doses of lithium orotate and the others a sham substance, to compare the findings. The trials would need to identify the dosage and duration of time for taking the substance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="tagline_hr | border_foreground border_half gutter_20_28--mobile
               margin_none text_align_left width_100px"&gt;&lt;p class="tagline | font_primary inline_block  margin_top_32"&gt;Kay Lazar can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:kay.lazar@globe.com" class="" target="_blank"&gt;kay.lazar@globe.com&lt;/a&gt; Follow her &lt;a href="https://www.twitter.com/GlobeKayLazar" class="" target="_blank"&gt;@GlobeKayLazar&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Boston Globe</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:12:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxOZnJTdVA5bEFJYk5faUM3MVNnQV9XVUNFd25zS1JVZFk2UGZ0QjAwN1dfbzdqTkpOcjRqRFNIQV9fWU9rcWkxcjMwajhPVVc5NUxwYVRucENfd2QwZXY3RTBudkdkci1OclAyQVBTN0ZLMnNEUW1kLUpUUlZIVFBQbFJmbG9XZlZQOVhsSURkVVNKSUl0Y1Naaw</guid></item><item><title>On Vaccines, RFK Jr.与主流大相径庭--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTE40LVltZEVSNGhocV9JUjM0T2t2alVSQVdoR1ltM2MyRmsxU3RaMkdTaEp3MkIyM1laRkJNbmlrT2kzM2NLNU5rWjBEczc3V2tycUkza2RsVkVqLXU3VmJNNklTd210a2FDOHJZQnUwQXBZNTNsSmJqbFJjSkZ4ODQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:55:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE40LVltZEVSNGhocV9JUjM0T2t2alVSQVdoR1ltM2MyRmsxU3RaMkdTaEp3MkIyM1laRkJNbmlrT2kzM2NLNU5rWjBEczc3V2tycUkza2RsVkVqLXU3VmJNNklTd210a2FDOHJZQnUwQXBZNTNsSmJqbFJjSkZ4ODQ</guid></item><item><title>科学家揭示了如何在不哭的情况下切洋葱，他们的方法非常简单。- evidencenetwork.ca</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitwFBVV95cUxQMXZ1WXNiQV81Q1c3ODlBblNaaXl2Tkhrd0wyekZjYW9IWVBKV0Vrd0hTdnFWNUo4YkZrdEZMbkRzZFRVS1RSY2w3b2x4MktsRHRTRUpUX0dleEkyTFZsdkJYdnRySVhVT09TYWMzdzJ3blZqVXVDMGMyTFdEVkNoVXpaakNDYjhqWGRqaUJMZTR6Y25PU0FTZUkySTBuVFV4SzJQdXVIUDkxbm9aTnlLcGViMC1kMDQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-entry-content"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chopping onions is a fundamental cooking skill that many home chefs dread due to the inevitable tears that follow. Recent scientific research from Cornell University has finally provided a definitive answer to this culinary conundrum. Their findings reveal that the key to tear-free onion cutting lies in two simple factors: using a sharp knife and cutting slowly. This breakthrough could transform how we approach this essential kitchen task and make meal preparation more enjoyable for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The science behind onion tears&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;When you slice into an onion, you’re breaking open cells that contain enzymes and sulfur compounds. These components mix together and create syn-propanethial-S-oxide, a volatile gas that rises through the air and irritates the sensitive membranes in your eyes. Your eyes respond to this irritation by producing tears to wash away the irritant.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;Scientists at Cornell University conducted detailed experiments to understand exactly how this irritating compound gets released during cutting. Using a specially designed guillotine fitted with different blades, they meticulously documented the spray patterns produced when cutting onions under various conditions.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The research team captured high-speed footage&lt;/strong&gt; of onion juice ejection during cutting, allowing them to analyze precisely how much spray was produced and what factors influenced it. This methodical approach finally provided scientific validation for what many chefs have long suspected about knife sharpness.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The relationship between our dietary choices and bodily functions extends beyond cooking techniques. Research has shown that &lt;a href="https://evidencenetwork.ca/the-brain-can-change-intestinal-bacteria-in-a-couple-of-hours/"&gt;the brain can change intestinal bacteria in a couple of hours&lt;/a&gt;, highlighting how interconnected our body systems truly are.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Sharp knives create fewer tears&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Cornell study conclusively demonstrated that knife sharpness plays a crucial role in determining how much onion spray is produced during cutting. &lt;em&gt;Dull blades significantly increase both the speed and number of ejected droplets&lt;/em&gt; that carry the tear-inducing compound.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;When using a blunt knife, the researchers observed that the blade tends to push down on the onion’s layers before actually cutting through them. This compression forces the layers to bend inward, storing elastic energy. As the cut progresses, these compressed layers spring back, forcefully ejecting juice into the air – and ultimately into your eyes.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In contrast, sharp blades slice cleanly through the onion’s cellular structure with minimal compression. This precision cutting reduces the amount of juice that gets sprayed into the surrounding air, resulting in fewer tears for the person doing the chopping.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;Maintaining a healthy lifestyle includes not just proper cooking techniques but also regular exercise. Studies show that &lt;a href="https://evidencenetwork.ca/take-10000-steps-a-day-if-you-can-well-but-already-7000-they-keep-in-health/"&gt;taking 7,000 steps daily can significantly improve health&lt;/a&gt;, making it an achievable goal for most people.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Cutting speed matters&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The second critical factor identified by the Cornell researchers was cutting speed. Contrary to what many might assume, &lt;strong&gt;faster cutting actually produces more tears&lt;/strong&gt;, not fewer. The research team found that rapid cutting motions generated more juice and created a finer mist of the irritating compound that more easily reaches the eyes.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Slowing down your cutting motion allows for more control and precision, which results in less spray. This measured approach might take a few extra seconds, but the comfort gained is well worth the minimal additional time investment.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Here are the key techniques to implement for tear-free onion cutting:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ol class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use a professionally sharpened chef’s knife&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Cut with deliberate, slow movements&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Minimize compression of the onion layers&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Maintain proper ventilation in your kitchen&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Consider chilling the onion briefly before cutting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Understanding how we interact with food extends beyond cooking techniques. Research indicates that &lt;a href="https://evidencenetwork.ca/there-is-a-lost-memory-of-the-meals-that-makes-us-eat-more-than-necessary/"&gt;there is a lost memory of meals that makes us eat more than necessary&lt;/a&gt;, showing how our relationship with food is influenced by psychological factors.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Our early development can also affect our overall health trajectory. Studies have found that &lt;a href="https://evidencenetwork.ca/growth-in-the-first-1000-days-of-life-affects-adult-stature/"&gt;growth in the first 1,000 days of life affects adult stature&lt;/a&gt;, emphasizing the importance of proper nutrition from an early age.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Additional benefits beyond comfort&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Cornell researchers noted that adopting these proper cutting techniques offers benefits beyond just preventing tears. &lt;em&gt;Minimizing airborne spray during food preparation can reduce the spread of potential pathogens in kitchen environments&lt;/em&gt;, contributing to overall food safety.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This is particularly important when cutting vegetables with tough outer layers that store significant elastic energy. The proper technique not only improves comfort but also supports better kitchen hygiene practices.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-table"&gt;&lt;table class="has-fixed-layout"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;Knife Condition&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Cutting Speed&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Tear Production&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Airborne Spray&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Sharp&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Slow&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Minimal&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Low&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Sharp&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Fast&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Moderate&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Moderate&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Dull&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Slow&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Moderate&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Moderate&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Dull&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Fast&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Excessive&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;High&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Recent medical research has identified interesting connections between medications and mental health, such as &lt;a href="https://evidencenetwork.ca/a-new-connection-between-the-competitive-drugs-of-the-glp-1-and-the-depression/"&gt;a new connection between GLP-1 drugs and depression&lt;/a&gt;, highlighting the complex interplay between different body systems.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Food waste remains a significant issue in modern society. Studies have shown that &lt;a href="https://evidencenetwork.ca/the-invisible-food-waste-of-the-canteens-a-chasm-of-costs-and-food-thrown/"&gt;the invisible food waste in canteens creates enormous costs&lt;/a&gt;, making efficient food preparation techniques all the more important.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The broader impact of proper technique&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Mastering the art of onion cutting not only improves your culinary experience but also contributes to better health outcomes. &lt;strong&gt;Reducing eye irritation makes cooking more enjoyable&lt;/strong&gt;, potentially encouraging more home-cooked meals. This can lead to healthier eating patterns and greater control over ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The precision skills developed through proper cutting techniques transfer to other aspects of cooking as well. Improving knife skills generally leads to more consistent food preparation, better presentation, and ultimately more satisfying meals.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Regular physical activity complements good nutrition for overall health. Research has shown that &lt;a href="https://evidencenetwork.ca/exercise-fights-cancer-now-we-understand-how/"&gt;exercise fights cancer through specific biological mechanisms&lt;/a&gt; that scientists are now beginning to understand fully.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The humble onion, found in cuisines worldwide from Italian pasta sauces to Indian curries, no longer needs to be a source of kitchen frustration. With the scientifically validated combination of a sharp knife and slow cutting motion, you can incorporate this flavorful vegetable into your cooking without reaching for tissues or resorting to swimming goggles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>evidencenetwork.ca</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxQMXZ1WXNiQV81Q1c3ODlBblNaaXl2Tkhrd0wyekZjYW9IWVBKV0Vrd0hTdnFWNUo4YkZrdEZMbkRzZFRVS1RSY2w3b2x4MktsRHRTRUpUX0dleEkyTFZsdkJYdnRySVhVT09TYWMzdzJ3blZqVXVDMGMyTFdEVkNoVXpaakNDYjhqWGRqaUJMZTR6Y25PU0FTZUkySTBuVFV4SzJQdXVIUDkxbm9aTnlLcGViMC1kMDQ</guid></item><item><title>明尼苏达州新型冠状病毒变异型有明显症状导致病例增加-补丁</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxPVTNwRDRYTW1PNENYMl9SWTNvSm1vYzhVby0wNmtIZXF0ZWlYZm1GSlItY1ZFRl9HTTI5clY5bkVsb3p6cVFRMVZuU3ZHcnBVbkhsWW9NQ1NpN2poSlRScC1nZjR5eDdDNVlZY3JYc2xCVm8yUUFXanRsczc2OE53WHA2Q1JfUlNsYWE4dGxvOWIxNXFiOFlV0gG3AUFVX3lxTE5UbEZVT0I5RWtDc0RoZ3ZCQ0ZpN3YwVUVyUzVZM1EzZk5xZVZ4b2pURW1WVWJYaDE3ak5RWTBkXzE3MXVyY1cyanhOOTNJZGRPTGxwc2xkYWxDV0hnWEZQUF96Sjg0MmJ3UmtqWjhTTUVSbEZQRnM0Z1Z6UjRaQktjOXliQkVJa2NrZUZnbGVwTE94b08zdjNuUEZFVzRMZUt5RGZxbGR0V3lLN2pNb3lfR1Fqd1dlbw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;MINNESOTA — A new COVID-19 variant known as "Stratus" is spreading in the U.S. this summer, and it may come with a surprising new symptom: hoarseness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officially labeled XFG, Stratus has quickly become the third-most dominant strain nationwide and is now driving up case estimates in Minnesota.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Stratus is similar in symptoms and seriousness to other Omicron variants, but experts say hoarseness may be a unique feature of this version.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/cfa-modeling-and-forecasting/rt-estimates/index.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;New national data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; shows Stratus accounted for 14 percent of COVID-19 cases in late June. It was first detected in Southeast Asia in January but didn’t appear in U.S. surveillance reports until May.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The World Health Organization classified XFG as a “variant under monitoring” in June.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting a full picture of COVID-19 activity can be difficult given shifting priorities in federal and state health policy. But several key measures help put together a picture of what’s happening in Minnesota.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;CDC: COVID-19 Cases Likely Growing Again In Minnesota&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;As of July 29, the CDC estimates a 91.85 percent probability that COVID-19 is growing in Minnesota.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The state’s epidemic trend is officially classified as growing, with a reproductive rate (Rt) of 1.05, meaning each infection is leading to more than one new case.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Emergency department visits for COVID-19 remain very low, making up just 0.38 percent of total ED visits statewide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;National Picture&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;Projections show infections are growing or likely to grow in 40 states and are unchanged in nine others. The highest rates of transmission are in the South, Mid-Atlantic, Northeast, and Midwest.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The CDC also said COVID viral activity in wastewater remains “low” nationally, though at least 10 states had “high” or “very high” levels as of July 12.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In Minnesota, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nwss/rv/COVID19-national-data.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;wastewater viral activity is currently low, with 25 sites reporting&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Although hoarseness appears to be unique to Stratus, other common symptoms include fever or chills, cough, shortness of breath, sore throat, congestion or runny nose, loss of taste or smell, fatigue, muscle and body aches, headache, nausea or vomiting, and diarrhea.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Health experts say the Stratus variant may be better than others at evading immunity. While vaccine guidance is evolving, the CDC still says COVID-19 vaccination helps protect against severe illness, hospitalization, and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Patch</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 14:26:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxPVTNwRDRYTW1PNENYMl9SWTNvSm1vYzhVby0wNmtIZXF0ZWlYZm1GSlItY1ZFRl9HTTI5clY5bkVsb3p6cVFRMVZuU3ZHcnBVbkhsWW9NQ1NpN2poSlRScC1nZjR5eDdDNVlZY3JYc2xCVm8yUUFXanRsczc2OE53WHA2Q1JfUlNsYWE4dGxvOWIxNXFiOFlV0gG3AUFVX3lxTE5UbEZVT0I5RWtDc0RoZ3ZCQ0ZpN3YwVUVyUzVZM1EzZk5xZVZ4b2pURW1WVWJYaDE3ak5RWTBkXzE3MXVyY1cyanhOOTNJZGRPTGxwc2xkYWxDV0hnWEZQUF96Sjg0MmJ3UmtqWjhTTUVSbEZQRnM0Z1Z6UjRaQktjOXliQkVJa2NrZUZnbGVwTE94b08zdjNuUEZFVzRMZUt5RGZxbGR0V3lLN2pNb3lfR1Fqd1dlbw</guid></item><item><title>纽约市的退伍军人疾病集群导致3人死亡， 70多人患病。它是什么，您如何获得它？ - yahoo.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi_wFBVV95cUxOdnFTRzQ1MGp0OE1tNnBKRWFBVWlkNUw4cDczYVBwWlhCSW90UFduRE4zR19pbFdJZkNGR29zb0MyN3B1UUdaRGxVWmZWX1hROEtTVV9UMzlfQWFrX05IbUEtazNObXdZNGhaYU1XUXVzVkJVbTgwZ0tWUkhtVDdGM1VNNmVCTjRvSWtPZVZfeE5YbVF0Y19TRThtV2FCODNXV0hFUkwybzhWUFFwUUhfYXBwZ3h3RFV0eS1VX2wwOXNMbU5vZ3dCRDhZTVFrZkU2aXhJUHp2WkswQ1pLVWdzUEhYOV9OWTFqdjlkY0tmMldGcUZaNTVDUGtHSXpWajg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Three people have died and over 70 people have been sickened by Legionnaires’ disease amid a cluster discovered in central Harlem in New York City, according to an update from &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:1;pos:1" href="https://www.nyc.gov/site/doh/health/health-topics/legionnaires-disease.page" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:health officials Wednesday;cpos:1;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;health officials Wednesday&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The disease was initially detected on July 25. Since then, the New York City Department of Health has been investigating the cluster and has sampled all cooling towers within the affected area, which help regulate a building’s temperature. Eleven cooling towers tested positive for the bacteria that cause Legionnaires’ disease. The remediation of the 11 towers required by the health department has been completed, according to a &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:2;pos:1" href="https://www.nyc.gov/site/doh/about/press/pr2025/nyc-health-provides-second-legionnaires-cluster-update.page" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Monday update;cpos:2;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Monday update&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The following ZIP codes and bordering communities have been affected in Harlem: 10027, 10030, 10035, 10037 and 10039.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Anyone in these ZIP codes with flu-like symptoms should contact a health care provider as soon as possible,"&lt;a data-i13n="cpos:3;pos:1" href="https://www.nyc.gov/site/doh/about/press/pr2025/nyc-health-provides-second-legionnaires-cluster-update.page" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:said acting health commissioner;cpos:3;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; said acting health commissioner&lt;/a&gt; Dr. Michelle Morse. "Legionnaires’ disease can be effectively treated if diagnosed early, but New Yorkers at higher risk, like adults aged 50 and older and those who smoke or have chronic lung conditions, should be especially mindful of their symptoms and seek care as soon as symptoms begin."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="what-is-legionnaires-disease"&gt;What is Legionnaires’ disease?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It’s a serious type of pneumonia, a lung infection, that is caused by Legionella bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;People can become sick from inhaling water vapor that’s contaminated with Legionella bacteria. Less commonly, a person can get sick when water contaminated with the bacteria accidentally enters the lungs by aspiration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="how-does-it-spread"&gt;How does it spread?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In general, Legionnaires’ is not transmitted from person to person. Legionella can grow and spread in human-made water systems like showerheads and sink faucets, hot tubs, decorative fountains, complex and large plumbing systems and cooling towers, according to the &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:4;pos:1" href="https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/causes/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Centers for Disease Control and Prevention;cpos:4;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There are also factors that make it easier for Legionella to grow and survive in water, including:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Biofilm, which is slime that enables germs to grow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Temperatures from 77 degrees to 113 degrees Fahrenheit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Not having enough disinfectant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Slow or no water movement (&lt;a data-i13n="cpos:5;pos:1" href="https://www.cdc.gov/drinking-water/prevention/preventing-waterborne-germs-at-home.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read more from the CDC;cpos:5;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Read more from the CDC&lt;/a&gt; about how to prevent waterborne germs while away from your home.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="what-are-the-symptoms-of-legionnaires-disease"&gt;What are the symptoms of Legionnaires’ disease?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Symptoms usually appear in a person within two to 14 days after they’ve been exposed to the bacteria, the CDC says. Symptoms can be similar to other types of pneumonia, such as:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Other symptoms can include confusion, diarrhea or nausea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="who-is-at-risk-of-getting-sick"&gt;Who is at risk of getting sick?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Most healthy people exposed to Legionella don’t become ill, according to the CDC’s website. However, the following people are at increased risk of getting sick from the bacteria:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;People 50 years and older&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Current or former smokers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;People with specific health issues or conditions, like cancer, chronic lung disease, diabetes, kidney failure, liver failure and a weak immune system&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="diagnosis-and-treatment"&gt;Diagnosis and treatment&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A chest x-ray can confirm if a person has pneumonia. But additional tests are needed to confirm if Legionella bacteria is the cause behind it, such as a urine test, or a lab test involving a sample from phlegm (sputum) or lung lavage (lung washing), &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:6;pos:1" href="https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/about/index.html#cdc_disease_basics_prevention-prevention" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:according to the CDC;cpos:6;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;according to the CDC&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The disease is treatable with antibiotics, but hospital care is often needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>yahoo.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:54:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_wFBVV95cUxOdnFTRzQ1MGp0OE1tNnBKRWFBVWlkNUw4cDczYVBwWlhCSW90UFduRE4zR19pbFdJZkNGR29zb0MyN3B1UUdaRGxVWmZWX1hROEtTVV9UMzlfQWFrX05IbUEtazNObXdZNGhaYU1XUXVzVkJVbTgwZ0tWUkhtVDdGM1VNNmVCTjRvSWtPZVZfeE5YbVF0Y19TRThtV2FCODNXV0hFUkwybzhWUFFwUUhfYXBwZ3h3RFV0eS1VX2wwOXNMbU5vZ3dCRDhZTVFrZkU2aXhJUHp2WkswQ1pLVWdzUEhYOV9OWTFqdjlkY0tmMldGcUZaNTVDUGtHSXpWajg</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr.大修疫苗损伤计划的誓言呼应了反疫苗运动的不满-美联社新闻</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitwFBVV95cUxQRFpSWGltbUhTUjRmeU96YW5jdy1kUWpTUElGSnNXZll5Tl9xSEpDSjVyWURQdjdCeW1veWstSlRiTHVzYnV4UjN6QndWVjUydWpJV3M3WmY2Y0s3bFBlUHJRM2o5SS1OOEg0R0FQTGxIcnJWZkRHOEhrRGpBVng1eHU0RTEyMS1wQktlVzlHcmNDVTRGZHQ1cmhpRWpCRTZUZWotYjFjSkpZaVVEbW9DRlBxajBqZ00?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxQRFpSWGltbUhTUjRmeU96YW5jdy1kUWpTUElGSnNXZll5Tl9xSEpDSjVyWURQdjdCeW1veWstSlRiTHVzYnV4UjN6QndWVjUydWpJV3M3WmY2Y0s3bFBlUHJRM2o5SS1OOEg0R0FQTGxIcnJWZkRHOEhrRGpBVng1eHU0RTEyMS1wQktlVzlHcmNDVTRGZHQ1cmhpRWpCRTZUZWotYjFjSkpZaVVEbW9DRlBxajBqZ00</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现世界上最常见癌症之一的病毒原因- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipgFBVV95cUxOcExrdDUwRXEtMnlBTGgtTlBhVnI5RlV2ZGdvRGl4RGI3NUw5dDBGYlNKM29vWS0tNXdaNzlKcHl6c3B1ajFvLWNwcWNoWmYxanRwUWVFMEtuNFBvSU4zYVNCaEZJV0tVcEVJUTZsMTc5Zi03SkdxMnVaY1AzZGZNM3RWWGJsUEd0eHVBQU1FcHZSY3JuRDQ1YTVjZ2FCR2lpMWhHQnVB?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A common type of &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Human_papillomavirus_infection"&gt;human papillomavirus&lt;/a&gt; (HPV) could be more dangerous than we thought. The  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="169949" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;virus&lt;/a&gt;, known as beta-HPV, was thought in rare cases to contribute to skin  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="169949" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; by worsening UV damage, but a new study suggests it can actually hijack the body's cells to directly drive cancer growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These fresh conclusions came from a study of a 34-year-old woman who sought medical help for &lt;a href="https://dermnetnz.org/topics/cutaneous-squamous-cell-carcinoma"&gt;cutaneous squamous cell carcinoma&lt;/a&gt; (cSCC) on her forehead. Her tumors were repeatedly growing back, even after immunotherapy and surgeries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/modified-herpes-virus-found-to-shrink-deadly-skin-cancers-in-clinical-trial"&gt;Modified Herpes Virus Found to Shrink Deadly Skin Cancers in Clinical Trial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A closer genetic analysis revealed something surprising: the beta-HPV had actually integrated itself into the DNA of the woman's tumor, where it was producing viral proteins that helped the cancer thrive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before now, beta-HPV had never been found to integrate into cellular DNA, let alone actively maintain a cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It suggests that there may be more people out there with aggressive forms of cSCC who have an underlying immune defect and could benefit from treatments targeting the immune system," &lt;a href="https://www.nih.gov/news-events/news-releases/beta-hpv-can-directly-cause-skin-cancer-immunocompromised-people"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; immunologist Andrea Lisco from the US National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases (NIAID).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woman who was the subject of this study had an inherited immune disorder, one which prevented her &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/T_cell"&gt;T cells&lt;/a&gt; from attacking HPV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_169952" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-169952" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/ProteinChart.jpg" alt="ZAP70 proteins" class="wp-image-169952 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/ProteinChart.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/ProteinChart-600x349.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-169952" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Issues with the ZAP70 protein were key to the research. (Ye et al., &lt;em&gt;NEJM&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;While tests revealed that the woman's immune system could still repair DNA damage from UV radiation – the typical cause of cSCC – the impairment of her T cells meant the beta-HPV could invade her skin cells and trigger the formation of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;T&lt;span&gt;he immunocompromised woman was also being treated for other HPV-related illnesses, including warts on the skin and in the mouth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once the cause of her condition was discovered, the patient received a bone marrow &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/publications/dictionaries/cancer-terms/def/stem-cell-transplant"&gt;stem cell transplant&lt;/a&gt;, to replace her dysfunctional T cells with healthy ones. This cleared up the aggressive skin cancer and her other HPV-caused issues, none of which returned during a three-year follow-up period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This discovery and successful outcome would not have been possible without the combined expertise of virologists, immunologists, oncologists and transplant specialists, all working under the same roof," &lt;a href="https://www.nih.gov/news-events/news-releases/beta-hpv-can-directly-cause-skin-cancer-immunocompromised-people"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Lisco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study by no means minimizes &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/sunlight-can-still-damage-skin-through-a-closed-window-heres-how"&gt;the role of UV radiation&lt;/a&gt; as a cause of skin cancer, but shows that there are other factors at work too. In rare cases like this, normally benign &lt;span&gt;viruses&lt;/span&gt; can have devastating effects in people with weakened immune systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That emphasizes the need for targeted, personalized &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/these-3-strategies-can-improve-outcomes-for-cancer-patients"&gt;cancer treatments&lt;/a&gt; that may well be more effective than conventional and generic approaches. It's likely that the woman involved in this study is far from the only one with this set of conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reason to be hopeful could come from progress against a related disease. Alpha-HPV is known as the cause of many cervical and throat cancers, and widespread vaccination against the virus has resulted in a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/young-american-deaths-from-cervical-cancer-fall-sharply-after-hpv-vaccine"&gt;drastic drop&lt;/a&gt; in deaths from those cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While a single, universal cure for cancer remains elusive, we are continuing to see steadily improving &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/experimental-drug-helped-cancer-patients-live-40-longer-in-clinical-trial"&gt;survival and recovery rates&lt;/a&gt; across many cancer types, including cSCC – something this new research should also help with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This discovery could completely change how we think about the development, and consequently the treatment, of cSCC in people who have a health condition that compromises immune function," &lt;a href="https://www.nih.gov/news-events/news-releases/beta-hpv-can-directly-cause-skin-cancer-immunocompromised-people"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Lisco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1056/NEJMoa2502114"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The New England Journal of Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:49:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxOcExrdDUwRXEtMnlBTGgtTlBhVnI5RlV2ZGdvRGl4RGI3NUw5dDBGYlNKM29vWS0tNXdaNzlKcHl6c3B1ajFvLWNwcWNoWmYxanRwUWVFMEtuNFBvSU4zYVNCaEZJV0tVcEVJUTZsMTc5Zi03SkdxMnVaY1AzZGZNM3RWWGJsUEd0eHVBQU1FcHZSY3JuRDQ1YTVjZ2FCR2lpMWhHQnVB</guid></item><item><title>80岁的“超级老人”的大脑就像50岁的人一样运作。原因如下- CNN</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMie0FVX3lxTE5HaUJyeTNZVmpzcmsxamNmaXpTY1BpYi1tRGFHVFYyckk5X29Md3cwQlc4SUNyZFVFNFNWaFpSRmdmYk5ZcmVpd2pwQ25DNFpyeFhuS1VuemNsMzU4dEZlNG05emNHaXNlalNqbWxEVDJCY2FlSXVwS2tzQdIBgAFBVV95cUxNQUFUTTJPaERRdGhXT2dWb1p2MnFSazVrUzRrRm9YLVZoTWhUeXhaQm1uTzdxVlZ2NndVajl3RjFtZTBxcWpnczBhZEFQRGVrLVVIOF9aUTlXRGNmelJreGlab3Ryc3V6WGZnaS1sMU1QTC1jU3hGRE9pZDRLUVZNVg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/action-bar/instances/cme0upk60003j27p7boogbnsx@published" data-label-id-prefix="action-bar-start-of-article" class="action-bar" data-dynamic-breakpoint-placement='{"extraLarge":{"placement":".layout-article-elevate__left"}}' data-expand-conditions='{"follow":{"extraLarge":{"alwaysExpand":true}},"shareOptions":{"large":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"medium":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"extraLarge":{"withAction":"follow","maxNumOfActions":2}}}'&gt;
    &lt;p class="action-bar__overlay"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet" tabindex="-1"&gt;
        
            
            &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet--action" data-title="share options"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/social-share/instances/cme0upk60003m27p7d6yfevnr@published" class="social-share_labelled-list"&gt;
    &lt;div class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links vossi-social-share_labelled-list" data-type="share-links"&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.facebook.com/dialog/share?app_id=80401312489&amp;amp;href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F08%2F07%2Fhealth%2Fsuperager-brain-research-wellness&amp;amp;display=popup" data-type="facebook" aria-label="share with facebook" title="Share with Facebook"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-facebook-circle" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.04139 1.33301C11.7458 1.33301 14.7488 4.33601 14.7488 8.04042C14.7488 11.3884 12.296 14.1632 9.08943 14.6663V9.97928H10.6523L10.9497 8.04042H9.08943V6.78225C9.08943 6.25182 9.34934 5.73475 10.1825 5.73475H11.0283V4.08409C11.0283 4.08409 10.2607 3.95309 9.52685 3.95309C7.99476 3.95309 6.99336 4.88165 6.99336 6.56269V8.04042H5.29031V9.97928H6.99336V14.6663C3.78677 14.1632 1.33398 11.3882 1.33398 8.04042C1.33398 4.33601 4.33699 1.33301 8.04139 1.33301Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Facebook&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F08%2F07%2Fhealth%2Fsuperager-brain-research-wellness" data-type="x" aria-label="share with x" title="Share with X"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-x-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.99386 8.11503L0 0.666992H4.74756L8.44753 5.27039L12.4004 0.687719H15.0151L9.71175 6.84331L16 14.667H11.2666L7.2603 9.6887L2.98317 14.6532H0.354296L5.99386 8.11503ZM11.9565 13.287L2.91105 2.04698H4.0571L13.0912 13.287H11.9565Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Tweet&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;a class="social-share_labelled-list__share" href="mailto:?subject=CNN%20content%20share&amp;amp;body=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A%0Ahttps%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F08%2F07%2Fhealth%2Fsuperager-brain-research-wellness" data-type="email" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="share with email" title="Share with email"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-email-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 24 24" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M2 6C2 4.89543 2.89543 4 4 4H20C21.1046 4 22 4.89543 22 6V18C22 19.1046 21.1046 20 20 20H4C2.89543 20 2 19.1046 2 18V6ZM4 6H20V9.11604L12 11.9396L4 9.11604V6ZM4 11.237V18H20V11.237L12.3328 13.943C12.1174 14.019 11.8825 14.019 11.6672 13.943L4 11.237Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Email&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/07/health/superager-brain-research-wellness" data-type="copy" aria-label="copy link to clipboard" title="Copy link to clipboard"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-hyperlink" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.64373 10.3574C5.38338 10.0971 5.38338 9.67496 5.64373 9.41461L9.88637 5.17197C10.1467 4.91162 10.5688 4.91162 10.8292 5.17197C11.0895 5.43232 11.0895 5.85443 10.8292 6.11478L6.58654 10.3574C6.32619 10.6178 5.90408 10.6178 5.64373 10.3574Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M4.22952 8.94321L5.64373 7.52899C5.90408 7.26865 5.90408 6.84654 5.64373 6.58619C5.38338 6.32584 4.96127 6.32584 4.70092 6.58619L3.28671 8.0004C1.98496 9.30215 1.98496 11.4127 3.28671 12.7144C4.58846 14.0162 6.69901 14.0162 8.00075 12.7144L9.41497 11.3002C9.67532 11.0399 9.67532 10.6178 9.41497 10.3574C9.15462 10.0971 8.73251 10.0971 8.47216 10.3574L7.05795 11.7716C6.2769 12.5527 5.01057 12.5527 4.22952 11.7716C3.44847 10.9906 3.44847 9.72426 4.22952 8.94321Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.94356 4.22916L7.52935 5.64338C7.269 5.90373 6.84689 5.90373 6.58654 5.64338C6.32619 5.38303 6.32619 4.96092 6.58654 4.70057L8.00075 3.28635C9.3025 1.98461 11.4131 1.98461 12.7148 3.28635C14.0165 4.5881 14.0165 6.69865 12.7148 8.0004L11.3006 9.41461C11.0402 9.67496 10.6181 9.67496 10.3578 9.41461C10.0974 9.15426 10.0974 8.73215 10.3578 8.4718L11.772 7.05759C12.553 6.27654 12.553 5.01021 11.772 4.22916C10.9909 3.44812 9.72461 3.44811 8.94356 4.22916Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Link&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__open" data-type="open" aria-label="open social share" title="Open social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-share-os" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19 12c.394 0 .714.32.714.714v8.572c0 .394-.32.714-.714.714H4.714A.715.715 0 014 21.286v-8.572a.715.715 0 011.429 0v7.857h12.857v-7.857c0-.394.32-.714.714-.714zm-7.664-9.79a.73.73 0 011.024 0l.076.075 4.916 4.854c.183.18.27.449.188.69a.734.734 0 01-1.216.314L12.57 4.5v11.786c0 .357-.357.714-.714.714s-.714-.359-.714-.714V4.5L7.372 8.143a.73.73 0 01-1.102-.091c-.21-.289-.149-.694.106-.946l4.884-4.821z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__close" data-type="close" aria-label="close social share" title="Close social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-close" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19.787 18.758l-6.792-6.781 6.746-6.735a.728.728 0 00-1.028-1.03l-6.747 6.737-6.711-6.7a.728.728 0 00-1.028 1.03l6.71 6.698-6.723 6.712a.727.727 0 101.027 1.03l6.725-6.714 6.793 6.782a.725.725 0 001.028 0 .727.727 0 000-1.03"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0upk60003l27p75co374om@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The human brain shrinks as it ages, affecting the ability to remember — it’s part of life. Yet there are a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2022/11/26/health/superager-secrets-good-memory-wellness"&gt;lucky few, called “SuperAgers,”&lt;/a&gt; who possess a brain that fights back. For these people, memories stay as sharp as they were 30 or more years in the past.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480000p3b6nuknd13oe@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Carol Siegler, who lives in the Chicago suburb of Palatine, is a SuperAger. At 82, she won the American Crossword Puzzle Tournament for her age group, which she said she entered “as a gag.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480000q3b6npajp63fm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I’ve auditioned twice for ‘Jeopardy!’ and did well enough on it to be invited to the live auditions. Then Covid hit,” Siegler told me in 2022, when she was 85.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480000r3b6nm406t2k0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Today, Siegler is still going strong, well on her way to her 90th birthday, said Tamar Gefen, an associate professor of psychiatry and behavioral sciences at the Mesulam Institute for Cognitive Neurology and Alzheimer’s Disease at Northwestern University in Chicago.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480000s3b6nnros55as@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Gefen conducts research at &lt;a href="https://www.brain.northwestern.edu/join/SuperAging.html" target="_blank"&gt;Northwestern’s SuperAging Program&lt;/a&gt;, which is currently studying 113 SuperAgers. Over the past 25 years, however, 80 SuperAgers have donated their brain tissue to the program, which has led to some fascinating discoveries.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480000t3b6n0i6anhh4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            CNN spoke to Gefen about those decades of work. She is a coauthor of a new analysis of the research that was published Thursday in &lt;a href="https://alz-journals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/alz.70312" target="_blank"&gt;Alzheimer’s &amp;amp; Dementia&lt;/a&gt;, the journal of the Alzheimer’s Association.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme1az84i00003b6n9l0wtdam@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;em&gt;This interview has been lightly edited and condensed for clarity. &lt;/em&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480000u3b6nr2n00ao8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;CNN: How do you define a SuperAger, and what have you found out about their behavior over the years?&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480000v3b6ndn91795l@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Tamar Gefen:&lt;/strong&gt; To be a SuperAger in our program at Northwestern, a person must be over 80 and undergo extensive cognitive testing. Acceptance in the study only occurs if the person’s episodic memory — the ability to recall everyday events and past personal history — is as good or better than cognitively normal people in their 50s and 60s.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480000w3b6n7yh00u99@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            We have screened close to 2,000 individuals who think they may be a SuperAger and less than 10% meet the criteria. Over the past 25 years, we have studied about 300 SuperAgers — a number of whom have donated their brain for research.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480000x3b6nkqnw5j7a@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            One key trait of SuperAgers is that they seem to be highly social people. They value connection and are often active in their communities. This is interesting because we know isolation is a risk factor for developing  dementia, and so staying socially active is a known protective feature.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480000y3b6nity3vqbs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Another common thread in all SuperAgers is a sense of autonomy, freedom and independence. They’re making decisions and living their lives the way that they want to live.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480000z3b6nt099y0o8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            I feel very strongly that successful aging is not just about sociability. If a person feels trapped, tethered or burdened, especially in a vulnerable state like poor health or older age, I think it can encroach on their entire psychosocial being.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb48000103b6nj9f17ofq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But as far as healthy behaviors, SuperAgers run the gamut. We have SuperAgers with heart disease, diabetes, who aren’t physically active, who don’t eat any better than their similar age peers.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb48000113b6nkmeou58e@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There is one SuperAger who drinks four beers every night. He laughs and says, “Maybe it’s done me wrong, but I’ll never know.” He doesn’t have an identical twin to compare his behavior to, so would he have lived to 108 instead of 98? We don’t know.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb48000123b6n5equlk0t@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;CNN: Many of your most intriguing discoveries have come from studying donor brain tissue. What have you discovered about the memory center of the SuperAger brain?&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb48000133b6nqtv2k92x@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Gefen: &lt;/strong&gt; Our &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25632151/" target="_blank"&gt;studies have shown&lt;/a&gt; that an area of the brain that is responsible for attention, motivation, and cognitive engagement — known as the cingulate cortex — is thicker in SuperAgers, even compared with those of people in their 50s and 60s.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb48000143b6nk1hivyjv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In the hippocampus, the memory center of the brain, we found SuperAgers have three times fewer tau tangles when compared to their “normal” peers. Abnormal formations of tau proteins are one of the key signs of Alzheimer’s.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb48000153b6ncaivddou@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In Alzheimer’s disease, tau also targets the neurons of the primary neurons of the cholinergic system — which is responsible for sustaining our attention in daily life. But that doesn’t happen in the brain of a SuperAger. Therefore, the cholinergic system appears to be stronger, and likely more plastic and flexible for reasons that we’re not sure about.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb48000163b6ngx94ktu7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            That’s interesting, because I see SuperAgers as focused. They can pay close attention, engage and actively listen. How else could they recall 13 out of 15 random words after 30 minutes?  I picture them engraving the words on their cortex with a chisel.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb48000173b6ng7h24yn0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            SuperAger brains also have bigger, healthier cells in the entorhinal cortex, an area essential for memory and learning, that has direct connections to the hippocampus. The entorhinal cortex, by the way, is one of the first areas of the brain to get hit by Alzheimer’s disease.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb48000183b6nkfsm8uvh@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/36180225/" target="_blank"&gt;another study&lt;/a&gt; we examined every layer of cells within the entorhinal cortex of SuperAgers, and we painstakingly measured the size of the neurons. We found that in layer two, which is the layer that is most important for information transmission, SuperAgers had humongous, plump, intact, beautiful, gigantic entorhinal cortex neurons.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb48000193b6n60s2h3i0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It was an incredible finding, because their entorhinal neurons were even larger than those in individuals who are much younger, some even in their 30s. That told us there is a structural integrity component at play — like the architecture, the bones, the skeleton of the neuron itself is sturdier.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480001a3b6npz5sjyzv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            We’re expanding the studies of these neurons to understand their biochemical signatures, determine what makes them special, and see if these signatures are found in other types of neurons in the brain of SuperAgers. Are these same neurons particularly vulnerable in those with Alzheimer’s disease, and if so, how and why?
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480001b3b6nfkrwktgp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;CNN: What have you learned from your research about how the brain of a SuperAger reacts to injury, disease and stress?&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480001c3b6npbpko3mn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Gefen:&lt;/strong&gt; We’re looking at the inflammatory system in the brain of SuperAgers, with the goal of understanding how the immune cells in their brain respond to disease and adapt to stress. Inflammation, once it crosses a certain threshold, is a major component of cell loss in Alzheimer’s disease and nearly all other neurodegenerative diseases.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480001d3b6nhwsg7k20@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Compared with the brain of same-age peers, SuperAgers have fewer activated microglia, the resident immune cells of the brain, in their white matter. White matter is the brain’s super highway, transporting information from one part of the brain to another.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480001e3b6np130em0k@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Here’s how it works: Microglia are activated because there is some kind of antigen or disease, typically something destructive in the brain. In some cases, however, microglia and other immune cells become hyperactive and go into overdrive, thus causing inflammation and possible damage.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480001f3b6nq6k6dvvv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The brain of a SuperAger, however, has fewer activated microglia. In fact, the levels of microglia&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;were on par with people in their 30s, 40s and 50s. That could mean there is less junk or disease in the brain of a SuperAger so the microglia have no need to be active. Or it could mean microglia are responding efficiently to in clearing out disease or toxins, and because they are more plastic and adaptable, the microglia are able to activate, respond and then calm down.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480001h3b6ncy0f936m@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            All of this is fascinating —  it may be that at the cellular level, the immune system of a SuperAger brain could be stronger or more adaptive, much like the layers of cells we found in the entorhinal cortex.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480001i3b6nn8f8ghci@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;CNN: Whether or not you were born with the right genes to protect your brain sounds like the luck of the draw. What does that mean for the future?&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vbr9n001p3b6nk9lpu5y5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Gefen: &lt;/strong&gt;Genetics are tricky. It’s not just whether you have a gene or not, it about how your internal and external environment works together to influence how a gene is “turned on,” or expressed — some may be more highly expressed, some will have lower expression. This is the epigenetic part of the puzzle.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480001k3b6nji89ndop@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There is a list of candidate genes that we are starting to study very carefully, these are genes that also have a role in aspects of longevity, senescence, cell repair and cognitive reserve to name a few.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480001l3b6no1wnwt2s@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            I’m excited about that, not only for the genetics that are heritable from parents, but also genetics at the cell level, that enable each neuron or immune cell to carry out its respective job within the brain.  With the technology that’s advancing so rapidly, I’m certain we’re going to get to a point where prevention or modification at the genetic level will be part of the playbook.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480001m3b6nkwax497k@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Clearly, there is not a one target resolution for Alzheimer’s disease. I know we all want that one easy fix but it’s just simply not going to happen.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0vb480001n3b6nt0s6u5oa@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It’s going to take many teams and many specialists to come together and create a kind of personalized cocktail for prevention or treatment. I think it’s possible, but it’s going to take time.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:49:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE5HaUJyeTNZVmpzcmsxamNmaXpTY1BpYi1tRGFHVFYyckk5X29Md3cwQlc4SUNyZFVFNFNWaFpSRmdmYk5ZcmVpd2pwQ25DNFpyeFhuS1VuemNsMzU4dEZlNG05emNHaXNlalNqbWxEVDJCY2FlSXVwS2tzQdIBgAFBVV95cUxNQUFUTTJPaERRdGhXT2dWb1p2MnFSazVrUzRrRm9YLVZoTWhUeXhaQm1uTzdxVlZ2NndVajl3RjFtZTBxcWpnczBhZEFQRGVrLVVIOF9aUTlXRGNmelJreGlab3Ryc3V6WGZnaS1sMU1QTC1jU3hGRE9pZDRLUVZNVg</guid></item><item><title>科学对褪黑激素、镁和其他睡眠补充剂的评价--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikwFBVV95cUxPQjRmRlZOVUtjMk5GYjMweDVyVGlqX0JsbklvMlFHWGJmMWtFMlJnR3pYOG1tZXZZcHEyd0dhQjFPZnRnVWdMa0pvdGdFQUl0QmVoaGw4QW01cGE1YkJsQ1BRdmZ5ajJYblFqWTgzZ29aTGtWN3BhSk9CeDNXYmxHUzY5WkhMWVZTeTcxX1hrZm9UOTg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="44TCVYEFR5HCTNGDWGI744PUZE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Do you struggle to fall asleep at night, or find yourself routinely waking up at 3 a.m.?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="PHNZZ3F5PNA6HEGSDSTYY4T3NE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Many people experience bouts of insomnia at some point in their lives, often due to anxiety. When these sleep issues persist for several months or longer, it’s usually a good idea to visit a doctor to see if you have an underlying condition, like depression, restless legs syndrome or sleep apnea, that requires medical treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="EZC65YERJZGEBA5Y4KKNVG2VNE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But for occasional periods of insomnia that leave you feeling bleary-eyed, experts say there may be some dietary supplements and even foods that can help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="73D67XOZ2RC6VC4VA5K6YASBGQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;It’s important to recognize that no dietary supplement is going to radically improve your sleep. Supplements shouldn’t be viewed as a long-term solution. And almost all supplements carry the risk of side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VH4NAHLAHJG5JGKK7AMLTA5S3U" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But some may produce modest benefits, such as helping you fall asleep slightly faster at night, and carry minimal side effects when taken in smaller doses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BSKIBFFHZ5B4HB5L2APFMWQZYU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;We spoke to sleep and nutrition experts and reviewed dozens of studies to find out what the science says about five popular supplements. Here’s what you need to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="V3B3IDTR6ZA2XL3V4CDIPZRAJM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Melatonin is one of the most popular sleep supplements, and for good reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CGDQYINH6NALXCWWYTSYC65WCM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A hormone that’s secreted in the pineal gland of your brain, melatonin regulates your sleep-wake cycle by synchronizing your body’s internal clock with the outside world. It’s produced primarily in the evening. But melatonin isn’t going to quickly send you off to sleep like a fast-acting sleeping pill. Instead, it promotes sleepiness by signaling to your body that it’s nighttime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DEP7S23IINHHNPMFQMDMMD7QVE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;For that reason, melatonin supplements are most helpful for people with sleep timing problems, said Phyllis C. Zee, the medical director of the Center for Circadian and Sleep Medicine at the Northwestern University Feinberg School of Medicine. That includes people with jet lag, shift workers who work late at night or early in the morning, and people who routinely struggle to fall asleep until it’s extremely late at night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="EZVVEH3CI5FE3N6YKGUB2AUI4E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;For those people, taking a melatonin supplement in the evening can set their biological clocks earlier, helping them fall asleep and wake up earlier, Zee said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BDJNMJ65LFD67BSYADGSTK4SEE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Melatonin supplements may also benefit older adults, because melatonin levels naturally decline with age, as well as postmenopausal women, said Fariha Abbasi-Feinberg, a sleep medicine specialist and spokeswoman for the American Academy of Sleep Medicine. “I think some people are more sensitive to it and can get some improvements in their sleep from it,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="PFN3OM4T6NELHEPECSKNJG7NUE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Many studies have examined whether melatonin can alleviate&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;insomnia, and the data is mostly mixed, Abbasi-Feinberg said. &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4273450/" target="_blank"&gt;Some studies&lt;/a&gt; have found that it can help people fall asleep faster and sleep more soundly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="G3WL72KPS5ARPFUHW4XKUQHSXA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But the American Academy of Sleep Medicine &lt;a href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/health/melatonin-what-you-need-to-know" target="_blank"&gt;says that&lt;/a&gt; there “isn’t enough strong evidence on the effectiveness or safety of melatonin supplementation for chronic insomnia” to recommend its use. If you find that you’re  having trouble falling asleep or staying asleep at least three times a week for three months or longer — the criteria for chronic insomnia — then you should visit a doctor or a sleep specialist, Zee said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ACPRGLSPKFCMXPGKZ4RT3XJT2Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;If you are going to try melatonin for an occasional sleep timing problem, it’s best that you use a low dose, around half a milligram to three milligrams, said Zee at Northwestern. You also have to get the timing right: Melatonin should be taken about two hours before bedtime for it to be most effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YSVXKGSAZ5BJTGCBB5UFKRG6CE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/06/25/melatonin-children-sleep-fda-study/" target="_blank"&gt;Some studies&lt;/a&gt; have shown that several melatonin products are &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/04/25/melatonin-gummies-dose-safety/" target="_blank"&gt;“inaccurately labeled,”&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/27855744/" target="_blank"&gt;several containing&lt;/a&gt; more melatonin than advertised. When shopping for melatonin, check for third-party certifications, which mean the products were independently vetted for purity and potency. Look for the black and yellow &lt;a href="https://quality-supplements.org/usp_verified_products" target="_blank"&gt;“USP Verified”&lt;/a&gt; logo or the blue and white &lt;a href="https://www.nsfsport.com/certified-products/" target="_blank"&gt;“NSF” logo&lt;/a&gt;. You can also go to each group’s website to look up products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2ZZ5YGPLQNC2NDJBF2JKELNHCE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;(The FDA &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/food/information-consumers-using-dietary-supplements/questions-and-answers-dietary-supplements" target="_blank"&gt;doesn’t approve or regulate supplements&lt;/a&gt; the way it does prescription drugs.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="K4KUXNXDIJDZ3IMLUIG3ZDG5IU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Magnesium plays an important role in good sleep. It promotes relaxation, calms the nervous system and helps produce melatonin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="OZVPQ3A4E5GLFPFYHMFVS6K45U" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/sleep/article/45/4/zsab276/6432454" target="_blank"&gt;Studies have linked&lt;/a&gt; inadequate magnesium consumption to shorter and poorer quality sleep. Scientists have also found &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/sleep/article/45/4/zsab276/6432454" target="_blank"&gt;in animal studies&lt;/a&gt; that magnesium deficiencies lead to reductions in melatonin levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JDGL2NKZSRG5RIMWKIQYFYCCHU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Magnesium supplements are widely touted as a sleep aid, and some studies have found that it can be helpful for people experiencing insomnia. But the studies showing benefits have been mostly small and not very conclusive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2BBBCE2GCBCULBZ4K75473ONYE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In one &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8053283/" target="_blank"&gt;systematic review and meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; published in 2021, scientists looked at three clinical trials involving 151 older adults with insomnia that compared magnesium supplements to placebo. It found that people assigned to take magnesium fell asleep about 18 minutes faster at night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XWCXOHZCVZC4VLIJD3FUU3U7EI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The researchers cautioned that more rigorous studies were needed. But given that magnesium is “very cheap and widely available,” they added, they could find no evidence discouraging its use for insomnia in older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="5SYMPHLP5RGBZLMCS6TALDNBKE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;While most people get plenty of magnesium from their diets, Abbasi-Feinberg said, she does occasionally recommend a low dose to people who routinely struggle to fall asleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="76O3OT62K5FLXGGVC3DPG2VGAY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“I’ll tell them to start with 100 or 200 milligrams of magnesium and see if that makes a difference,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GLJ3DRHUEVDBTOQTMW5B4VHKDA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;She stressed that people should stick to a low dose because magnesium can have side effects, including nausea, vomiting and diarrhea. These side effects typically occur with doses above 350 milligrams. “It’s important to note that more is not better,” said Zee at Northwestern. “Check with your doctor and let them know that you’re taking magnesium and the dose to avoid possible interactions with other medications or medical conditions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TUDCANEELVAYFIKJAVRUI32LCA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A healthy gut may promote healthy sleep. &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6779243/" target="_blank"&gt;Studies have found&lt;/a&gt; that higher levels of gut microbiome diversity — generally considered a sign of a healthy gut — are associated with longer, better sleep and fewer nighttime awakenings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GAGKH7I3I5HXXN3JGZKEXLTZJQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Many hormones and metabolites that are produced by our gut microbes act directly on the brain to influence sleep regulation, including neurotransmitters like serotonin, said Chris Damman, a gastroenterologist at the Digestive Health Center at the University of Washington Medical Center and the author of &lt;a href="https://gutbites.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Gut Bites MD&lt;/a&gt;, a blog on gut health and nutrition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4VLX6SSZGZCJ3NUEYMPOIGGNAI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;That’s one reason Abbasi-Feinberg encourages her patients to consume probiotics, which are live bacteria and other microorganisms that confer health benefits. But probiotic supplements — which are available in capsules, gummies, powders and pills&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;—&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;can have some downsides. For one, they tend to contain concentrated doses of just a few strains of bacteria. &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/03/28/probiotics-supplements-gut-health-microbiome/" target="_blank"&gt;Studies have shown&lt;/a&gt; that taking them may actually reduce the microbial diversity in your gut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="PS25EFQFUBE4JIQGQXFNE4ARCM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Instead, Abbasi-Feinberg recommends that you get probiotics from fermented foods, like plain yogurt, kefir, kimchi, sauerkraut and tempeh. These fermented foods typically contain not only probiotics (the live microbes) but also prebiotics (the fiber the microbes eat) and postbiotics (the vitamins and nutrients they produce).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DVCURU7VPVHM7NUMXSZPPIUTAM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;One &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/1602898" target="_blank"&gt;clinical trial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;involving 29 people found that older adults who drank a little more than a half cup of fermented milk every day for three weeks fell asleep more quickly at night and had fewer nighttime awakenings compared to when they drank a placebo. Several studies have shown that fermented foods also have other health benefits, including &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/07/04/probiotics-prebiotics-postbiotics-microbiome/" target="_blank"&gt;reducing inflammation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ISA62BORHFDOLJ6WA7QL7U5DC4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Abbasi-Feinberg said she tells patients to add fermented foods to their diets because they have the potential to improve their sleep and have very little downside. “If there’s no risk involved and the benefit is there, then they’re worth a try,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3EVRDXZNNFBKNOBKD7O3YUIDHU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;It’s well known that vitamin D is essential for building strong bones. But it’s also necessary for good sleep. Vitamin D helps the body convert tryptophan into serotonin, a neurotransmitter that plays an important role in how well and how long you sleep. As &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11082867/" target="_blank"&gt;one recent study&lt;/a&gt; noted, vitamin D receptors have been found in regions of the brain that regulate sleep, suggesting that it plays a direct role in our nightly shut-eye.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ZFMFEQ54MZBZVHCLGIOXQAE5YM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“Vitamin D deficiencies can cause issues with low energy and low mood,” said Abbasi-Feinberg, “and sleep can be affected as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3FEOH4WGTRCCPL4YN3KDYJ2XV4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;There’s &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28475473/" target="_blank"&gt;some evidence&lt;/a&gt; that taking vitamin D can improve sleep. But the data are mixed, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2590142721000094" target="_blank"&gt;not every study&lt;/a&gt; has shown benefits. Also, some of the studies involved taking a single large dose as a shot at weekly or biweekly intervals, rather than a daily pill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="L5NVKIEFJNEAJKHPWPCGS33XZA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Abbasi-Feinberg said she sometimes encounters patients with sleep problems who work from home and rarely get any exposure to morning sunshine. “They roll out of bed and turn their computer on and, boom, they’re at work and they don’t get outside,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ZR3FRL3QHBHR3LBCUHBQO3LMGQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;That can be a problem because exposure to sunshine helps your body produce vitamin D. It also halts production of melatonin and resets your circadian rhythm, which can help you sleep better at night. For that reason, Abbasi-Feinberg often prescribes morning sunshine to her patients — rather than a vitamin D supplement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VMSNTDTULFBBXG54UT2YO7JRTA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“The best way to get vitamin D is to go out into the sunshine,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="list-header-SVSSSC6PQJEWHAD4W3OA64I4H4-42" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;h2 id="SVSSSC6PQJEWHAD4W3OA64I4H4" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="SVSSSC6PQJEWHAD4W3OA64I4H4" data-testid="article-header"&gt;5. Ashwagandha&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="#secondary-nav" class="skip-link sr-only sr-only-focusable black underline brad-md pa-lg mb-xs border-box font-sans-serif font-bold"&gt;Return to menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YGQ7N3WXBJEOVDVLIT6SVTHHYE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;This popular evergreen shrub has been used for centuries in Ayurveda — a traditional medicine system originating in India — for a variety of reasons. Nowadays, it’s commonly recommended as a sleep aid. There’s &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/03/04/should-i-take-ashwagandha-benefits-risks/" target="_blank"&gt;some evidence&lt;/a&gt; that it can help with insomnia. But the data are not conclusive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RQTWO5YA7BHHLMBNJ23FCOXYEM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Advocates of ashwagandha say it’s useful for insomnia because it alleviates stress and anxiety. In a &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0257843" target="_blank"&gt;meta-analysis published in 2021&lt;/a&gt;, scientists analyzed five randomized trials involving 400 people that looked at the effects of ashwagandha on sleep compared to placebo. They found a “small but significant effect” of ashwagandha on overall sleep. People who were assigned to take an ashwagandha supplement daily slept on average about 25 minutes longer each night and had greater improvements in sleep quality compared to people who were given placebo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="N2UDOF6BI5BBVES7PJBMVY6WAE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But the scientists also cautioned that there was limited data on ashwagandha’s potentially serious side effects, and they said that more research was needed to determine whether it was safe for long-term use. (It has been linked to a handful of cases of &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK548536/" target="_blank"&gt;liver toxicity&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="UMG6LVAE3ZHHDDMHCKJGQITQ4U" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Abassi-Feinberg said she doesn’t necessarily discourage people from trying ashwagandha or other Ayurvedic remedies to help them sleep if they’re not known to be harmful. But she feels that there’s not enough strong evidence to recommend them. “I’m not enthusiastic about them because I feel like the data just aren’t there yet,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="OQW3RIPEAZGEBEEEXDFS66UFOM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Experts &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/03/04/should-i-take-ashwagandha-benefits-risks/" target="_blank"&gt;also recommend&lt;/a&gt; that some people avoid ashwagandha altogether for safety reasons, such as women who are pregnant or nursing, people with an autoimmune,&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;liver, or thyroid disorder, and people who are taking sedative medications such as gabapentin or benzodiazepines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HGTIXJI4XFFF3IDH6X7B6VHUW4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Do you have a question about healthy eating? Email &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:EatingLab@washpost.com"&gt;&lt;i&gt;EatingLab@washpost.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; and we may answer your question in a future column.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:34:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxPQjRmRlZOVUtjMk5GYjMweDVyVGlqX0JsbklvMlFHWGJmMWtFMlJnR3pYOG1tZXZZcHEyd0dhQjFPZnRnVWdMa0pvdGdFQUl0QmVoaGw4QW01cGE1YkJsQ1BRdmZ5ajJYblFqWTgzZ29aTGtWN3BhSk9CeDNXYmxHUzY5WkhMWVZTeTcxX1hrZm9UOTg</guid></item><item><title>阿尔茨海默氏症可能始于大脑的边界，科学家发现- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxQTG1zYVNNY1JDaEVNeTB2dUpKTTRxYzZod3lSOGw0VFBiNXhZU2VpdFEtNUpxVnBMNmw1cXJtRW5HQlpkdGR6UGVLcFdIaXdnbTRLbVhaQ1BnUUMtZlFiam5VcHpZU0JxUkl4cmswcE1rRjVvWVZxb3ZScmQtRThnSmh0VUtmdnZ4TWdhaU0zYm9GYzhRYlE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;To find a cure for  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="170418" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease, we need to understand how and where it gets started, and new research suggests we might be looking in the wrong place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists from the US and Germany have linked genetic risk for Alzheimer's and other brain diseases to the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blood%E2%80%93brain_barrier"&gt;blood-brain barrier&lt;/a&gt; – the blood vessels and immune cells that surround and protect the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Alzheimer's is closely associated with abnormal clumps and tangles of proteins &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/we-may-finally-understand-how-the-tangled-proteins-in-dementia-cause-cells-to-die"&gt;damaging neurons&lt;/a&gt; inside the brain, their findings suggest the initial trigger for the disease could be an outside intruder slipping through a compromised brain boundary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/blood-brain-barrier-guardian-shows-promise-against-alzheimers"&gt;Blood-Brain Barrier 'Guardian' Shows Promise Against Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When studying diseases affecting the brain, most research has focused on its resident neurons," &lt;a href="https://gladstone.org/news/blood-vessels-and-immune-cells-drive-risk-alzheimers-and-stroke"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; neuroscientist Andrew Yang, from the Gladstone Institute of Neurological Disease in California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I hope our findings lead to more interest in the cells forming the brain's borders, which might actually take center stage in diseases like Alzheimer's."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous genetics studies found variations in DNA sequences linked with neurological conditions often occur not in genes that code for proteins, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/our-genomes-are-full-of-junk-dna-that-could-be-way-more-important-than-we-realized"&gt;but in sections outside of them&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These flanking sequences often served to fine-tune the expression of nearby genes to help control the cell's activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yang and his colleagues developed a new genetic analysis technology called MultiVINE-seq. This method can isolate &lt;a href="https://www.centenary.org.au/news/vascular-endothelial-cells/"&gt;vascular&lt;/a&gt; and immune cells from brain tissue and measure their gene activity and chromatin accessibility (how 'open' DNA is to being used by the cell).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_170421" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-170421" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/BrainTissue.jpg" alt="Brain tissue" class="wp-image-170421 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/BrainTissue.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/BrainTissue-600x337.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-170421" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The researchers studied brain tissue. (Gladstone Institute)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Putting the tech to work on 30 postmortem brain tissue samples from people with and without neurological disease, the researchers built up a comprehensive, layered picture of which genetic variations were linked to brain conditions such as Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of these &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-discover-deep-brain-genes-linked-to-parkinsons-and-adhd"&gt;genetic variations&lt;/a&gt; were found in cells patrolling the borders of the brain, including &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Endothelium"&gt;endothelial cells&lt;/a&gt; that help manage access to the brain, and immune system T cells. Certain variants suggested inflammatory immune cells could be triggering or accelerating Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Before this, we knew these genetic variants increased disease risk, but we didn't know where or how they acted in the context of brain barrier cell types," &lt;a href="https://gladstone.org/news/blood-vessels-and-immune-cells-drive-risk-alzheimers-and-stroke"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; neuroscientist Madigan Reid, from the Gladstone Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our study shows that many of the variants are actually functioning in blood vessels and immune cells in the brain."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neurodegenerative diseases are complex and affected &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/award-winning-image-reveals-a-hidden-culprit-behind-alzheimers"&gt;by many factors&lt;/a&gt;, so progress in fighting them is slow. However, this latest study gets us another step closer to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/surprise-alzheimers-finding-brains-support-cells-may-be-fueling-disease"&gt;understanding how diseases like Alzheimer's work&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/these-4-distinct-patterns-may-signal-alzheimers-according-to-science"&gt;These 4 Distinct Patterns May Signal Alzheimer's According to Science&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-might-not-actually-be-a-brain-disease-says-expert"&gt;Previous research&lt;/a&gt; has already linked Alzheimer's disease to broader issues with the immune system, not just within the brain. We also know that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-cause-of-alzheimers-might-be-coming-from-within-your-mouth"&gt;other parts of the body&lt;/a&gt; may be involved, via how they message and interact with the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team also found that different genetic risk variants had different effects on the borders of the brain, depending on the disease – another important finding that can teach us more about various diseases, and how to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/sometimes-alzheimers-strikes-early-this-experimental-drug-may-help"&gt;develop treatments&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This work brings the brain's vascular and immune cells into the spotlight," &lt;a href="https://gladstone.org/news/blood-vessels-and-immune-cells-drive-risk-alzheimers-and-stroke"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Yang.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Given their unique location and role in establishing the brain's relationship with the body and outside world, our work could inform new, more accessible drug targets and lifestyle interventions to protect the brain from the outside in."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.neuron.2025.07.001"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Neuron&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:01:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxQTG1zYVNNY1JDaEVNeTB2dUpKTTRxYzZod3lSOGw0VFBiNXhZU2VpdFEtNUpxVnBMNmw1cXJtRW5HQlpkdGR6UGVLcFdIaXdnbTRLbVhaQ1BnUUMtZlFiam5VcHpZU0JxUkl4cmswcE1rRjVvWVZxb3ZScmQtRThnSmh0VUtmdnZ4TWdhaU0zYm9GYzhRYlE</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr.通过伪科学gobbledygook为mRNA疫苗削减5亿美元辩护- Ars Technica</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiswFBVV95cUxQaVBKMWI5Zk5KN2Voakd3Q0VWRFF0NW9peVkzLW10YndMdXp2UUZjZlo5WlU0MFlRQXZOdE44cTczd3YtZEZ5ckZoeWRGQ3c2bXAtQ3MyZWFfb0FoalVNcVF0U3NXc3FIa3FhYVY4ZkVLZjg4RWxWN2lZU01nNHFYT1RUS1U2UHE0eUxFQ3prZTcxaGk1YWNwTWQ4M2ZLVC0yeUpkNE1uYk1QdGhLeDRadncwVQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
                      
                      
          
&lt;p&gt;If anyone needed a reminder that US health secretary and fervent anti-vaccine advocate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has no background in science or medicine, look no further than &lt;a href="https://x.com/SecKennedy/status/1952851097019633766"&gt;the video he posted on social media&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the two-and-a-half-minute clip, Kennedy announced that he is cancelling nearly $500 million in funding for the development of mRNA-based vaccines against diseases that pose pandemic threats. The funding will be clawed back from 22 now-defunct contracts awarded through the federal agency tasked with developing medical countermeasures to public health threats. The agency is the Biomedical Advanced Research and Development Authority (BARDA).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kennedy is generally opposed to vaccines, but he is particularly hostile to mRNA-based vaccines. Since the remarkably successful debut of mRNA COVID-19 vaccines during the COVID-19 pandemic—which were developed and mass-produced with unprecedented speed—Kennedy has continually disparaged and spread misinformation about them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the video on Tuesday, Kennedy continued that trend, erroneously saying that, "as the pandemic showed us, mRNA vaccines don't perform well against viruses that infect the upper respiratory tract." In reality, COVID-19 vaccines are estimated to have saved &lt;a href="https://www.commonwealthfund.org/blog/2022/two-years-covid-vaccines-prevented-millions-deaths-hospitalizations"&gt;more than 3 million lives&lt;/a&gt; in the US in just the first two years of the pandemic and additionally prevented more than 18 million hospitalizations in the US in that time. Nearly all &lt;a href="https://ourworldindata.org/grapher/covid-vaccine-doses-by-manufacturer?country=~USA"&gt;COVID-19 vaccines used in the US&lt;/a&gt; are mRNA-based.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, Kennedy's video only went more off the rails from there. He continued on with this nonsensical explanation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here's the problem: mRNA only codes for a small part of viral proteins usually a single antigen. One mutation, and the vaccine becomes ineffective. This dynamic drives a phenomenon called antigenic shift meaning that the vaccine paradoxically encourages new mutations and can actually prolong pandemics as the virus constantly mutates to escape the protective effects of the vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Fact-check&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To unpack this nonsense, let's start with how mRNA-based vaccines work. These vaccines deliver a snippet of genetic code—in the form of messenger RNA (mRNA)—to cells. Our cells then translate that mRNA code into a protein that the immune system can, essentially, use for target practice, producing antibodies and cell-based responses against it. After that, if the immune system ever encounters that snippet on an actual invading virus or other germ, it will then recognize it and mount a protective response. Such snippets of germs or other harmful things that can prompt an immune response are generally called antigens.&lt;/p&gt;

          
                      &lt;p class="ars-interlude-container in-content-interlude mx-auto max-w-xl"&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 11:15:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQaVBKMWI5Zk5KN2Voakd3Q0VWRFF0NW9peVkzLW10YndMdXp2UUZjZlo5WlU0MFlRQXZOdE44cTczd3YtZEZ5ckZoeWRGQ3c2bXAtQ3MyZWFfb0FoalVNcVF0U3NXc3FIa3FhYVY4ZkVLZjg4RWxWN2lZU01nNHFYT1RUS1U2UHE0eUxFQ3prZTcxaGk1YWNwTWQ4M2ZLVC0yeUpkNE1uYk1QdGhLeDRadncwVQ</guid></item><item><title>“超级老人”如何保持年轻？ 25年的研究揭示了什么。-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihwFBVV95cUxPbnZwZE5veFBiMU9CMzFtSmxUTFN2bUtPSW13S0tHTUQzT2V4b0U1NGo0cjEzN3Rjbi1MVmVLc20wRjVrRmtrTEEtWkZFUjdicDlFSS1zSGpiN3VIYklYSW0tNE9HcDJsXy1SSWNmejlaRXdlT3dUT1d1ZnZVNGlzVUlpaElBTFE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 11:00:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxPbnZwZE5veFBiMU9CMzFtSmxUTFN2bUtPSW13S0tHTUQzT2V4b0U1NGo0cjEzN3Rjbi1MVmVLc20wRjVrRmtrTEEtWkZFUjdicDlFSS1zSGpiN3VIYklYSW0tNE9HcDJsXy1SSWNmejlaRXdlT3dUT1d1ZnZVNGlzVUlpaElBTFE</guid></item><item><title>医生说这是最令人担忧的Ozempic副作用- bestlifeonline.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiW0FVX3lxTE4xQW9qVmxkU3Y4R1FpdzhyMWUzT19BS3NHMDdFTGFUUzNCeXBIWURkc0labWhPZlFKTGpuTUs5WTlOVk9zdy1XSF9hUnNvNld0a1NabWQ3V3pzaW8?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content noskimwords"&gt;
						
																			&lt;svg class="circle" viewbox="10 1846 49 48" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;
								&lt;path d="M34.467 1893.367c13.071 0 23.667-10.596 23.667-23.667 0-13.071-10.596-23.667-23.667-23.667-13.071 0-23.667 10.596-23.667 23.667 0 13.071 10.596 23.667 23.667 23.667" fill="#E8021D" fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
								&lt;path d="M23.808 1869.718h19.918M36.638 1862.247l7.78 7.78M36.765 1877.153l7.534-7.534" stroke="#FFF" fill="none"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						
						&lt;p&gt;After gaining Hollywood recognition in 2021, GLP-1 drugs remain as popular as ever. &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://bestlifeonline.com/ozempic-no-sex-drive/" target="_blank"&gt;Ozempic&lt;/a&gt;, the queen bee of these weight-loss medications, is only approved to treat type 2 diabetes. However, that hasn’t stopped celebrities and the average patient from using the drug off-label as an appetite suppressant. But with those figure-slimming perks come a score of potentially dangerous side effects, one of which has doctors very concerned.&lt;/p&gt;

  
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://bestlifeonline.com/weight-loss-drugs-pancreatitis/"&gt;Ozempic and Mounjaro Patients Report Potentially Fatal New Side Effect&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Doctors are worried about Ozempic-related muscle loss.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without proper dietary guidelines in place, taking GLP-1 drugs can be a slippery slope, many doctors have warned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="htlad-mob-square-fixed first_ad karma_unit inline hide-desktop"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s this constant struggle between eating protein and making sure you’re meeting your nutritional requirements, and then taking this drug that doesn’t allow you to eat,” explained anesthesiologist &lt;strong&gt;Nicole Martin&lt;/strong&gt;, MD, on her &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h3GoE53zOvM&amp;amp;list=PLiGFuLdrTqlSz0iV5_NM41-0KwplHfLz-&amp;amp;index=8" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Scrubs to Stilettos&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt; podcast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This merry-go-round can cause patients to become “nutritionally deficient” and “&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://bestlifeonline.com/ozempic-skinny-fat/"&gt;skinny fat&lt;/a&gt;,” a term used to describe someone with a low BMI (body mass index) but lack of muscle density.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When you restrict your calories, and you don’t eat well, and you don’t exercise, now you’re losing lean muscle mass,” further explained &lt;strong&gt;Tiffany Moon&lt;/strong&gt;, MD, doctor and &lt;i&gt;Scrubs to Stilettos&lt;/i&gt; podcast co-host.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As &lt;i&gt;Best Life&lt;/i&gt; previously reported, “Strong muscles contribute to osteoporosis prevention, joint protection, bone growth, and better balance. A 2024 study published in &lt;i&gt;JAMA Network Open&lt;/i&gt; found that taking GLP-1 drugs led to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://bestlifeonline.com/weight-loss-drugs-bone-loss/"&gt;decreased muscle mass&lt;/a&gt; and increased bone mineral density (BMD).”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This alarming side effect was also flagged in a recent study conducted by nutrition experts from the University of Utah College of Health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://bestlifeonline.com/ozempic-hair-loss/" target="_blank"&gt;Ozempic Patients Report Another Troubling Side Effect: “I’ve Lost at Least Half My Hair.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;GLP-1 drugs can cause a 10% reduction in lean muscle mass.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GLP-1 drugs like Ozempic can decrease lean muscle mass by roughly 10 percent, according to a new study published in the journal &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://gophysiotherapy.co.uk/lean-muscle-mass-important/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Cell Metabolism&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="karma_unit inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed karma_unit--halfpage"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A decline in lean body mass—defined as “body weight that isn’t fat”—can disrupt your energy levels, skeletal muscles, and bone strength, “potentially compromising physical functions and quality of life, particularly in those susceptible to sarcopenia,” warned the authors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a preclinical mouse model, researchers observed negative changes in lean mass and muscle exertion. Notably, about 45 percent of weight loss was attributed to a reduction in lean mass. Skeletal muscle also shrank by six percent, and “they found that, for some muscles, strength decreased as the mice lost weight,” per the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1092776" target="_blank"&gt;news release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The authors cautioned against “drawing a one-to-one parallel with humans,” noting that both weight gain and loss have varying effects on mice and humans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, these results do corroborate previous theories about Ozempic’s adverse effect on lean muscle mass. In fact, their research ties back to a 2023 AARP report that revealed “for every pound you lose, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.aarp.org/health/drugs-supplements/anti-obesity-medications-risks/" target="_blank" data-citation="true"&gt;about 25 percent&lt;/a&gt; is muscle and bone.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://bestlifeonline.com/semaglutide-er-visits/"&gt;Ozempic and Wegovy May Have Landed 25,000 People in the ER—Here’s the Scary Reason Why&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Ozempic is also known to cause bone loss.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bone frailty and weaker muscles are a natural sign of aging; however, certain medications, such as Ozempic, can &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://bestlifeonline.com/avoid-ozempic-over-65/"&gt;expedite these changes&lt;/a&gt; in adults 65 and up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Significant weight loss, especially over a short time, can also contribute to a decrease in bone density, which may put older adults at increased risk of bone fractures or exacerbate pre-existing conditions such as osteoporosis,” &lt;strong&gt;HaVy Ngo-Hamilton&lt;/strong&gt;, PharmD, a pharmacist and clinical consultant at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.buzzrx.com/blog/authors/havy-ngo-pharmd" target="_blank"&gt;BuzzRx&lt;/a&gt;, previously explained to &lt;em&gt;Best Life&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, it can make this age group more susceptible to “health complications, disability, and mobility issues,” she added. Consequently, many health officials don’t encourage Ozempic treatment in geriatrics.&lt;/p&gt;

													&lt;div class="gnp-authority-signal-disclaimer gnp-disclaimer--health-disclaimer"&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;We offer the most up-to-date information from top experts, new research, and health agencies, but our content is not meant to be a substitute for professional guidance. When it comes to the medication you're taking or any other health questions you have, always consult your healthcare provider directly.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
						
																																																&lt;/div&gt;
											&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>bestlifeonline.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:26:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiW0FVX3lxTE4xQW9qVmxkU3Y4R1FpdzhyMWUzT19BS3NHMDdFTGFUUzNCeXBIWURkc0labWhPZlFKTGpuTUs5WTlOVk9zdy1XSF9hUnNvNld0a1NabWQ3V3pzaW8</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，我们的大脑含有锂-其损失可能有助于驱动阿尔茨海默氏症- Gizmodo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirwFBVV95cUxNMnJPLTFaLWNQdVVKWmxnZXFCVV9KZDl4dEpIZHo3MmM2c3BWejNfemxjdnJ2dHVZVjk3T3pYdW1vYkJabENmelExaXp2RGk0NXNRUDEzSjdXM0J4b1llekNmcS12M2tjUUVYSUhCNTM4ajZGeC1QM3FtMXU3WHBYTzRKSlhCSGpEUXRFWWpEaHVXYWt2bXBoalRHS2Q5LTVaTi1GVnJvNFlqSk5TdGIw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-lg lg:leading-[29px] font-serif max-w-none"&gt;
              
              
              &lt;p&gt;Alzheimer’s disease is one of the cruelest conditions a person can develop. And even with recent advances, there’s only so much that can be done once its symptoms emerge. Research out this week might highlight a critical and previously missed factor driving the disease, one that could even lead to new treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-4 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Scientists at Harvard Medical School led the study, &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-025-09335-x"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; Wednesday in Nature. By studying human brain samples and mice, they found evidence that our brains naturally contain the element lithium—and that its deficiency can help explain the damage caused by Alzheimer’s. The findings are well supported and may have uncovered an important aspect of the neurological disorder, an outside expert told Gizmodo.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The study researchers “have performed detailed and well-designed studies to investigate how low lithium levels are associated with [Alzheimer’s disease] at the diagnostic, protein, cellular and gene levels,” said Timothy Chang, a neurologist at the University of California, Los Angeles who was not involved with the study. Chang is also director of the California Alzheimer’s Disease Center at UCLA.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The brains of people with Alzheimer’s are different in many ways from others. In particular, they contain high levels of misfolded amyloid beta and tau, two proteins that normally have important functions. But these aren’t the only changes seen in Alzheimer’s. And it was while investigating these other changes that the Harvard researchers made their discovery.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;With the help of existing projects that collected postmortem tissue samples, they compared levels of around 30 metals in the brains of people who died along varying stages of cognitive health. The only major difference they found was with lithium. People with cognitively healthy brains had relatively high levels of lithium, whereas those with Alzheimer’s had much lower levels. Importantly, this loss of lithium was apparent even in people who only experienced mild memory problems before dying.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The researchers also studied healthy mice and genetically modified mice that develop a version of Alzheimer’s disease. When they depleted lithium from these mice, it appeared to accelerate the buildup of unhealthy amyloid beta and tau in the brain, along with memory decline. They also found evidence that this loss is caused by amyloid beta plaques binding to the brain’s lithium and that this loss of lithium seems to negatively affect all of the brain’s major cell types.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Though there has been some limited research &lt;a href="https://journalbipolardisorders.springeropen.com/articles/10.1186/s40345-024-00348-5"&gt;suggesting&lt;/a&gt; a possible connection between lithium and Alzheimer’s, the authors say theirs is the first to show that our brains naturally carry it. What’s more, their findings hint that lithium is essential to good brain health and that its absence is key to the development of Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“This is the first study to suggest that lithium deficiency might contribute to Alzheimer’s disease. The reason this has not been proposed is because it was not believed that lithium is a natural substance in the brain with biological effect, just a drug with pharmacological effects at high doses,” senior author Bruce Yankner, professor of genetics and neurology in Harvard Medical School’s Blavatnik Institute, told Gizmodo. “As such, this study is the first to explore the consequences of lithium deficiency in the brain.”&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The implications of this study, while still early, could certainly be dramatic. Yankner and his team were also able to identify a lithium-based compound that wasn’t so easily bound by amyloid beta. And when they gave mice (older healthy mice and mice with Alzheimer’s) this compound, it appeared to prevent the damaging brain changes and memory loss normally inevitable with the neurodegenerative condition. Even the best amyloid-based &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/fda-approval-for-leqembi-drug-alzheimers-treatment-1850615742"&gt;treatments&lt;/a&gt; for Alzheimer’s available today, by contrast, only modestly delay its progression.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Other forms of lithium are used in medicine to treat certain mental health disorders, particularly depression. But these versions require high dosages to work as intended and come with many side effects as a result. The team’s compound, however, required a much lower dose to be effective in the mice, and no sign of toxicity was observed at all.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“Further clinical studies in humans would be necessary to evaluate if the right type and dose of lithium can prevent or slow Alzheimer’s disease,” Chang noted.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Yankner and his team are now moving ahead with the research needed to show their compound (or something similar) can be safely tested in human clinical trials. But even before then, the team’s discovery could pay off in other ways. It might be possible to screen for Alzheimer’s risk in the future by measuring people’s lithium levels, for example. And there are still many mysteries left to untangle about lithium and its role in brain health.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“As a neuroscientist, I am excited about exploring the physiology of lithium in the brain,” Yankner said. “I suspect we have just scratched the surface of what will be some very interesting biology.”&lt;/p&gt;
                          &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxNMnJPLTFaLWNQdVVKWmxnZXFCVV9KZDl4dEpIZHo3MmM2c3BWejNfemxjdnJ2dHVZVjk3T3pYdW1vYkJabENmelExaXp2RGk0NXNRUDEzSjdXM0J4b1llekNmcS12M2tjUUVYSUhCNTM4ajZGeC1QM3FtMXU3WHBYTzRKSlhCSGpEUXRFWWpEaHVXYWt2bXBoalRHS2Q5LTVaTi1GVnJvNFlqSk5TdGIw</guid></item><item><title>麻疹在抵制疫苗的艾伯塔省农村地区迅速蔓延-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijAFBVV95cUxPcENwVXNlbHNZZ05UZjBPcDFHQVhMeG02aUlIVkJSWXVRRUlSTldpLW9ZMzBuNHVjeGh6d3dkOG82LUJ5Y3UteE02ZTBRYWNlYXJpWFNybEZCb29rTDVKZ1JyRmdpZ3lwSTc1Q2tRRXBmNTJWVHppQlZqZ3NlNm1ER1hSQW55ai1NblNMNA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:03:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxPcENwVXNlbHNZZ05UZjBPcDFHQVhMeG02aUlIVkJSWXVRRUlSTldpLW9ZMzBuNHVjeGh6d3dkOG82LUJ5Y3UteE02ZTBRYWNlYXJpWFNybEZCb29rTDVKZ1JyRmdpZ3lwSTc1Q2tRRXBmNTJWVHppQlZqZ3NlNm1ER1hSQW55ai1NblNMNA</guid></item><item><title>北部海滩患有流感的儿童在医院死亡后的验尸报告- Manly Observer</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxQRTF1STlBUW5tQ25SdU4ycjl5ZDBBWHZ4UGpSb3F0NDk4MTBNQnhIN3pPd200dG14OFNadm1QSllZOEZsN3Z5M2JFamhOVFpzNl9ZWlVZUXhCMUh3QmRyTXhxbm5ONU5Ub2pwZ1A2cXFYclRUb21OOWFXN0tyZHZKeGNIYUhGZHA1VXR0ZkpMZnhOM0kxS0xQNGVpYVVpUzc3OWxZ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="tdb-block-inner td-fix-index"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Northern Beaches kindergartener has tragically died at Northern Beaches Hospital this week after contracting influenza A (the flu). She had been discharged twice from Sydney Children’s Hospital earlier that day.


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Northern Beaches Hospital spokesperson confirmed that the tragic death of the child, who we understand to be a six year old girl, will be subject to a Coronial Inquest.


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The girl was initially taken to Sydney Children’s Hospital, Randwick, and was discharged only to be re-presented by her father a short time later. She was then diagnosed with influenza and discharged again.


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The child was later brought to Northern Beaches Hospital, where she later died.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone_load_1636522323"&gt;&lt;broadstreet-zone place="0" callback="zone_load_1636522323" zone-id="176487" keywords="not_home_page,not_landing_page,is_article_page,latest-news,coronial-inquest-after-northern-beaches-child-with-flu-dies-in-hospital,post" soft-keywords="true" zone-alias=""&gt;&lt;/broadstreet-zone&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;It has left a tight school community in shock as they support her bereft parents, who we understand advocated for her care persistently.  We have elected to withhold details of the school and family at this time, and will update if permission is given to provide these details.


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hospitals respond&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Northern Beaches Hospital spokesperson told &lt;em&gt;Manly Observer&lt;/em&gt; this evening, via a statement, that they were “deeply saddened by the tragic loss of a young child.”


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our heartfelt condolences go out to the child’s family and loved ones during this incredibly difficult time.


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Alongside Sydney Children’s Hospital Network, where the child received care earlier in the day, we will undertake the appropriate investigations in line with NSW Health policy, including a joint independent review. A coronial inquest has also been called into the child’s passing.”


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“While we cannot comment on the specifics of the case during the review period, our thoughts are with the family, and we will continue to offer them our full support.&lt;strong&gt;”&lt;/strong&gt;


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Sydney Children’s Hospital confirmed that the patient had been discharged twice on Monday, 4 August. They said a patient “presented to the Emergency Department at Sydney Children’s SCHN and Following clinical assessment, the child was discharged.”


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The statement continues: “The patient represented shortly after, and following a diagnosis of influenza, was discharged with at-home guidance.


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Sydney Children’s Hospitals Network (SCHN) has learnt the patient later tragically died.


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“SCHN expresses our deepest condolences to the family for the loss of their child.


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“SCHN is progressing an initial review into the patient’s care while at the hospital. Based on this initial review, SCHN will work with Northern Sydney Local Health District as part of the joint independent clinical governance process.”


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The matter has been referred to the Coroner.


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Internal reviews are usually conducted within 100 days.


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Manly Observer</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:47:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQRTF1STlBUW5tQ25SdU4ycjl5ZDBBWHZ4UGpSb3F0NDk4MTBNQnhIN3pPd200dG14OFNadm1QSllZOEZsN3Z5M2JFamhOVFpzNl9ZWlVZUXhCMUh3QmRyTXhxbm5ONU5Ub2pwZ1A2cXFYclRUb21OOWFXN0tyZHZKeGNIYUhGZHA1VXR0ZkpMZnhOM0kxS0xQNGVpYVVpUzc3OWxZ</guid></item><item><title>研究发现每周吃薯条会增加2型糖尿病的风险- BBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5JNXlNWEpOQUtkVUZMX1BIQkRMQTd6TEVINkpvUnNxYnh0TWhwZkdnemZ5ZFgxc3pMR0pQMUpYMC13MnlYUFdxVGdHd2kwZEE4NnBEUGhGSElkd9IBX0FVX3lxTE1PRjNBZzBfbEVSaUpRSTZENHJiR1dEY3J4MzQwVTlUU0tobnpnbXNCWlAtemtSLVNyY1lLTzdLS01HS05kdFNzbllsQUNMS1N4RWltQXoyWnJJZTBveVFj?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 dfvxux"&gt;Study links fries to higher type 2 diabetes risk&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gyQxwn"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250728-162205-9b8a2dcb37-web-2.26.0-8/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/2e30/live/ff791180-72ef-11f0-9eb3-2b71669c0257.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/2e30/live/ff791180-72ef-11f0-9eb3-2b71669c0257.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2e30/live/ff791180-72ef-11f0-9eb3-2b71669c0257.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/2e30/live/ff791180-72ef-11f0-9eb3-2b71669c0257.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/2e30/live/ff791180-72ef-11f0-9eb3-2b71669c0257.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/2e30/live/ff791180-72ef-11f0-9eb3-2b71669c0257.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/2e30/live/ff791180-72ef-11f0-9eb3-2b71669c0257.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2e30/live/ff791180-72ef-11f0-9eb3-2b71669c0257.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="PA Media A red background with a white plate and cone of French fries on top. A persons hand is in view. They are taking a french fry out of the pot and holding it towards the camera. " class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;PA Media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;The research team found those who ate fries five times a week appeared to have a 27% increased risk&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A new study has found that eating three or more servings of French fries a week could increase the risk of developing type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;An international team of researchers, including an expert from the University of Cambridge, investigated links between potato consumption and the risk of type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Overall they found a 20% increased risk for those who ate French fries at least three times a week, but not for those who ate baked, boiled or mashed potatoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Dr Faye Riley, from Diabetes UK, said: "This research shows that the link between potatoes and type 2 diabetes isn't as clear-cut as it might seem."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Academics analysed data from studies tracking the health of more than 205,000 medical workers in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Repeated surveys were taken about people's diets over almost four decades and during follow-up periods 22,000 cases of type 2 diabetes were documented. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 eOFjmw"&gt;Complex condition &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"The association between higher potato intake and increased [type 2 diabetes] risk is primarily driven by intake of French fries," the study authors wrote in The British Medical Journal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"Higher intake of French fries, but not combined baked, boiled, or mashed potatoes, was associated with a higher risk of [type 2 diabetes]."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The research team also found replacing three servings of potatoes each week with whole grains was found to lower the risk of type 2 diabetes by 8%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;They added replacing potatoes with white rice, however was also associated with an increased risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Dr Riley, research communications lead at Diabetes UK, said: "Type 2 diabetes is a complex condition, with many factors influencing its development, including genetics, age and ethnicity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"Diet is just one part of the picture, but this study suggests that how food is prepared can make a difference and reinforces the advice to prioritise whole grains and cut back on fried or heavily processed foods as a way to support a balanced diet and reduce your risk."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dHQIrb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:07:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5JNXlNWEpOQUtkVUZMX1BIQkRMQTd6TEVINkpvUnNxYnh0TWhwZkdnemZ5ZFgxc3pMR0pQMUpYMC13MnlYUFdxVGdHd2kwZEE4NnBEUGhGSElkd9IBX0FVX3lxTE1PRjNBZzBfbEVSaUpRSTZENHJiR1dEY3J4MzQwVTlUU0tobnpnbXNCWlAtemtSLVNyY1lLTzdLS01HS05kdFNzbllsQUNMS1N4RWltQXoyWnJJZTBveVFj</guid></item><item><title>中国用无人机、罚款和蚊帐对抗蚊媒基孔肯雅病毒--Politico</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivwFBVV95cUxPT296QXA0d0o4bzJnSGQtYk13bURfVlJobGl0RDE5ODdsZHJZdHNoVFhwUVFmUlRPR3lmQ20xN1ZZMmNrZ0FvbWstSUIzbWJ2WXgzMEhtUGFNbmkxQVRRQmF0RlBmM2FzM2E2Z0dWbktINXdob1BQVm5DZFNyQlNra2Ryd1A2UGZJc0JqNkttTVBGczgxclI1cjdDLWdRb0l0SzlNa1NDN1Rpd1ZkSVRVN1hOWUlqYWJXQlBwd3Z5QQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Politico</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 03:43:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxPT296QXA0d0o4bzJnSGQtYk13bURfVlJobGl0RDE5ODdsZHJZdHNoVFhwUVFmUlRPR3lmQ20xN1ZZMmNrZ0FvbWstSUIzbWJ2WXgzMEhtUGFNbmkxQVRRQmF0RlBmM2FzM2E2Z0dWbktINXdob1BQVm5DZFNyQlNra2Ryd1A2UGZJc0JqNkttTVBGczgxclI1cjdDLWdRb0l0SzlNa1NDN1Rpd1ZkSVRVN1hOWUlqYWJXQlBwd3Z5QQ</guid></item><item><title>新的研究估计，洛杉矶野火可能与440人死亡有关- CNN</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgFBVV95cUxNYVhVVU9zNzROQ01udUlPS0RLT1JaQkFVRHNjcjg1MWlvdE5ITkotTWljWnNpYTg5Z0VIOVY4VjFVLUpGcnphZDRLRjExZ3p2aVpjUFQ2NVlYc3JkS19ZaG5va3lTN3NRSjhPZ3dBV1JUWWV2a0U1M0hzQ1RiSlBzLU1INGJmZ9IBiwFBVV95cUxNeE1Dejg4d003a0Z0a1ZQaVAyUjRoTXk2ci1XdnVpZ1VsY3pFRFdDUmpyMmc5S1dJemd0VTl0Y2VXV2VJSnR5TkpVUXZVUTJQbHRDVkI5QU9mQU1odVdFRTkzZm5KNHl4UnltU2xBWWVIUlZKN2RmUHhqUFdWVXhKdmJjYnpfR1BQbGFZ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/action-bar/instances/cme0neqsc000r27qi16zp8q39@published" data-label-id-prefix="action-bar-start-of-article" class="action-bar" data-dynamic-breakpoint-placement='{"extraLarge":{"placement":".layout-article-elevate__left"}}' data-expand-conditions='{"follow":{"extraLarge":{"alwaysExpand":true}},"shareOptions":{"large":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"medium":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"extraLarge":{"withAction":"follow","maxNumOfActions":2}}}'&gt;
    &lt;p class="action-bar__overlay"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet" tabindex="-1"&gt;
        
            
            &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet--action" data-title="share options"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/social-share/instances/cme0neqsc000u27qi80w231hh@published" class="social-share_labelled-list"&gt;
    &lt;div class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links vossi-social-share_labelled-list" data-type="share-links"&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.facebook.com/dialog/share?app_id=80401312489&amp;amp;href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F08%2F06%2Fus%2Flos-angeles-wildfires-440-excess-deaths-study&amp;amp;display=popup" data-type="facebook" aria-label="share with facebook" title="Share with Facebook"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-facebook-circle" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.04139 1.33301C11.7458 1.33301 14.7488 4.33601 14.7488 8.04042C14.7488 11.3884 12.296 14.1632 9.08943 14.6663V9.97928H10.6523L10.9497 8.04042H9.08943V6.78225C9.08943 6.25182 9.34934 5.73475 10.1825 5.73475H11.0283V4.08409C11.0283 4.08409 10.2607 3.95309 9.52685 3.95309C7.99476 3.95309 6.99336 4.88165 6.99336 6.56269V8.04042H5.29031V9.97928H6.99336V14.6663C3.78677 14.1632 1.33398 11.3882 1.33398 8.04042C1.33398 4.33601 4.33699 1.33301 8.04139 1.33301Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Facebook&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F08%2F06%2Fus%2Flos-angeles-wildfires-440-excess-deaths-study" data-type="x" aria-label="share with x" title="Share with X"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-x-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.99386 8.11503L0 0.666992H4.74756L8.44753 5.27039L12.4004 0.687719H15.0151L9.71175 6.84331L16 14.667H11.2666L7.2603 9.6887L2.98317 14.6532H0.354296L5.99386 8.11503ZM11.9565 13.287L2.91105 2.04698H4.0571L13.0912 13.287H11.9565Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Tweet&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;a class="social-share_labelled-list__share" href="mailto:?subject=CNN%20content%20share&amp;amp;body=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A%0Ahttps%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F08%2F06%2Fus%2Flos-angeles-wildfires-440-excess-deaths-study" data-type="email" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="share with email" title="Share with email"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-email-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 24 24" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M2 6C2 4.89543 2.89543 4 4 4H20C21.1046 4 22 4.89543 22 6V18C22 19.1046 21.1046 20 20 20H4C2.89543 20 2 19.1046 2 18V6ZM4 6H20V9.11604L12 11.9396L4 9.11604V6ZM4 11.237V18H20V11.237L12.3328 13.943C12.1174 14.019 11.8825 14.019 11.6672 13.943L4 11.237Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Email&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/06/us/los-angeles-wildfires-440-excess-deaths-study" data-type="copy" aria-label="copy link to clipboard" title="Copy link to clipboard"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-hyperlink" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.64373 10.3574C5.38338 10.0971 5.38338 9.67496 5.64373 9.41461L9.88637 5.17197C10.1467 4.91162 10.5688 4.91162 10.8292 5.17197C11.0895 5.43232 11.0895 5.85443 10.8292 6.11478L6.58654 10.3574C6.32619 10.6178 5.90408 10.6178 5.64373 10.3574Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M4.22952 8.94321L5.64373 7.52899C5.90408 7.26865 5.90408 6.84654 5.64373 6.58619C5.38338 6.32584 4.96127 6.32584 4.70092 6.58619L3.28671 8.0004C1.98496 9.30215 1.98496 11.4127 3.28671 12.7144C4.58846 14.0162 6.69901 14.0162 8.00075 12.7144L9.41497 11.3002C9.67532 11.0399 9.67532 10.6178 9.41497 10.3574C9.15462 10.0971 8.73251 10.0971 8.47216 10.3574L7.05795 11.7716C6.2769 12.5527 5.01057 12.5527 4.22952 11.7716C3.44847 10.9906 3.44847 9.72426 4.22952 8.94321Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.94356 4.22916L7.52935 5.64338C7.269 5.90373 6.84689 5.90373 6.58654 5.64338C6.32619 5.38303 6.32619 4.96092 6.58654 4.70057L8.00075 3.28635C9.3025 1.98461 11.4131 1.98461 12.7148 3.28635C14.0165 4.5881 14.0165 6.69865 12.7148 8.0004L11.3006 9.41461C11.0402 9.67496 10.6181 9.67496 10.3578 9.41461C10.0974 9.15426 10.0974 8.73215 10.3578 8.4718L11.772 7.05759C12.553 6.27654 12.553 5.01021 11.772 4.22916C10.9909 3.44812 9.72461 3.44811 8.94356 4.22916Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Link&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__open" data-type="open" aria-label="open social share" title="Open social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-share-os" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19 12c.394 0 .714.32.714.714v8.572c0 .394-.32.714-.714.714H4.714A.715.715 0 014 21.286v-8.572a.715.715 0 011.429 0v7.857h12.857v-7.857c0-.394.32-.714.714-.714zm-7.664-9.79a.73.73 0 011.024 0l.076.075 4.916 4.854c.183.18.27.449.188.69a.734.734 0 01-1.216.314L12.57 4.5v11.786c0 .357-.357.714-.714.714s-.714-.359-.714-.714V4.5L7.372 8.143a.73.73 0 01-1.102-.091c-.21-.289-.149-.694.106-.946l4.884-4.821z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__close" data-type="close" aria-label="close social share" title="Close social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-close" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19.787 18.758l-6.792-6.781 6.746-6.735a.728.728 0 00-1.028-1.03l-6.747 6.737-6.711-6.7a.728.728 0 00-1.028 1.03l6.71 6.698-6.723 6.712a.727.727 0 101.027 1.03l6.725-6.714 6.793 6.782a.725.725 0 001.028 0 .727.727 0 000-1.03"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0neqsc000t27qi2xx6fwb4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The wildfires that ravaged Los Angeles earlier this year — burning entire neighborhoods to the ground, straining firefighting resources and forcing tens of thousands of people to flee their homes — may have led to hundreds more deaths than were recorded, a new study suggests.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0neuyl00003b6nmgi6vw43@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            While officials reported that the Palisades and Eaton fires directly killed at least &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/california-wildfires-los-angeles-deaths-75642a4e6cd66a34cbced64c10dd4f3b" target="_blank"&gt;30 people &lt;/a&gt;when they incinerated parts of Los Angeles County, the blazes may be linked to 410 additional deaths from January 5 to February 1, according to &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/article-abstract/2837351#:~:text=While%20there%20were%20only%2030,were%20attributable%20to%20the%20wildfires." target="_blank"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; published Wednesday in the The Journal of the American Medical Association. That would make for a total of 440 wildfire-related deaths, according to the study.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0opyjn000p3b6ntq4u1uk4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “These additional deaths likely reflect a combination of factors, including increased exposure to poor air quality and health care delays and interruptions,” the study says.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0potqa00153b6nmrhh9z3a@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The wildfires’ impact on his loved ones motivated Andrew Stokes, a mortality demographer and one of the authors of the study, to probe for  excess deaths.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0qbjbd001d3b6nijxjz087@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Having had many family and friends who were directly affected made me feel compelled to look into this further, using my expertise as a demographer and a person who studies mortality statistics,” the Boston University associate professor told CNN.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0p1jce000v3b6nwlcucvrs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The new findings highlight the need to quantify just how deadly wildfires and other climate-related emergencies can be beyond direct fatalities. The emergencies can have long-term health effects that extend well beyond the disaster itself, experts say.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0qi4w2001k3b6nkciuld07@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Years ago, Stokes evaluated the excess deaths during the pandemic after many deaths went uncounted, he said. After developing models to understand the true toll of the virus, Stokes used that expertise to look at the true mortality burden of natural disasters such as the Los Angeles wildfires.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0nphbe00073b6nk9sk6ot9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Along with deaths directly related to the wildfire, the researchers counted deaths partially and indirectly attributed to the wildfires. That includes lung or heart conditions exacerbated by smoke or stress, disruptions to health systems and mental health impacts, according to the study.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0o0kh4000a3b6n27lesffe@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            To conduct the study, the researchers compared recorded deaths in Los Angeles County from January to February with figures from previous years, excluding 2020 to 2023 due to the COVID-19 pandemic. That helped researchers estimate how many deaths would have been expected in that time period had no wildfires occurred, Stokes said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0qldfb001q3b6n3ny2biap@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            They then calculated excess deaths as the difference between observed and expected deaths, according to the study.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0ok2i8000g3b6nipk4blcq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “In Los Angeles County, weekly deaths consistently exceeded expected deaths during the period from January 5 to February 1, 2025,” the study says.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0oc1ub000d3b6nvqr511gj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A total of 6,371 deaths were observed in the county, compared with 5,931 expected deaths, according to the study. This means that nearly 7% of the recorded deaths in Los Angeles County were excess deaths linked to the wildfires.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0qiqg0001o3b6njg3yscn9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Stokes said he was “really surprised and alarmed” at the findings. “The magnitude of the underreporting in the official data is just very severe,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0qncns001w3b6nnwxxqpzn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But he hopes that quantifying the excess deaths can spur authorities to provide more assistance to those still grappling with the devastation.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0p77vq000z3b6nngwt1n31@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The researchers note that the data is preliminary and the toll could grow.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0qqbt900223b6nkuob69mp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “That 440 value that we estimate is clearly the lower bound, because we only look at the first weeks after the wildfire started,” Stokes said. “These medium and long- term effects … could manifest over time as people develop wildfire related diseases.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0ps4z600173b6n7vrewn07@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Future studies should investigate the longer-term health impacts of the wildfires and the specific causes of excess wildfire deaths, the researchers said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 03:39:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxNYVhVVU9zNzROQ01udUlPS0RLT1JaQkFVRHNjcjg1MWlvdE5ITkotTWljWnNpYTg5Z0VIOVY4VjFVLUpGcnphZDRLRjExZ3p2aVpjUFQ2NVlYc3JkS19ZaG5va3lTN3NRSjhPZ3dBV1JUWWV2a0U1M0hzQ1RiSlBzLU1INGJmZ9IBiwFBVV95cUxNeE1Dejg4d003a0Z0a1ZQaVAyUjRoTXk2ci1XdnVpZ1VsY3pFRFdDUmpyMmc5S1dJemd0VTl0Y2VXV2VJSnR5TkpVUXZVUTJQbHRDVkI5QU9mQU1odVdFRTkzZm5KNHl4UnltU2xBWWVIUlZKN2RmUHhqUFdWVXhKdmJjYnpfR1BQbGFZ</guid></item><item><title>科学家说，用一种古老的疗法--锂--可以保护衰老的大脑免受阿尔茨海默氏症的侵害</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMid0FVX3lxTE9xYTN2bWFTMlpmUnhuazZNSGUxT0hfQ3FobmVERm9vVFhFRHVQR29tSEtXQXhVbHl6X1VfODF0R1JvTElIQ1VjXzVVNTNHdGNYckFNUVlOS0F0UmlKUEJ2SERVem1GYWhRbGhTQ3kzS0kzRjllUldJ0gF8QVVfeXFMTV9kRmRMVklOdm5wNjRlNk40cVFSVnRtcnhUTkdhRmZkUlp4RUxXUVBuMW1EdTFRaW52VVEwZThQVVpHVnJLOWdiVW9pSURSdXVMeVp1QV9EMC00ZlYtTWFBVFdIdDlpbkhvWF9FamJaLUFjeUpWU3lLNjR3Yw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/action-bar/instances/cme0m8w3a000r27nu14dehlg0@published" data-label-id-prefix="action-bar-start-of-article" class="action-bar" data-dynamic-breakpoint-placement='{"extraLarge":{"placement":".layout-article-elevate__left"}}' data-expand-conditions='{"follow":{"extraLarge":{"alwaysExpand":true}},"shareOptions":{"large":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"medium":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"extraLarge":{"withAction":"follow","maxNumOfActions":2}}}'&gt;
    &lt;p class="action-bar__overlay"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet" tabindex="-1"&gt;
        
            
            &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet--action" data-title="share options"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/social-share/instances/cme0m8w3a000u27nu00z3dhbx@published" class="social-share_labelled-list"&gt;
    &lt;div class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links vossi-social-share_labelled-list" data-type="share-links"&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.facebook.com/dialog/share?app_id=80401312489&amp;amp;href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F08%2F06%2Fhealth%2Flithium-alzheimers-brain-study&amp;amp;display=popup" data-type="facebook" aria-label="share with facebook" title="Share with Facebook"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-facebook-circle" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.04139 1.33301C11.7458 1.33301 14.7488 4.33601 14.7488 8.04042C14.7488 11.3884 12.296 14.1632 9.08943 14.6663V9.97928H10.6523L10.9497 8.04042H9.08943V6.78225C9.08943 6.25182 9.34934 5.73475 10.1825 5.73475H11.0283V4.08409C11.0283 4.08409 10.2607 3.95309 9.52685 3.95309C7.99476 3.95309 6.99336 4.88165 6.99336 6.56269V8.04042H5.29031V9.97928H6.99336V14.6663C3.78677 14.1632 1.33398 11.3882 1.33398 8.04042C1.33398 4.33601 4.33699 1.33301 8.04139 1.33301Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Facebook&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F08%2F06%2Fhealth%2Flithium-alzheimers-brain-study" data-type="x" aria-label="share with x" title="Share with X"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-x-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.99386 8.11503L0 0.666992H4.74756L8.44753 5.27039L12.4004 0.687719H15.0151L9.71175 6.84331L16 14.667H11.2666L7.2603 9.6887L2.98317 14.6532H0.354296L5.99386 8.11503ZM11.9565 13.287L2.91105 2.04698H4.0571L13.0912 13.287H11.9565Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Tweet&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;a class="social-share_labelled-list__share" href="mailto:?subject=CNN%20content%20share&amp;amp;body=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A%0Ahttps%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F08%2F06%2Fhealth%2Flithium-alzheimers-brain-study" data-type="email" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="share with email" title="Share with email"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-email-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 24 24" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M2 6C2 4.89543 2.89543 4 4 4H20C21.1046 4 22 4.89543 22 6V18C22 19.1046 21.1046 20 20 20H4C2.89543 20 2 19.1046 2 18V6ZM4 6H20V9.11604L12 11.9396L4 9.11604V6ZM4 11.237V18H20V11.237L12.3328 13.943C12.1174 14.019 11.8825 14.019 11.6672 13.943L4 11.237Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Email&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/06/health/lithium-alzheimers-brain-study" data-type="copy" aria-label="copy link to clipboard" title="Copy link to clipboard"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-hyperlink" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.64373 10.3574C5.38338 10.0971 5.38338 9.67496 5.64373 9.41461L9.88637 5.17197C10.1467 4.91162 10.5688 4.91162 10.8292 5.17197C11.0895 5.43232 11.0895 5.85443 10.8292 6.11478L6.58654 10.3574C6.32619 10.6178 5.90408 10.6178 5.64373 10.3574Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M4.22952 8.94321L5.64373 7.52899C5.90408 7.26865 5.90408 6.84654 5.64373 6.58619C5.38338 6.32584 4.96127 6.32584 4.70092 6.58619L3.28671 8.0004C1.98496 9.30215 1.98496 11.4127 3.28671 12.7144C4.58846 14.0162 6.69901 14.0162 8.00075 12.7144L9.41497 11.3002C9.67532 11.0399 9.67532 10.6178 9.41497 10.3574C9.15462 10.0971 8.73251 10.0971 8.47216 10.3574L7.05795 11.7716C6.2769 12.5527 5.01057 12.5527 4.22952 11.7716C3.44847 10.9906 3.44847 9.72426 4.22952 8.94321Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.94356 4.22916L7.52935 5.64338C7.269 5.90373 6.84689 5.90373 6.58654 5.64338C6.32619 5.38303 6.32619 4.96092 6.58654 4.70057L8.00075 3.28635C9.3025 1.98461 11.4131 1.98461 12.7148 3.28635C14.0165 4.5881 14.0165 6.69865 12.7148 8.0004L11.3006 9.41461C11.0402 9.67496 10.6181 9.67496 10.3578 9.41461C10.0974 9.15426 10.0974 8.73215 10.3578 8.4718L11.772 7.05759C12.553 6.27654 12.553 5.01021 11.772 4.22916C10.9909 3.44812 9.72461 3.44811 8.94356 4.22916Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Link&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__open" data-type="open" aria-label="open social share" title="Open social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-share-os" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19 12c.394 0 .714.32.714.714v8.572c0 .394-.32.714-.714.714H4.714A.715.715 0 014 21.286v-8.572a.715.715 0 011.429 0v7.857h12.857v-7.857c0-.394.32-.714.714-.714zm-7.664-9.79a.73.73 0 011.024 0l.076.075 4.916 4.854c.183.18.27.449.188.69a.734.734 0 01-1.216.314L12.57 4.5v11.786c0 .357-.357.714-.714.714s-.714-.359-.714-.714V4.5L7.372 8.143a.73.73 0 01-1.102-.091c-.21-.289-.149-.694.106-.946l4.884-4.821z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__close" data-type="close" aria-label="close social share" title="Close social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-close" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19.787 18.758l-6.792-6.781 6.746-6.735a.728.728 0 00-1.028-1.03l-6.747 6.737-6.711-6.7a.728.728 0 00-1.028 1.03l6.71 6.698-6.723 6.712a.727.727 0 101.027 1.03l6.725-6.714 6.793 6.782a.725.725 0 001.028 0 .727.727 0 000-1.03"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m8w3a000t27nu25xxfozr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In a major new finding almost a decade in the making, researchers at Harvard Medical School&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;say they’ve found a key that may unlock many of the mysteries of Alzheimer’s disease and brain aging — the humble metal lithium.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk700042e6d9nbs3ezv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Lithium is best known to medicine as a mood stabilizer given to people who have bipolar disorder and depression. It was approved by the US Food and Drug Administration in 1970, but it was used by doctors to treat mood disorders for nearly a &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3712976/" target="_blank"&gt;century beforehand&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk700072e6d3ciy5a48@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Now, for the first time, researchers have shown that lithium is naturally present in the body in tiny amounts and that cells require it to function normally — much like vitamin C or iron. It also appears to play a critical role in maintaining brain health.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk700092e6dqorrd12k@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In a series of experiments reported Wednesday in the &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-025-09335-x#Ack1" target="_blank"&gt;journal Nature&lt;/a&gt;, researchers at Harvard and Rush universities found that depleting lithium in the diet of normal mice caused their brains to develop inflammation and changes associated with accelerated aging.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000a2e6dr41esi18@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In mice that were specially bred to develop the same kinds of brain changes as humans with Alzheimer’s disease, a low-lithium diet revved the buildup of sticky proteins that form plaques and tangles in the brains that are hallmarks of the disease. It also sped up memory loss.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000b2e6duy5bw3rj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Maintaining normal lithium levels in mice as they aged, however, protected them from brain changes associated with Alzheimer’s.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0pqn82000c3b6n2q1tyubz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            If further research supports the findings, it could open the door to new treatments and diagnostic tests for Alzheimer’s, which affects an estimated 6.7 million older adults in the United States, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/alzheimers-dementia/about/index.html#:~:text=A%20growing%20problem,getting%20lost%20in%20familiar%20areas." target="_blank"&gt;according to&lt;/a&gt; the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000c2e6dmf1gei3r@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The research provides a unifying theory that helps explain so many of the puzzle pieces scientists have been trying to fit together for decades.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000d2e6dqvo9k9tb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It is a potential candidate for a common mechanism leading to the multisystem degeneration of the brain that precedes dementia,” said Dr. Bruce Yankner, a professor of genetics at Harvard Medical School, who led the study. “It will take a lot more science to determine whether this is a common pathway… or one of several pathways,” to Alzheimer’s, he added. “The data are very intriguing.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000e2e6drk22gs88@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In an editorial published in Nature, Dr. Ashley Bush, a neuroscientist who directs the Melbourne Dementia Research Center at the University of Melbourne in Australia, said the researchers “present compelling evidence that lithium does in fact have a physiological role and that normal aging might impair the regulation of lithium levels in the brain.” He was not involved in the study.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000f2e6dnf557bld@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Close examination of human and animal brain tissues, along with genetic investigations in the study, found the mechanism that appears to be at play: Beta amyloid plaques — the sticky deposits that gum up the brains of Alzheimer’s patients — bind to lithium and hold it, including the type that’s normally present in the body, as well as the commonly prescribed form. This binding depletes lithium available for nearby cells, including important scavengers known as microglia.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000g2e6dmb1i7t9t@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When the brain is healthy and functioning normally, microglia are waste managers, clearing away beta amyloid before it can accumulate and can cause harm.  In the team’s experiments, microglia from the brains of lithium-deficient mice showed a reduced ability to sweep away and break down beta amyloid.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000h2e6dxorelmou@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Yankner believes this creates a downward spiral. The accumulation of beta amyloid soaks up more and more lithium, further crippling the brain’s ability to clear it away.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000i2e6de4jl714f@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            He and his colleagues tested different lithium compounds and found one — lithium orotate — that doesn’t bind to amyloid beta.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000j2e6dya77ckhf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When they gave lithium orotate to mice with signs of Alzheimer’s in their brains, these changes reversed: Beta amyloid plaques and tangles of tau that were choking the memory centers of the brain were reduced.  Mice treated with lithium were once again able to navigate mazes and learn to identify new objects, whereas those who got placebos showed no change in their memory and thinking deficits.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0pfoh500033b6n9wf3kjrr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In its natural form, lithium is an element, a soft, silvery-white metal that readily combines with other elements to form compounds and salts. It’s naturally present in the environment, including in food and water.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0pq0uw00073b6nqfqlcqc5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Scientists have never fully known how it works to improve mood — only that it does. The original formula for 7Up soda included lithium — it was called 7Up Lithiated Lemon Soda — and &lt;a href="https://science.howstuffworks.com/environmental/earth/geology/lithium.htm" target="_blank"&gt;touted&lt;/a&gt; as a hangover cure and mood lifter “for hospital or home use.” Some hot springs known to contain mineral water brimming with lithium became sought out &lt;a href="https://ashland.news/viewpoint-the-virtues-of-ashlands-lithia-water/" target="_blank"&gt;wellness destinations&lt;/a&gt; for their curative powers.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000k2e6drwqnc6r5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Still, people who take prescription doses of lithium — which were much higher than the doses used in the new study — can sometimes develop thyroid or kidney toxicity.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0rj6tb00022e6dslccooq8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Tests of the mice given low doses of lithium orotate showed no signs of damage.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000l2e6d42997iem@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            That’s encouraging, Yankner said, but it doesn’t mean people should try to take lithium supplements on their own.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000m2e6dxf3k1ntl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “A mouse is not a human. Nobody should take anything based just on mouse studies,” Yankner said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000n2e6d4kgn5nr0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The lithium treatment data we have is in mice, and it needs to be replicated in humans. We need to find the right dose in humans,” he added.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000o2e6dil2gmghu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The normal amounts of lithium in our bodies, and the concentrations given to the mice, are small — about 1,000 times lower than doses given to treat bipolar disorder, Yankner notes.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000p2e6dw1alkjx0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Yankner said he hoped toxicity trials of lithium salts would start soon.  Neither he nor any of his co-authors have a financial interest in the outcome of the research, he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000q2e6d2a7gwazq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The National Institutes of Health was the major funder of the study, along with grants from private foundations.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000r2e6dk5mdboxt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “NIH support was absolutely critical for this work,” Yankner said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000s2e6d5dbyhdzd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The new research corroborates earlier studies hinting that lithium might be important for Alzheimer’s. A large Danish study &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28832877/" target="_blank"&gt;published in 2017&lt;/a&gt; found people with higher levels of lithium in their drinking water were less likely to be diagnosed with dementia compared with those whose tap water contained naturally lower lithium levels. Another &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8929585/#:~:text=We%20found%20that%20lithium%20was,with%20either%20AD%20or%20VD." target="_blank"&gt;large study&lt;/a&gt; published in 2022 from the United Kingdom found that people prescribed lithium were about half as likely has those in a control group to be diagnosed with Alzheimer’s, suggesting a protective effect of the drug.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000t2e6ddw3xyw1r@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But lithium’s use in psychiatry caused it to become type cast as therapeutic, Yankner said.  No one realized it might be important to the body’s normal physiology.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000u2e6d6wnffvp6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            That happened in part because the amounts of lithium that typically circulate in the body are so small, they couldn’t be quantified until recently. Yankner and his team had to adapt new technology to measure it.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000v2e6doq3wa1ns@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In the first stage of the research, the scientists tested the brain tissue and blood of older patients collected by the brain bank at Rush University for trace levels of 27 metals.  Some of the patients had no history of memory trouble, while others had early memory decline and pronounced Alzheimer’s.  While there was no change in the levels of most metals they measured, lithium was an exception.  Lithium levels were consistently lower in patients with mild cognitive impairment or Alzheimer’s compared to those with normal brain function.  The brains of patients Alzheimer’s disease also showed increased levels of zinc and decreased levels of copper, something scientists had observed before.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000w2e6d66gj0hwf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Consistently finding lower lithium levels in the brains of people with memory loss amounted to a smoking gun, Yankner said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000x2e6dwumleo05@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “At first, frankly, we were skeptical of the result because it wasn’t expected,” said Yankner.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000y2e6dni9fbw4c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But it held up even when they checked samples from other brain banks at Massachusetts General Hospital, Duke and Washington universities.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk7000z2e6dsb5lfpap@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We wanted to know whether this drop in lithium was biologically meaningful, so we devised an experimental protocol where we could take lithium selectively out of the diet of mice and see what happens,” Yankner said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk700102e6di9q310pn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When they fed the mice a low-lithium diet, simply dropping their natural levels by 50%, their brains rapidly developed features of Alzheimer’s.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk700112e6dqw5g1321@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The neurons started to degenerate. The immune cells in the brain went wild in terms of increased inflammation and worse maintenance function of the neurons around them, and it looked more like an advanced Alzheimer patient,” Yankner said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk700122e6drn0o0irw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The team also found the gene expression profiles of lithium-deficient mice and people who had Alzheimer’s disease looked very similar.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk700132e6d7po1ibpw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The researchers then started to look at how this drop in lithium might occur. Yankner said in the earliest stages there’s a decrease in the uptake of lithium in the brain from the blood. They don’t yet know exactly how or why it happens, but it’s likely to be from a variety of things including reduced dietary intake, as well as genetic and environmental factors.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk700142e6dqvmyrtep@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The major source of lithium for most people is their diet. Some of the foods that have the most lithium are leafy green vegetables, nuts, legumes and some spices like turmeric and cumin. Some mineral waters are also rich sources.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk700152e6d5a9tixep@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In other words, Yankner said, a lot of the foods that have already proven to be healthy and reduce a person’s risk of dementia may be beneficial because of their lithium content.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cme0m9kk700162e6d4g3bjap0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “You know, oftentimes one finds in science that things may have an effect, and you think you know exactly why, but then subsequently turn out to be completely wrong about why,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:58:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE9xYTN2bWFTMlpmUnhuazZNSGUxT0hfQ3FobmVERm9vVFhFRHVQR29tSEtXQXhVbHl6X1VfODF0R1JvTElIQ1VjXzVVNTNHdGNYckFNUVlOS0F0UmlKUEJ2SERVem1GYWhRbGhTQ3kzS0kzRjllUldJ0gF8QVVfeXFMTV9kRmRMVklOdm5wNjRlNk40cVFSVnRtcnhUTkdhRmZkUlp4RUxXUVBuMW1EdTFRaW52VVEwZThQVVpHVnJLOWdiVW9pSURSdXVMeVp1QV9EMC00ZlYtTWFBVFdIdDlpbkhvWF9FamJaLUFjeUpWU3lLNjR3Yw</guid></item><item><title>随着特朗普政府撤资，对mRNA疫苗的了解- Axios</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMid0FVX3lxTE5vTU42ejBoZXBqdDZjR1dPUkpyWUZWUXpRdk95XzNtOXA2am1qSXBqQW0yUzhtcVExNmZQNHRrTXdJLW1aLXdac1kwN2JxMXJHR09CZzFaNEZNODlqclRsUWNxcXlaOXR2M2FlaDdRY1dmLU0xMVJZ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:01:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE5vTU42ejBoZXBqdDZjR1dPUkpyWUZWUXpRdk95XzNtOXA2am1qSXBqQW0yUzhtcVExNmZQNHRrTXdJLW1aLXdac1kwN2JxMXJHR09CZzFaNEZNODlqclRsUWNxcXlaOXR2M2FlaDdRY1dmLU0xMVJZ</guid></item><item><title>长期以来，这种习惯一直被认为是“健康的” ，但现在一些长寿专家对此提出了警告- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMibEFVX3lxTE9TeDdQR25mYnVwZG1taFJTUEJja1NqUnJBT0dySC0wN0VuT0tuVS1nZjh6WWVvUmpWaXdNcnc5VEtDYU5SLVcyY1lFaVNHTElEajVaLTVCLUdCTlRRaFRTWkgxSEM0NkhPeGhCbg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-7
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139126051" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;So, how should we approach protein with an eye toward longevity? Bhanote and Sehgal are of the same mind about this: Eat more protein-rich plants and fish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While fish certainly isn’t a plant, it is thought of differently than animal-based proteins because it has a completely different nutritional makeup than meat, and scientific research has repeatedly shown benefits to human health when consumed regularly. Eating fish regularly has been associated with &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25969396/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7918805" data-affiliate="true"&gt;reducing the risk of premature death by 12%.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sehgal explained that plant-based proteins (such as beans, lentils, chickpeas, soy, nuts and seeds) are loaded with antioxidants, fiber and nutrients that keep our hearts healthy, reduce inflammation and lower the risk of chronic diseases. “These foods are naturally low in AGEs and do not contribute to TMAO production, making them much gentler on your cells and overall health,” Bhanote added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC8804093" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7918805" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Scientific studies show&lt;/a&gt; that having a diet that prioritizes plant-based proteins lowers the risk of mortality associated with cardiovascular disease and other causes. In other words, replacing animal proteins with plant proteins can add years to your life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While most Americans meet or exceed the protein recommendation for meat, poultry and eggs, 90% of Americans &lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2021-03/Dietary_Guidelines_for_Americans-2020-2025.pdf" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7918805" data-affiliate="true"&gt;aren’t meeting the recommended guidelines for seafood&lt;/a&gt;. Sehgal told HuffPost that seafood high in protein and unsaturated fats supports &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32529206/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7918805" data-affiliate="true"&gt;brain health&lt;/a&gt;, promotes &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC8182174/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7918805" data-affiliate="true"&gt;hormone balance&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC8199776/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7918805" data-affiliate="true"&gt;helps fight inflammation&lt;/a&gt; — all of which contribute to longevity.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Again, no one is disputing that protein is important. It’s crucial to get enough and, as Ferree pointed out, it’s especially important to get enough as we age. But other nutrients are important too, which is why Sehgal said the best diet for longevity is a balanced one that includes a wide variety of nutrient-rich foods. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The benefit of eating a balanced diet full of plants certainly isn’t revolutionary news, but it is backed up by many scientific studies. When it comes to longevity — and health in general — science-backed wins out over trendy and new. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/is-protein-healthy_l_66db5de1e4b01c1d24fc1de6" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7918805"&gt;&lt;em&gt;HuffPost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:31:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibEFVX3lxTE9TeDdQR25mYnVwZG1taFJTUEJja1NqUnJBT0dySC0wN0VuT0tuVS1nZjh6WWVvUmpWaXdNcnc5VEtDYU5SLVcyY1lFaVNHTElEajVaLTVCLUdCTlRRaFRTWkgxSEM0NkhPeGhCbg</guid></item><item><title>长期以来，这种习惯一直被认为是“健康”的，但现在一些长寿专家对此提出了警告- Yahoo Lifestyle Canada</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV95cUxPVHZQODZ3V19KYktLN0E5VU5XNHlIVW5CdjFCTkxWSHA1TjMxaFNPQi1BcktGQVBqUV9hRDR2Qml3V0t5YW1wRlYzX2NaZi02eE5KLXZjS1BEYkF1OHpldVIwUXc1OHFHUzBaX2NzZ2dnT18xN3NDLWRrR2REM0NMcUxB?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Getting &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/steps-reduce-risk-chronic-diseases-diabetes_l_63504e1ee4b0b7f89f5d77eb" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:10,000 steps a day;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;10,000 steps a day&lt;/a&gt;. Improving your &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/dare-to-be-100-how-old-ar_b_7443528" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:VO2 max;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;VO2 max&lt;/a&gt;. Putting &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/best-foods-for-longevity_l_65bd4bbde4b0102bd2d9247f" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:berries on your breakfast;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;berries on your breakfast&lt;/a&gt;. What are the habits you embrace in an effort to live a long, healthy life? Certainly it’s the routines we do regularly that impact our health the most.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But there’s one well-intentioned habit in particular that longevity experts say can actually take years off your life instead of adding more to it: eating too much animal-based protein. Thought a high-protein diet was a good thing? As doctors explain here, getting too much can backfire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Overemphasizing Protein Isn’t Actually Healthy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/toxic-things-about-women-society-normalizes?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:17 Toxic "Lies" Society Normalizes About Women That Are Actually Scams, According To Older Women;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;17 Toxic "Lies" Society Normalizes About Women That Are Actually Scams, According To Older Women&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Anna Blazhuk / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Whey protein powder in a measuring scoop, protein shake in a glass and strawberry on pink table in sunlight&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/maryleavines/marriage-fallopian-tube-removal-infertility-divorce?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:I Had My Fallopian Tubes Removed To End My Marriage. My Then-Husband's Reaction Shocked Me.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;I Had My Fallopian Tubes Removed To End My Marriage. My Then-Husband's Reaction Shocked Me.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Before we get into why too much protein isn’t good for longevity, it’s important to note that the nutrient is absolutely important. &lt;a href="https://www.a4m.com/suzanne-ferree.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Suzanne J. Ferree;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Suzanne J. Ferree&lt;/a&gt;, who is double-board-certified in family medicine and anti-aging and regenerative medicine, told HuffPost that it’s especially important to get enough as we age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“The common theory is that we need to cut protein-rich foods as we age, but the research actually only supports this in younger people, not in those of us over 50,” Ferree said. &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC8068133" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Scientific research backs this up;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Scientific research backs this up&lt;/a&gt;, showing that older adults need more protein than younger adults because our bodies naturally lose muscle as we age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So yes, protein is absolutely important. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/how-much-protein-to-eat_l_63a22684e4b0aeb2ace83986" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:How much protein a person needs each day;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;How much protein a person needs each day&lt;/a&gt; varies based on one’s individual health and needs, but the Food and Drug Administration recommends aiming for 50 grams of protein a day as part of a 2,000-calorie diet. The problem is that many people are eating more protein than they need. On top of that, Americans are overconsuming a specific type of protein that isn’t all that healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In general, there are two types of proteins: animal-based proteins and plant-based proteins. &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC10222455" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Research has shown;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Research has shown&lt;/a&gt; that plant-based proteins are healthier than animal-based proteins. Unfortunately, Americans are consuming more of the latter than the former.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“A common mistake is the overemphasis on consuming a high-protein diet, particularly one rich in animal-based proteins, with the belief that it is essential for longevity and muscle preservation. Many people assume that the more protein they consume, the healthier they will be, leading to an overconsumption of animal products like meat, dairy and eggs,” said &lt;a href="https://www.drbhanote.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Monisha Bhanote;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Monisha Bhanote&lt;/a&gt;, a quintuple-board-certified physician and longevity expert.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Most Americans are eating &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/07/28/well/eat/how-much-protein-do-we-need.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:about 100 grams;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;about 100 grams&lt;/a&gt; of protein a day, double the recommended amount. &lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2021-03/Dietary_Guidelines_for_Americans-2020-2025.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:According to a Dietary Guidelines for Americans report;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;According to a Dietary Guidelines for Americans report&lt;/a&gt;, 75% of Americans meet or exceed the recommendation for meat, poultry and eggs. Bhanote says this is exactly what can take years off one’s life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Marilyna / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/scarymouse/wholesome-posts-from-this-week-march-14?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:20 Wholesome Posts I Found On The Internet This Week That Are So Urgently Needed Right Now;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;20 Wholesome Posts I Found On The Internet This Week That Are So Urgently Needed Right Now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Excessive consumption of animal-based proteins can actually accelerate aging and undermine cellular health, contrary to popular belief,” she said. She explained that the biggest reasons for this come down to two harmful compounds: advanced glycation end products (AGEs) and trimethylamine N-oxide (TMAO).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“AGEs are harmful compounds that form when proteins or fats combine with sugar in the bloodstream,” Bhanote said. She explained that animal-based foods — especially if they are grilled, fried or roasted — are high in AGEs. &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6600625/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Research shows;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Research shows&lt;/a&gt; that these compounds can accumulate in your tissues and, over time, can lead to oxidative stress and inflammation, which are key drivers of cellular aging. “AGEs damage proteins, DNA and other vital cellular structures, accelerating the aging process and contributing to chronic diseases like diabetes, cardiovascular disease and Alzheimer’s,” Bhanote said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;What about TMAO? Bhanote explained that elevated levels of &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC9235870/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:TMAO;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;TMAO&lt;/a&gt; have been linked to an increased risk of cardiovascular diseases, including atherosclerosis, heart attack and stroke — all of which obviously are not good for longevity. “TMAO promotes the accumulation of cholesterol in the arteries and impairs the body’s ability to remove it, leading to inflammation and further damage to the cardiovascular system. This not only compromises heart health but also affects overall cellular function and longevity,” Bhanote said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Related to the mistake many people make of overemphasizing protein in their diet, &lt;a href="https://cbb.yale.edu/people/raghav-sehgal" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Raghav Sehgal;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Raghav Sehgal&lt;/a&gt;, a Ph.D. student and Gruber fellow at Yale University whose research focuses on human aging, told HuffPost that one common mistake people make when it comes to longevity is focusing on “miracle diets” promising fast results. The biggie that’s relevant here: the &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/keto-effects-body_l_5d9b58abe4b099389803e441" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:ketogenic diet;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;ketogenic diet&lt;/a&gt;, which prioritizes fat and protein while minimizing carbohydrates. For many people doing keto, meat and eggs are hero foods; however, as previously explained, eating too many animal products can take years off your life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How To Use Protein To Work For You, Not Against You  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Aleksandr Zubkov / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/scarymouse/wholesome-posts-from-this-week-april-4?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:19 Wholesome Posts I Saw This Week That Were So Cute, They Legitimately Put Me In A Happier Mood;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;19 Wholesome Posts I Saw This Week That Were So Cute, They Legitimately Put Me In A Happier Mood&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So, how should we approach protein with an eye toward longevity? Bhanote and Sehgal are of the same mind about this: Eat more protein-rich plants and fish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While fish certainly isn’t a plant, it is thought of differently than animal-based proteins because it has a completely different nutritional makeup than meat, and scientific research has repeatedly shown benefits to human health when consumed regularly. Eating fish regularly has been associated with &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25969396/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:reducing the risk of premature death by 12%.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;reducing the risk of premature death by 12%.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Sehgal explained that plant-based proteins (such as beans, lentils, chickpeas, soy, nuts and seeds) are loaded with antioxidants, fiber and nutrients that keep our hearts healthy, reduce inflammation and lower the risk of chronic diseases. “These foods are naturally low in AGEs and do not contribute to TMAO production, making them much gentler on your cells and overall health,” Bhanote added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC8804093" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Scientific studies show;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Scientific studies show&lt;/a&gt; that having a diet that prioritizes plant-based proteins lowers the risk of mortality associated with cardiovascular disease and other causes. In other words, replacing animal proteins with plant proteins can add years to your life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While most Americans meet or exceed the protein recommendation for meat, poultry and eggs, 90% of Americans &lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2021-03/Dietary_Guidelines_for_Americans-2020-2025.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:aren’t meeting the recommended guidelines for seafood;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;aren’t meeting the recommended guidelines for seafood&lt;/a&gt;. Sehgal told HuffPost that seafood high in protein and unsaturated fats supports &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32529206/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:brain health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;brain health&lt;/a&gt;, promotes &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC8182174/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:hormone balance;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;hormone balance&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC8199776/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:helps fight inflammation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;helps fight inflammation&lt;/a&gt; — all of which contribute to longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Again, no one is disputing that protein is important. It’s crucial to get enough and, as Ferree pointed out, it’s especially important to get enough as we age. But other nutrients are important too, which is why Sehgal said the best diet for longevity is a balanced one that includes a wide variety of nutrient-rich foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The benefit of eating a balanced diet full of plants certainly isn’t revolutionary news, but it is backed up by many scientific studies. When it comes to longevity — and health in general — science-backed wins out over trendy and new. &lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/is-protein-healthy_l_66db5de1e4b01c1d24fc1de6" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:HuffPost.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;HuffPost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/alanavalko/unhinged-microfeminisms?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:&amp;quot;He Thinks This Is Hostile And He Is Correct&amp;quot; — Women Are Sharing The &amp;quot;Unhinged&amp;quot; Ways They Practice Microfeminism That Reaally Grind A Small Man's Gears;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;"He Thinks This Is Hostile And He Is Correct" — Women Are Sharing The "Unhinged" Ways They Practice Microfeminism That Reaally Grind A Small Man's Gears&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/alexandraschlagel/which-zodiac-sign-is-the-most-datable?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:It's Time To Find Out Which Zodiac Sign Is The Most Datable;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;It's Time To Find Out Which Zodiac Sign Is The Most Datable&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/dannicaramirez/ugly-privilege-viral-tik-tok-explained?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:A Woman Went Viral After Saying She Has &amp;quot;Ugly Privilege&amp;quot; — Here's What It Means And What It Says About Society Today;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;A Woman Went Viral After Saying She Has "Ugly Privilege" — Here's What It Means And What It Says About Society Today&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/emilylaurence/is-protein-healthy-sc?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read it on BuzzFeed.com;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Read it on BuzzFeed.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Lifestyle Canada</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxPVHZQODZ3V19KYktLN0E5VU5XNHlIVW5CdjFCTkxWSHA1TjMxaFNPQi1BcktGQVBqUV9hRDR2Qml3V0t5YW1wRlYzX2NaZi02eE5KLXZjS1BEYkF1OHpldVIwUXc1OHFHUzBaX2NzZ2dnT18xN3NDLWRrR2REM0NMcUxB</guid></item><item><title>瘟疫在Evergreen附近杀死猫，自2023年以来首次在Jeffco确诊病例- KDVR</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipgFBVV95cUxPT0k0MTZtVENqY0hiQU5rOUpMNDYzdDBXNkNfT3dGZGEtMGcza2tTSTlySTFJTExPSnR6SGJRTFR2SGpaOUVaRlBlZG84WmNDMHRjM3NDU0dWVGRXQkwzTWtqM0VySzNMZlVVUmJrZHYtRENmaFF5dUZ4cDJhUjN6VXd0UEkwUS1VT0RXYl80c2dTRlhoNnkyNXR5akRJd3c5bmlyMEFB0gGrAUFVX3lxTE9XOUtBOUU3dEZIWmNxVTB4NHQzdExDeWtRVTZ6bm9PQ0VFc2t0eFVybnRsUWQ3bmdmN29KZ3RVYXdVdHhFNnpSeEtCZ0Itb0laUlBqR2YzXzVyRFh2eXJHS05hU0tFTHJ2dHQtMXZXb1JHWW9Uekl1VTE2em4zQ2FXTnVUazZnWlZsMGJyWEVpMlg5NVc1UEpHeUxEU2tqR0c3MndENVlFblV0bw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content article-body rich-text "&gt;
		
		


&lt;p&gt;DENVER (&lt;a href="http://kdvr.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;KDVR&lt;/a&gt;) — A domestic cat is dead after it contracted plague, according to Jefferson County Public Health.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The cat was located in Evergreen near Cub Creek Park, and is being hailed as the first confirmed plague case in Jefferson County since 2023. The agency said the cat did not survive the disease.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;“It’s not uncommon to see a few animal cases of plague in the warmer months in Colorado,” said Jim Rada, Jefferson County Environmental Health Director. “Like with this case, sometimes our local veterinarians are the first to see plague when our pets get sick. In many ways, they are a first line of defense both in helping keep our pets safe from fleas that could make our pets sick and in treating them if they are exposed to plague.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p hidden data-minutemedia-viewport="mobile" data-player-id="nrh3mjd6" data-stn-player="" data-s2n-api="minuteMediaS2NApi"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What is plague? Can you treat plague?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Jefferson County Public Health explained that plague is a disease caused by bacteria and is often spread to humans and pets through flea bites or direct contact with infected animals. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p hidden data-minutemedia-viewport="desktop" data-player-id="nrh3mjd6" data-stn-player="" data-s2n-api="minuteMediaS2NApi"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The health department said that human cases of plague are rare and can be life-threatening if not treated. Early, effective treatment includes antibiotics. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Symptoms of plague in humans may include sudden high fever, chills, headache, nausea and swollen lymph nodes. Symptoms of the disease in pets can include fever, low energy, loss of appetite and swollen lymph nodes.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;To reduce the risk of getting plague, officials recommend that you:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay away from wild animals&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Never touch dead or sick animals&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Keep pets on leashes and away from wildlife&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Do not let pets roam freely outside&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Talk to your vet about flea prevention in pets&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Watch for signs of illness in pets&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Seek medical attention if you feel sick&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Anyone who is concerned they may have been exposed to plague or has symptoms is asked to contact their healthcare provider immediately. &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;If there’s concern that a pet has been exposed or has symptoms, contact a veterinarian as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;More information about plague is available from &lt;a href="https://www.jeffco.us/2368/Plague" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Jefferson County Public Health online&lt;/a&gt; or by calling 303-232-6301.&lt;/p&gt;

		&lt;p class="article-content-cta-group"&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

	
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KDVR</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:06:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPT0k0MTZtVENqY0hiQU5rOUpMNDYzdDBXNkNfT3dGZGEtMGcza2tTSTlySTFJTExPSnR6SGJRTFR2SGpaOUVaRlBlZG84WmNDMHRjM3NDU0dWVGRXQkwzTWtqM0VySzNMZlVVUmJrZHYtRENmaFF5dUZ4cDJhUjN6VXd0UEkwUS1VT0RXYl80c2dTRlhoNnkyNXR5akRJd3c5bmlyMEFB0gGrAUFVX3lxTE9XOUtBOUU3dEZIWmNxVTB4NHQzdExDeWtRVTZ6bm9PQ0VFc2t0eFVybnRsUWQ3bmdmN29KZ3RVYXdVdHhFNnpSeEtCZ0Itb0laUlBqR2YzXzVyRFh2eXJHS05hU0tFTHJ2dHQtMXZXb1JHWW9Uekl1VTE2em4zQ2FXTnVUazZnWlZsMGJyWEVpMlg5NVc1UEpHeUxEU2tqR0c3MndENVlFblV0bw</guid></item><item><title>华盛顿调查可能的第一个本地疟疾病例- KING5.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi0wFBVV95cUxPUjVHbGVkYWpzYmRHd2drTnVEVF9BZHBDOTdhVTQya3hoUnB6M1R0S1N3WnNoWXlXc2VRVmFFMjlQTmpMRFV6NHBkRFRfQWtVSVBtRlhKZkVWRjVQLWhiT0F2QVA5SWFlUGI0ai1ZdmlHWlNlNGxGeHdrQkk3Z2xYWFA4TEE4aXJjSVAwT24xallXSVdSM3c4T0l0VDNOQlBmTzJPem01eGd5Wkg0M25WaG9uRG5PbVc5ZG10c0xFd2hNTXZJMk1kaEIyWGFVMGxQZlpZ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article__summary"&gt;If confirmed, it would be Washington’s first locally acquired infection.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class="article__body"&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TACOMA, Wash. — Health officials are investigating what could be the first case of locally acquired malaria ever recorded in Washington state.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A woman in Pierce County who has not recently traveled was diagnosed with the disease Saturday and is receiving treatment, officials said. Her condition is being monitored.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While malaria infections are typically linked to travel, this case may have originated from within the state. The most likely scenario, officials say, is that a mosquito bit someone infected with a travel-related case of malaria and later transmitted the disease to the Pierce County patient.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                        
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This risk of getting infected with malaria in Pierce County remains very low,” said Dr. James Miller, Tacoma-Pierce County health officer. “Malaria is a rare disease overall in the United States — and the vast majority of cases in the United States occur following exposures in countries with ongoing transmission.”&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In response, the Tacoma-Pierce County Health Department is working with the Washington State Department of Health to implement mosquito trapping and testing in the area.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Washington typically reports 20 to 70 malaria cases per year, all tied to travel. Nationally, the U.S. sees about 2,000 to 2,500 cases annually. Between May and October 2023, 10 locally acquired cases were reported in four states — the first such U.S. cases in 20 years.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Malaria is transmitted by Anopheles mosquitoes, which live in parts of the United States. If they bite someone with an active malaria infection, they can pass the parasite to others.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Malaria can cause fever, chills, sweats and headaches. Other symptoms that can occur can affect gastrointestinal, respiratory, muscular, and neurological systems.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KING5.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0wFBVV95cUxPUjVHbGVkYWpzYmRHd2drTnVEVF9BZHBDOTdhVTQya3hoUnB6M1R0S1N3WnNoWXlXc2VRVmFFMjlQTmpMRFV6NHBkRFRfQWtVSVBtRlhKZkVWRjVQLWhiT0F2QVA5SWFlUGI0ai1ZdmlHWlNlNGxGeHdrQkk3Z2xYWFA4TEE4aXJjSVAwT24xallXSVdSM3c4T0l0VDNOQlBmTzJPem01eGd5Wkg0M25WaG9uRG5PbVc5ZG10c0xFd2hNTXZJMk1kaEIyWGFVMGxQZlpZ</guid></item><item><title>在科罗拉多斯普林斯发现的蝙蝠狂犬病检测呈阳性- KKTV</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiAFBVV95cUxPU0VSLVNIYUswTGctNE1oV1RxVThQa2NSMlBDV1A3VWU2MjdsTUlCdnVtdW5OcTdQR1Qza29ETGY0NVc1SlYwRGRQa1U5WnNraWpzNDRocTZuSmVGWnB1QXJwUFI5djZaV3BJaThpcUt1SWphMGdNdldMZFg5bDFqOGd1WG9yTlla?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body | article w-100"&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;COLORADO SPRINGS, Colo. (KKTV) - El Paso County Public Health (EPCPH) shared Wednesday that a bat found in Colorado Springs had tested positive for rabies, making it the first animal in the county to test positive for the disease in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;According to county health officials, a person came in contact with the bat on Saturday, and the animal was sent off for testing. That test came back positive on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;The health department said the person who touched the bat is receiving treatment to prevent getting the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;EPCPH said that while human exposure to animals infected with rabies is rare, they want to remind the public to avoid contact with wild animals, teach children not to interact with wild animals and keep pets on a leash to prevent exposure to the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="w-100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;“Adults, and especially children, who see a sick or injured animal may naturally want to help,” Dr. Bernadette Albanese, co-medical director of El Paso County Public Health, said. “It’s important not to touch wild animals and to warn children of the dangers of wildlife encounters. Animals that are sick or injured should be reported to Colorado Parks and Wildlife. The public should be particularly cautious in the summer months when people spend more time outdoors.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;EPCPH said if you’ve had contact with a wild animal, particularly if you’ve been bitten or scratched, you should talk with a health care professional to determine your risk for rabies or other illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;The health department went on to say because bats have small teeth and bite marks may disappear quickly, you should seek medical advice and make a report to EPCPH if you have any kind of physical encounter with a bat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.elpasocountyhealth.org/rabies/" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.elpasocountyhealth.org/rabies/"&gt;Click here for more rabies prevention tips from El Paso County Public Health.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="w-100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;The health department said last year, six animals tested positive for rabies in El Paso County. All of them were bats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="copyright |"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Copyright 2025 KKTV. All rights reserved.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KKTV</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxPU0VSLVNIYUswTGctNE1oV1RxVThQa2NSMlBDV1A3VWU2MjdsTUlCdnVtdW5OcTdQR1Qza29ETGY0NVc1SlYwRGRQa1U5WnNraWpzNDRocTZuSmVGWnB1QXJwUFI5djZaV3BJaThpcUt1SWphMGdNdldMZFg5bDFqOGd1WG9yTlla</guid></item></channel></rss>