<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>5种不同寻常的健康习惯专家宣誓效忠，包括嗡嗡声-无聊的熊猫</title><link>https://www.boredpanda.com/unusual-wellness-habits-from-experts/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="open-list-post-description"&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In this age of booming social media, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;wellness trends&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; are everywhere. Some vanish overnight, while others surprise us by earning the approval of doctors and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;research-backed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; practitioners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;These aren’t your typical “drink more water” or “go for a walk” tips, but rather odd-sounding habits that no one really talks about.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;From humming to calm your nervous system to drinking coffee for its unexpected health perks, and even a handful of other rituals that seem strange at first glance, these &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;quirky practices&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; might actually be &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;more powerful&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; than they appear.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A group of experts across various fields spoke exclusively with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bored Panda&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;, breaking down exactly how these unusual techniques work.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ql-align-justify"&gt;&lt;img src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/unusual-wellness-habits-from-experts-1.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ql-align-justify"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/medium-shot-smiley-doctor-patient_34728747.htm#fromView=search&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;position=4&amp;amp;uuid=68127fff-f789-45ea-902f-44e327c60639&amp;amp;query=doctor+patient" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" class=" staff-link"&gt;freepik (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to the specialists, these surprising habits can boost your mood, soothe your mind, and improve your overall quality of life by tapping into the body’s natural rhythms rather than relying on expensive gadgets or complicated routines.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;So, here are &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5 weird-but-proven&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; health hacks that experts genuinely swear by, along with the science that makes them worth trying.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Medical Disclaimer: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;All content in this article is provided for educational purposes only and is not a substitute for medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bored Panda</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:58:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTFBVSkc0N0tCRTdPVEdoZDdWMGY5Qk9zc1hLUEFrVTJmS1loOTlrMnFuWFY5VGhHRWF6OHJFSHFGOGZoUjdNS0tacVgwUXFNYllJYmNtLWpobERPN1VMZ3hMa28tYk5PbmcxU01halZvUmV4QQ</guid></item><item><title>“他们没有症状” ： CAR-T疗法使自身免疫性疾病缓解-自然</title><link>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03885-w</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__teaser" data-test="access-teaser"&gt; &lt;figure class="figure"&gt;&lt;picture class="embed intensity--high"&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03885-w/d41586-025-03885-w_51762128.jpg?as=webp 767w, //media.nature.com/lw319/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03885-w/d41586-025-03885-w_51762128.jpg?as=webp 319w" sizes="(max-width: 319px) 319px, (min-width: 1023px) 100vw,  767px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" alt="A coloured scanning electron micrograph image of a single chimeric antigen receptor T-cell, an organic white blob with a surface covered in short tendrils." loading="lazy" src="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03885-w/d41586-025-03885-w_51762128.jpg"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="figure__caption u-sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span class="mr10"&gt;CAR T cells (pictured) are being used to treat autoimmune diseases.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Credit: Eye Of Science/Science Photo Library&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Engineered immune cells are being used to successfully treat people with a range of debilitating autoimmune conditions, such as ulcerative colitis, rheumatoid arthritis and &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-023-03968-6" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-023-03968-6" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;lupus&lt;/a&gt;. Researchers say positive results from around a dozen studies over the past three years suggest CAR-T-cell therapy could eventually be used treat any disease in which the immune system attacks the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAR-T-cell therapy exploits the immune system’s T cells that fight off infection: these cells are collected from a person and tweaked to produce proteins called chimeric antigen receptors. They are then reintroduced into the body to target antigens expressed by B cells, another type of immune cell. In autoimmune disorders, these B cells make antibodies that attack the body’s own healthy tissues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The use of the therapy for immune conditions has exploded since 2021, when a 20-year-old woman in Germany with severe lupus became the first person with an autoimmune disorder to be treated with CAR T cells&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR1" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. Clinician–researcher David Simon, who was involved in that treatment&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR2" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, says the CAR-T therapies have since entered phase I and II clinical trials for autoimmune conditions including systemic sclerosis, myositis and rheumatoid arthritis. Phase III trials are also under way for lupus and myasthenia gravis, a condition that causes weakness in the muscles that are used to breathe, swallow and see.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simon, who focuses on rheumatoid arthritis at the Charité University Hospital in Berlin, says people in CAR-T-cell therapy trials for rheumatoid arthritis and lupus seem to be ‘cured’. “They lose their autoantibodies which trigger the disease, and they don’t have any symptoms anymore,” he adds. “This is something totally new which we didn’t observe before.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAR-T-cell therapy has become a routine treatment for &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-022-00241-0" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-022-00241-0" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;several types of cancer&lt;/a&gt; since it was &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nature.2017.22304" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/nature.2017.22304" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;first approved&lt;/a&gt; to treat blood cancers in 2017. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A new frontier&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ulcerative colitis, a condition that affects the colon and causes stomach pain, ulcers and bloody diarrhoea, is one of the latest diseases in which CAR-T-cell therapy has shown promise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In September, gastroenterologist Markus Neurath and his colleagues at the University Hospital Erlangen in Germany, reported using CAR T cells to treat a 21-year-old woman with ulcerative colitis&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR3" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. After the treatment, she showed signs of remission that persisted for 14 weeks, no longer needed medication and could return to work. “The result was quite amazing,” adds Neurath. His team plans to test the treatment in a few more people before proceeding to a controlled clinical trial involving many individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, Bing Du, an immunologist at East China Normal University in Shanghai, and his team published the results of a CAR-T pilot study using immune cells from a donor to treat drug-resistant lupus&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR4" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. Donor-derived cells could act like a generic version of CAR-T treatment that could be mass-produced, cutting manufacturing time and lowering costs&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR5" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. Last year, Du was also involved in a &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-03209-4" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-03209-4" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;world-first study&lt;/a&gt; of bioengineered and modified immune cells from a donor for the treatment of two rare and severe autoimmune diseases&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR6" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of the latest study, four women with a form of lupus that affects multiple organs received chemotherapy to reduce levels of their white blood cells, followed by an infusion of donor-derived CAR T cells. After three months, the women no longer experienced symptoms such as arthritis, swelling of blood vessels and alopecia, and one was in remission and no longer needed any medication. The other three women received low-dose steroids as a maintenance therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results of the trial were “much better than we could imagine”, says Du, and might be due to CAR T cells triggering the total depletion of dysfunctional B cells that attack the body’s tissues. “The immune system had to reset not only B cells, but also the rest of the immune system,” he adds, potentially allowing new, healthy B cells to replace the dysfunctional cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Nature</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:50:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiX0FVX3lxTFB4TzRtTG95SW04eDNDanpjeWRYMUdXOUNPc0dXcW1aVXYtNUo3Zlc4UWVDeGxjblRlWUU5eVBlM3RtXzczQjBIMU1WSHNlQXYyZnFUU3lqWW1DOFFHanYw</guid></item><item><title>青春期会持续到32岁吗？科学家解锁大脑的五个时代-半岛电视台</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2025/11/26/does-adolescence-last-until-32-scientists-unlock-brains-five-eras</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wysiwyg wysiwyg--all-content" aria-live="polite" aria-atomic="true"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study has found that adolescence can continue until the age of 32, as humans hit four major “turning points” in brain development at the ages of about nine, 32, 66 and 83.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Published on Tuesday in the journal, Nature Communications, the study examined nearly 4,000 scans of the brains of participants ranging in age up to 90.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;section class="more-on"&gt;&lt;h2 class="more-on__heading"&gt;Recommended Stories &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;list of 3 items&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;end of list&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers mapped out the brain’s development using this data and discovered that humans go through five “brain phases” – and within them, four significant life turning points as they grow, mature and decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, they discovered, it is not until age 32 that human personality and intelligence “plateau” and stabilise following changes in early adolescence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-are-the-five-phases"&gt;What are the five phases?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the study, brain development and ageing undergo five separate phases:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="spaced-bullet-spacing"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Childhood – from birth to age nine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adolescence – from nine to 32&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adulthood – from 32 to 66&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Early ageing – from 66 to 83&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Late ageing – from 83 onwards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 id="when-does-the-brain-shift-from-one-phase-to-the-next"&gt;When does the brain shift from one phase to the next?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the brain adapts to new surroundings and situations between birth and old age, researchers found that four ages – nine, 32, 66 and 83 – were the most pivotal in the brain’s development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shifts are characterised by developments such as puberty, personality stabilisation, “reorganisation” and decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In detail, these are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img data-recalc-dims="1" loading="lazy" class="size-arc-image-770 wp-image-4132402" src="/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/INTERACTIVE-BRAIN-PHASES-NOV26-2025-1764155777.png?quality=80" alt="INTERACTIVE - BRAIN PHASES - NOV26, 2025-1764155777" data-interactive="true" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Childhood – birth to nine years old&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;During this period, the grey and white matter of the brain rapidly grow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to information from United States-based Johns Hopkins Medicine, while grey matter primarily processes and interprets information, white matter transmits that information to other parts of the nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the brain, grey matter refers to the darker, outer portion, while white matter describes the lighter, inner section underneath,” Johns Hopkins says. “In the spinal cord, this order is reversed: the white matter is on the outside, and the grey matter sits within.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the authors of the new study: “The first few years of life are marked by consolidation and competitive elimination of synapses [the junctions where neurons meet and communicate with each other] and rapid increases in grey and white matter volume.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This age also aligns with the onset of puberty, which begins between eight and 13 years old for females and nine and 14 years old for males, marking the initiation of significant alterations in hormone expression and robust neurological changes,” it added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The report also found that the shift to adolescence introduced an “increased risk” of mental health, cognitive and behavioural disorders due to changes in hormones and a “neurobiological shift”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Adolescence – 9 to 32&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previously, it was accepted that adolescence begins with puberty and ends before the age of 20. However, the study found that while adolescence certainly begins with puberty, its ending point is less clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The transition to adulthood is influenced by cultural, historical and social factors, making it context-dependent rather than a purely biological shift,” the researchers found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our findings suggest that in Western countries (ie, the United Kingdom and United States of America), adolescent topological development extends to around 32 years old, before brain networks begin a new trajectory of topological development,” they added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study found that by age 32 in Western countries, the brain experiences the “most directional changes and a large shift in trajectory” compared with other turning points in life, as this is when white matter integrity and volume in the brain are increasing rapidly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors did not suggest a reason for this being the case in Western countries, and did not elaborate on how adolescence continues in people in other regions of the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Adulthood – 32 to 66&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study found that while brain development rapidly accelerates during the first two phases of life, in adulthood – the longest phase – there are no major turning points until the 60s, as the brain develops more slowly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This period of network stability also corresponds with a plateau in intelligence and personality,” it found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early ageing – 66 to 83&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the brain does not show any abrupt signs of decline during this phase, shifts in the patterns of connection in the brain do occur due to a decrease in white matter integrity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brain now works more independently in separate regions, coordinating less as a single whole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The early 60s mark an important shift in health and cognition, with the onset of dementia and elevated blood pressure for many, both of which can accelerate brain ageing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Late ageing – 83 onwards&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;While there is less data on this era of the brain’s progression than the other phases due to a low sample size, the study’s findings correlated with a declining trend in brain connectivity, the authors said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Therefore, this could reflect a true weakening relationship between age and structural brain topology in late life,” they added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="why-is-this-significant"&gt;Why is this significant?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new research into the period of adolescence is the most significant finding from the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the World Health Organization, adolescence ranges from 10 to 19 years of age. In 2018, a report in The Lancet medical journal found that adolescence ended in the 20s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Duncan Astle, professor of neuroinformatics at Cambridge University in England and one of the authors of the study, told The Independent newspaper that the new report helps us better understand the brain’s vulnerabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Looking back, many of us feel our lives have been characterised by different phases. It turns out that brains also go through these eras,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Al Jazeera</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:33:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxNR0lXWW94U29PM0pjcUllbVJLaTNjeTZYMlpFRXhKR0l2NVZPRzdGUVpNRUlESU0tRFMweXF6alpIVy1rSDZyODRCUndaYXJocmk0M2d2QmhyQkhYNjRmN0dHUlFqY3c3Z1VXalJ2a0ltWEtOMDJaOU1VT21oZ1JDbXBLTnV2Zkt6VG5Qbm9rSVRIekktUUZmaG5QS0g3cy1mc0VVa1R4ZUVFN0U</guid></item><item><title>青春期会持续到32岁吗？科学家解锁大脑的五个时代-半岛电视台</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2025/11/26/does-adolescence-last-until-32-scientists-unlock-brains-five-eras</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wysiwyg wysiwyg--all-content" aria-live="polite" aria-atomic="true"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study has found that adolescence can continue until the age of 32, as humans hit four major “turning points” in brain development at the ages of about nine, 32, 66 and 83.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Published on Tuesday in the journal, Nature Communications, the study examined nearly 4,000 scans of the brains of participants ranging in age up to 90.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;section class="more-on"&gt;&lt;h2 class="more-on__heading"&gt;Recommended Stories &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;list of 3 items&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;end of list&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers mapped out the brain’s development using this data and discovered that humans go through five “brain phases” – and within them, four significant life turning points as they grow, mature and decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, they discovered, it is not until age 32 that human personality and intelligence “plateau” and stabilise following changes in early adolescence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-are-the-five-phases"&gt;What are the five phases?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the study, brain development and ageing undergo five separate phases:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="spaced-bullet-spacing"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Childhood – from birth to age nine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adolescence – from nine to 32&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adulthood – from 32 to 66&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Early ageing – from 66 to 83&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Late ageing – from 83 onwards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 id="when-does-the-brain-shift-from-one-phase-to-the-next"&gt;When does the brain shift from one phase to the next?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the brain adapts to new surroundings and situations between birth and old age, researchers found that four ages – nine, 32, 66 and 83 – were the most pivotal in the brain’s development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shifts are characterised by developments such as puberty, personality stabilisation, “reorganisation” and decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In detail, these are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img data-recalc-dims="1" loading="lazy" class="size-arc-image-770 wp-image-4132402" src="/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/INTERACTIVE-BRAIN-PHASES-NOV26-2025-1764155777.png?quality=80" alt="INTERACTIVE - BRAIN PHASES - NOV26, 2025-1764155777" data-interactive="true" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Childhood – birth to nine years old&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;During this period, the grey and white matter of the brain rapidly grow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to information from United States-based Johns Hopkins Medicine, while grey matter primarily processes and interprets information, white matter transmits that information to other parts of the nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the brain, grey matter refers to the darker, outer portion, while white matter describes the lighter, inner section underneath,” Johns Hopkins says. “In the spinal cord, this order is reversed: the white matter is on the outside, and the grey matter sits within.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the authors of the new study: “The first few years of life are marked by consolidation and competitive elimination of synapses [the junctions where neurons meet and communicate with each other] and rapid increases in grey and white matter volume.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This age also aligns with the onset of puberty, which begins between eight and 13 years old for females and nine and 14 years old for males, marking the initiation of significant alterations in hormone expression and robust neurological changes,” it added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The report also found that the shift to adolescence introduced an “increased risk” of mental health, cognitive and behavioural disorders due to changes in hormones and a “neurobiological shift”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Adolescence – 9 to 32&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previously, it was accepted that adolescence begins with puberty and ends before the age of 20. However, the study found that while adolescence certainly begins with puberty, its ending point is less clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The transition to adulthood is influenced by cultural, historical and social factors, making it context-dependent rather than a purely biological shift,” the researchers found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our findings suggest that in Western countries (ie, the United Kingdom and United States of America), adolescent topological development extends to around 32 years old, before brain networks begin a new trajectory of topological development,” they added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study found that by age 32 in Western countries, the brain experiences the “most directional changes and a large shift in trajectory” compared with other turning points in life, as this is when white matter integrity and volume in the brain are increasing rapidly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors did not suggest a reason for this being the case in Western countries, and did not elaborate on how adolescence continues in people in other regions of the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Adulthood – 32 to 66&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study found that while brain development rapidly accelerates during the first two phases of life, in adulthood – the longest phase – there are no major turning points until the 60s, as the brain develops more slowly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This period of network stability also corresponds with a plateau in intelligence and personality,” it found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early ageing – 66 to 83&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the brain does not show any abrupt signs of decline during this phase, shifts in the patterns of connection in the brain do occur due to a decrease in white matter integrity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brain now works more independently in separate regions, coordinating less as a single whole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The early 60s mark an important shift in health and cognition, with the onset of dementia and elevated blood pressure for many, both of which can accelerate brain ageing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Late ageing – 83 onwards&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;While there is less data on this era of the brain’s progression than the other phases due to a low sample size, the study’s findings correlated with a declining trend in brain connectivity, the authors said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Therefore, this could reflect a true weakening relationship between age and structural brain topology in late life,” they added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="why-is-this-significant"&gt;Why is this significant?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new research into the period of adolescence is the most significant finding from the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the World Health Organization, adolescence ranges from 10 to 19 years of age. In 2018, a report in The Lancet medical journal found that adolescence ended in the 20s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Duncan Astle, professor of neuroinformatics at Cambridge University in England and one of the authors of the study, told The Independent newspaper that the new report helps us better understand the brain’s vulnerabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Looking back, many of us feel our lives have been characterised by different phases. It turns out that brains also go through these eras,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Al Jazeera</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:33:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxNR0lXWW94U29PM0pjcUllbVJLaTNjeTZYMlpFRXhKR0l2NVZPRzdGUVpNRUlESU0tRFMweXF6alpIVy1rSDZyODRCUndaYXJocmk0M2d2QmhyQkhYNjRmN0dHUlFqY3c3Z1VXalJ2a0ltWEtOMDJaOU1VT21oZ1JDbXBLTnV2Zkt6VG5Qbm9rSVRIekktUUZmaG5QS0g3cy1mc0VVa1R4ZUVFN0XSAbABQVVfeXFMTU5GaFZmODZBSDR0TDNWNWV5S1FzdzVOQ3hDeWEwT3ZqMU5JeUp1M3dKc0llRHlCX2MzUXp3dVBzVjJ5YUZHcEVQSC1pT1ZVSXAzeVdkMXEzSGhGeVc0X1JJYXVFUUw4bnoycW9FNHdXS1RjLVR1RVpnREFvdzJMM2FIdElUM2xPT1Zrd0ZzMTNZeHU5MzlZOFBUVmdrRG9nLVZ5NlVqZEZrcno2c0w5ZFE</guid></item><item><title>ADHD诊断正在增长。怎么回事？ -大自然</title><link>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03855-2</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__teaser" data-test="access-teaser"&gt; &lt;p&gt;In some parts of the world, record numbers of people are being diagnosed with attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD). In the United States, for example, government researchers last year reported that more than 11% of children had received an ADHD diagnosis at some point in their lives&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR1" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; — a sharp increase from 2003, when around 8% of children had (see ‘ADHD among US boys and girls’).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;article class="recommended pull pull--left u-sans-serif" data-label="Related"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03143-z" class="u-link-inherit" data-track="click" data-track-label="recommended article"&gt;&lt;img class="recommended__image" alt="" src="//media.nature.com/w400/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03855-2/d41586-025-03855-2_51483336.jpg"&gt;&lt;p class="recommended__title u-serif"&gt;Why is autism really on the rise? What the science says&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But now, top US health officials argue that diagnoses have spiralled out of control. In May, the Make America Healthy Again Commission — led by US health secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr — said ADHD was part of a “crisis of overdiagnosis and overtreatment” and suggested that ADHD medications did not help children in the long term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what, exactly, is going on?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One thing that’s clear is that several factors — including improved detection and greater awareness of ADHD — are causing people with symptoms to receive a diagnosis and treatment, whereas they wouldn’t have years earlier. Clinicians say this is especially true for women and girls, whose pattern of symptoms was often missed in the past. Although some specialists are concerned about the risks of overdiagnosis, many are more worried that too many people go undiagnosed and untreated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, the rise in awareness and diagnoses of ADHD has fuelled a public debate about how it should be viewed and how best to provide support, including when medication is required. The emergence of the neurodiversity movement is challenging the view of ADHD as a disorder that should be ‘treated’, and instead proposes that it’s a difference that should be better understood and supported — with more focus on adapting schools and workplaces, for instance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="figure"&gt;&lt;picture class="embed intensity--high"&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03855-2/d41586-025-03855-2_51741560.png?as=webp 767w, //media.nature.com/lw319/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03855-2/d41586-025-03855-2_51741560.png?as=webp 319w" sizes="(max-width: 319px) 319px, (min-width: 1023px) 100vw,  767px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" alt="ADHD among US boys and girls. Chart showing that ADHD prevalence among children in the United States varies by age and is higher for boys than for girls." loading="lazy" src="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03855-2/d41586-025-03855-2_51741560.png"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="figure__caption u-sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Source: Ref. 1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I do have a big problem with ‘disorder’,” says Jeff Karp, a biomedical engineer at Brigham and Women’s Hospital in Boston, Massachusetts, who has ADHD. “It’s the school system that’s disordered. It’s not the kids.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But many clinicians and people with ADHD argue that it is associated with difficulties — ranging from academic struggles to an increased chance of injuries and substance misuse — that justify its label as a medical condition, and say that medication is an important and effective part of therapy for many people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I hear a lot of people talking about ADHD being a gift and a superpower, and I do applaud that,” says Jeremy Didier, a clinician specializing in ADHD who is president of Children and Adults with Attention Deficit–Hyperactivity Disorder (CHADD), a non-profit US group based in Lanham, Maryland, and who has ADHD herself. “But I do not want to downplay the impact that ADHD can have on someone’s life when it’s either undiagnosed or poorly managed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She and others say both models — neurodiversity and medical — have merit. “Bringing those two together in a meaningful and productive way, I think that’s maybe the biggest challenge” for the field, says Sven Bölte, a specialist in child and adolescent psychiatric science at the Karolinska Institute in Stockholm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A real rise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A slew of studies suggests that diagnoses of ADHD have gone up in many high-income countries in the past two to three decades — similar to a &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02636-1" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02636-1" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;rise in autism diagnoses&lt;/a&gt; (see ‘ADHD on the rise’). The rate of new ADHD diagnoses in the United Kingdom, for example, doubled in boys and quadrupled in girls between 2000 and 2018, according to one study&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR2" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. In adults, the rate shot up even more. “We have numbers suggesting that we’re seeing a rise,” says Max Wiznitzer, a paediatric neurologist at Rainbow Babies and Children’s Hospital in Cleveland, Ohio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="figure"&gt;&lt;picture class="embed intensity--high"&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03855-2/d41586-025-03855-2_51741554.png?as=webp 767w, //media.nature.com/lw319/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03855-2/d41586-025-03855-2_51741554.png?as=webp 319w" sizes="(max-width: 319px) 319px, (min-width: 1023px) 100vw,  767px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" alt="ADHD on the rise. Chart showing the increase of ADHD diagnoses in the US between 1997 and 2018." loading="lazy" src="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03855-2/d41586-025-03855-2_51741554.png"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="figure__caption u-sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Source: US CDC NHIS Annu. Rep. (&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/adhd/data/adhd-throughout-the-years.html" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.cdc.gov/adhd/data/adhd-throughout-the-years.html" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;https://go.nature.com/3XEGYXJ&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what explains the surge? It doesn’t seem to be a big rise in the prevalence of the symptoms and traits that characterize ADHD — namely hyperactivity, impulsivity and inattention, researchers say. When scientists use standard procedures to rigorously assess symptoms in representative samples of a population, they find that the ‘true’ prevalence of ADHD is fairly consistent in different parts of the world — estimated at around 5.4% in children&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR3" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; and 2.6% in adults&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR4" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, according to two comprehensive global studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts say there are several reasons these figures are much lower than the 11% diagnosis level in US children that the country’s health authorities reported last year&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR1" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. That number comes from the US National Survey of Children’s Health conducted in 2022, in which parents were asked whether a doctor or other health-care provider had ever said their child has ADHD. But this method of assessing prevalence would lead to inflated counts, says Luis Rohde, a psychiatrist and ADHD specialist at the Federal University of Rio Grande do Sul in Porto Alegre, Brazil. Some children were probably misdiagnosed — perhaps by a physician without specialist training — and would not be classified as having ADHD in a thorough clinical evaluation. Some parents might have misremembered, perhaps if they were told that their child had symptoms without a formal diagnosis, he says. And some children who once had a diagnosis would no longer have received one at the time of the survey if their symptoms had waned and they were reassessed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;article class="recommended pull pull--left u-sans-serif" data-label="Related"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-01969-1" class="u-link-inherit" data-track="click" data-track-label="recommended article"&gt;&lt;img class="recommended__image" alt="" src="//media.nature.com/w400/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03855-2/d41586-025-03855-2_51250548.png"&gt;&lt;p class="recommended__title u-serif"&gt;How to make America healthy: the real problems — and best fixes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers and specialists highlight other factors that are likely to be driving up the number of diagnoses. One is a change in diagnostic criteria in &lt;i&gt;The&lt;/i&gt; &lt;i&gt;Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders&lt;/i&gt; (&lt;i&gt;DSM&lt;/i&gt;). In the fourth edition of this widely used manual, introduced in 1994, a child or adult ADHD diagnosis required the presence of at least six of a list of nine inattention symptoms and/or six or more of nine hyperactivity symptoms, and stipulated that these had to be present before the age of seven. (This reflects the idea that ADHD is a neurodevelopmental condition that arises during childhood brain development.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the fifth edition, &lt;i&gt;DSM-V,&lt;/i&gt; arrived in 2013, the criteria were slightly relaxed. Symptoms had to be present before age 12, and adult diagnosis required a minimum of five symptoms. (Children still had to have at least six.) “So when we expand the criteria, obviously you increase a little bit the prevalence,” says Rohde, who was involved in those revisions. It has also become more common for clinicians to diagnose ADHD along with other conditions, when in the past they tended to focus on one, says Bölte: “That fuels the figures.” ADHD commonly occurs with autism, as well as with anxiety, depression and other disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The impairment requirement&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, a thorough ADHD assessment involves collecting a detailed history and completing behaviour questionnaires, including input from family members and, for children, from schools. In the United States, the condition can be diagnosed by a range of health professionals, including psychiatrists, other mental-health specialists and primary-care physicians such as paediatricians, who might not have dedicated training in ADHD. But countries differ: in Brazil and many other low- and middle-income nations, people with ADHD symptoms tend to be sent to neurologists and psychiatrists for ADHD assessment and diagnoses, and there is a shortage of such specialists, Rohde says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;i&gt;DSM-V&lt;/i&gt; defines three ‘presentations’ of ADHD. People with ‘predominantly inattentive’ ADHD show symptoms such as making careless mistakes, struggling to sustain attention, losing things and being easily distracted. Those with predominantly hyperactive-impulsive ADHD have traits such as fidgeting, restlessness, talking excessively and interrupting others. In a third, combined presentation, people show both sets of symptoms. A diagnosis requires that symptoms are present for at least six months and in two or more settings (such as school, home, work); are not explained by another condition such as anxiety; and cause an impairment, such as struggling with schoolwork, losing a job or having relationship problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="figure"&gt;&lt;picture class="embed intensity--high"&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03855-2/d41586-025-03855-2_51736478.jpg?as=webp 767w, //media.nature.com/lw319/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03855-2/d41586-025-03855-2_51736478.jpg?as=webp 319w" sizes="(max-width: 319px) 319px, (min-width: 1023px) 100vw,  767px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" alt="Conceptual illustration showing an abstract human profile with a jumbled pink string inside." loading="lazy" src="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03855-2/d41586-025-03855-2_51736478.jpg"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="figure__caption u-sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Illustration by Ada Zielińska&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The impairment requirement is key, clinicians say. These traits vary across the population: some individuals are very hyperactive or inattentive, and some not at all. But people tend to be diagnosed with ADHD when their symptoms significantly interfere with their lives. “The medical part of ADHD comes in when your life is becoming derailed,” says Margaret Sibley, a specialist in psychiatry and behavioural sciences at the University of Washington School of Medicine in Seattle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bölte says that clinicians are interpreting the diagnostic criteria “far more liberally and openly” than in the past. This is another factor — aside from changes in the diagnostic criteria — that is driving the apparent surge in ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But working out when someone crosses the impairment line involves a subjective and sometimes tricky judgement, say specialists. And there is an ongoing debate about whether a person’s level of impairment should be defined relative to their own potential or to a population average.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s clear is that more parents as well as children are deemed as crossing that threshold. Wiznitzer says that when he diagnoses a child, “almost invariably [one of] the parents has it”, too. (That’s because genes are a major contributor to ADHD: the disorder has a heritability&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR5" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; of roughly 70–80%.) Even though the parents were probably symptomatic as children, many were not identified as having the condition, he says. But now, they are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;ADHD on TikTok&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another reason why diagnoses have surged is an increase in public awareness of ADHD — fuelled by an explosion of discussion on TikTok and other social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Information online “connects with some people who have had these symptoms and impairments for a long time, but never understood what they were,” says Sibley. That leads them to seek information and professional help, pushing diagnoses up. And people might be eager to receive a diagnosis if it allows them to access help and services for themselves or a child, such as adaptations to support learning at school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The surge in ADHD has led to concerns, particularly in the United States, about questionable diagnoses being given without a thorough clinical evaluation — through online services, for example, or by medical professionals without ADHD training. “They’ve got a visit for 15 or 20 minutes, and the diagnosis is made,” says Stephen Hinshaw, a specialist in child and adolescent mental health and ADHD at the University of California, Berkeley. But Didier says that a bigger problem is the number of people with ADHD who are undiagnosed or untreated. She emphasizes how important it is for people to have access to a thorough, accurate assessment from a trained professional who specializes in ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lack of recognition of ADHD is a particular problem in low- and middle-income countries, says Rohde. “The problem here is clearly underdiagnosis, stigma and undertreatment,” he says, which particularly affects “vulnerable people and communities”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;article class="recommended pull pull--left u-sans-serif" data-label="Related"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02636-1" class="u-link-inherit" data-track="click" data-track-label="recommended article"&gt;&lt;img class="recommended__image" alt="" src="//media.nature.com/w400/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03855-2/d41586-025-03855-2_51426444.jpg"&gt;&lt;p class="recommended__title u-serif"&gt;Autism is on the rise: what’s really behind the increase?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many specialists say they’re observing a rapid rise of diagnoses in girls and women&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR6" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. In part, that’s thought to be because women and girls are more likely to have symptoms of inattention — rather than more-noticeable hyperactivity — and to find organizational and other strategies that ‘mask’ those symptoms. Didier says that, despite being an ADHD specialist and diagnosing the condition in three of her sons, she and other ADHD practitioners missed the signs and symptoms in her daughter until she was a teenager. “It’s egregious that we don’t have more research on ADHD trajectories in women,” Sibley says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changes in the world itself are yet another possible contributor to increased diagnoses. Some researchers speculate that schools, work, technology and other aspects of modern lives have become so complex and taxing that they are pushing more people beyond the threshold of impairment. In Sweden, says Bölte, schools are sometimes chaotic, with complex schedules and grading systems. “Many students are very confused and fed up with school and do not understand it any more,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study published last year&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR7" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; revealed that parents think their children are struggling more. The research team examined how parents viewed the ADHD symptoms of more than 27,000 nine-year-old children born in Sweden. Parents consulted in 2016–18 tended to say that their children were more impaired than did parents consulted in 2004–06, even though their kids had the same number of symptoms. “Environment around the child is crucial,” says Samuele Cortese, who studies ADHD at the University of Southampton, UK, and was involved in the work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Context is key&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Karp describes ADHD as “context-dependent”. In a school where children are expected to sit still and be quiet, “it makes these traits seem like a problem”, he says. But when someone with ADHD is in an environment that nurtures and empowers them, they “can then channel their neurotype to do incredible things”. Karp is not against medication — and sometimes takes it himself — but would like more emphasis on institutions and society evolving so that people with ADHD can thrive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers, meanwhile, are finding evidence that the severity of symptoms can vary over time. In a 2021 study, Sibley and her colleagues analysed detailed records of more than 550 children who were diagnosed with ADHD and followed for up to 16 years&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR8" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. The researchers found that 64% of young people had fluctuations in ADHD — times when their symptoms faded but then recurred.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sibley and her team hypothesized that people’s symptoms might flare up when they were facing increased demands in their lives, such as when starting a new school or having a child. But in fact, the opposite seemed to be true, according to a later analysis by Sibley and her colleagues&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR9" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. This could be because people are able to take on more responsibility when their symptoms abate. But the alternative explanation — one that has “really resonated”, Sibley says — is that people with ADHD need a degree of activity and accountability in their lives to perform and stay engaged. Sibley thinks there might be a U-shaped curve: too many or too few demands and obligations mean that people with ADHD don’t function at their best — but at a “sweet spot”, they do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Nature</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 10:02:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiX0FVX3lxTE9SZmV2VUEzamtFbVMtYkZBQ0JOS0o3OFFmZjZjZUtCM1RQOXVkQlZkTGRlZzdCUEhXYWZWQzJ2WldfUkpMLTNpM1RSaHlWY3VRNWt2VXJGR2dFTGdVS2pR</guid></item><item><title>“微生物组有点像森林” ：阴道中的细菌如何改善健康- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20251125-how-bacteria-in-the-vagina-can-improve-health</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 kfxpiP"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It's also a good idea to follow a healthy diet. Research shows that that not getting enough &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0022316622030504" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;micronutrients&lt;/a&gt;, such as vitamins A, C, D and E, β-carotene, folate and calcium, may increase the risk of BV&lt;i id="." class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;. &lt;/i&gt;A high &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0022316622093713" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;dietary fat intake&lt;/a&gt; is also associated with an increased risk of BV. Some – but not all studies – have additionally shown that obese women are also more likely to &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://microbiomejournal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s40168-021-01011-2" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;have a microbiome&lt;/a&gt; that contains fewer &lt;i id="lactobacillus," class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;Lactobacillus, &lt;/i&gt;emphasising the importance of maintaining a healthy body mass index (BMI).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Finally, it appears that smoking can affect the vaginal microbiome. One study took vaginal swabs from &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://bmcinfectdis.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/1471-2334-14-471" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;20 smokers and non-smokers&lt;/a&gt;. Half of the smokers tested had &lt;i id="lactobacillus" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;Lactobacillus&lt;/i&gt;-depleted microbiomes in comparison to just 15% of non-smokers. Studies have also revealed an increased prevalence of &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9959050/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;BV in smokers&lt;/a&gt;, as well as a greater risk of preterm birth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Giving up smoking, maintaining a healthy BMI, and consuming a diet rich in vitamins could therefore all be good ways of looking after the vagina.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Eating plenty of leafy green vegetables, getting enough sleep, drinking enough water," says Goodfellow. "All these general things that improve your health will probably improve your vaginal microbiome too."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;i id="for-trusted-insights-into-better-health-and-wellbeing-rooted-in-science,-sign-up-to-the" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;For trusted insights into better health and wellbeing rooted in science, sign up to the &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://cloud.email.bbc.com/HealthFix_Newsletter_Signup?&amp;amp;at_bbc_team=studios&amp;amp;at_medium=emails&amp;amp;at_objective=acquisition&amp;amp;at_ptr_type=&amp;amp;at_ptr_name=bbc.com&amp;amp;at_format=Module&amp;amp;at_link_origin=featurescallout&amp;amp;at_campaign=healthfix&amp;amp;at_campaign_type=owned" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;&lt;i id="health-fix-newsletter" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;Health Fix newsletter&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id=",-while" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;, while &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://cloud.email.bbc.com/SignUp10_08?&amp;amp;at_bbc_team=studios&amp;amp;at_medium=Onsite&amp;amp;at_objective=acquisition&amp;amp;at_ptr_name=bbc.com&amp;amp;at_link_origin=featuresarticle&amp;amp;at_campaign=essentiallist&amp;amp;at_campaign_type=owned" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;&lt;i id="the-essential-list" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;The Essential List&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="delivers-a-handpicked-selection-of-features-and-insights." class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt; delivers a handpicked selection of features and insights.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;i id="for-more-science,-technology,-environment-and-health-stories-from-the-bbc,-follow-us-on" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;For more science, technology, environment and health stories from the BBC, follow us on &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/BBCFuture/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;&lt;i id="facebook" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;Facebook&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;i id="and" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;and &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.instagram.com/bbcfuture_official/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;&lt;i id="instagram" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;Instagram&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="." class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxQNTJUUDFnQnptaDctNDNPTUg1MjQ1blZLaktlX05ablJxU2VjT3VlcUpfR3Z1dUo4RjNITDhtTVBhVVowejR3SmJnaEtfdlZtM3Jud0JKRXkyRExqYTdxbmtnaHVkTVhZaE9ON1IwRXl6TExFc0R1cVB2bkJBY2VmZVh3Tmw2Y280NmVFbTJpalVLYmM</guid></item><item><title>南卡罗来纳州的麻疹爆发显示疫苗错误信息的寒蝉效应- KFF健康新闻</title><link>https://kffhealthnews.org/news/article/measles-outbreak-south-carolina-vaccine-misinformation-kennedy-rfk/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;
								
&lt;p&gt;BOILING SPRINGS, S.C. — Near the back corner of the local library’s parking lot, largely out of view from the main road, the South Carolina Department of Public Health opened a pop-up clinic in early November, offering free measles vaccines to adults and children.&lt;/p&gt;







&lt;p&gt;Spartanburg County, in South Carolina’s Upstate region, has been fighting a measles outbreak since early October, with more than 50 cases identified. Health officials have encouraged people who are unvaccinated to get a shot by visiting its mobile vaccine clinic at any of its several stops throughout the county.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But on a Monday afternoon in Boiling Springs, only one person showed up.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It’s progress. That progress is slow,” Linda Bell, the state epidemiologist with the Department of Public Health, said during a recent press briefing. “We had hoped to see a more robust uptake than that in our mobile health units.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As South Carolina tries to contain its measles outbreak, public health officials across the nation are concerned that the highly contagious virus is making a major comeback. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has tallied &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html"&gt;more than 1,700 measles cases&lt;/a&gt; and 45 outbreaks in 2025. The largest started &lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/news/article/texas-measles-outbreak-cdc-vaccines-rfk-trump/"&gt;in Texas&lt;/a&gt;, where hundreds of people were infected and two children died.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For the first time in more than two decades, the United States is poised to lose its measles &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/other-health/measles-elimination-status-what-it-is-and-how-the-u-s-could-lose-it/#:~:text=Measles%20has%20been%20officially%20%E2%80%9Celiminated,in%20any%20year%20since%201992."&gt;elimination status&lt;/a&gt;, a designation indicating that outbreaks are rare and rapidly contained.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;South Carolina’s measles outbreak isn’t yet as large as those in other states, such as &lt;a href="https://www.nmhealth.org/about/erd/ideb/mog/"&gt;New Mexico&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.azdhs.gov/preparedness/epidemiology-disease-control/measles/index.php"&gt;Arizona&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.kdhe.ks.gov/2314/Measles-Outbreak-Data"&gt;Kansas&lt;/a&gt;. But it shows how a confluence of larger national trends — including historically low vaccination rates, skepticism fueled by the pandemic, misinformation, and “health freedom” ideologies proliferated by conservative politicians — have put some communities at risk for the reemergence of a preventable, potentially deadly virus.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Everyone talks about it being the canary in the coal mine because it’s the most contagious infectious disease out there,” said Josh Michaud, associate director for global and public health policy at KFF, a health information nonprofit that includes KFF Health News. “The logic is indisputable that we’re likely to see more outbreaks.”&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block block--newsletter  " data-type="kaiser-health-news/newsletter" data-align="center"&gt;
	
	&lt;p class="newsletter__description"&gt;
		Subscribe to KFF Health News' free Morning Briefing.	&lt;/p&gt;
	

&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Schools and ‘Small Brush Fires’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Spartanburg’s vaccination rate is among the lowest of South Carolina’s 46 counties. And that was true “even before covid,” said Chris Lombardozzi, a senior vice president with the Spartanburg Regional Healthcare System.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nearly 6,000 children in Spartanburg County schools last year — 10% of the total enrollment — either received an exemption allowing them to forgo required vaccinations or did not meet vaccine requirements, according to data published by the state.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Lombardozzi said the county’s low vaccination rate is tied to misinformation not only published on social media but also spread by “a variety of nonmedical leaders over the years.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The pandemic made things worse. Michaud said that fear and misinformation surrounding covid vaccines “threw gasoline on the fire of people’s vaccine skepticism.” In some cases, that skepticism transferred to childhood vaccines, which historically have been less controversial, he said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This made communities like Spartanburg County with low vaccination rates more vulnerable. “Which is why we’re seeing constant, small brush fires of measles outbreaks,” Michaud said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In Spartanburg, the overall percentage of students with required immunizations fell from 95.1% to 90% between the 2020-21 and 2024-25 academic years. Public health officials say a minimum of 95% is required to prevent significant spread of measles.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Children who attend public and private schools in South Carolina are required to show that they’ve received some vaccinations, including the measles, mumps, and rubella vaccine, but religious exemptions are relatively easy to obtain. The exemption form must be notarized, but it does not require a doctor’s note or any disclosure about the family’s religious beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The number of students in South Carolina who have been granted religious exemptions has increased dramatically over the past decade. That’s particularly true in the Upstate region, where religious exemptions have increased sixfold from a decade ago. During the 2013-14 school year, 2,044 students in the Upstate were granted a religious exemption to the vaccine requirements, according to &lt;a href="https://www.postandcourier.com/features/your_health/religious-exemptions-for-school-vaccine-requirements-worry-public-health-experts-in-south-carolina/article_86dc5de0-926f-11e7-93ba-47e9fd2cff5f.html"&gt;data published by The Post and Courier&lt;/a&gt;. By fall 2024, that number had jumped to more than 13,000.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Some schools are more exposed than others. The beginning of the South Carolina outbreak was largely linked to one public charter school, Global Academy of South Carolina, where only 17% of the 605 students enrolled during the 2024-25 school year provided documentation showing they had received their required vaccinations, according to data published by the Department of Public Health.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;No one from Global Academy responded to interview requests.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;‘Health Freedom’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In April, after visiting a Texas family whose daughter had died from measles, Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. wrote on social media that the “most effective way to prevent the spread of measles is the MMR vaccine.” He made a similar statement during an interview on “Dr. Phil” later that month.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But these endorsements stand at odds with other statements Kennedy has made that cast doubt on vaccine safety and have falsely linked vaccines with autism. The CDC, under his authority, now claims such links “&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/news/article/cdc-autism-baseless-new-guidance-website/"&gt;have been ignored by health authorities&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“What would I do if I could go back in time and I could avoid giving my children the vaccines that I gave them?” he said on a podcast in 2020. “I would do anything for that. I would pay anything to be able to do that.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Throughout 2025, he has made other &lt;a href="https://www.factcheck.org/2025/03/rfk-jr-misleads-about-measles-vaccine-in-hannity-interview/"&gt;misleading or unsupported statements&lt;/a&gt;. During a congressional hearing in September, Kennedy defended his past claims that he was not anti-vaccine but affirmed his stated position that no vaccines are safe or effective.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Emily Hilliard, a spokesperson for the Department of Health and Human Services, told KFF Health News that Kennedy is “pro-safety, pro-transparency, and pro-accountability.” Hilliard said HHS is working with “state and local partners in South Carolina” and in other states to provide support during the measles outbreaks.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Kennedy has frequently championed the idea of health freedom, or freedom of choice, regarding vaccines, a talking point that has taken root among Republicans.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That has had a “chilling effect all the way down through state and local lawmakers,” Michaud said, making some leaders hesitant to talk about the threat that the ongoing measles outbreaks poses or the effectiveness and safety of the MMR vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Brandon Charochak, a spokesperson for South Carolina Gov. Henry McMaster, said the governor was not available to be interviewed for this article but referenced McMaster’s comment from October that measles “is a dangerous disease, but in terms of diseases, it’s not one that we should panic about.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;On a separate occasion that month, the Republican governor said he does not support vaccine mandates. “We’re not going to have mandates,” he said, “and I think we are responding properly.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Even though the South Carolina Department of Public Health has repeatedly encouraged measles vaccines, the push has been notably quieter than the agency’s covid vaccine outreach efforts.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In 2021, for example, the agency partnered with breweries throughout the state for a campaign called “Shot and a Chaser,” which rewarded people who got a covid vaccine with a free beer or soda. By contrast, the pop-up measles vaccine clinic at the Boiling Springs Library featured no flashy signage, no freebies, and wasn’t visible from the library’s main entrance.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Edward Simmer, interim director of the Department of Public Health, would not speak to KFF Health News about the measles outbreak. During a legislative hearing in April, Republican state lawmakers voted against his permanent confirmation because of his past support for covid vaccines and masking. One lawmaker specifically criticized the agency during that hearing for the Shot and a Chaser campaign.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Public health officials in other states also have been blocked from new roles because of their covid response. In Missouri, where &lt;a href="https://health.mo.gov/living/families/schoolhealth/dashboard.php"&gt;MMR vaccine rates have declined&lt;/a&gt; among kindergartners since 2020 and measles cases have been reported this year, Republican lawmakers &lt;a href="https://www.kcur.org/politics-elections-and-government/2022-02-01/missouri-senate-rejects-governors-pick-for-health-director-over-support-for-covid-vaccines"&gt;rejected a public health director&lt;/a&gt; in 2022 after vaccine opponents protested his appointment.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In South Carolina, Simmer, lacking lawmakers’ confirmation, leads the public health agency in an interim capacity.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;South Carolina Sen. Tom Davis of Beaufort was the only Republican on the Senate Medical Affairs Committee who voted to confirm Simmer in April. He told KFF Health News that his Republican colleagues raised valid questions about Simmer’s past support for covid vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But, Davis said, it would be “tremendously unfortunate and not beneficial from a public health perspective” if the Republican Party just took a stance against vaccines “as a matter of policy.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Department of Public Health had administered 44 doses of the MMR vaccine through its mobile health unit from October to mid-November. The last mobile vaccine clinic was scheduled for Nov. 24. But health officials are encouraged that patients are seeking vaccines elsewhere. The agency’s tracking system shows that providers across Spartanburg County administered more than twice as many measles vaccines in October as they did a year ago.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As of mid-November, more than 130 people remained in quarantine, most of them students at local elementary and middle schools. Cases have also been linked to a church and Greenville-Spartanburg International Airport.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“We’re reminding people that travel for the upcoming holidays increases the risk of exposures greatly,” said Bell, the state epidemiologist. “Due to that risk, we’re encouraging people to consider getting vaccinated now.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;KFF Health News correspondent Amy Maxmen contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	


							&lt;/div&gt;

													&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KFF Health News</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxQUjExdS1qaFNfOWNOUXJ6UlhWRTh0eFFiWTVRSjRrUVg3VzRQdEZuMThIRldab3IzaU9ma0xvTm95MTlLV0dRdGxfQXNjTG5qQVJsS0hReEJIcHBIS3lDRlJ1ZUhWVDRFSUE1eXZfbHpKZ2R1SFZ2N3NnSE5vRnBrSm9sQktvdHBYeUhzYW9MMHFmNTh6b0JVdVN1QUZwT25vMEhmbUpyX1ZyUQ</guid></item><item><title>高血压补充剂清除小鼠阿尔茨海默氏症的迹象- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/supplement-for-high-blood-pressure-clears-signs-of-alzheimers-in-mice</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A build-up of sticky proteins in the brain is a key hallmark of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimer-s-disease"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;, thought to be closely linked to the disease's progression. Now scientists have found a new way to clear these harmful clumps in the brains of mice and the eyes of fruit flies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This potentially promising  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="182889" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; treatment involves an oral dose of &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arginine"&gt;arginine&lt;/a&gt;, an amino acid already used as a medication for conditions including &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cardiac-arrest-and-heart-attacks-arent-the-same-heres-how-to-tell-them-apart"&gt;chest pain&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-blood-pressure-guidelines-mean-you-may-now-have-hypertension"&gt;high blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The discovery was made by a team from Kindai University and Japan's National Institute of Neuroscience, who focused on the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-of-our-biggest-hopes-for-alzheimers-treatment-doesnt-seem-to-work"&gt;amyloid-beta plaques&lt;/a&gt; seen in Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the same results can be achieved in human brains, we may have another avenue for potentially tackling a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-simple-new-compound-reverses-alzheimers-symptoms-in-rats"&gt;key molecular symptom&lt;/a&gt; of Alzheimer's – in a safe and easily applied way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/we-may-now-know-why-alzheimers-erases-memories-of-our-loved-ones"&gt;We May Now Know Why Alzheimer's Erases Memories of Our Loved Ones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our study demonstrates that arginine can suppress amyloid-beta aggregation both in vitro and in vivo," &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1106825"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; neuroscientist Yoshitaka Nagai, from Kindai University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What makes this finding exciting is that arginine is already known to be clinically safe and inexpensive, making it a highly promising candidate for repositioning as a therapeutic option for Alzheimer's disease."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_182892" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-182892" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/FlyModel.jpg" alt="Fly model diagram" class="wp-image-182892 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/FlyModel.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/FlyModel-600x477.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-182892" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Arginine reduced amyloid-beta clumping (in green) in fruit fly models. (Fujii et al., &lt;em&gt;Neurochem. Int.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers bred male mice with Alzheimer's-like aggregations of amyloid-beta, then added arginine to the animals' drinking water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arginine significantly &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-simple-new-compound-reverses-alzheimers-symptoms-in-rats"&gt;reduced the protein build-up&lt;/a&gt; in the animals' brains and alleviated some of the related toxic effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mice given arginine also showed reduced behavioral abnormalities during tests and had less active neuroinflammatory genes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the treatment may not be just scrubbing away the protein plaques; it could be reversing some of the harm being done to the brain, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further experiments in fruit flies and test tubes added to the evidence that arginine could possibly clear out amyloid-beta clumps and stop them from forming in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists already knew that arginine can act as a kind of chemical chaperone, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/brain/awaa115"&gt;preventing the abnormal misfolding&lt;/a&gt; and clumping of proteins, like those seen in Alzheimer's disease. Animal studies also show arginine can &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0305318"&gt;cross the blood-brain barrier&lt;/a&gt;, which is key for treating brain diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Given its excellent safety profile and low cost, arginine could be rapidly translated to  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="182889" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; for Alzheimer's and potentially other related disorders," &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1106825"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Nagai.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before we get ahead of ourselves here, it's important to note that the researchers used a relatively high dose of arginine in their animal tests, and more work needs to be done to figure out a safe treatment dose for humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And while mouse and fruit fly models are often good substitutes for human diseases, there's no guarantee that these findings are going to carry over. The  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/animal-testing" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73085" data-postid="182889" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;animal testing&lt;/a&gt; has produced encouraging results, and clinical trials can now be considered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, there &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-of-our-biggest-hopes-for-alzheimers-treatment-doesnt-seem-to-work"&gt;remains some uncertainty&lt;/a&gt; that clearing away amyloid-beta plaques can actually work as a way of treating Alzheimer's. These clumps are definitely &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/here-s-where-alzheimer-s-plaques-might-really-come-from"&gt;harmful to neurons&lt;/a&gt;, but it's &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-blood-test-accurately-predicts-alzheimers-years-ahead-of-first-symptoms"&gt;still unclear&lt;/a&gt; whether they're helping to drive Alzheimer's to begin with, or &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newly-identified-proteins-may-explain-devastating-effects-of-alzheimers"&gt;signs of other mechanisms&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/toxic-tiny-rna-molecules-identified-as-culprit-in-alzheimers-neuron-death"&gt;at work&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even with those caveats though, it's another encouraging step forward in our understanding of how Alzheimer's works and how we might be able to tackle it – another promising treatment option to add &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer-drugs-show-alzheimers-promise-in-mice"&gt;to an ever-growing list&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our findings open up new possibilities for developing arginine-based strategies for neurodegenerative diseases caused by protein misfolding and aggregation," &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1106825"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Nagai.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.neuint.2025.106082"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Neurochemistry International&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 03:29:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxQODM4aEprWXdBZUllRklPV0x4OHZiOE0tNzZ3YTJPREZZTENxakdkZS1LSlEweWYzTVd4YWhmYXQxcXBjMmh2VE9aV0IzWE5HaHE4dXdwRnpBSmhTRG1CNV9kR1pCaFBWWUZvWkJraURyZjBVQ1RMcnRwbmJiWGlQcWVKMHpxbjJhWVRJNzk0V2xMaFR3anBESEJBZDllYlk</guid></item><item><title>科学家报告：首创疗法提升人体试验视力- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/first-of-its-kind-treatment-boosts-vision-in-human-trial-scientists-report</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Taking a photo of a friend? You've probably got their face centered and focused. Driving down a highway? Eyes on the road.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But for millions of adults with age-related macular degeneration, that crucial, central field of sight is blurred beyond recognition. &lt;a href="https://www.aao.org/eye-health/tips-prevention/promising-new-treatments-amd"&gt;Current treatments&lt;/a&gt; can only slow its progression or augment vision, but the blur will usually continue to worsen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="183000" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trial&lt;/a&gt; of a treatment based on  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/stem-cells" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73034" data-postid="183000" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;stem cell&lt;/a&gt; transplants has found the procedure may be able to safely reverse the cumulative damage to the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/common-fruit-could-reduce-chances-of-eye-disease-macular-degeneration"&gt;hard-working macula&lt;/a&gt; – that part of the retina &lt;a href="https://www.nei.nih.gov/learn-about-eye-health/eye-conditions-and-diseases/age-related-macular-degeneration"&gt;responsible for all you see directly in front of you&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/gold-injections-in-the-eye-may-be-the-future-of-vision-preservation"&gt;Gold Injections in The Eye May Be The Future of Vision Preservation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's the first time this particular stem cell treatment has been tested in humans, and as a phase 1/2a clinical trial, the main focus of the investigation was safety and efficacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effectiveness of the treatment compared with existing therapies won't be known until at least the end of phase 3, but the preliminary results were positive enough that trials are proceeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier testing in the lab showed the transplant process was safe enough to proceed with in-human trials: the transplanted  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/stem-cells" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73034" data-postid="183000" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;stem cells&lt;/a&gt; retained their retinal identity, and no tumours or toxicity were observed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screening 18 potentially eligible patients, the researchers enrolled six volunteers aged 71 to 86 who had been diagnosed with dry age-related macular degeneration (&lt;a href="https://www.nei.nih.gov/learn-about-eye-health/eye-conditions-and-diseases/age-related-macular-degeneration"&gt;the most common type, making up around 80 percent of all macular degeneration cases&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three of the participants had worse vision in general, with visual acuity scores ranging from 20/200 to 20/800 (which means they could only see the first, biggest letter on the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Snellen_chart"&gt;Snellen chart&lt;/a&gt;, at best). The other three had scores between 20/70 and 20/200.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike the less common and more rapid 'wet' macular degeneration, the 'dry' form of the condition is a gradual loss of vision caused by tiny deposits of fats and proteins destroying the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Retinal_pigment_epithelium"&gt;retinal pigment epithelial cells&lt;/a&gt; (RPEs) that support the eye's light-sensitive tissues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_183119" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-183119" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/MD_of_the_eye_diagram2_642.jpg" alt="diagram of macular degeneration" class="wp-image-183119 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/MD_of_the_eye_diagram2_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/MD_of_the_eye_diagram2_642-600x280.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-183119" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Diagram showing early stages of dry macular degeneration, caused by deposits of fats and proteins known as drusen beneath the RPE. (&lt;a href="https://www.mdfoundation.com.au/about-macular-disease/age-related-macular-degeneration/what-is-amd/"&gt;Macular Disease Foundation Australia&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The treatment involves surgically transplanting stem cells sourced from an eye bank that can produce new RPEs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each of the trial's participants received a relatively low dose of 50,000 RPE stem cells through a single injection. The cells were inserted under the retina of the superior temporal macula in the patients' most-impaired eye.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, the trial showed the treatment is safe, with no sign of the immune problems or tumors that &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/new-stem-cell-test-may-reduce-tumour-risk-14932"&gt;can sometimes arise&lt;/a&gt; in stem cell transplants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No adverse events were related to the stem cells themselves, though there were a few of the typical complications seen in this kind of eye surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Significantly, each patient experienced an improvement in vision in the eye that received the transplant that was not apparent in the other, suggesting the stem cells were doing exactly what scientists had hoped they would.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One year after the treatment, the three participants who had the worst vision were able to see an average of 21 more letters on an eye chart than they had at the start of the trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although we were pleased with the safety data, the exciting part was that their vision was also improving," &lt;a href="https://www.michiganmedicine.org/health-lab/adult-stem-cells-show-therapeutic-promise-treating-vision-loss-macular-degeneration"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Rajesh Rao, a physician-scientist and ophthalmologist at Michigan Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We were surprised by the magnitude of vision gain in the most severely affected patients who received the adult stem cell-derived RPE transplants. This level of vision gain has not been seen in this group of patients with advanced dry AMD."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trial is continuing to monitor patients who received higher doses (150,000 and 250,000 cells). If those doses are also deemed safe, it will help determine whether Rao and team can scale up human testing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.stem.2025.08.012"&gt;Cell Stem Cell&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:18:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxNRmgxbi1IWjRfOHF2aWNrclRESHJub3g3UEZaaGFoT0FIQlh3VmUxRUMwd0Q1LUprZ2tGTVpwSnRBMk9zTHVBbC1uZXhfOEhmVEJWNUYxNU5JeEw2aG82YzJUWUxTeWZfcWZoNUkteVJ3d3NFSjV1NlpNVkFnTW5QUHVGeHJBSFVySWw4V3FWaDVCWjV3c3VMWG1mQTRZY2o2X3AtWm93</guid></item><item><title>在Wasatch High的8名学生中证实了麻疹；犹他州的麻疹总数使100例感染病例黯然失色- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51410730/measles-confirmed-in-8-students-at-wasatch-high-utahs-total-eclipses-100-infections</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;HEBER CITY — Eight cases of measles have been reported among Wasatch High School students, health officials confirmed on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Wasatch County Health Department initially announced on Monday there were five people with measles in the county — all of whom are Wasatch High School students — but they suspected two others may also be infected as they were awaiting test results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those two suspected cases, along with a third, all came back positive the next day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This brings Wasatch County's total confirmed cases to eight," department spokesperson Lana North said in a statement on Tuesday. "The three new cases are all unvaccinated Wasatch County high school students."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The health department suspects that people inside the high school during its normal hours may have been exposed to the virus on Nov. 14, 17 and 18, and at a school play on Nov. 15.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A letter with notification and guidance was sent to Wasatch High School families to inform them of the situation," a press release issued by the health department reads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jonelle Fitzgerald, the health department's director, said a wastewater test taken on Nov. 6 showed the presence of the virus within the community, "and with cases existing in other parts of the state, we weren't surprised to see cases here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent rise in cases in Wasatch County comes as the state's total number of cases hits triple digits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://epi.utah.gov/measles-response/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Utah Department of Health and Human Services&lt;/a&gt; data dashboard shows 102 measles infections across the state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Southwest Utah Health District leads the state's infections with 74 measles cases, followed by Utah County, with nine cases, and Wasatch County's eight infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twenty-four people have been diagnosed with measles over the last three weeks, the dashboard reports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a major holiday marks a time for gatherings among family and loved ones, health officials warn that measles is highly contagious and spreads easily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles symptoms, which typically appear within one to three weeks after exposure, can include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;High fever&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cough&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Runny nose&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Red, watery eyes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A rash that starts on the face and spreads downward&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Wasatch County Health Department said it advises anyone experiencing symptoms to call their health care provider immediately, especially those who are unvaccinated or who have been exposed to a known case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials encourage residents to get both doses of the MMR vaccine, as they say it is 97% effective in preventing the illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:05:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxNUXh0bnd0RzNqR3Q5UExmX0xkVmRjQzN0NzBtdDNRS3I2c0lxNzBDdnR1VVk4NVdKVlNRTGdoY0NuWXBPQ2ljcG8ybnU3VWNZMmNyaDZEYzU3OFlVQ1FkNHc5MVB0SnFDZTJ0cnJkRkh4Sk1QYzlyNmI4SklfaE5fYXA1WkZWOXltay1sczcwVGc5Mk1Ka1JudG9pNU9SV2ZkN2lESlVRT3M2OXpVUFM2Sk83NjF5OUFXTVFsbQ</guid></item><item><title>路易斯安那州最高卫生官员，新冠疫苗的批评者，将担任疾控中心副手：疫苗-健康新闻- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/11/25/nx-s1-5620991/louisiana-surgeon-general-ralph-abraham-cdc-deputy</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-99415" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Dr. Ralph Abraham spoke at a Trump re-election rally in Lake Charles, La., on Oct. 11, 2019. At the time, Abraham was a Republican congressman running for governor of Louisiana. He lost that race, but was named the state's first surgeon general in 2024.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Gerald Herbert/AP
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Gerald Herbert/AP
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;The second-highest ranking official at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention will be Dr. Ralph Abraham, the head of Louisiana's health department.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;He has questioned the safety of the COVID vaccine and forbidden his department from promoting vaccines to the public.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Abraham will join the agency as principal deputy director, according to an official for the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services who was not authorized to speak to the media about a personnel matter.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A former Republican congressman and a physician with a practice in Richland Parish, &lt;a href="https://ldh.la.gov/office-of-the-surgeon-general" target="_blank"&gt;Abraham&lt;/a&gt; has been a vocal supporter of Health Secretary &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/about/leadership/robert-kennedy.html" target="_blank"&gt;Robert F. Kennedy, Jr.&lt;/a&gt;, and shares some of his views on vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Abraham, 71, has called COVID vaccines "&lt;a href="https://x.com/la_surgeon/status/1966237494627983445" target="_blank"&gt;dangerous&lt;/a&gt;." During a Sept. 2024 state legislative meeting, Abraham said he would support investigating the debunked link between &lt;a href="https://www.healthcarejournalbr.com/journal/november-december-2024" target="_blank"&gt;vaccines and autism&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The position has been vacant since &lt;a href="https://farmington.edu/about/news/umf-proudly-announces-dr-nirav-dinesh-shah-former-principal-deputy-director-of-the-u-s-cdc-as-the-2025-umf-commencement-speaker/" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Nirav Shah&lt;/a&gt;, who served under the Biden administration, stepped down in February.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Shah called Abraham's appointment "atrocious."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The CDC is part of the Department of Health and Human Services, led by Kennedy. The CDC's current acting director is &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/08/29/nx-s1-5522036/cdc-rfk-hhs-monarez-jim-oneill-leadership" target="_blank"&gt;Jim O'Neill&lt;/a&gt;, who most recently worked as an investor.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Because neither Kennedy nor O'Neill is a doctor or scientist, Abraham's medical degree is useful to help further their views, Shah said.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"With the addition of Dr. Abraham, they now have a scientific gloss that they can put on their anti-vaccine theories," Shah said.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"He gives Secretary Kennedy some scientific and medical cover for their odious and unscientific beliefs," he added.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Abraham was named Louisiana's first Surgeon General in 2024, under Republican Governor &lt;a href="https://gov.louisiana.gov/page/meet-the-governor" target="_blank"&gt;Jeff Landry&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Soon after, Abraham moved to &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2024/12/20/nx-s1-5223440/louisiana-ban-public-health-promoting-covid-flu-mpox-vaccines-landry-rfk-jr-anti-vaccine" target="_blank"&gt;ban the promotion of COVID, flu and mpox vaccines&lt;/a&gt; by the state health department. He then &lt;a href="https://www.wwno.org/public-health/2025-02-17/louisiana-medical-organizations-criticize-states-ban-on-vaccine-promotion" target="_blank"&gt;banned all vaccine promotion and events&lt;/a&gt; by the health department in February, hours after Kennedy was confirmed as health secretary.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In late 2024, cases of whooping cough in Louisiana began to climb, eventually growing to &lt;a href="https://stacks.cdc.gov/view/cdc/232491" target="_blank"&gt;387 cases&lt;/a&gt;, the worst outbreak of whooping cough in the state in 35 years.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Early in the outbreak, two infants died from the disease. Infants are not eligible for their first pertussis vaccine until they're &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/hcp/vaccine-recommendations/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;2 months old&lt;/a&gt;, but they can acquire immunity if their mother was immunized while pregnant.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;After the infant deaths, Abraham's health department &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/10/28/nx-s1-5576494/louisiana-whooping-cough-pertussis-infant-deaths" target="_blank"&gt;waited three months&lt;/a&gt; before issuing an official alert to physicians and warning the public in a press release.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Dr. Abraham's record shows that when an emergency in public health materializes, his instinct is to sweep it under the rug," Shah said.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In the event of the next pandemic, "that could mean the difference between controlling a major outbreak versus letting it fester and explode," he added.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The principal deputy director is the second in command at the CDC, said &lt;a href="https://www.ncicp.org/staff-member/anne-schuchat-md/" target="_blank"&gt;Anne Schuchat&lt;/a&gt;, who worked there for 33 years, including as principal deputy director from 2015 to 2021. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Most appointees are CDC employees who've worked at the agency for many years, and have experience in crisis management and emergency response to public health threats, she said.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Responsibilities can run from overseeing every aspect of CDC's work within the U.S., to coordinating emergency responses to outbreaks around the world.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Schuchat called Abraham's appointment "scary."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"This appears to be one more step away from health and towards danger," Schuchat said. "We know that vaccinations are saving lives and protecting health and preventing outbreaks, and ideology should not outweigh the evidence."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In the Louisiana legislature, Abraham supported bills to &lt;a href="https://www.wwno.org/politics/2025-04-23/bill-banning-fluoride-in-louisianas-public-water-systems-clears-senate-committee" target="_blank"&gt;ban fluoride in public water systems&lt;/a&gt;, and to expand access to &lt;a href="https://www.shreveporttimes.com/story/news/2025/04/30/louisiana-surgeon-general-recommends-ivermectin-as-covid-for-his-patients-and-backs-deregulation/83362570007/" target="_blank"&gt;ivermectin to treat COVID&lt;/a&gt;, despite &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2022/03/30/1089809588/ivermectin-covid-treatment-brazil-study" target="_blank"&gt;evidence that it is not effective against COVID&lt;/a&gt;. The fluoride bill failed, but the ivermectin bill passed.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Picking Abraham for this position was an "irresponsible choice," said &lt;a href="https://www.law.georgetown.edu/faculty/lawrence-o-gostin/" target="_blank"&gt;Lawrence Gostin&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of global health law at Georgetown University.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Dr. Abraham has little trust in science and he is likely to further erode the credibility of the CDC," he said.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;HHS has not said when Abraham will start his new role.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story comes from NPR's partnership with &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wwno.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;WWNO&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;KFF Health News&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 01:02:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxPRTJESjQxZ2M5RFlxeE5iQlh6R3U3RTRWeWFxMVNIYVY0OEFhcUxtdEZLVjRmUldoRVgzaXNCWE5EWHBmNjNJZVd2c3pDSFd5ajZMblBWSjhvWEUyRFNkeUFZMUNrck1fYmJKWVIyZ01MTTJkQW9zNWJVUkNsUklHVzRDX3NGWnh5VmZ6dmN1RnFvN0VDUzhnRXY4SE1heWRVT3pzcGpjNUJQQklab2FxQU00NzlOQVJqR01kVGRYVQ</guid></item><item><title>“令人兴奋”的新癌症血液检测结果隐藏了一个相关问题- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/exciting-new-cancer-blood-test-results-hide-a-concerning-problem</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Progress in cutting the global toll of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="183081" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; remains painfully slow, but a new blood test has sparked unusual levels of hope. Researchers say it could one day make routine screening far more effective by catching cancers earlier, when treatment has the best chance of saving lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Galleri blood test, developed by US firm Grail, is the latest entrant to attract worldwide attention, after early trial results were described as "exciting" by researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://grail.com/press-releases/grail-pathfinder-2-results-show-galleri-multi-cancer-early-detection-blood-test-increased-cancer-detection-more-than-seven-fold-when-added-to-uspstf-a-and-b-recommended-screenings/"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; claims the test, currently being trialled by the NHS, can detect signals from 50 cancers and correctly identify the disease in 62 per cent of people who receive a positive result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-7-warning-signs-of-brain-cancer-you-might-easily-miss"&gt;The 7 Warning Signs of Brain Cancer You Might Easily Miss&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also appears to be highly accurate at ruling cancer out, with a reported 99.6 percent success rate among those who were disease-free. At first glance, these headline figures appear to represent a significant step forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But before we reach for the champagne, it's worth looking more closely at what these numbers really mean. Early promise does not always translate into real-world performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_183094" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-183094" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/cancer_cell_illo_642.jpg" alt="cancer cells illustration" class="wp-image-183094 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/cancer_cell_illo_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/cancer_cell_illo_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-183094" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;New cancer blood test aims to identify cancers of varying types. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAGv7Q2bTYc/"&gt;ninjadesign/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pathfinder 2 trial, involving 23,161 people aged over 50 from the US and Canada with no prior cancer diagnosis, produced the figures now circulating widely. Of the 216 participants who tested positive, 133 were later found to have cancer, giving the "positive predictive value" (PPV) of 62 percent that has been &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/c205g21n1zzo"&gt;so&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://eu.usatoday.com/story/life/health-wellness/2025/11/05/galleri-early-cancer-detection-blood-test/87009742007/"&gt;widely&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2025/10/18/cancer-blood-test-seven-times-more-effective-than-current/"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That metric answers a crucial question: "If I test positive, what's the chance I actually have cancer?" It also means, however, that 38 percent of positive results were false alarms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Specificity – how often a test avoids falsely diagnosing cancer – is equally important, given the anxiety and medical follow-up triggered by an incorrect result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here, the test performed well: 99.6 percent of people without cancer received a correct negative result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet even this strong number has implications. If everyone aged over 50 in the UK were tested – more than 26 million people – the same rate would still generate over 100,000 false positives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What has been less widely discussed is sensitivity, the measure of how many true cancer cases the test actually detects. On this measure, the result was 40.4 percent, meaning the test missed around three in every five cancers that appeared over the following year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Galleri test results:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" alt="A chart showing how many cancer cases the Galleri test would correctly identify." src="https://images.theconversation.com/files/704517/original/file-20251125-56-27chsg.jpg?ixlib=rb-4.1.0&amp;amp;q=45&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;w=754&amp;amp;fit=clip" srcset="https://images.theconversation.com/files/704517/original/file-20251125-56-27chsg.jpg?ixlib=rb-4.1.0&amp;amp;q=45&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;w=600&amp;amp;h=511&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;dpr=1 600w, https://images.theconversation.com/files/704517/original/file-20251125-56-27chsg.jpg?ixlib=rb-4.1.0&amp;amp;q=30&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;w=600&amp;amp;h=511&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;dpr=2 1200w, https://images.theconversation.com/files/704517/original/file-20251125-56-27chsg.jpg?ixlib=rb-4.1.0&amp;amp;q=15&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;w=600&amp;amp;h=511&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;dpr=3 1800w, https://images.theconversation.com/files/704517/original/file-20251125-56-27chsg.jpg?ixlib=rb-4.1.0&amp;amp;q=45&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;w=754&amp;amp;h=642&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;dpr=1 754w, https://images.theconversation.com/files/704517/original/file-20251125-56-27chsg.jpg?ixlib=rb-4.1.0&amp;amp;q=30&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;w=754&amp;amp;h=642&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;dpr=2 1508w, https://images.theconversation.com/files/704517/original/file-20251125-56-27chsg.jpg?ixlib=rb-4.1.0&amp;amp;q=15&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;w=754&amp;amp;h=642&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;dpr=3 2262w" sizes="(min-width: 1466px) 754px, (max-width: 599px) 100vw, (min-width: 600px) 600px, 237px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;The Galleri cancer test in numbers. (John Ferguson, &lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/"&gt;CC BY-SA&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The figure that's been less widely reported&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;That shortfall may disappoint those hoping for a catch-all screening tool. It also raises the risk that patients could be falsely reassured by a negative result, potentially delaying a diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Statisticians caution that the reported PPV, specificity, and sensitivity are estimates rather than fixed values, and each comes with uncertainty. They also note that tests often perform less well outside carefully controlled trials, meaning real-world accuracy could be lower.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, where does this leave the Galleri test? It may well become a useful addition to future screening programmes, provided that negative results are not viewed as definitive by patients or doctors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the low sensitivity means many cancers would still be missed in its current form. The test is also expensive – US$949 (£723) in the US – and no evidence yet shows that widely using it reduces cancer deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The early data is encouraging, but perhaps the excitement deserves to be tempered. This technology may be a step forward, but it is not a solution on its own.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/270438/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/john-ferguson-2527786"&gt;John Ferguson&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Lecturer in Statistical Science, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-galway-2699"&gt;University of Galway&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/the-cancer-blood-test-making-waves-and-what-the-numbers-really-show-270438"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:27:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxQVkp0SDA1YS1nWV9hcDdmVjF0OHhabUdPbnNCdnRZZms0ZkQtNXhETDFOV2Y4cTR1LXVvR095cHFOcFlGSTFkQldXRURkcFdTRGZMMDI5MmJ1dExOZWpJd1g3UEhNenVwaFRKdGp3UHNFOWNyeFdFOHZlUl95WXoyWlpUMWVLSHRSSW1HUmhyNVVQdlc1c3NQVA</guid></item><item><title>他很漂亮，但他有一个巨大的盲点-纽约时报</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/25/science/pheasants-blind-spot-vision.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:01:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxPTVRTeG9yQzNNUTBNY0JUbExlTEtnQS1hTThnLVZncmNrUXl4R3NCNmRnd1RKSk5uOUxjekJSb2w1T1V2UlpUU3ZLd0N1LXpmamlGSmQ3R0NXM0ZFLXJwUWdJY3F0NTkzeHItQXU2LUtuV2V4REtvQjFWTl9FX0taNA</guid></item><item><title>爱达荷州南部艾滋病毒/艾滋病病例激增，卫生官员敦促提高警惕- KBOI</title><link>https://idahonews.com/news/local/hivaids-cases-surge-in-southern-idaho-health-officials-urge-vigilance</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText_storyText__C3hWI StoryText_storyText__C3hWI"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;BOISE, Idaho (CBS2) — &lt;/span&gt;South Central Public Health District (SCPHD) is raising alarms over a significant rise in HIV and AIDS cases across Southern Idaho. Recent data reveals that in SCPHD's eight-county region, which includes Blaine, Camas, Cassia, Gooding, Jerome, Lincoln, Minidoka, and Twin Falls, new HIV and AIDS cases in 2025 have already surpassed the total numbers from 2024. Specifically, HIV cases have tripled from five in 2024 to 15 in 2025, while AIDS cases have increased from one to nine in the same period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SCPHD is urging residents to mitigate their risk by using condoms and seeking timely HIV and STI testing after sexual contact with new partners. "HIV is now a manageable condition with proper treatment; however, cases that are undiagnosed or go untreated remain a serious concern," said Jacob Ward, SCPHD epidemiologist. He emphasized the importance of early testing and consistent treatment to protect long-term health, noting that untreated HIV can progress to AIDS, severely weakening the immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In observance of World AIDS Day on Dec. 1, SCPHD will offer free HIV screenings at its Twin Falls and Jerome locations on select days in December. Residents can walk in for testing at the Twin Falls Office on Thursday, Dec. 4, and at the Jerome Office on Tuesday, Dec. 9, between 8 a.m. and 7 p.m. Spanish-speaking services will be available at both locations. Idahonews.com has reached out to Southwest District Health, which covers the Boise area, to determine how many cases have been reported. We will update this story as we learn more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KBOI</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 23:45:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxQY1BsREtLeDRPNHplX19uaHBVcHJKTkpJMXFnWkpSc3pIUVR2LUdPREhSSU1HZE12TnZtUkFVV0QxZGl5WlctbkVVWFVlLUFZZzhtMndCYVhiRHNlXzRvNmxvQ2VEWHZaQ0dqN1ZISjhIV2xmdVNWVTJaM2FMajVWZnhjVGs4LXhkV2xma0htTzRFYVIwdEhMUnNjc015dkRpUlp3ZQ</guid></item><item><title>每天喝咖啡可能会减缓严重精神疾病患者的生物学衰老- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-daily-coffee-biological-aging-people.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 23:30:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQYzMtSkFUSmVyWVM2SEw0SWxoZjJtMy1leFF6QUZraWFRNUhMRXBrNjhKdWxza2Z3a1Y5THhXSHZOa2pXSWpndTdMeGM5czBSdnhSUmZ4TWpKVGNHNDdNRHAwLW8yNHZEV2ZFU090bUdCMXlqbFZBRWowSV91OHVlX0J6bzhqWVE</guid></item><item><title>奶酪消费和痴呆风险：您每周的奶酪习惯可能会揭示未来的大脑健康状况-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/cheese-consumption-and-dementia-risk-what-your-weekly-cheese-habit-may-reveal-about-future-brain-health/articleshow/125569666.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Something is comforting about cheese. It is familiar, versatile and woven into so many everyday meals, whether it is paneer in a curry, cheddar in a sandwich or mozzarella on a Friday night pizza. Most of us think about cheese in terms of flavour and convenience, not long term health. Yet researchers have begun looking at whether small dietary choices, such as how often you eat cheese, might relate to your future brain health. The idea sounds almost too simple, but sometimes lifestyle habits that seem insignificant can form quiet patterns over time. As conversations around dementia risk grow, even a food as ordinary as cheese has found its way into scientific discussion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A major peer reviewed study titled&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/17/21/3363" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Cheese Consumption and Incidence of Dementia in Community Dwelling Older Japanese Adults: The JAGES 2019–2022 Cohort Study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; followed more than 7,900 adults aged 65 and older for three years and found that weekly cheese consumption was linked with a lower incidence of dementia. This does not mean cheese prevents dementia, but the association is strong enough to merit attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Sleepless in middle age: A risky link to dementia&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How your weekly cheese consumption may be linked to lower dementia risk&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study compared adults who ate cheese at least once a week with those who did not eat cheese at all. Among weekly cheese eaters, around 3.4 per cent developed dementia during the follow-up period, compared with about 4.5 per cent in non-cheese eaters. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After accounting for factors such as age, income, physical activity and existing health conditions, the cheese eating group still showed a hazard ratio of 0.76, which translates to roughly a 24 per cent relative reduction in dementia risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The absolute difference remains small, but when viewed at a population level, especially in countries where cheese is not regularly consumed, even small nutritional habits may add up. The study’s strength lies in its large sample size and careful adjustment of lifestyle factors, which helps rule out some of the common confounders that often appear in nutrition research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What the research says about &lt;keyword id="31003993" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="cheese-consumption-and-dementia-risk" source="keywords"&gt;cheese consumption and dementia risk&lt;/keyword&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the study did not prove a direct cause, it offered several theories for why cheese might be linked with better cognitive outcomes. Cheese contains high-quality proteins, essential fatty acids and vitamin K2, all of which support vascular and neurological health. Since the health of blood vessels is closely tied to cognitive function, foods that promote vascular wellbeing could indirectly influence dementia risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another theory relates to the gut microbiome. Many cheeses, particularly fermented varieties, contain beneficial bacterial cultures and bioactive peptides that may support a healthier gut environment. Research over recent years has shown a strong connection between gut health and the ageing brain, although this particular study did not differentiate types of cheese. Still, the idea that fermented dairy foods can influence long-term cognitive outcomes has become an active area of scientific interest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is also possible that people who eat cheese tend to have more diverse or nutrient-rich diets overall. The study found that non-cheese eaters often had generally poorer dietary patterns. Therefore, cheese consumption might act as a marker for a healthier eating style rather than being the single protective factor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why cheese might support brain health according to emerging science&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond the nutrient profile, researchers believe cheese may align with dietary patterns that support better brain ageing. Diets rich in whole foods, moderate in healthy fats and balanced in protein are often associated with reduced dementia risk. When cheese is consumed in moderation, it can contribute to this balance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cheese also provides satiety, which may indirectly improve diet quality by limiting excessive snacking or reducing reliance on highly processed foods. While this is not explicitly measured in the study, nutritional habits tend to work as a network of behaviours rather than isolated choices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, it is important to understand the limits of the evidence. The study did not measure biomarkers or track the effects of different cheese varieties. Nor did it explore portion sizes, meaning the results apply only to frequency, not quantity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What can your own diet take from the cheese and dementia risk findings&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings do not suggest that increasing cheese intake alone will meaningfully change your dementia risk. Instead, they highlight the value of a well-rounded diet where cheese can play a part. Eating cheese once or twice a week fits comfortably within most healthy eating patterns, especially when combined with fruits, vegetables, whole grains, nuts and omega-rich foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you enjoy cheese already, the research offers a gentle reassurance that your weekly habit may align with positive long-term patterns. If you avoid dairy because of intolerance or preference, there is no need to add cheese solely for brain health. Plenty of foods such as leafy greens, berries, legumes and oily fish also support cognitive wellbeing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What the study means for long term brain health and everyday eating&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The connection between cheese consumption and dementia risk adds a thoughtful angle to our understanding of diet and ageing. It is an association, not a prescription, but it invites a broader discussion about the small consistent choices that support brain health across decades. Cheese can be part of this picture, but it remains just one element among sleep, exercise, social engagement, mental stimulation and overall diet quality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If anything, the study reminds us that brain health is shaped by a mosaic of everyday habits. Your weekly cheese habit might be one of them, offering not a magic solution but a small, meaningful piece of the larger puzzle of healthy ageing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for general informational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the guidance of a qualified healthcare provider regarding any medical condition or lifestyle change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also read| &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/why-your-habit-of-swinging-your-leg-could-be-linked-to-stress-alertness-and-even-metabolism/articleshow/125560227.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Why your habit of swinging your leg could be linked to stress, alertness and even metabolism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwJBVV95cUxPeWJyeVE5NVVFTXpHTmNYb1pFX1hNRjhQdDY3ZU5XUV8tVlozMHQtMmVCVmc1eDNyWDZ6eEdYNzlQUE1GcEhvMHVEZElYX1packVpOW9NTU93Wl8ydnUxT1BvcXFMd0QxWkxBeXp3YXczUGpoMUR4bzJPaXVobjhhWGJZd3h4YnpSclBrQmF1M1h6ZTlhNDdfUlNmRG5JaUdkVUdDak5rX3RvYldlQ3prOTRkRndyTjZuNnV5R0dXVWRpZHRoOE1KYWVnbkhhekR4a2NMM01sbEZXUjdNSGZoZEQzdW9XNGc4UWUtZldPcW4zemhhVG5RRTcyVWtWd3hJbnA0a05DQWlVSWRsRExZUEtfQjZpX1dwQzdsY1JMeVZZOVlwT2RvVnZhZw</guid></item><item><title>GLP-1药物可改善心脏健康，但前提是您要继续服用- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/health/2025/11/glp-1-drugs-improve-heart-health-but-only-if-you-keep-taking-them/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
          
          
&lt;p&gt;Of the 308 who benefited from tirzepatide, 254 (82 percent) regained at least 25 percent of the weight they had lost on the drug by week 88. Further, 177 (57 percent) regained at least 50 percent, and 74 (24 percent) regained at least 75 percent. Generally, the more weight people regained, the more their cardiovascular and metabolic health improvements reversed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Data gaps and potential off-ramps&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, there were 54 participants of the 308 (17.5 percent) that didn’t regain a significant amount of weight (less than 25 percent.) This group saw some of their health metrics worsen on withdrawal of the drug, but not all— blood pressure increased a bit, but cholesterol didn’t go up significantly overall. About a dozen participants (4 percent of the 308) continued to lose weight after stopping the drug.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers couldn’t figure out why these 54 participants fared so well; there were “no apparent differences” in demographic or clinical characteristics, they reported. It’s clear the topic requires further study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, overall, the study offers a gloomy outlook for patients hoping to avoid needing to take anti-obesity drugs for the foreseeable future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oczypok and Anderson highlight that the study involved an abrupt withdrawal from the drug. In contrast, many patients may be interested in slowly weaning off the drugs, stepping down dosage levels over time. So far, data on this strategy and the protocols to pull it off have little data behind them. It also might not be an option for patients who abruptly lose access or insurance coverage of the drugs. Other strategies for weaning off the drugs could involve ramping up physical activity or calorie restriction in anticipation of dropping the drugs, the experts note.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to more data on potential GLP-1 off-ramps, the pair calls for more data on the effects of weight fluctuations from people going on and off the treatment. At least one study has found that the regained weight after intentional weight loss may end up being proportionally higher in fat mass, which could be harmful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For now, Oczypok and Anderson say doctors should be cautious about talking with patients about these drugs and what the future could hold. “These results add to the body of evidence that clinicians and patients should approach starting [anti-obesity medications] as long-term therapies, just as they would medications for other chronic diseases.”&lt;/p&gt;


          
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                  
          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:44:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxQeXBFWlYtdmlxUVZIQlRGMzhKLVh5OEtfS29yS3FKMkxBMy1mZnNaVzk5ck1qY282VjhqNjdQMElKNTY4OVFZLUNhZUdLMk5sdVprSVFJbUJpY0tad0s1YlVQaE9FcmJPcnljeGdBbS1IcHN4aTY1WWxFdkltMHpjbC1KZzJQcEROSkd1WVRQc3VxaUp0OTZUOENJTGtQSnYzaHhXZnBYS0k</guid></item><item><title>肯塔基州第三名婴儿死于百日咳，全国病例连续第二年居高不下- CIDRAP</title><link>https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/pertussis/third-infant-kentucky-dies-whooping-cough-national-cases-stay-high-second-year-row</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-field-body field--type-text-long field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;&lt;p&gt;An infant in Kentucky who was unvaccinated against pertussis, or whooping cough, has died, marking the third death from the deadly bacteria in the state this year. Before 2025, Kentucky had last recorded an infant whooping cough death in 2018.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.chfs.ky.gov/News/Documents/Third%2520Infant%2520Pertussis%2520Death%2520Reported%2520in%2520Kentucky%2520in%252012%2520Months.pdf"&gt;&lt;u&gt;State officials&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; said Kentucky is seeing the most pertussis activity since 2012 and expects more in the coming weeks. So far this year, Kentucky has reported at least 566 cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt; Many illnesses can be prevented through vaccination, which helps protect not only the individual but also those around them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We are deeply saddened to learn of another infant death in Kentucky due to pertussis and are concerned by the volume of cases we are seeing throughout the commonwealth,”&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Steven Stack, MD, the state secretary of Kentucky’s Cabinet for Health and Family Services, said in a statement. “We continue to urge Kentuckians to get their whooping cough vaccine and to make sure they are up to date on all other recommended immunizations. Many illnesses can be prevented through vaccination, which helps protect not only the individual but also those around them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Numbers surge post-pandemic&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nationally, there are more than 25,000 cases of whooping cough reported so far in 2025, according to a new report from&lt;a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/25000-cases-whooping-cough-recorded-year-higher-pre/story?id=127831021"&gt;&lt;u&gt; ABC news&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. In 2024, more than 33,000 cases were reported by November. Pertussis cases had dropped significantly during the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2019, 18,600 whooping cough cases were reported nationwide. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), however, says that many cases go unrecognized and unreported.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Reported cases of pertussis have been trending down since a peak in November 2024. However, preliminary case report numbers remain elevated in 2025 compared to immediately before the pandemic,” &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/php/surveillance/index.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;the CDC said.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;u&gt; &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.fox4news.com/news/whooping-cough-cases-rise-texas"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Texas has reported&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the most whooping cough activity this year, with at least 3,500 cases so far in 2025, and two associated deaths among infants. Both Louisiana and Washington state also reported high activity at the beginning of the year.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts say falling vaccination rates seen during the pandemic are likely the reason for the increased activity. &lt;a href="https://www.nfid.org/infectious-disease/whooping-cough/"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Infants at 2 months&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of age and older should receive their initial vaccine (in a series of five) against pertussis, as should pregnant women and infant caregivers.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CIDRAP</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 21:57:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxPc2tKNUlLT29CVUlYMW9uazBkaENSOXhXa2JmcTJNRWw5ekJXYnFIWFFSNzdFcVpacnhDdDd0TzVwNnU3MFZ4Sm9aQ1J0SWtHNjlJWGZuT2tpWFlmWjN3cVBia3ZXMFNuSTRUeVdjdGE5cW5Zdllab252dUpKbTQ0SzdOaFJ2SE9KWm5zdDUzXzUyQVJsaEFncHZ6V0hDQUw2RFFTVURjcWh5SkRQSDRRVldqWXFmT2pUSVZR</guid></item><item><title>男孩在家人面前死亡，据称医生称喉咙痛“只是一种病毒” - TMZ</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2025/11/25/boy-dies-after-doctor-dismisses-sore-throat/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;header class="article__header"&gt;
                              &lt;h1 class="article__header--headline-title"&gt;Boy Dies in Front of Family, Doctor Allegedly Called Sore Throat 'Just a Virus'&lt;/h1&gt;
                    &lt;h2 class="article__header--headline-fragments"&gt;
                          &lt;span class="article__header--hf1 text-uppercase h3"&gt;11-Year-Old Boy&lt;/span&gt;
                          &lt;span class="article__header--hf2 text-uppercase h1"&gt;Dies In Front of Family ...&lt;/span&gt;
                          &lt;span class="article__header--hf3 text-none h2"&gt;Mom Claims Dr. Said It's 'Just a Virus'&lt;/span&gt;
                      &lt;/h2&gt;
        
        
        
                  &lt;p class="date-wrapper"&gt;
                        Published &lt;time class="published-datetime" datetime="2025-11-25T13:36:37-08:00"&gt;November 25, 2025 1:36 PM PST&lt;/time&gt;
                                                                      &lt;span class="divider"&gt;|&lt;/span&gt;
                Updated &lt;time datetime="2025-11-25T14:49:15-08:00"&gt;November 25, 2025 2:49 PM PST&lt;/time&gt;
                                    &lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/header&gt;

      &lt;div class="article__blocks clearfix"&gt;
        
        
    

    &lt;section id="cb-b0d8e3cb389522ddf46c06d21766bea0" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;An 11-year-old boy in England died in front of his mother and grandmother at home ... just hours after complaining to his doctor about a sore throat and being told it was nothing to worry about.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    &lt;section id="cb-0f4054c3d63bfff2af23fe3a902a563f" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frankie-Rae Law&lt;/strong&gt; went to see a doctor on Nov. 14 in England, but he was told his sore throat was "just a virus," and he was sent home and died ... according to the South West News Service.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    &lt;section id="cb-e67fe712102350a7c5b09757f720a9ff" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;The boy's mother, &lt;strong&gt;Keleigh Law&lt;/strong&gt;, says her son's condition got worse in a hurry later that night ... she says he was laughing and playing around like usual when all of a sudden, he started having trouble breathing.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;
&lt;a id="continued" class="continued-anchor"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;

    

    &lt;section id="cb-f1956c1d62e9a0e3b49031ca1be90eb4" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Keleigh says her son came to the living room, gasping for air, and his face expressed "absolute sheer horror." She says they went to the bathroom, and within moments, he was unconscious, slumped over the toilet.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    &lt;section id="cb-4ded924e7135e781b1d1799905ddcccb" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;She says his lips were gray, and his eyes were glazed ... and his grandma performed CPR for 30 minutes, but he only opened his eyes for a couple of seconds and spat up some saliva before knocking out again.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    &lt;section id="cb-60eb14420d5fcebd5caebb35f43799f3" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Keleigh called paramedics, and her son was rushed to a hospital, where doctors put him on a ventilator and told her the chance of survival was "very thin." She says she was told he would have brain damage if he survived, and she ultimately pulled the plug.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    

    &lt;section id="cb-f88aa31cca8a1f0f42b04c1d9459b097" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  canvas-block-is-last " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Frankie-Rae's cause of death is unclear ... his mom says she has no clue what was wrong with him and feels like she "failed him."&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TMZ</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 21:36:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxPQV9aelZPM3NFSEJIM2xXcThhZWczdG0waFdPZUJvVXdyTGo0TmVXNWFka2t5ejUxOE1XTXVwbGEyWVNjSTMwaDlZTGtlU0hEOVJzOUtoNDRXSGVXak9mbFQ5NGpia3hXNWRUX2FiRVY2Y2VQRVYwTWgybTB1Q3NRdw</guid></item><item><title>路易斯安那州官员称新冠疫苗“危险” ，因为疾病预防控制中心的关键职位-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/nov/25/ralph-abraham-deputy-cdc-director</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Ralph Abraham, a top Louisiana health official who stopped promoting mass vaccination policies and once described &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/coronavirus-outbreak" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Covid-19&lt;/a&gt; vaccines as “dangerous”, has been appointed deputy director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), it was revealed on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) has not formally announced Abraham’s appointment, but the center’s internal database now lists Abraham as the federal agency’s principal deputy director, effective this week. Abraham’s appointment was confirmed &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/11/25/cdc-new-deputy-vaccine-ralph-abraham/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;to the Washington Post&lt;/a&gt; by an HHS spokesperson.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Abraham’s appointment is certain to cause renewed anxiety among health experts as rifts deepen over US vaccine policy under the leadership of the health secretary, &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/robert-f-kennedy-jr" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Robert F Kennedy Jr&lt;/a&gt;, who is reconstituting leadership at US federal health agencies in ways that &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/sep/17/cdc-director-susan-monarez-key-takeaways" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;prioritize vaccine skepticism&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="d8a3fe59-44f3-4c13-909d-91902064b7dc" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":3,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"RFK Jr’s anti-vaccine fight and US fear for public health: key moments from ousted CDC director’s testimony","elementId":"d8a3fe59-44f3-4c13-909d-91902064b7dc","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/sep/17/cdc-director-susan-monarez-key-takeaways"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;As Louisiana’s surgeon general since 2024, Abraham drew criticism for directing state health agencies to stop promoting mass vaccination as a public health strategy, and for criticizing “blanket government mandates” for immunizations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Earlier this year, Abraham wrote that “missteps” during the Covid-19 pandemic had caused a loss of trust in government.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Government should admit the limitations of its role in people’s lives and pull back its tentacles from the practice of medicine,” &lt;a href="https://ldh.la.gov/news/7478" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;he wrote&lt;/a&gt;, adding that “restoring this trust requires returning medical decisions to the doctor-patient relationship, where informed, personalized care is guided by compassion and expertise rather than blanket government mandates.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Notably, after Abraham left a congressional seat he had held from 2015 to 2021, his elected successor was his chief of staff, Luke Letlow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Letlow, who received Abraham’s support while running for Congress, then died from Covid-19 in December 2020 – days before he was due to be sworn in – at a time when protective vaccines against the virus were not widely available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Letlow’s widow, Julia Letlow, was subsequently elected to her late husband’s seat, with constituents who live in an area with a history of generally low vaccination rates. In April 2021, Julia Letlow told CBS News: “I would’ve given anything – I would’ve given everything – for that shot to be available for us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Looking back now, and for someone to turn it away, it’s heartbreaking to me.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The CDC currently has no permanent director following the &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/aug/27/cdc-director-susan-monarez-ousted" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;ousting of Susan Monarez&lt;/a&gt; over the summer. The HHS deputy secretary, Jim O’Neill, is serving as acting CDC director, making Abraham effectively No 1 at the institution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The agency, headquartered in Atlanta, Georgia, was rocked when a gunman &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/aug/11/atlanta-cdc-shooting" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;opened fire&lt;/a&gt; there. One of the suspect’s neighbors &lt;a href="https://www.ajc.com/news/2025/08/active-shooter-reported-on-emory-university-campus/?postId-9997223" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;told the Atlanta Journal-Constitution&lt;/a&gt;: “He very deeply believed that vaccines hurt him and were hurting other people.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Abraham’s elevation adds to the vaccine skeptics working at the CDC under Kennedy, who has previously cut funding to vaccine research programs and purged pro-vaccine members from the CDC’s federal vaccine advisory board.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Abraham’s position on vaccines has previously brought him into conflict with the Louisiana US senator Bill Cassidy, a pro-vaccination physician, when Abraham &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/louisiana-vaccination-surgeon-general-8e2eecde047648e6fb62c4b44edd6566" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;canceled the state’s mass&lt;/a&gt; vaccination program. The state is now in the midst of its worst &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/10/28/nx-s1-5576494/louisiana-whooping-cough-pertussis-infant-deaths" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;whooping cough outbreak&lt;/a&gt; in three decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Nonetheless, on the same day that Abraham canceled Louisiana’s mass vaccination program, Cassidy &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/feb/16/louisiana-vaccines-rfk-jr" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;voted to confirm&lt;/a&gt; Kennedy as HHS secretary. And Kennedy has now appointed Abraham.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Asked by CNN last weekend if Kennedy’s vaccine positions could cause harm to Americans, the senator responded that “anything that undermines the understanding, the correct understanding, the absolute scientifically based understanding that vaccines are safe and that, if you don’t take them, you’re putting your child or yourself in greater danger, anything that undermines that message is a problem.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 21:35:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNZi0zTlhMcXhOcXlLUTc0REU5bFVnWGo5MzZGZmQwYktEdm5rUm1wUnpYRUJWLXlYcUFPYWNvUTZwWXRBeHlDcE13VWJkTWlQT0F5WTdkWnFXU3c5azZkcUtnZGJ5TnNjaVBmUl9HUjZfVTZtZnRwUk9wRUFmYkpHRExVbXhvWTlC</guid></item><item><title>研究绘制了成人8种长COVID症状模式- CIDRAP</title><link>https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/covid-19/study-maps-8-long-covid-symptom-patterns-adults</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-field-body field--type-text-long field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A large, prospective US &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-025-65239-4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;study&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; has identified eight distinct long-COVID trajectories, highlighting the diverse manifestations of the condition and laying the groundwork for future studies to evaluate risk factors and biomarkers that could explain variations in symptoms and identify therapeutic targets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The study, led by a team at Massachusetts General Hospital, followed 3,659 participants (69% female) from the National Institutes of Health Researching COVID to Enhance Recovery (RECOVER) Adult Cohort. The National Institutes of Health established RECOVER to address COVID as a global health priority.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Researchers tracked participants from 3 to 15 months after their first COVID infection. Almost all participants (99.6%) were infected with the Omicron variant. The enrollment period spanned October 29, 2021, to June 27, 2023. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Overall, 10.3% of participants met the criteria for long COVID at three months, and 81% of them continued to report persistent or fluctuating symptoms more than a year later.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The findings were published last week in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Nature Communications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;14% of participants experienced worsening symptoms over time&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Eight symptom trajectories emerged. About 5% of the infected cohort had “persistent, high” symptom burden across the entire 15-month period, while 12% experienced “intermittently high” symptoms. Another 10% showed moderate symptoms that gradually improved, and 9% experienced low-level symptoms that largely resolved by month six. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Notably, 14% followed worsening or delayed-worsening trajectories, including a group whose symptoms remained minimal until spiking at month 15.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The study compared infected participants with an uninfected cohort over the same period. While persistent and improving symptoms were less common among uninfected adults, some worsening patterns appeared in both groups, raising the possibility that not all symptom increases reflect long COVID.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The authors note several study limitations, including reliance on symptom surveys collected every three months (which may not have captured more granular, day-to-day changes), and the inability to capture trajectories beyond 15 months. Still, the large sample size, representative population, detailed symptom questionnaire, standardized long-COVID index, and minimal loss to follow up provide a clearer picture of long COVID’s different trajectories. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In a Mass General Brigham (MGB) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/about/newsroom/press-releases/insights-into-long-covid-trajectories-in-adults"&gt;&lt;span&gt;press release&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, corresponding author Bruce Levy, MD, of the MGB Department of Medicine, said, “Our findings will help determine what resources are needed for clinical and public health support of individuals with long COVID and will also inform efforts to understand long COVID’s biological basis.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CIDRAP</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 21:02:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPOWNFYXdUUnI5QllVN21ESk5xSVZ3NFBaNVdLakFYdnZSV2FpWVZYaE1Yc2l3MHdLeVlwV3R3VWoxeVlpTHBjUVpwQWdJT3JzOXl0VWdDLURvMU5VVFRlOXdUeHVzUUF1VkhjX0JFX1huV3JVYm9QVS1mUUpsOEg2em1hUVkyMGtqamNJ</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心悄悄关闭了疫苗搜索工具。它什么时候回来还不清楚。- NOTUS —美国新闻</title><link>https://www.notus.org/health-science/cdc-quietly-turned-off-vaccine-search-tool</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="RichTextArticleBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                    &lt;p&gt;Over the summer, a government website that helped Americans find vaccines got a MAHA makeover. Then it stopped working altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration removed language from &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="http://vaccines.gov" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Vaccines.gov&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; that said “Vaccines can help you stay healthy” on June 24, according to a NOTUS analysis of &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://web.archive.org/web/20250624010930/https://www.vaccines.gov/en/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;previous&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://web.archive.org/web/20250624202844/https://www.vaccines.gov/en/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;versions&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; of the site cached by &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="http://web.archive.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;web.archive.org&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. It also cut the site’s FAQ section explaining “The best way to protect yourself and your loved ones is to get the vaccines recommended for you” and — most critically — changed the search tool that allowed users to enter their ZIP code to find vaccination sites in their area.&lt;/p&gt;
    
        

    
&lt;p&gt;Now, the ZIP code search doesn’t work. A site banner on the page states: “The functionality of this website may be impacted while it is being updated.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changes to a Centers for Disease Control and Prevention &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.notus.org/health-science/robert-f-kennedy-changes-to-cdc-website-vaccine-language" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; linking vaccines to rising autism rates drew &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.notus.org/health-science/sen-bill-cassidy-cdc-anti-vaccine-language-change-rfk-jr" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;widespread criticism&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; when they were made last week. But it appears that the agency has been quietly pulling back its online vaccination resources for much longer. The CDC did not give NOTUS a timeline for when Vaccines.gov would function again — nor did it answer repeated inquiries about the stated updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“&lt;i&gt;&lt;u&gt;As publicly stated on the website banner&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;, the functionality of this website may be impacted while it is being updated,” a CDC spokesperson told NOTUS via email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The changes to Vaccines.gov were made at a tumultuous moment for the CDC and U.S. vaccine policy. One day after the Trump administration removed information from the site, the CDC Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices — made up of a cadre of vaccine skeptics &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.notus.org/health-science/rfk-jr-cdc-vaccine-recommendation-panel" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;hand-selected&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; by Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. — held its &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/06/25/nx-s1-5438482/cdc-vaccine-committee-acip-meeting-rfk" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;first meeting&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; of the MAHA era.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around six weeks later, the website was &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://web.archive.org/web/20250803013924/https://www.vaccines.gov/en/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;edited&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://web.archive.org/web/20250807022021/https://www.vaccines.gov/en/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;again&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to include the banner alerting users that the functionality might be impacted while the site is being updated, cached versions show.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="Enhancement" data-align-center&gt;
        &lt;div class="Enhancement-item"&gt;
            
            
                
                    
                        
                            &lt;bsp-carousel class="Carousel" data-module data-credit-parenthesis&gt;
    
    &lt;a class="AnchorLink" id="gallery-940001" name="gallery-940001"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;


    

    
    &lt;a class="AnchorLink" id="gallery-940001" name="gallery-940001"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;





    &lt;div class="Carousel-slides"&gt;
        
            
                &lt;div class="Carousel-slide"&gt;
                    &lt;div class="CarouselSlide"&gt;
    
    &lt;div class="CarouselSlide-info"&gt;
        &lt;div&gt;
            &lt;span class="CarouselSlide-slideCount"&gt;1 of 2:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="CarouselSlide-infoDescription"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot/web.archive.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="CarouselSlide-infoAttribution"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A screenshot of Vaccines.gov before the Trump administration made changes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

                &lt;/div&gt;
            
                &lt;div class="Carousel-slide"&gt;
                    &lt;div class="CarouselSlide"&gt;
    
    &lt;div class="CarouselSlide-info"&gt;
        &lt;div&gt;
            &lt;span class="CarouselSlide-slideCount"&gt;2 of 2:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="CarouselSlide-infoDescription"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot/web.archive.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="CarouselSlide-infoAttribution"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A screenshot of Vaccines.gov after the Trump administration made changes to the website’s language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

                &lt;/div&gt;
            
        
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/bsp-carousel&gt;
                        
                    
                
            
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vaccines.gov was originally launched by the Biden administration in &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://bidenwhitehouse.archives.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2022/03/30/fact-sheet-biden-administration-launches-covid-gov-a-new-one-stop-shop-website-for-vaccines-tests-treatments-masks-and-the-latest-covid-19-information/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;2021&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. It &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.usds.gov/projects/vaccines-dot-gov" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;grew&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; out of a collaboration between the CDC and researchers at Boston Children’s Hospital, who had previously collaborated to develop the vaccination search engine &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="http://vaccinefinder.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;VaccineFinder.org&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. That site remains active, but it’s unclear if its team is still receiving government funds. The website &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://web.archive.org/web/20201119044644/https://www.vaccinefinder.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;no longer sports&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; the CDC’s logo.&lt;/p&gt;
    
        

    
&lt;p&gt;John Brownstein, whose team at Boston Children’s ran Vaccinefinder.org, &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/02/24/business/vaccine-finder-org.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;told&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; the New York Times in 2021 that the project received around $1 million per year from the federal government to maintain the site, first from HHS, then from CDC directly beginning in 2017. He said at the time that they also received over $8 million to expand to include COVID-19 vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most recent record of government funding for Vaccines.gov NOTUS was able to locate was a &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://sam.gov/workspace/contract/opp/2997179c770f471aa9903b4bf49ca396/view" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;2023 grant&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A spokesperson for Vaccinefinder.org told NOTUS via email that their organization ran Vaccines.gov until their funding contract ended in July.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We are not aware of who at CDC maintains the website now,” the spokesperson said. They did not immediately respond to questions about whether the contract was canceled or not renewed. Brownstein and Boston Children’s Hospital did not immediately respond to requests for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One former CDC official who requested anonymity to speak candidly said Vaccines.gov was formerly under the jurisdiction of the CDC’s National Center for Immunization and Respiratory Diseases, but currently, “decisions are being made by CDC leadership/HHS leadership.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If it’s down, it would be because IRD was directed to take it down,” the official said.&lt;/p&gt;
    
        

    
&lt;p&gt;Former NCIRD director Demetre Daskalakis confirmed that Vaccines.gov was a “CDC asset” that HHS “took over.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I have heard that they are planning to ‘update it’ and shudder to think what that will mean,” Daskalakis told NOTUS via email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Federal, state and local health organizations have continued to refer to Vaccines.gov as a resource for people searching for vaccines — despite the fact that the website is a dead end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You can locate a vaccine site at &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.vaccines.gov/search/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.vaccines.gov/search/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,” the Department of Veterans Affairs website says on a &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.va.gov/long-beach-health-care/programs/seasonal-vaccination/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;page&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; that was updated this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Visit Vaccines.gov to: Find vaccination locations near you from your health department or pharmacies,” says a &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.usa.gov/covid-tests-vaccinations" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;page on USA.gov&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; that was updated last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even HHS still &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.hhs.gov/immunization/get-vaccinated/where/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;advertises&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; its own broken website on a page about where to get vaccinated against COVID-19, along with a texting service and number to call to find vaccination sites, both of which also appear to no longer be active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration has already made changes to other Biden-era health websites, including &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="http://covid.gov" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Covid.gov&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="http://covidtests.gov" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Covidtests.gov&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, which used to host information about treatment, testing and vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now they are about the controversial theory that the COVID-19 pandemic started in a Chinese lab.&lt;/p&gt;
                                &lt;/div&gt;
                            
                            

                            
                                
                                
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NOTUS — News of the United States</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 21:00:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxOZ2EyV2FVTkF0LVdwVXI3aEl6T0ZkeS1GckhRV3RKdFVNV3hjaW5UYlIxXzJRZmtKVXh1aUZwWkxWZEZlcFI1bXJVZkhnRFJ5VEJvOGZNejdSQnpwdnpjUll1clR0bnZrQ254NjZkYlBSaXVheGxVXzhaT3Z5NUxyNzZMd0pBdw</guid></item><item><title>美国诺如病毒病例呈上升趋势，自8月以来阳性检测率翻了一番- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/us-cases-norovirus-rise-double-rate-positive-tests/story?id=127872876</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;Cases of norovirus are rising across the United States, doubling over the last few months, according to updated data from the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/nrevss/php/dashboard/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; (CDC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Nearly 14% of tests came back positive for norovirus during the most recent week ending Nov. 15, compared to roughly 7% about three months ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Test positivity is a metric used to identify how many people are confirmed to have norovirus after an illness is suspected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Health experts have said that, like other measurements, test positivity is imperfect as it depends on the number of tests that are ordered, which can vary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Last December saw a &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/norovirus-cases-rise-us/story?id=117138204" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;record-breaking rate of norovirus cases&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. with nearly 25% of tests coming back positive. Cases had been trending down since then but have begun to rise in recent weeks, CDC data shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Norovirus virus particles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;STOCK PHOTO/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Electronic health records data &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://nam04.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.epicresearch.org%2Fdata-tracker%2Fcommunicable-diseases&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CMary.Kekatos%40abc.com%7C381ce600d3ac44c0616108de2c29d046%7C56b731a8a2ac4c32bf6b616810e913c6%7C1%7C0%7C638996755258563493%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=Mr3S9UN5qU4E2kDJtMVNGzNcoFIYFeu03WRStFwwFf0%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;from Epic Research&lt;/a&gt; show that Alabama, Nebraska, Oklahoma, Texas and Wyoming are some of the states currently experiencing the highest number of norovirus cases. Emergency department visits have been on the rise since July, Epic Research data shows. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Norovirus is a &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/norovirus/about/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;highly contagious virus&lt;/a&gt; that is the most common cause of viral gastroenteritis, which is an inflammation of the inside lining of the gastrointestinal tract.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Although it's often referred to as the "stomach bug" or "stomach flu," norovirus illness is not related to influenza.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Norovirus is the leading cause of foodborne illness in the U.S., causing 58% of foodborne illnesses each year, and responsible for about 2,5000 outbreaks annually, according to the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/norovirus/data-research/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The most &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/norovirus/about/index.html#cdc_disease_basics_symptoms-signs-and-symptoms" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;common symptoms&lt;/a&gt; are nausea, vomiting, stomach pain and diarrhea. Patients, however, can also experience fever, headaches and body aches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Typically, an infected person will develop symptoms between 12 to 48 hours after being infected. However, norovirus typically resolves quickly and, in most healthy adults, lasts one to three days, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Health experts say the best way to prevent getting norovirus is to wash hands with warm soap and water for 20 seconds. Hand sanitizer alone does not work well against norovirus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;The &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/norovirus/prevention/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;CDC says&lt;/a&gt; people should wash their hands after using the toilet or changing diapers as well as when eating, preparing or handling food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:58:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxPZkE1TTZVZnZROUpkdVVaaXgtSWtvMmVwM3VqakR1OFplS25GQzRyajlzajh2NF82RFNxYTI0Tmx3VTB1N3pHWXU3alA4X1FYdEQ4OTVQaDY1VnJ2U2c3cGpMODBxaU9la0JhLTIzUFA2YzNzU0FYbkJmLXhqMmpGWUhGZnBVRG5IazBPWGxNbEQwN2RUSDU1T0tMYTlVSmpL0gGmAUFVX3lxTE5vWlA0d3M2NzNnVzB1OFFseFQzVk9PTlFZcDZKcWFoa3FpSzFKNjlwa2lYd2M3TU80Mjk5bUhtdFhDZDFCSUNOaHBxWVJRWW01Sk1BOGhtUDJ0UzdZd2d3S0l1cWRfQzZUTXBIY0YxdTFVODl1S2d2bTdWLWVaSTQwTFV1YnQxOWlMMHJ5bXZCa3NBaU1WYTM2bzBpc1FsZzhfQldiaHc</guid></item><item><title>研究人员强调与慢性大麻使用相关的新诊断- WSB-TV</title><link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/national/researchers-highlight-new-diagnosis-tied-chronic-cannabis-use/HODGBPDY5NHKVFNHFEFGRDXPJ4/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="default__ArticleBody-sc-tl066j-1 jPcFTl article-body-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;A condition connected to long-term cannabis use has been recognized as a formal diagnosis, researchers said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;The World Health Organization stated cannabis hyperemesis syndrome can cause severe stomach pain, vomiting and nausea, &lt;a href="https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/uw-study-researchers-highlight-new-diagnosis-tied-chronic-cannabis-use/LUPADHUMVVHYHIIC4GBTERQ7SI/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/uw-study-researchers-highlight-new-diagnosis-tied-chronic-cannabis-use/LUPADHUMVVHYHIIC4GBTERQ7SI/"&gt;according to KIRO&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;The new diagnosis code allows doctors to identify the condition more easily by reviewing a patient’s medical history, aiding addiction researchers and healthcare providers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;“It helps us count and monitor these cases,” said Beatriz Carlini, a research associate professor at the University of Washington School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more" class="taboola-read-more"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;The syndrome is still relatively new, and many doctors are not familiar with it. Researchers are uncertain why it affects some cannabis users and not others. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;Treatments have been identified, including home remedies like hot showers, which can alleviate symptoms when other treatments fail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;Medications such as Haldol and over-the-counter options like capsaicin cream have also been shown to ease symptoms of cannabis hyperemesis syndrome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[DOWNLOAD: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wsbtv.com/smart-tv/" title=""&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free WSB-TV News app for alerts as news breaks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more-8" class="taboola-read-more-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[SIGN UP: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://membercenter.wsbtv.com/newsletters"&gt;&lt;b&gt;WSB-TV Daily Headlines Newsletter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph body-copyright"&gt;©2025 Cox Media Group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WSB-TV</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:57:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxQdXdDZWI4WndVbGc4YnFZSjlvZlRndmIwdXJwTkJFOGxTWUMxOHJkQVVEMUpPVENHZzRoUWlrQnNmZmdCRExfTEhTN0dMQnZSM3lMUjlya3U3Y21VcmFxNms2MTFzeHlKQUVyYU1CZFlhS2ZEMEptSjVqdG5NYnI1c1dTT1l1Y24taUhPT1NCTk5kX2FxZGRaeGY0WHpZazRHTmcyUy1wZTQzeWFtNWpfWkVMSldtRGF0TllqNDRnYzdOUUnSAdcBQVVfeXFMUGxkMFJfaE42cFJTX181ZG1BNlZFSTJMd0VxaFpOTUliN2EyckRpQXMwcmtpd1ZFeXo4MWl3X05NVGxWNTg5WFk5RzBHVzFESXdHOWdxdlFIRmZuOGNKcDg0cHZzS2tHZWZuaHJVTVRKRUVGd1BHeUxtaGlBWjZmOW5FYjZnSWR5R2VrVmhBTF9GWG5CUkx1Skt5VjdUdEFVTzVfTm1rNWVrLW9FU3Bnc0VYRkdHN00ySmQ2OFJLbVRVaUtuX3lnX0YzSXJ5RlRLejVXRm03V28</guid></item><item><title>研究发现， GLP-1药物的产后处方大幅增加-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/25/health/postpartum-glp1-prescription-increase-study.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:54:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxPUW9Bc1hNS0JoUUxIREkzbFNFUjVUSWNyTE1LOTFRanBsZGhpR1ZIQ1YxZGNkREJQOS0wZ0FuRktWVGRyc04tYmlQZzVhSFBkU1Vmb05icmZSdEJuYmo1cW84WFRmTEIwWkdfZ0Z0R2JNdHpHazBMeXpUX2NJdm1jNEZVLXBzNUtzNFZKbXlWQlpOS2hL</guid></item><item><title>爱达荷州中南部公共卫生区报告HIV和艾滋病病例“急剧增加” - KTVB</title><link>https://www.ktvb.com/article/news/local/south-central-public-health-district-steep-increase-hiv-aids-in-idaho/277-17fc7f67-eff4-4bdb-9789-4d89573eb9d7</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article__summary"&gt;The health district is asking residents to stay vigilant in protecting their health by testing for STIs early and often.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class="article__body"&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TWIN FALLS, Idaho — The South Central Public Health District in Idaho has reported a "steep increase" in HIV and HIV-3, commonly known as AIDS, in several Idaho counties. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The South Central Public &lt;a href="/article/news/local/maternity-desert-oregon-county-fights-to-restore-labor-and-delivery-care-with-federal-funding/277-9b41be07-e924-4276-93b8-49bf91643258" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; District (SCPHD) oversees eight counties in Idaho, including Blaine, Camas, Cassia, Gooding, Jerome, Lincoln, Minidoka, and Twin Falls. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                        
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In those eight counties, new cases of HIV and HIV-3 in 2025 have "far outpaced total case numbers from 2024," a news release announced. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to numbers provided by SCPHD, there were five cases of HIV reported last year. However, in 2025, there were 15 cases reported. For HIV-3 cases, or AIDS cases, there was only one reported case in 2024. There have been nine reported cases this year. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SCPHD is now urging residents of these counties, and all Idahoans, to practice vigilance. SCPHD asks that residents reduce their risk of contracting HIV by using condoms and obtaining up-to-date HIV and STI testing following sexual acts with a new partner. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“HIV is now a manageable condition with proper treatment; however, cases that are undiagnosed or go untreated remain a serious concern," SCPHD Epidemiologist Jacob Ward said in a news release. "When HIV is not treated, it can progress to AIDS. This severely weakens the immune system and increases the risk of life-threatening infections and illnesses. Early testing and consistent treatment are so important to protecting long-term health.”&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;World AIDS Day is set to be held on Monday, Dec. 1. To honor the day, SCPHD will be offering free HIV screenings all day on selected dates at its Twin Falls and Jerome locations. SCPHD is doing so to support community health and early detection, a news release said. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walk-in testing at the SCPHD Twin Falls office is scheduled for Thursday, Dec. 4. At the Jerome office, walk-in testing is available on Tuesday, Dec. 9, between 8 a.m. and 7 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information regarding public health in South Central Idaho, &lt;a href="https://phd5.idaho.gov/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;you can visit this link here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For statewide public health information,&lt;a href="https://healthandwelfare.idaho.gov/health-wellness/community-health/public-health-districts" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; visit this link here.  &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KTVB</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:51:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5AFBVV95cUxOWUNNSDkwSDJqeVRkbWoxdjJkaTlNblhBSVptWllWeUQyNEJJWXlEc294d0xSWklXb1VaR1dUV3h6UlhSQ0REMzB4Sm1ZZHV1ejViajR3RUlQNC0zVFlScDNsMDV5UVMxclA1QVI4YXRtS0lFcXJPLWtNTkp4Ny1WeE1zc0o3UkVRcG5tOWI5YzVSUFlMLXdjOHBkdmpfYmpXNE1QTEh0YUFGN3B1SERoczczRjdrSWtrRHdDMGxuSi02NFUzZVdQMlNGR2FSRkNrbGJVeTFoZzFMUE45Rzh5Qk8tVVo</guid></item><item><title>路易斯安那州卫生官员停止了州疫苗运动，成为疾病预防控制中心的第二号-华盛顿邮报</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/11/25/cdc-new-deputy-vaccine-ralph-abraham/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="I56KBNCZMBF2XCJY65UHHIUFDM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A Louisiana health official who ordered his health department to stop promoting mass vaccinations this past winter during a surge in influenza cases has been tapped to serve as the new No. 2 leader at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:46:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxNQVVjY042aWlUSENPNFUxZDJuOXBQeEFtQjIycUJvQmF4a2hjWnNqUjNYQjQ1ODlMYzllZ0NRR2hiWWRHSEhGM29SaW9SNVp6YmZRelRRTldwOUg0NFlTMF8walR5ajdsVWRmZ21BRm1TdHRodHlzb1BGTTI0dV95QzZNczVoYVpzMFlhZUItMA</guid></item><item><title>Valerie Bertinelli刚刚分享了她的美味4种成分抗炎甜点- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/valerie-bertinelli-4-ingredient-anti-inflammatory-dessert-11846849</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Valerie's yummy 4-ingredient anti-inflammatory dessert is chia pudding. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;She uses a flavored protein shake as her liquid, plus blackberries and gut-healthy yogurt on top. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chia seeds have omega-3 fatty acids that may help lower inflammation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If there's anyone we trust to give us a classic recipe that they've been enjoying for years, it's Valerie Bertinelli. We loved her &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8057560/valerie-bertinelli-anti-inflammatory-snack-for-years/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;favorite old-fashioned snack&lt;/a&gt;, and now the actor and &lt;em&gt;Food Network&lt;/em&gt; host has another simple recipe to share.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Bertinelli shared an easy dessert that only takes four ingredients to make. It's customizable, tasty and may even help reduce inflammation. Here's what she had to say about her go-to cold dessert.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-making-valeries-chia-pudding"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Making Valerie's Chia Pudding &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "I made chia pudding for my treat for the day," Bertinelli said. "And it's really easy: you take 2 tablespoons of chia seeds and a half a cup of liquid."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/chia-seeds-benefits-11705262" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Chia seeds&lt;/a&gt; have plant-based omega-3 fatty acids, fiber and protein. They can help reduce inflammation, lower cholesterol and can help promote weight loss, if that is your goal. Chia pudding is a great way to incorporate the healthy seeds into your diet in a delicious way.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Plus, the liquid that Bertinelli added was Core Power's Strawberry Banana High-Protein Shake. We named Core Power as one of our favorite protein shakes on the market in &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7964007/best-protein-shakes-protein-powders/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;EatingWell's&lt;/em&gt; protein shake taste test&lt;/a&gt;, so we definitely approve of this option!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "I stirred it up, put it in the fridge, let it sit for about four hours," Bertinelli explained. "Overnight's better, but I forgot to make it last night. And then I put a little bit of vanilla yogurt on top and some fresh blackberries."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-valerie-fights-inflammation-with-dessert"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Valerie Fights Inflammation with Dessert &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Topping off the pudding with blackberries and yogurt adds an extra &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-foods-to-fight-inflammation-11762781" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;anti-inflammatory punch&lt;/a&gt; to this recipe. Adding these foods into your eating pattern can contribute to reducing inflammation, and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7669105/sneaky-signs-you-could-have-inflammation/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;combat symptoms&lt;/a&gt; like joint stiffness, mental fog and digestive issues.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; That's all it takes! Just four ingredients for a fruity and satisfying bite. Bertinelli's recipe is very similar to our own &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/chia-seed-pudding-8430793" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;chia pudding formula&lt;/a&gt; that we absolutely swear by. It's completely customizable and so easy to make ahead of time.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It's so nutritious that you could actually eat it for breakfast and be fueled to take on the rest of the morning. Recipes like our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/258640/chai-chia-pudding/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Chai Chia Pudding&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/8034698/berry-orange-chia-pudding/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Berry-Orange Chia Pudding&lt;/a&gt; are perfect for adding to your morning routine.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; P.S. to Valerie: Since you mentioned that you're looking for low-sugar yogurt recommendations in your video, check out these &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7904866/best-plant-based-yogurts/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;editor-loved plant-based yogurts&lt;/a&gt; that have no more than 4 grams of added sugar per serving.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxNd1I4UXBYUElVSUtwa2hYei1Cek1CUzBpWHRneHNOUE10cVdRQ2ducVFZWTRmY0pKXzNNdXM0MTBZeWdHNEZlZ3FpM0VFekxyaHRkTVFoUmlfa0s5bVNDUENLWXJ2ZlEwM0kxamJnbWppZk80ZVVHeGUyZWhUb295ZkhjVFNkRjJ6QzJXV2NuRjZuX01RZ0kwRQ</guid></item><item><title>备受争议的路易斯安那州外科医生被选为疾病预防控制中心的领导角色- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/controversial-louisiana-surgeon-general-tapped-cdc-leadership-role-rcna245824</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-73a9fa" class="body-graf"&gt;Louisiana Surgeon General Ralph Abraham — a vocal supporter of the "Make America Healthy Again" movement and a harsh critic of Covid shots — has been named principal deputy director at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-990ab1" class="body-graf"&gt;A spokesperson for the Department of Health and Human Services confirmed the appointment to NBC News, though it hadn’t been made public as of Tuesday afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-031b89" class="body-graf"&gt;The principal deputy director at the CDC is a high-level appointment. As second in command, Abraham would be in a position to act as a key adviser on a variety of public health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f8e988" class="body-graf"&gt;A three-term Louisiana congressman, Abraham practiced for 10 years as a veterinarian before going to medical school. According to his &lt;a href="https://ldh.la.gov/assets/docs/Secretary/OfficialDocs/Official-Bio_Ralph-Abraham.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;biography on the Louisiana Department of Health website&lt;/a&gt;, Abraham was a “practicing family medicine physician” when he was appointed as state surgeon general in 2024. He described himself as a “&lt;a href="https://pro.stateaffairs.com/la/health-care/ralph-abraham-maha-robert-kennedy-jeff-landry" target="_blank"&gt;country doctor&lt;/a&gt;” in an essay published in April.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-82eac5" class="body-graf"&gt;While Abraham is licensed to practice medicine in Louisiana, the &lt;a href="https://lailluminator.com/2025/02/18/abraham-board/" target="_blank"&gt;Louisiana Illustrator reported&lt;/a&gt; in February that he did not appear to be board-certified in the specialty of family medicine. A search for Abraham on the &lt;a href="https://portfolio.theabfm.org/diplomate/find.aspx?ts=638996677" target="_blank"&gt;American Board of Family Medicine’s website&lt;/a&gt; yielded no results. A separate search on the &lt;a href="https://online.lasbme.org/#/verifylicense" target="_blank"&gt;Louisiana State Board of Medical Examiner’s site&lt;/a&gt; lists Abraham as a general practitioner but not a family medicine doctor. (Board certification isn’t required to practice any particular specialty, but it’s viewed as an extra layer to ensure a doctor’s credentials, experience and expertise, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.abpsus.org/physician-board-certified-specialties/" target="_blank"&gt;American Board of Physician Specialties&lt;/a&gt;.)  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-597546" class="body-graf"&gt;Abraham’s new position makes him the most senior scientist at CDC. The current acting director, &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/separate-measles-mumps-rubella-vaccine-acting-cdc-director-rcna235971" target="_blank"&gt;Jim O’Neill, is not a medical doctor&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-2c2a62" class="body-graf"&gt;Dr. Richard Besser, who served as an acting director of the CDC in 2009 under the Obama administration, said he is “greatly concerned” that Abraham’s appointment will serve as an extension of Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy’s well-established distrust of vaccines. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-12c622" class="body-graf"&gt;“Dr. Abraham, rather than being someone who will push back on that, I think, will further the Secretary’s agenda,” said Besser, a pediatrician and president of the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, said. “I would expect that Dr. Abraham will have a lot of authority over what takes place within the agency.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b8e3d8" class="body-graf"&gt;Abraham has been vocal in his opposition of Covid vaccines. In September, &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/louisiana-surgeon-general-says-covid-160350442.html" target="_blank"&gt;he told the Shreveport Times&lt;/a&gt; that he “sees Covid vaccine injuries every day.” There was no explanation of the kind of injuries he was referring to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9e105c" class="body-graf"&gt;In February, The &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/louisiana-vaccination-surgeon-general-8e2eecde047648e6fb62c4b44edd6566" target="_blank"&gt;Associated Press reported&lt;/a&gt; that Abraham directed the Louisiana Department of Health, in an internal memo, to “no longer promote mass vaccination” through media campaigns like those for flu shots typically seen at the beginning of the winter respiratory virus season. The AP obtained the memo signed by Abraham. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a54cd1" class="body-graf"&gt;Abraham’s office did not immediately respond to a request for comment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-2b3f3c" class="body-graf"&gt;While flu activity is low so far this season, according to the&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-46.html" target="_blank"&gt; CDC’s latest flu report&lt;/a&gt;, Louisiana is reporting the highest levels of flu-like illnesses in the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c076ad" class="body-graf"&gt;In the past year, with Abraham at the helm, the state’s Department of Health waited several months after two babies died of whooping cough before&lt;a href="https://ldh.la.gov/assets/oph/Center-CP/HANs/2025/HAN-25_2-Statewide-Increase-in-Pertussis-Cases.pdf" target="_blank"&gt; formally alerting the public&lt;/a&gt; about a rise in cases across the state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1def2b" class="body-graf"&gt;&lt;a href="https://x.com/la_surgeon/status/1990813242055114835" target="_blank"&gt;On X&lt;/a&gt;, Abraham &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/trump-acetaminophen-fda-pregnancy-autism-cause-rcna232909" target="_blank"&gt;touted a drug called leucovorin&lt;/a&gt; as a promising treatment for some children with autism. There is limited evidence that it could help a small number of children, but large studies suggesting broad benefits are lacking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-365cee" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;As a Republican candidate for governor for Louisiana in 2019, Abraham released&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/louisiana-governor-s-race-ad-takes-aim-transgender-rights-n1045176" target="_blank"&gt; TV ads taking aim at abortion rights&lt;/a&gt; and the transgender community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;div class="expanded-byline-contributors articleBylineContainer"&gt;&lt;div class="expanded-byline article-expanded-byline" data-activity-map="expanded-byline-article-bottom"&gt;&lt;div class="expanded-byline__bio-wrapper expanded-byline__bio "&gt;&lt;p class="byline-bio expanded-byline__bio "&gt;Erika Edwards is a health and medical news writer and reporter for NBC News and "TODAY."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="expanded-contributors"&gt;Pilar Melendez contributed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:24:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxPZjZKdjIwYjR2Y2JabFdoREtLQV9wc0NXaUFoTHc0QjByX0lnSldnOFZ0WVVVUXM4S0wwNlY5UERQTFhjR0dydHRaWEhGaEEwZVk2clYxUjdOV09qcWwzNXN4dzQzWTZ1bGdabzI0TF9oX2hSV2I2M2dfQ0l4SmMycURLR1BvWnBPTjZJbVFvYUxjallpZ0s2RWlOSUNoWXdtUnhxUGZxWGROcW0yRXJSZzVyLWlZOEJ6YnBFN9IBVkFVX3lxTE9QQm9YbDlocGtCenZLR0czQ0R4QkFIQWJ5SUhraTBjLXBYaXRoQWNsc01zUWRmSHNfOURhSzhENXd5TVpqZHBlRWpDNi1uUGVuS2ptNkpR</guid></item><item><title>关于致命的大麻呕吐综合征- Axios的须知事项</title><link>https://www.axios.com/2025/11/25/cannabis-hyperemesis-syndrome-thc-symptoms-use</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:20:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxQbllaQkp5VWowQ2VjSmJPSDg0MUtsSlZ0MWt6czZva2paelFDTllIdDk4T1RUQjhvRGdjalRvNG12NldISUk2SUZMZ0h0Y0cybllKREpsM01fY1N4STByTjV3b0xVeGViZ1FqVWc4TjZscHpRSFlGcGdROVZwaXRwSGUxaDVodw</guid></item><item><title>想要更明亮的微笑，但喜欢咖啡和葡萄酒？尝试这些专家提示来避免染色。- CNET</title><link>https://www.cnet.com/health/personal-care/want-a-brighter-smile-but-lovecoffee-or-wine-try-these-expert-tips/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="c-ShortcodeContent c-ShortcodeContent-theme:default sm:u-col-2 md:u-col-6 lg:u-col-12"&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p1"&gt;Many of us enjoy a cup of coffee in the morning or a glass of wine to wind down at the end of the day, but these tasty beverages can stain your teeth if you're not careful. In a&lt;a target="_self" data-id="73eab0d7-6c5a-4c4a-8a3d-020a3b36026a" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/TooAfraidToAsk/comments/1jg8z7q/how_do_you_drink_coffee_without_staining_your/"&gt; recent Reddit thread&lt;/a&gt; one coffee enthusiast sought advice after noticing some staining on their front teeth. It's a common concern, so we consulted an expert to find out how you can enjoy your favorite drinks while keeping your pearly whites nice and bright.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p2"&gt;According to Dr. Anjali Rajpal, a board-certified dentist at &lt;a data-id="21ff9cfb-d62d-42d2-a2e2-f0acc1ba011e" href="https://bhdentalarts.com/" target="_self"&gt;Beverly Hills Dental Arts&lt;/a&gt;, there are different techniques you can use to prevent teeth staining while still getting to enjoy your favorite beverage. Plus, if your teeth have already been stained, Rajpal offers advice on how to brighten your pearly whites. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="e73c270c-bc57-4195-b0c6-3678087461b1" data-ng-block="{"&gt;Why do coffee and wine stain your teeth?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The short answer is a combination of chromogens (a substance that can be colorless but can be converted into a colored compound, often through a chemical reaction), tannins and acidity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-small c-shortcodeImage-pullRight"&gt;&lt;a rel href="https://www.cnet.com/health-tips/" target="_blank" class="c-shortcodeImage_imageContainer"&gt;   &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Coffee and red wine stain teeth because they contain dark pigments called chromogens that stick to enamel. Tannins in these drinks help the pigments bind more strongly to the teeth. Their acidity also weakens enamel, making it easier for stains to set in," Rajpal told CNET. She explains that darker roasts and concentrated coffees, such as espresso, tend to stain teeth more than lighter brews. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-all-top spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Likewise, red wine stains more than white, especially darker, tannin-rich varieties like cabernet sauvignon and malbec. "The longer these drinks stay in contact with your teeth, the more likely they are to cause staining," Rajpal said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="d0ab6dfb-7584-4bb3-b456-3635e0baa530" data-ng-block="{"&gt;Do certain types of coffee or wine stain your teeth more than others?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It turns out that, yes, some &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/home/kitchen-and-household/this-coffee-expert-tested-40-k-cups-here-are-the-5-id-put-in-my-keurig/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;types of coffee&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and wine can stain your teeth more. "Darker roasts and concentrated coffee like espresso tend to stain teeth more than lighter brews. Red wine stains more than white, especially darker, tannin-rich varieties like cabernet sauvignon and malbec," Rajpal explains. She also mentions that the longer these drinks stay in contact with your teeth, the more likely they are to cause staining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The type of coffee and wine isn't the only thing you should consider when trying to keep your teeth white. The temperature of a drink can influence how much it can stain your teeth. Hot beverages are more likely to cause stains than iced ones. "Heat can slightly expand enamel, making it more porous and allowing pigments to penetrate more easily," Rajpal said. "While iced drinks may have less impact due to quicker consumption and lower enamel exposure, the type and frequency of the drink matter more overall."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large c-shortcodeImage-hasCaption"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_caption g-inner-spacing-right-small g-text-xxsmall"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain types of coffee can stain your teeth more than others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;Boy_Anupong/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="9a262815-f7ba-4301-bedc-74aac512a505" data-ng-block="{"&gt;Expert dental tips to keep your teeth white without giving up your favorite drinks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protecting your teeth from stains doesn't mean you have to give up your morning cup of Joe. Follow these dentist-approved tips to keep your pearly whites healthy and bright:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="6264b957-5a97-40ff-8290-8d1e3075381f" data-ng-block="{"&gt;1. Sip your drink through a straw&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Straws help the liquid bypass your front teeth, minimizing the contact that leads to visible staining. Rajpal recommends using a straw for iced drinks and rinsing your mouth with water afterward" to reduce staining from coffee or wine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="1861bc20-29f8-46dc-baac-06c239c70392" data-ng-block="{"&gt;2. Drink your coffee or wine in one sitting&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the worst things you can do is sip your coffee or wine slowly for hours. "Sipping slowly throughout the day constantly exposes your enamel to staining compounds and gives your teeth less time to recover, making stains more likely to build up over time," Rajpal says. Try to enjoy your drink over a 15- to 30-minute period, then rinse with water after.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="2ebdcf23-1095-4ec0-b2f8-cc6bf37bb025" data-ng-block="{"&gt;3. Rinse, don't brush, right after&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know this one seems counterintuitive, but brushing your teeth right after you have coffee or wine can actually do more harm. "Avoid brushing immediately after drinking, as acids can soften enamel and make it more vulnerable," Rajpal recommends. "Wait at least 30 minutes before brushing to protect softened enamel, and give a break between snacking or eating to boost natural cleansing by saliva."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="8a374af1-4de1-4ce9-9443-d8642596648e" data-ng-block="{"&gt;4. Pair your drink with enamel-friendly foods&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain foods can help neutralize acid and reduce the length of time pigments stay on teeth. Rajpal recommends crunchy foods like apples, carrots and celery, which gently scrub teeth and boost saliva, which helps wash away pigments. Cheese and leafy greens create a protective layer on enamel, while strawberries contain natural acids that can mildly brighten teeth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large c-shortcodeImage-hasCaption"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_caption g-inner-spacing-right-small g-text-xxsmall"&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are foods you can eat to give your smile a boost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;kiboka/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="bb968052-2165-404b-8525-00333a97470b" data-ng-block="{"&gt;5. Maintain teeth-whitening habits&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's best to wait at least 30 minutes before brushing to protect softened enamel. Timing also matters -- give your teeth a break between snacking or eating to boost natural cleansing by saliva. Rajpal also recommends products like remineralizing &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/personal-care/best-whitening-toothpaste/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;toothpaste&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and minimal intervention paste (a topical tooth cream that protects teeth and can improve overall oral hygiene).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;Peopleimages/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="4712c71d-c1b5-47b9-a50f-396ad0d6a423" data-ng-block="{"&gt;How to whiten teeth stained by coffee or wine&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If your teeth are already showing signs of staining, there are things you can do to whiten your teeth at home or at the dentist's office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="0d2d399d-59a1-4ba6-97e6-4d5eed03764e" data-ng-block="{"&gt;Get a professional cleaning&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before trying whitening products, Rajpal recommends scheduling a professional cleaning to remove surface stains and plaque buildup. For deeper stains, you can consider whitening treatments like in-office whitening or custom take-home trays. Maintaining results requires good oral hygiene and limiting staining habits. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="37b607dd-2b9a-4d32-9ba8-e6049c4f2f0d" data-ng-block="{"&gt;Try gentle at-home whitening products&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the easiest and most affordable ways to whiten your teeth at home is to use &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/personal-care/best-teeth-whitening-kits/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;whitening toothpaste or kits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. "Whitening strips use peroxide-based gels to lift surface stains, but they may contain other ingredients and preservatives, which may increase sensitivity," Rajpal said, adding that "LED kits often enhance this process with light to accelerate results."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a target="_self" data-id="aa2c8d48-1b16-4d89-9cd0-d61904aa0098" href="https://www.cnet.com/health/personal-care/best-teeth-whitening-strips/"&gt;Best Teeth Whitening Strips in 2025&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-cy="shortcodeFaq" class="c-shortcodeFaq g-container-rounded-small"&gt; &lt;div&gt; &lt;div data-cy="shortcodeFaq_sections" class="c-shortcodeFaq_sections"&gt;&lt;div class="c-shortcodeFaqQuestion c-shortcodeFaq_question g-border-thin-light-top"&gt; &lt;div data-cy="shortcodeFaq_answer" class="c-shortcodeFaqQuestion_answer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;How long it will take to get rid of stains on your teeth will depend on the method of whitening that you choose. You may see results from in-office professional whitening in a single session, depending on the severity of the staining. Meanwhile results from at-home whitening strips may take several weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="c-shortcodeFaqQuestion c-shortcodeFaq_question g-border-thin-light-top"&gt; &lt;div data-cy="shortcodeFaq_answer" class="c-shortcodeFaqQuestion_answer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coffee and wine are just two of the most common teeth staining drinks. Other beverages such as tea, soda and fruit juices can also cause staining. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNET</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxObl9OSnRZYklnMXoyS2twSHdfQzZDajRpTTYwSUlLN21ob21lNWw2ekxWUTduc3VTNWlPTXlfQ3plakRrUmpQaV9md1lkTy1sV2pMS09OUEJNNG54NXl1S291UFdFYjhSanU5TEdSaTJHamFfanA3MUkwYTdnZzRhbUhYZXBpZEE0UzhsOGhZQ3VzendBVUR4eVRDZnRXQk4wR20wN2pXY1h0WXJJR1E</guid></item><item><title>你的大脑有一个内置的隔离模式-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://neurosciencenews.com/neuroscience-sickness-isolation-29979/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;New research uncovers the exact immune-to-brain pathway that drives the loss of social motivation during sickness. Scientists showed that when the cytokine IL-1β binds to receptors on neurons within the dorsal raphe nucleus, it activates a circuit that reduces social interaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This pathway acts independently of lethargy, revealing that social withdrawal is an actively generated behavioral response rather than a passive one. The findings highlight a precise neural mechanism by which the immune system reshapes behavior during illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Immune–Brain Link:&lt;/strong&gt; IL-1β directly activates neurons in the dorsal raphe nucleus to suppress social behavior.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Circuit:&lt;/strong&gt; Only the pathway from the DRN to the lateral septum reproduced full social withdrawal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not Just Fatigue:&lt;/strong&gt; Blocking this circuit prevented withdrawal but did not stop illness-related lethargy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Picower Institute at MIT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“I just can’t make it tonight. You have fun without me.” Across much of the animal kingdom, when infection strikes, social contact shuts down. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study details how the immune and central nervous systems implement this sickness behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It makes perfect sense that when we’re battling an infection, we lose our desire to be around others. That protects them from getting sick and lets us get much needed rest. What hasn’t been as clear is how this behavior change happens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the research published Nov. 25 in &lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt;, scientists at The Picower Institute for Learning and Memory of MIT and collaborators used multiple methods to demonstrate causally that when the immune system cytokine interleukin-1 beta (IL-1β) reaches the IL-1 receptor 1 (IL-1R1) on neurons in a brain region called the dorsal raphe nucleus, that activates connections with the intermediate lateral septum to shut down social behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our findings show that social isolation following immune challenge is self-imposed and driven by an active neural process, rather than a secondary consequence of physiological symptoms of sickness, such as lethargy,” said study co-senior author Gloria Choi, associate professor in The Picower Institute and MIT’s Department of Brain and Cognitive Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jun Huh, Harvard Medical School associate professor of immunology, is the paper’s co-senior author. The lead author is Liu Yang, a research scientist in Choi’s lab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A molecule and its receptor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choi and Huh’s long collaboration have identified other cytokines that affect social behavior by latching on to their receptors in the brain, so in this study their team hypothesized that the same kind of dynamic might cause social withdrawal during infection. But which cytokine? And what brain circuits might be affected?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get started, Yang and her colleagues injected 21 different cytokines into the brains of mice, one by one, to see if any triggered social withdrawal the same way that giving mice LPS (a standard way of simulating infection) did. Only IL-1β injection fully recapitulated the same social withdrawal behavior as LPS. That said, IL-1β also made the mice more sluggish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IL-1β affects cells when it hooks up with the IL-1R1, so the team next went looking across the brain for where the receptor is expressed. They identified several regions and examined individual neurons in each.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The dorsal raphe nucleus (DRN) stood out among regions, both because it is known to modulate social behavior and because it is situated next to the cerebral aqueduct, which would give it plenty of exposure to incoming cytokines in cerebrospinal fluid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The experiments identified populations of DRN neurons that express the IL-1R1, including many involved in making the crucial neuromodulatory chemical serotonin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From there, Yang and the team demonstrated that IL-1β activates those neurons, and that activating the neurons promotes social withdrawal. Moreover, they showed that inhibiting that neural activity prevented social withdrawal in mice treated with IL-1β, and they showed that shutting down the IL-1R1 in the DRN neurons also prevented social withdrawal behavior after IL-1β injection or LPS exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notably, these experiments did not change the lethargy that followed IL-1β or LPS, helping to demonstrate that social withdrawal and lethargy occur through different means.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our findings implicate IL-1β as a primary effector driving social withdrawal during systemic immune activation,” the researchers wrote in &lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tracing the circuit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the DRN identified as the site where neurons receiving IL-1β drove social withdrawal, the next question was what circuit they effected that behavior change through. The team traced where the neurons make their circuit projections and found several regions that have a known role in social behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using optogenetics, a technology that engineers cells to become controllable with flashes of light, the scientists were able to activate the DRN neurons’ connections with each downstream region. Only activating the DRN’s connections with the intermediate lateral septum caused the social withdrawal behaviors seen with IL-1β injection or LPS exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a final test, they replicated their results by exposing some mice to salmonella.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Collectively, these results reveal a role for IL-1R1-expressing DRN neurons in mediating social withdrawal in response to IL-1β during systemic immune challenge,” the researchers wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though the study revealed the cytokine, neurons and circuit responsible for social withdrawal in mice in detail and with demonstrations of causality, the results still inspire new questions. One is whether IL-1R1 neurons affect other sickness behaviors. Another is whether serotonin has a role in social withdrawal or other sickness behaviors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to Yang, Choi and Huh, the paper’s other authors are Matias Andina, Mario Witkowski, Hunter King, and Ian Wickersham.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding: &lt;/strong&gt;Funding for the research came from The National Institute of Mental Health, the National Research Foundation of Korea, the Denis A. and Eugene W. Chinery Fund for Neurodevelopmental Research, the Jeongho Kim Neurodevelopmental Research Fund, Perry Ha, the Simons Center for the Social Brain, the Simons Foundation Autism Research Initiative, The Picower Institute for Learning and Memory, and The Freedom Together Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Key Questions Answered:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq wp-block-yoast-faq-block"&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1764095211436"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: What triggers social withdrawal during infection?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: An immune molecule called IL-1β activates a specific brain receptor that shuts down social behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1764095212519"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Which brain circuit drives this withdrawal response?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: Neurons in the dorsal raphe nucleus activate pathways to the lateral septum to suppress social interaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1764095212302"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Is social withdrawal just due to lethargy when sick?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: No — the study shows it is an active, separate neural process, not a side-effect of feeling sluggish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Editorial Notes:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list has-background"&gt;&lt;li&gt;This article was edited by a Neuroscience News editor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Journal paper reviewed in full.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Additional context added by our staff.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this neuroscience and social isolation research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#462227302f222c29062b2f3268232233" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;David Orenstein&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://mit.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Picower Institute at MIT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;David Orenstein – Picower Institute at MIT&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2025.10.040" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;IL-1R-positive dorsal raphe neurons drive self-imposed social withdrawal in sickness&lt;/a&gt;” by Gloria Choi et al. &lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IL-1R-positive dorsal raphe neurons drive self-imposed social withdrawal in sickness&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sick animals exhibit behavioral changes that extend beyond physiological symptoms, such as appetite loss and hypoactivity, and include a decline in social interactions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While social isolation during sickness has been recognized to have the evolutionary benefit of staving off disease spread, the molecular and neural mechanisms underlying this response remain unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cytokines—immune-derived signaling molecules—have emerged as neuromodulators impacting brain function during inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Through behavioral screening, we identify a unique role for the cytokine interleukin-1β (IL-1β) in promoting social withdrawal during sickness. IL-1β directly modulates the activity of IL-1R1-expressing neurons in the dorsal raphe nucleus (DRN) (IL-1R1&lt;sup&gt;DRN&lt;/sup&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activation of these neurons is sufficient to elicit social withdrawal, while their inhibition or genetic deletion of IL-1R1 rescues self-imposed social isolation during systemic inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our findings reveal a neural mechanism that actively promotes social disengagement in sick animals, highlighting the role of IL-1R1&lt;sup&gt;DRN&lt;/sup&gt; neurons in driving these behavioral adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:45:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE50bW82UU5ndGQteWJlX2M5UUxlTUJNODk1dVA3LWQyWC0xY3RJV2dLcWRHZGlZYmh5clpLbjAtei03OTVwZzlaRE5hSWtIV3kySXNzU3puUWM3ZnNoZzEwbHJqbUJVMmRlNXVmeXhNUkJtcDNObVE</guid></item><item><title>全球首个肺癌预防疫苗试验，获得£ 206万资金用于癌症预防--印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/worlds-first-lung-cancer-prevention-vaccine-trial-funded-with-2-06-million-to-stop-cancer-before-it-starts/articleshow/125560666.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the first time, people at high risk of lung cancer can participate in a clinical trial of an experimental vaccine designed to prevent the disease. Led by University College London and the University of Oxford, this groundbreaking trial marks a major step in cancer prevention. Unlike conventional treatments, which target cancer after it develops, the vaccine aims to train the immune system to recognise early abnormal lung cells and eliminate them before they form tumours. By intervening at the earliest stages, researchers hope LungVax could significantly reduce the incidence of lung cancer and improve survival rates. This historic trial has the potential to transform approaches to one of the world’s deadliest cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding early lung cancer and the LungVax phase I trial&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lung cancer remains one of the most lethal forms of cancer, with survival rates stubbornly low despite decades of research. In the UK alone, around 48,500 people are diagnosed with lung cancer each year, and approximately 72% of these cases are linked to smoking, the largest preventable cause of cancer globally. Researchers have now pinpointed the biological mechanisms behind the early formation of lung cancer in smokers, identifying abnormal proteins called neoantigens and tumour-associated antigens that appear on the surface of lung cells at the earliest stages of cancer development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;By understanding these early cellular changes, scientists are now able to develop vaccines that teach the immune system to recognise and attack abnormal cells before they progress into malignant tumours. The LungVax clinical trial has been awarded up to £2.06 million in funding from Cancer Research UK, with additional support from the CRIS Cancer Foundation. This funding will support a four-year Phase I trial, designed to establish both the safety and the optimal dosing of the vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase I trials are primarily concerned with safety, side effects, and identifying the appropriate dosage. In this trial, researchers will carefully monitor how participants respond to LungVax, documenting any adverse effects and observing the immune system’s response to the vaccine. Subject to regulatory approvals, the trial is expected to begin in summer 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How LungVax works&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike conventional cancer therapies, which often target tumours after they have developed, LungVax is a preventative vaccine. Lung cancer cells differ from healthy cells in that they display unique ‘red flag’ proteins on their surface, produced by mutations in the cell’s DNA. These proteins are called neoantigens and tumour-associated antigens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The LungVax vaccine contains genetic instructions that teach the immune system to recognise these abnormal proteins. Once trained, the immune system can identify and destroy early-stage cancer cells before they form full tumours. The vaccine builds on mRNA technology first refined during the COVID-19 pandemic, enabling safe and effective delivery of these instructions to the body’s immune cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Professor Sarah Blagden, co-founder of LungVax from the University of Oxford, explains that this is a unique opportunity to actively prevent lung cancer. “Years of research into the biology of cancer, understanding the earliest cellular changes, will now be put to the test. Our hope is that LungVax will allow people to receive preventative protection against this lethal disease,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Target groups for the initial trial&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Phase I trial will initially focus on two groups of participants:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Individuals diagnosed with early-stage lung cancer who have had the tumour surgically removed but remain at risk of recurrence.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;People undergoing routine lung cancer screening under the NHS Lung Cancer Screening Programme in England, who may be at high risk of developing the disease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If the trial demonstrates safety and promising immune responses, the vaccine could progress to larger clinical trials, ultimately reaching a wider population at risk of lung cancer.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While smoking cessation remains the most effective strategy to reduce lung cancer risk, vaccines like LungVax offer a complementary approach. By targeting cancer at its earliest stage, these interventions could significantly improve survival rates and reduce the burden of lung cancer worldwide. With the launch of this historic trial, the medical community is taking its first step towards a future in which lung cancer prevention is not just a possibility but a reality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:29:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwJBVV95cUxNY25DUF91TFI2ajAwVHg4LU9CaU0xT090NjZ2MWFpRmdMb0FhdzZPVmtQZUdKMU1EbTFGUndQY25NTGh2ZG5QaWFkcmx5YTQ2TEoxWnE5ZU1URS1wekVjS2pQSk5PQS1EcERiWjNfRlhON2tHbkhHNnBxc2R4YjhtWU4zdS1EeVc0SGpLUXZ4dEo0eHh3ZlRLVC0tSXdEbEswd1VNNVVQU0taOGdoMnI4d0U5M0hWNWNBTGU5cDExaGprSWQ5eTQ4Qm1SQWxzalJralRTaGFicmVTTE1GdDVDdXhwSngzZHZBeWhHQkpQdnN1WjZ0czFLcDdfLTFCaEhwQk1SUktqV1NzVzRHUERWYk1qeF9xX25KWk40YmFva0Uzdzd3Y2pMSFp0dS1MZlXSAbQCQVVfeXFMT3JTOG94c3kxT1VDNmJrMXIxMzZFM1hBSTJ5eGdPMTVjaDZ3M1ZsZjVpWDdoQnQ1MzdQdTVKdWZVSWZGbTVkRFYySG14NGdXSkVrMnlJLVdQdTJMMG1rb0xROTBwS3hOSWlyWjZBU083ZnV6VlFITUJ3b18zek9QMUFaVlU3dGFxMnBULWU5S0tFdzU3Q0p0YnN5S01Gb212Z29DY3NFbl9WT0RRTTRLdmROT3BQd1JBa1d6SUtKRjA4UWU1dnZscDFQNWpTRkpacFlCRElBY3M1dGtyNmJFMG51ZUQ0TEQ4RkdTU2k3Q0FBdUJ0a0Q4RmhIeXlrck5hTjVjanBTd0YzajJQOE1pNGRuWHZlbEdncDhrNWpZYnhlTmdSVUliTkV4WWs4TjRDNzNKaW0</guid></item><item><title>大脑中的细菌碎片会影响您的睡眠吗？这就是《科学》。- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/could-pieces-of-bacteria-in-your-brain-affect-your-sleep-heres-the-science</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Sleep is one of the essential physiological needs for human survival, alongside food, water, and air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But sleep is socially driven, influenced by environmental and personal factors, and a recent study suggests it may be affected by fragments from bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Historically, scientists have thought it unlikely that &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/gut-microbes-23988"&gt;gut microbes&lt;/a&gt; affect physiological sleep regulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/neuroscience/articles/10.3389/fnins.2025.1608302/full"&gt;recent study&lt;/a&gt;, published in &lt;em&gt;Frontiers in Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;, indicated bacterial cell wall components (peptidoglycan) have been found in areas of the brain called the brainstem, olfactory bulb, and hypothalamus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/fragments-of-bacteria-in-our-gut-may-lull-our-brains-to-sleep-at-night"&gt;Fragments of Bacteria in Our Gut May Lull Our Brains to Sleep at Night&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peptidoglycan, also known as murein in scientific lore, is a strong, mesh-like layer outside the plasma membrane of most bacterial cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This helps contain the bacteria's shape and rigidity. Without peptidoglycan, bacteria would just be little water balloons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_182944" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-182944" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/bacterial_cell_sleeping_642.jpg" alt="bacterial cells" class="wp-image-182944 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/bacterial_cell_sleeping_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/bacterial_cell_sleeping_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-182944" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Bacterial walls are rigid, made of a material called peptidoglycan. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAG04vPHQko/"&gt;TrueCreatives/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent study suggested that the concentration of peptidoglycan seems to increase in periods of sleep deprivation or changes in sleeping patterns. This is a sign that the gut microbiota might play a role in sleep quality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This work was carried out on nine male mice which were housed in a 12-hour light/dark cycle. Measurements were taken over 48 hours to map brain activity cycles during sleep and rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Afterwards the mice were euthanised. Different areas of the brain were separated immediately so isolated areas could be measured independently for peptidoglycan levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been conducted and designed in a rigorous fashion. But the study exclusively used adult male mice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although animal models can be &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4283646/"&gt;translated to humans&lt;/a&gt;, the crossover in microbiota research is weak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Animal research into microbiota can only tell us so much about what is happening in our guts because the environment in which humans and mice live is vastly different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17183312/"&gt;breakthrough paper in 2006&lt;/a&gt; raised mice without any microorganisms in their bodies, known as germ-free mice, and then transplanted some of them with the gut microbiota from obese mice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study found the mice who had the gut microbiota transplant gained more body fat than germ-free mice colonised with microbiota from lean mice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This breakthrough research suggested that the gut microbiota might contribute to weight gain and a knock-on effect obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But follow-up studies using &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2774355#247496527"&gt;fecal microbiota transplantation&lt;/a&gt; from lean humans into obese adolescents did not lead to weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Findings in mice can suggest mechanisms but not necessarily predict outcomes in humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, the recent sleep research on mice has ignored the other 49% of the population, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10731147/"&gt;females&lt;/a&gt;. It's a gap that risks leaving half the world in the dark about sleep health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So when it comes to understanding the &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41392-022-00974-4"&gt;gut microbiota&lt;/a&gt;, does it really matter what organisms are found in the gastrointestinal tract of rodents and how this might interfere with their sleep patterns?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-of-over-400000-people-links-gut-bacteria-with-insomnia-risk"&gt;Study of Over 400,000 People Links Gut Bacteria With Insomnia Risk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our brain is traditionally considered sterile and protected by the blood-brain barrier. This tight system blocks microbes and molecules from entering the brain in healthy people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is no evidence to suggest that there is a brain microbiome, unlike within the digestive system and on our skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, previous studies have shown &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/1422-0067/22/8/4235"&gt;fragments&lt;/a&gt; that relate to bacteria, such as peptidoglycan and lipopolysaccharides, can be detected within the brain. This is probably because the fragments are smaller than bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blood-brain barrier and intestinal wall are more permeable in conditions like sleep deprivation, inflammation, ageing or even after strenuous exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_182950" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-182950" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/blood_brain_barrier_sleeping_642.jpg" alt="brain model" class="wp-image-182950 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/blood_brain_barrier_sleeping_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/blood_brain_barrier_sleeping_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-182950" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Blood vessels in the brain are surrounded by a barrier that prevents microbes from entering. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAG1rGeB284/"&gt;baehakqinugroho/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day-to-day variations in the cells that make up the wall of your intestines may be affected due to the direct effects of circadian regulation on the junctions between the cell membrane and its other compartments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These junctions form a seal that prevents the passage of molecules and ions between cells, essentially controlling what passes through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When these junctions relax, this allows the organisms found in the GI tract to enter the blood, which are then transported around the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's unclear whether that is good or bad, but leaky junctions have been associated with &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0889159111001279?via%3Dihub"&gt;inflammatory bowel disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some research suggests that our microbiota is closely linked through the &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10059722/"&gt;gut-brain axis&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although large amounts of research on the gut-brain axis have been conducted on rats and mice, there are very few translational links between what has been researched in animals and what actually happens in the human body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This means researchers would need to make a massive investment in researching how the gut microbiome interacts with our organs and other physiological systems with &lt;a href="https://www.ukri.org/news/uk-research-network-to-unlock-gut-immune-and-brain-health-links/"&gt;large-scale human interventions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since there is still much we do not understand about the gut microbiome, we are a long way off this kind of scientific insight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, this study does reflect growing scientific and &lt;a href="https://researchbriefings.files.parliament.uk/documents/POST-PN-0574/POST-PN-0574.pdf"&gt;public interest&lt;/a&gt; in the intersection between human microbiology and neuroscience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may be that we are only beginning to appreciate just how interconnected the human body and everything in it is.&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/266928/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/lewis-mattin-2435643"&gt;Lewis Mattin&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Lecturer, Life Sciences, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-westminster-916"&gt;University of Westminster&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/gut-microbes-may-have-links-with-sleep-deprivation-266928"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:04:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxNMHNQR1loNnRncVhCNWdWTUp0RWhMM2dfUUR4eUpYYWJHNlZvdU5RX3diNFl1ejc0MDBsN0FqTlNWclJmUE1HODhzU0VoSmZlcXhiSzE5OEFmSzJqV0ZKV3pjM3M3WXJKdlByUzNrakpoVTRsZ0ZER0huZTBlV1hxS2V6cVl0dEx2UlRkVXNJNnUzbkVPdnVzUzBiWlFtdTk1NmdZRjhn</guid></item><item><title>从血糖到肠道细菌，豆类如何改善您的健康-对话</title><link>https://theconversation.com/from-blood-sugar-to-gut-bacteria-how-beans-can-improve-your-health-269653</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="grid-ten large-grid-nine grid-last content-body content entry-content instapaper_body inline-promos" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Celebrity chefs &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/jamie-oliver-6971"&gt;Jamie Oliver&lt;/a&gt;, Hugh Fearnley‑Whittingstall and Tom Kerridge have backed a new campaign that is putting the spotlight on beans. The &lt;a href="https://foodfoundation.org.uk/sites/default/files/2025-09/Bean%20project%20overview_2025.pdf"&gt;Bang In Some Beans&lt;/a&gt; campaign is a bid to double the UK’s intake of beans, legumes and pulses by 2028.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such a campaign is long overdue. Despite beans on toast being a British favourite, beans, pulses and legumes remain under-consumed in the UK. According to data from &lt;a href="https://foodfoundation.org.uk/sites/default/files/2025-10/TFF_Beans%20Facts_DIGITAL.pdf"&gt;the Food Foundation&lt;/a&gt;, two-thirds of the UK population eat less than one portion of beans a week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beans are one of the most affordable and nutritious foods out there. With food costs continuing to rise and poor nutrition contributing to a growing number of diseases, beans may offer a solution to both problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Encouraging greater bean consumption could also help close the UK’s fibre gap, as most of the UK population &lt;a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/statistics/national-diet-and-nutrition-survey-2019-to-2023/national-diet-and-nutrition-survey-2019-to-2023-report"&gt;do not meet&lt;/a&gt; the recommended 30g of fibre per day. Beans are one of the simplest, most achievable ways to bridge that gap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you still aren’t convinced, here are just a few of the health benefits beans can provide: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;1. They can help you manage your weight&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beans are a great source of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/10408398.2011.596639"&gt;protein, fibre and micronutrients&lt;/a&gt; such as iron, magnesium and potassium. Increasing bean intake could improve your health and reduce &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/10408398.2011.596639"&gt;chronic disease risk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu13020519"&gt;Research also shows&lt;/a&gt; that people who consume higher amounts of beans have lower body weight, smaller waist circumference and lower blood pressure. These are all associated with reduced risk of multiple chronic diseases including obesity, diabetes and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/9781119776802.ch19"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only are beans low in calories, their high fibre and protein content can help increase satiety (the feeling of fullness), which is a key factor in appetite regulation and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12937-024-00937-1"&gt;long-term weight management&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;2. They’re good for your heart&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An abundance of research links eating beans to a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu13020519"&gt;healthy heart&lt;/a&gt;. Diets rich in beans can significantly lower LDL (“bad”) cholesterol, improve blood pressure and reduce inflammation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1039/C0FO00080A"&gt;fibre&lt;/a&gt; in beans binds cholesterol in the gut so it can be excreted from the body. Their potassium and magnesium content supports vascular function, which is essential for a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/advances/nmz003"&gt;healthy heart&lt;/a&gt;. This is why, for those managing cardiovascular diseases or hyperlipidaemia, beans should be a cornerstone of a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/ajh/hpt155"&gt;heart healthy diet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;3. They’re good for blood sugar levels&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beans have a low glycaemic index. This means they release energy slowly, which &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fnut.2022.1044427"&gt;reduces blood sugar spikes&lt;/a&gt;. Their fibre and protein content also helps slow carbohydrate absorption, which promotes better blood sugar control. Both factors are important for &lt;a href="http://doi.org/10.1001/2013.jamainternmed.70"&gt;preventing or managing type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/10408398.2020.1762162"&gt;Evidence from clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; shows incorporating beans into meals also benefits other aspects of blood sugar in people with, or at risk of, type 2 diabetes – such as improving fasting blood sugar and insulin levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/ejcn.2014.228"&gt;randomised controlled trial&lt;/a&gt; of over 100 people with type 2 diabetes found that those who consumed at least one cup of legumes daily for three months not only had better blood sugar control, they also had a significant decrease in body weight, waist circumference, cholesterol levels and blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;4. They can benefit gut health&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu13113701"&gt;Beans support gut health&lt;/a&gt; by providing both soluble and insoluble fibre. These act as prebiotics, feeding &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3920/BM2020.0028"&gt;beneficial gut bacteria&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fermentation of these fibres in the gut also produces short-chain fatty acids, prebiotics which have &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3945/ajcn.117.156265"&gt;anti-inflammatory effects&lt;/a&gt; and support the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu5041417"&gt;colon&lt;/a&gt;. Regular consumption contributes to improved digestion and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cofs.2017.01.005"&gt;bowel regularity&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="align-center "&gt;
            
            &lt;figcaption&gt;
              &lt;span class="caption"&gt;Beans have many gut health benefits.&lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;span class="attribution"&gt;&lt;a class="source" href="https://www.shutterstock.com/image-photo/young-female-shopper-chooses-beans-jar-2541740017"&gt;BearFotos/ Shutterstock&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;
          &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Boosting your bean consumption&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You don’t need to make any sorts of dramatic dietary changes in order to incorporate more beans in your diet. Here are a few simple ways to eat more beans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Start gradually.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin with small portions (about half a cup of cooked beans) a few times a week, increasing this as your digestive system adjusts and to avoid &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu15194121"&gt;flatulance and bloating&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Mix up varieties.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rotate between beans such as chickpeas, kidney beans, lentils, black beans and cannellini beans. Diversity &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/app142210215"&gt;boosts nutrient variety&lt;/a&gt; and keeps meals interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Add beans to familiar dishes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stir beans or other legumes into soups, stews, curries, salads or pasta sauces. Even a handful can make a meaningful difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Choose canned beans.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are just as nutritious as dried or fresh beans – just ensure you rinse them well to reduce the sodium content. If you do use dried beans, ensure you soak them overnight and cook them thoroughly to neutralise anti-nutrients such as &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu12102929"&gt;phytates&lt;/a&gt; (which can reduce absorption of other nutrients) and improve their digestibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nutritionally speaking, chickpeas and lentils are good choices, as they’re high in fibre and protein. Black beans &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.foodchem.2017.02.124"&gt;contain antioxidants&lt;/a&gt; – compounds which have been linked to lower risk of diseases such as cancer, diabetes and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/fsn3.3217"&gt;Alzheimer’s disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, the best beans are the ones you can integrate into your diet and will eat regularly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, there are some groups of people who should be mindful when increasing their bean intake, as some of the compounds they contain can have a negative impact on health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People with &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/irritable-bowel-syndrome-ibs-140564"&gt;IBS&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/ibd-18679"&gt;IBD&lt;/a&gt; or digestive sensitivities may struggle with bloating or gastric discomfort if they &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/ecco-jcc/jjae190.1144"&gt;consume large amounts of beans&lt;/a&gt;. Beans should be introduced into the diet gradually based on how well your body tolerates them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People with kidney disease may want to be careful due to the &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/kidney360/fulltext/2020/01000/potassium_homeostasis,_chronic_kidney_disease,_and.14.aspx"&gt;high potassium content in beans&lt;/a&gt;. In this case, it’s important to consult with a doctor before consuming diets rich in beans. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those who suffer from low iron or zinc levels may also want to be careful with how they prepare beans. The &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fpls.2022.992169"&gt;anti-nutrient compounds&lt;/a&gt; in beans can disrupt the absorption of minerals, which is why it’s so important to soak beans and cook them well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beans are a nutritional powerhouse. High in fibre, protein and key micronutrients, they support heart, metabolic and gut health while being both affordable and environmentally friendly.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

        

        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Conversation</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:27:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPSlhpQkVVQVNYX0VJVXYwcGkzd0JSbVEyOVY3cGpMdEpGYkthaTFwbEpUWjdwdzE5dV8wN25jSU45aXdDYjYzNTF0LXdzTWU1UVM3UFBmMlEtV21GelJoMnFvRU9FN1M2UHlaUXpUcGxLZHJnMWRhYjhkUEhOM0N6U3Njc2FhT2FfVlBoU0RYaHMyNzY5LW1UTFdZOGNldmUxT1hz</guid></item><item><title>常见的营养素缺乏症可能引发年轻人的早期脑损伤- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/a-common-nutrient-deficiency-may-be-triggering-early-brain-damage-in-young-adults/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:00:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxOOGt4elNaV3pqamMwLXNaSFh2Z0daenBBb3NKVHUzMUI1aUw2WW9mWE1BVGdhcTBHRGxOT2xDa0hYMzNVQ0JJYjNON2tvMGpoU3VtSHVjTzNZS2o4Z0NyZEFvYnU4YVhuQmZmd3JUUDdudEdlYUE2RW5FMGV5clhNZmxMMU5EdFV2elNQTlVkX2h4NV9sNG9oQWktWFAxQS0xLVhGSkhkQnNUT2c</guid></item><item><title>隐藏在显而易见的致命癌症—以及为什么大多数患者从未接受过筛查-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/deadly-cancer-hiding-plain-sight-165619166.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A new study from Northwestern Medicine suggests that current &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/cancer/lung-cancer" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:lung cancer screening guidelines;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;lung cancer screening guidelines&lt;/a&gt; may be missing most Americans who develop the disease — and researchers say it’s time for a major change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Published in JAMA Network Open, the study analyzed nearly 1,000 lung cancer patients who were treated at Northwestern Medicine between 2018 and 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The goal was to see how many of those patients would have qualified for screening under existing guidance from the U.S. Preventive Services Task Force (USPSTF).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/hidden-type-breast-cancer-could-exposed-new-breakthrough-tech" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Stealth Breast Cancer That Hides From Scans Targeted In Breakthrough Tech;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stealth Breast Cancer That Hides From Scans Targeted In Breakthrough Tech&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;USPSTF currently recommends annual CT scans for adults ages 50 to 80 who have a 20 pack-year smoking history (the equivalent of one pack of cigarettes per day for 20 years) and either &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/respiratory-health/stop-smoking" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:still smoke;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;still smoke&lt;/a&gt; or quit within the last 15 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Only about 35% of those diagnosed with lung cancer met the current criteria to undergo screenings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS/mvaj7wvj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read On The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Read On The Fox News App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Current lung cancer screening guidelines may be missing most people who develop the disease, a new study shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;That means roughly two-thirds of patients would not have been flagged for testing before their diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Not only does that approach miss many patients who had quit smoking in the past or did not quite meet the high-risk criteria, it also misses other patients at risk of &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/cancer" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:lung cancer;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;lung cancer&lt;/a&gt;, such as non-smokers," Luis Herrera, M.D., a thoracic surgeon at Orlando Health, told Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The study noted that these patients tended to have adenocarcinoma, the most common type of lung cancer among never-smokers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Missed patients tended to have adenocarcinoma, the most common type of lung cancer among never-smokers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Those missed by the guidelines were more often women, people of Asian descent and individuals who had &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/never-smoked-you-could-still-risk-developing-lung-cancer-doctors-warn" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:never smoked;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;never smoked&lt;/a&gt;, the study found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The research team also compared survival outcomes. Patients who didn’t meet the screening criteria had better survival, living a median of 9.5 years compared with 4.4 years for those who did qualify.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/erin-andrews-had-no-symptoms-before-cancer-diagnosis-pushes-early-screenings" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Erin Andrews Had 'No Symptoms' Before Cancer Diagnosis, Pushes For Early Screenings;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Erin Andrews Had 'No Symptoms' Before Cancer Diagnosis, Pushes For Early Screenings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While this difference partly reflects &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/medical-research/cancer-research" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:tumor biology;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;tumor biology&lt;/a&gt; and earlier detection, it also highlights how current screening rules fail to catch a broad range of cases that could be treated sooner, according to researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"The current participation in lung cancer screening for patients who do qualify based on smoking history is quite low," said Herrera, who was not involved in the study. This is likely due to the complexity of the risk-based criteria and stigma associated with smoking and lung cancer, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foxnews.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here For More Health Stories;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Click Here For More Health Stories&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;To test an alternative, the researchers modeled a different approach: screening everyone between the ages of 40 and 85, regardless of smoking history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Under that universal, age-based model, about 94% of the cancers in their cohort would have been detected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Universal screening procedures could save lives and hundreds of thousands of dollars, according to the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Such a change could prevent roughly 26,000 U.S. deaths each year, at a cost of about $101,000 per life saved, according to their estimates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The study emphasized that this would be far more cost-effective than current screening programs for breast or &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/colorectal-cancer-diagnoses-soar-among-younger-adults-one-key-reason" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:colorectal cancer;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;colorectal cancer&lt;/a&gt;, which cost between $890,000 and $920,000 per life saved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Sign Up For Our Health Newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Click Here To Sign Up For Our Health Newsletter&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Herrera noted the many challenges in the adoption of lung cancer screening, from lack of awareness to some providers not recommending the screening test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;However, he added, "The cost of screening is covered by most health insurance plans and many institutions also offer discounts for patients who don’t have insurance."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Lung cancer remains the deadliest cancer in the country, killing more people each year than colon, prostate and &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/cancer/breast-cancer" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:breast cancer;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;breast cancer&lt;/a&gt; combined. But because of the narrow eligibility criteria based on smoking history, millions at risk never get screened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Northwestern Medicine researchers argue that expanding screening to include all adults within an age range could help close those gaps, especially for groups often underdiagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers argue that expanding screening to include all adults could help catch the missing cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The study was conducted at a single academic center, which means the patient population may not represent the wider U.S. population. It also looked back at &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/medical-research" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:existing data;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;existing data&lt;/a&gt;, so it can’t prove how the new model would perform in real-world screening programs, the researchers acknowledged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS?pid=AppArticleLink&amp;amp;af_dp=foxnewsaf%3A%2F%2F&amp;amp;af_web_dp=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.foxnews.com%2Fapps-products" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Download The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here To Download The Fox News App&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The cost and mortality projections rely on assumptions that could shift depending on how screening is implemented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The researchers also didn’t fully account for the potential downsides of broader screening, such as false positives or unnecessary follow-ups, they noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/lifestyle/quizzes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Test Yourself With Our Latest Lifestyle Quiz;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Test Yourself With Our Latest Lifestyle Quiz&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;For patients who don’t qualify for lung cancer screening, there are other opportunities for &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/health-care" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:lung evaluations;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;lung evaluations&lt;/a&gt;, including "heart calcium scores, CT scans and other imaging modalities that can at least evaluate the lungs for any suspicious nodules," Herrera added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Original article source:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/deadly-cancer-hiding-plain-sight-why-most-patients-never-get-screened" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The deadly cancer hiding in plain sight — and why most patients never get screened;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;The deadly cancer hiding in plain sight — and why most patients never get screened&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:56:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNalBoYlZrRGU0bXk3TURaenJDVmZmV2hUQmUwVWF2LXBudm91TmdtR0lzckhDaWRhZ0E1bVptODlhd3dtUVpXWERjQzdySGd2dVB0NUxUdlJOeko0SHFvcFlWTy1PQThZa2tFb2VFLTJfcWVmcU5sMzhhN2kxcW1KVWFyVjBRU1ZyMWVF</guid></item><item><title>胆固醇不仅仅是“好”或“坏” --《经济学人》</title><link>https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2025/11/25/theres-more-to-cholesterol-than-simply-good-or-bad</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Economist</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:50:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxPVVd4QlFjMkZVZ3F3bVF4S0hLUkZqZVhRaFNUMDBxSXkxd1U4cEJnUFNZWTBJaTFLSHFsYUxpbTlrY2djWEZPYzczRFJwTjY2cHFVSUdvcEJDQVVhSFowcU1VdVVzZTM3OFJjSmRQX0xtNUllazhJNEpFNFljNDNpT1lJaGR2M09HZTVuZ3ZGSmExbUdBd2g5dnRJdkdRU3NyWTBDZWRidm54b2ozMXpn</guid></item><item><title>让感恩节美食成为“蓝色区域”的5种方法- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/11/25/health/blue-zone-thanksgiving-recipe-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmieonkt0000t3b6ns699y7s9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note_elevate inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    &lt;span class="editor-note__prefix vossi-editor-note_elevate__prefix"&gt;EDITOR’S NOTE:&lt;/span&gt;  The podcast Chasing Life With Dr. Sanjay Gupta explores the medical science behind some of life’s mysteries big and small. You can listen to episodes &lt;a href="https://swap.fm/l/clat112425" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieoctj900bt26p2fhwf8jjv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;(CNN) —&lt;/strong&gt; The food people consume has long been understood to shape them in some way.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieom9mm000h3b6n2lisklpk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Tell me what you eat, and I will tell you what you are,” French gourmand Jean Anthelme Brillat-Savarin famously wrote in 1826.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieom9mm000i3b6nvqmel5w5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            How you choose to nourish yourself plays a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/11/13/health/ultraprocessed-foods-colorectal-cancer-risk-wellness"&gt;large role in health&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/01/09/health/live-longer-diet-wellness"&gt;even longevity&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/04/28/health/ultraprocessed-food-death-wellness"&gt;modern-day studies&lt;/a&gt; have shown.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieom9mm000j3b6ni8tj06y1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            National Geographic fellow and best-selling author Dan Buettner knows this as well as anyone, and he has tips you can use — even for holiday feasts﻿. For two decades, he has been studying “blue zones,” places around the globe where people live the longest and healthiest lives. Diet is one of the major reasons why these folks have an edge.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieom9mm000k3b6ndfkbk13z@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/01/29/health/longevity-blue-zone-meals-wellness"&gt;People in blue zones&lt;/a&gt;, including Okinawa, Japan, and the island of Sardinia in Italy, eat plant-based diets that prioritize whole foods. “These simple peasant foods taste maniacally delicious,” Buettner told CNN Chief Medical Correspondent Dr. Sanjay Gupta recently on his podcast, Chasing Life. “That’s the word I like to use.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieom9mm000l3b6nxca2vat1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Buettner’s latest cookbook, “&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Blue-Zones-Kitchen-One-Meals/dp/1426224125/" target="_blank"&gt;The Blue Zones Kitchen One Pot Meals&lt;/a&gt;: 100 Recipes to Live to 100,” puts a spin on the healthy ingredients people use in these far-flung places so that they&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;appeal to the American palate.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieom9mm000m3b6nlvxol83p@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Buettner collaborated with &lt;a href="https://jeichstaedt.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Johannes Eichstaedt&lt;/a&gt;, who directs Stanford University’s Computational Psychology and Well-Being Lab, using artificial intelligence to analyze 675,000 recipes from popular websites including Food Network and Allrecipes.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;“We found that most of the most popular recipes in America followed one of seven different patterns,” Buettner explained. “And then we kind of reverse engineered deliciousness.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieom9mm000o3b6np4fm3ak3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Additionally, the recipes have other virtues to overcome common concerns.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieom9mm000p3b6npx22i4bs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “When you have the competition from fast food and processed food, one of the biggest objections you’re going to get is, ‘I don’t have time. No. 2, ‘I can’t afford it.’ No. 3, ‘I don’t know how to do it.’ No. 4, ‘I don’t think it’ll be delicious,’” he explained.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieom9mm000q3b6ng77uxg6f@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            To develop a cookbook of one-pot recipes, Buettner said, “I started with these criteria: that every recipe had to take less than 20 minutes to combine, it had to cost less than three bucks a serving, and it had to be maniacally delicious.”&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieocv3e00003b6nn7c7mqv2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            You can listen to the full episode &lt;a href="https://swap.fm/l/clat112425" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/html-embed/instances/cmieopqb0000v3b6ndrz2hetu@published" class="html-embed" data-editable="settings" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    


&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieoqati000y3b6n4bt9rvgh@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Thanksgiving apparently did not get the longevity-promoting memo, since many of the dishes Americans typically love to devour during the feast are a few sticks of butter in excess of being health-promoting.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieor2gy00133b6n5u4pbucv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But that doesn’t mean you have to toss the turkey out with the gravy. Small tweaks can help you align your holiday meal with blue-zone eating patterns. Here are Buettner’s five tips.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieor2gy00143b6npl29y98k@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The &lt;a href="https://www.bluezones.com/2022/11/the-true-first-thanksgiving/" target="_blank"&gt;original Thanksgiving&lt;/a&gt; staples — beans, corn and squash — are also three of the most longevity-boosting foods on the planet, Buettner said in an email.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieor2gy00153b6n7a1iputd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            He noted that versions of this nutrient-packed trio are not just part of traditional Native American diets, but also those of people living in the blue zones  of Costa Rica’s Nicoya region and the island of Icaria in Greece.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieor2gy00163b6n4s51f03h@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Build your menu around these, and you’re already eating like centenarians.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieot7px001e3b6ntfu7s341@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Add a longevity-boosting salad or vegetable-forward side dish (or two) to the feast, Buettner suggested.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieot7px001f3b6nba7z93x8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Blue-zone tables are full of leafy greens: mustard greens, collards, wild arugula, fennel fronds,” he said. “A simple, herb-heavy salad or roasted seasonal vegetables can lighten a traditionally heavy meal.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieot7px001g3b6nodx7ojil@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Here’s a side dish recipe from “One Pot Meals” to try:
    &lt;/p&gt;

  



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieot7px001i3b6n1scae81q@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Serves 4
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieot7px001j3b6ns533jnph@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Cook time: 35 minutes
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieot7px001k3b6nnxf3eufs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;For the glaze&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/list/instances/cmieot7x4001t3b6npmfuxtx0@published" class="list-elevate vossi-list" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
  &lt;ul data-editable="items" class="list__items list__items--ul"&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.0.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            1 tablespoon extra-virgin olive oil
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.1.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            1 tablespoon lemon juice
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.2.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            1 tablespoon honey
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieot7px001l3b6ncew4uqic@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;For the carrots&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/list/instances/cmieot7xy001v3b6n12rsz68w@published" class="list-elevate vossi-list" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
  &lt;ul data-editable="items" class="list__items list__items--ul"&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.0.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            12 ounces carrots, peeled (about 5 medium carrots)
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.1.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            1 tablespoon extra-virgin olive oil
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.2.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            ½ teaspoon salt
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.3.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            ¼ teaspoon cumin seed
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.4.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            ¼ teaspoon caraway seed
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.5.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            ¼ teaspoon coriander seed
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.6.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            ¼ teaspoon fennel seed
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.7.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            ¼ teaspoon smoked paprika (hot or sweet, according to taste)
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.8.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            ¼ cup carrot greens or fresh parsley, chopped, for garnish
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

  

  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/list/instances/cmieot7z6001x3b6nurl6qvji@published" class="list-elevate vossi-list" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
  &lt;ol data-editable="items" class="list__items list__items--ol"&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.0.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            Preheat your oven to 350 degrees Fahrenheit.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.1.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            In a ramekin or small bowl, whisk together the glaze ingredients until the honey is dissolved, then set aside.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.2.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            Cut the carrots lengthwise in half or quarters so that the widest ends are about ¼ inch thick.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.3.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            Toss the carrots in the oil to coat evenly, then add the salt and spices and toss again.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.4.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            Spread the carrots in a single layer on a13-x-9-inch sheet pan, with curved sides facing up.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.5.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            Roast the carrots for 30 minutes, then remove the pan from the oven. Drizzle the glaze over the carrots, and return to the oven for 5 more minutes.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.6.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            Garnish with the chopped greens before serving.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieot7px001m3b6nenyzleca@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In accompaniments calling for refined grains, swap in whole-grain alternatives.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieot7px001n3b6n6nb2zvu6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Instead of white rolls or refined stuffing, try whole-grain sourdough, barley or wild rice,” Buettner said. “These keep blood sugar stable and keep you fuller with fewer calories.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieot7px001o3b6nugbks8mu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Even if you go with your favorites, you can tweak them to be healthier, as Buettner does in his take on whipped potatoes.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieot7px001q3b6n1tp38n4x@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Serves 4 to 6
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieot7px001r3b6n34kcpoa2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Cook time: 20 minutes
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/list/instances/cmieot80r001z3b6nvdcxhvdc@published" class="list-elevate vossi-list" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
  &lt;ul data-editable="items" class="list__items list__items--ul"&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.0.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            1 pound Yukon Gold potatoes
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.1.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            ¼ cup extra-virgin olive oil
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.2.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            1 teaspoon salt
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.3.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            2 tablespoons fresh chives, minced
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

  

  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/list/instances/cmieot83500213b6n9rga1l8b@published" class="list-elevate vossi-list" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
  &lt;ol data-editable="items" class="list__items list__items--ol"&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.0.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            Trim any dark spots off the potatoes, then halve or quarter the potatoes so all the pieces are roughly the same size, about 2 inches across.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.1.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            Put the potatoes in a deep pot that’s large enough to hold them with plenty of room to spare.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.2.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            Cover the potatoes with water by about 2 inches.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.3.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            Bring the water to a boil and cook until a knife can pierce the potatoes with minimal resistance, about 20 minutes.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.4.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            Use a colander to drain the water, then return the potatoes to the pot.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.5.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            Add the oil, salt and chives and use an immersion blender to whip it all into a smooth, velvety puree.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.6.text" class="list__item vossi-list__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text"&gt;
            Taste for seasoning and serve.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

  



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieovqwc002c3b6nvecr7dzr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Instead of piling up your plate with every dessert on offer, try to reframe the way you think about the course.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieovqwc002d3b6ni9s801m1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “You don’t need to ban dessert, just change the equation,” Buettner said. “In Sardinia, people enjoy a single simple sweet after meals, not an avalanche of pies.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieovqwc002e3b6nio0wjrm3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Another option: Try naturally sweet foods like baked apples, roasted squash or dates, he suggested.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  &lt;h2 class="subheader inline-placeholder subheader-elevate vossi-subheader vossi-subheader--size-h2" data-editable="text" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/subheader/instances/cmieovqwc002f3b6nzcgn88bz@published" data-component-name="subheader" id="strengthen-ties-with-family-and-friends" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
        Strengthen ties with family and friends
&lt;/h2&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieovqwc002g3b6ngmgd0mq6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Make the holiday social, active and purposeful. “A blue-zone Thanksgiving doesn’t end at the table,” Buettner said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieovqwc002h3b6n1of245hu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Nor does it start there. “Play a game, ask everyone to share a gratitude story or include elders in the cooking,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieovqwc002i3b6nl7tf2s8p@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            And, post-meal, head outside for a stroll, not to the couch — at least not right away!
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmieovqwc002j3b6nqukqy1ij@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Longevity isn’t just about what’s on the plate,” he said. “It’s the whole web of connection around it.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmieoyc4n002r3b6nzowsfket@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note_elevate inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    &lt;span class="editor-note__prefix vossi-editor-note_elevate__prefix"&gt;EDITOR’S NOTE:&lt;/span&gt;  We hope these five tips help you make your Thanksgiving offerings more blue-zone aligned. Listen to the full episode &lt;a href="https://swap.fm/l/clat112425" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. And join us next week for a new episode of the Chasing Life podcast.
&lt;/p&gt;

  

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:47:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxNdDdSN2VhOENXMGJpSmF1Y1BkM3p3UG5ZUkRlczBoS2ItTlRUVUMwbWV6S1hLekhNVDJVZ2RpYk1oVDFrN1VVOU9UMF93R3ZUdVdLby15QVQzcWo4aTdtZGF3N0k2MUFsZGZxLTBTSVR5dzh0R21ub2JmNjZEb200R0lR</guid></item></channel></rss>