<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>6200万美国人养成了与出生缺陷和自闭症有关的坏习惯--《每日邮报》</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15085097/cannabis-thc-pregnancy-birth-defects-autism.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Smoking cannabis could have a catastrophic effect on &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/fertility/index.html" id="mol-2bd8cc60-8e58-11f0-ac7c-e970e0b4e8cc" class=""&gt;fertility&lt;/a&gt; and fetal development, a new study suggests. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the US, cannabis use has nearly doubled in the past decade with 21.8 percent of individuals aged 12 years and older - 61.8 million people - reporting marijuana use in 2023, up from 12.6 percent in 2013. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers from the University of Toronto in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/canada/index.html" id="mol-bffff970-8e5a-11f0-ac7c-e970e0b4e8cc"&gt;Canada&lt;/a&gt; say this dramatic rise, partly driven by decriminalization and legalization of recreational cannabis, has raised concerns about the drug's impact on fertility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To understand this better, they conducted two studies. The first, a lab study, exposed oocytes, or immature human egg cells, to THC - the psychoactive ingredient that makes one 'high' after consuming marijuana - and measured their chromosomal development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the second study, the team used data from 1,059 egg cell fluid samples taken from patients undergoing &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/ivf/index.html" id="mol-561fd420-8e5b-11f0-ac7c-e970e0b4e8cc" class=""&gt;in vitro fertilization&lt;/a&gt; (IVF), a fertility treatment that involves taking eggs and sperm and creating embryos in a lab setting for implantation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sixty-two samples of the fluid samples tested positive for THC, resulting in a six percent positivity rate. They then compared these to the 'clean' samples to assess how the eggs' cells developed differently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In both studies, the researchers found that THC &lt;span&gt;was associated with lower rates of embryos that contained the correct number of chromosomes, which can lead to birth defects and miscarriages. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the analysis of IVF patients, 60 percent of embryos in the THC-positive group had the proper number of chromosomes, compared to 67 percent in the THC-negative group. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Smoking cannabis could have a catastrophic effect on fertility and fetal development, a new study suggests (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In the lab study, THC exposure led to a nine percent increase in rates of embryos containing an improper number of chromosomes, and more than doubled the rate of abnormalities in spindles, structures that assist in chromosomal development. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, the researchers caveated their results, noting that people undergoing IVF are taking large amounts of hormones, so their findings may not be generalizable to the larger public.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Samples used in the study came from females under the age of 40 and it is unclear as to when they consumed THC products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Most chromosomally abnormal embryos will either fail to implant in the uterus or will result in miscarriage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In more rare instances, the abnormal embryos may result in chromosomal disorders, such as Down syndrome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Additionally, exposing immature egg cells to THC disrupted their ability to sort chromosomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;An abnormality in the way an egg cell's chromosomes line up during cell division is linked with miscarriage and birth defects such as Edwards syndrome, which causes deadly growth delays, and Patau syndrome, which causes physical and developmental abnormalities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Autism Research Institute notes that previous research has also found that prenatal exposure to cannabis may increase likelihood of autism, with animal studies suggesting THC can lead to genetic mutations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Similarly, chromosomal abnormalities and defects are tied to autism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These effects were seen in the recent study with people who had THC in their systems from marijuana products while they were pregnant or undergoing IVF.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Off the back of their investigation, the authors of the recent study conclude: 'These findings underscore the need for increased awareness and caution among people with ovaries, particularly those undergoing fertility treatments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Our study highlights the importance of informing patients about the potential risks associated with cannabis consumption and provides a basis for regulatory bodies, medical professional societies, and public health organizations to establish recommendations and guidelines regarding cannabis consumption during fertility treatment.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The findings &lt;a target="_blank" class="" rel="nofollow" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-025-63011-2#Sec2"&gt;were published&lt;/a&gt; in the medical journal, Nature Communications.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;In the analysis of IVF patients, just 60 percent of embryos in the THC-positive group had the proper number of chromosomes, compared to 67 percent in the THC-negative group. These 'abnormal' results are pictured above&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Previous research has also looked at how marijuana can harm fertility. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2023 study led by the University of &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/california/index.html" id="mol-2bdd3930-8e58-11f0-ac7c-e970e0b4e8cc"&gt;California&lt;/a&gt;, Irvine (UCI), found adolescent female mice exposed to tetrahydrocannabinol (THC), the psychoactive chemical in the drug, had 50 percent fewer healthy ovarian follicles than the control group by the time they were adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers believe the body's endocannabinoid system - which is stimulated when marijuana is used - damages follicles or causes them to activate too quickly, depleting them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With marijuana use now commonplace among teens across America, researchers fear many young women are unknowingly damaging their likelihood of having a child in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the study was on mice, separate research has shown that pregnant women who use cannabis are at a greater risk of birth defects, miscarriages and stillbirths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other research has found that marijuana may damage semen quality and affect male fertility too&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a 2018 study out of Tulane and the University of Washington, researchers looked at samples from men in Washington, where the drug has been legal for recreational use since 2012, and compared it with their cannabis consumption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They found that men who had consumed cannabis in their lifetime were more likely to have abnormally-shaped sperm and lower concentrations of sperm compared to men who had never used the drug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:01:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxNb0hRYy1uNTNRVHVSMnBVX3pMY3ZMWHFiYmNTT2VyVGVFY3hJSGZUZ3RrTU5sRG5venF6aFlhNlRaZzFUYTZYSm5ObXhuZm9ZTnVFQnA4bWhRMkI2czdVR1BlR2psOURjZXBHaVFSSTlJVkRUQVV2THM3aDFBZHJnc000MktETkI2YnVYVDRvNmZuTE5YUGhMRzNONHhjX3ZtV3fSAacBQVVfeXFMTzI1QU9CZ01tR3d2OTQyeThKdTAzX2NlQi01QTJCUFNZcHdLV3E4MjdleWVWOVk2cnlvUEo3dEUwamNkWVRUbTk3V2dvQzFmNWZOc0JSVXhfOXVGb3F4RkNGZEV4S0NvTlZoMXduZGtqM2FPQmRXcVYxc0hYTDA5dnZpTlJqWDRrUDZJQWZST3A1SDVTQ3JvNXBEQWp0Wk8xdUM5MUZqZ2M</guid></item><item><title>杀死查理的天使明星Farrah Fawcett的“禁忌”癌症的新警报飙升-医生发现谁有风险-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15088799/women-cervical-anal-cancer-farrah-fawcett.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Thousands of women could be offered screening for a little-discussed &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-9616f680-8f23-11f0-b861-4f2c49e4320e"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;, after a major study revealed survivors of another cancer face elevated risks years later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The research focused on anal cancer, which remains rare but is rising fastest in older women – and found that those who have previously had cervical cancer are at significantly higher risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Current guidelines recommend screening for certain high-risk groups, including people with &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/hiv_aids/index.html" id="mol-96191960-8f23-11f0-b861-4f2c49e4320e"&gt;HIV&lt;/a&gt; and women with a history of vulvar cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But doctors say a crucial group is being overlooked, as cases of the disease continue to climb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rates are rising most sharply among women over 65, with cases in this age group increasing by around 4 per cent a year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One of the most famous cases was American actress Farrah Fawcett – a 1970s TV icon best known for Charlie's Angels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She revealed her anal cancer diagnosis in 2006, which at the time sparked tabloid speculation about her sex life because of the stigma surrounding the disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Fawcett died in 2009, aged 62, after the cancer spread. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;One of the most famous cases was American actress Farrah Fawcett – a 1970s TV icon best known for Charlie’s Angels (pictured with her long-term partner, actor Ryan O’Neal)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Fawcett revealed her cancer diagnosis in 2006, which at the time sparked tabloid speculation about her sex life. Fawcett died in 2009, aged 62, after the cancer spread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If the trend continues, oncologists at the US National Cancer Institute warn numbers could double in less than 20 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now researchers led by Dr Haluk Damgacioglu, an expert in disease modelling at the Medical University of South Carolina, say women who have survived cervical cancer should also be considered high risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In their study, more than 85,500 women diagnosed with cervical cancer between 1975 and 2021 were tracked for an average of nine years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Those already diagnosed with anal cancer, or who developed it within two months of their cervical cancer diagnosis, were excluded from the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Among the remaining women, 64 went on to develop anal cancer – with risk climbing sharply 10 to 15 years after treatment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nearly 60 per cent of cases in women aged 65 to 74 occurred more than 15 years after their cervical cancer diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The threshold currently used to justify screening programmes is 17 cases per 100,000 people. In this age group, the study found rates of 17.6 per 100,000 – high enough to qualify.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Writing in the journal JAMA Network Open, Dr Damgacioglu said: 'These findings support the need for age-based and duration-based anal cancer screening recommendations for women with a cervical cancer history.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;HPV is thought to be behind at least 90 per cent of anal cancers and 99 per cent of cervical cancers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He added: 'In summary, this study provides critical data to inform anal cancer screening recommendations among a high-risk population of women with a history of cervical cancer.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team is now calling for further research to weigh up the risks and benefits of screening, and to determine the best age to introduce it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cervical cancer itself remains a major killer, with around two women dying from it every day in the UK. It is often dubbed a 'silent killer' because symptoms can be mistaken for less serious problems such as period pain and fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If caught early, the chance of surviving at least five years after an anal cancer diagnosis is around 95 per cent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But this plummets to just 15 per cent if the disease is detected late, once it has spread to other parts of the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the UK, women aged 25 to 49 are invited for cervical screening – more commonly known as a smear test – at their GP surgery every three years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Yet uptake remains low, with only about 70 per cent of eligible women, or 4.6million, attending their scheduled test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Around 1,600 people are diagnosed with anal cancer in the UK every year, the majority of them women. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Desperate Housewives star Marcia Cross was famously diagnosed with anal cancer in 2017, which she attributes to a strain of HPV that may have also caused her husband's throat cancer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Among the most high-profile cases in the US was Desperate Housewives actress Marcia Cross, who revealed her diagnosis in 2017.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Common symptoms include bleeding from the anus, pain in or around the area, small lumps felt around the anus, changes in bowel habits, and passing mucus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These issues can also be caused by more common conditions such as haemorrhoids or anal fissures – but persistent or unusual symptoms should always be checked by a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Both cervical and anal cancers are linked to infection with high-risk strains of human papillomavirus (HPV), which is transmitted through sexual contact. More than 90 per cent of cases are thought to be caused by HPV. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are more than 100 types of HPV, and only around 30 can affect the genital area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many people never show symptoms, and the majority of cases go away without treatment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, in some cases it can cause tissue to grow abnormally, resulting over many years in cancer.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The warning comes as health chiefs are urging under-25s who left school without receiving a life-saving cancer vaccine to come forward for the jab.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:40:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxOLW5oTmFfY09GaGI5UEtzWnRLbG4zeFRSbGJqcDNjSUFFcVlPakR3MUFiVGFfWV9zSU9wZDNEZllHeUpvcE1QUE5lWjBrSDJTWnphT21yS2JIUWVNTUQ0OFZickJmOHR0NHVtenBNeUJBdGRpaFNfZ3RnRlN5d3lCdjZ5QWRqQXhTam5iMGdaTWpYazQwS1pvOFhfaDk1SEXSAaQBQVVfeXFMUFYtaWtxMFhENXFNTnMtUzh4NVZhN1hjc09zVEFreGVzODFNVUhHdzYwYml6WVdKcHlaZjJoSVI1MDRONXJPVFZsaElTRnFnSFU4WUdKZi1JcTJJbjJOTTc2YWc0dndTNzdseWM5djRXSHRsSjFhTUtPRW5Sam0xYnh5VzZPaW5PMU5jOTVSaTd6NlJLVFF6UkZ2ZUJPOVhvUm1aR0g</guid></item><item><title>意见|不接种疫苗代价高昂--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2025/09/11/vaccines-skipping-cost/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6VMV3H2DPBGP3OUUU7RU2SI7C4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Donald G. McNeil Jr., a former global health reporter for the New York Times, is the author of “The Wisdom of Plagues: Lessons From 25 Years of Covering Pandemics.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ESKLBY6OXJGZZDU4JNE4ODBHNU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Robert F. Kennedy Jr.’s efforts to undermine vaccines in America are not just scientifically absurd. They’re also financially ruinous. The costs of medical care in the United States have been skyrocketing for years, forcing health insurers to raise their premiums faster than overall inflation and pushing the Medicare’s trust fund ever &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/medicare/faqs-on-medicare-financing-and-trust-fund-solvency/"&gt;deeper into trouble&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:01:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTFA2cWFadFJ5QkJfejNCLWhvR3otUWk2cTFZSFNrd2VpaDI3b1d2bDJpZlg4a3ZXd0Q2TURENVNreWt4MFdRbFFlckhSRTJuX3Q0cU5nWTFxdmttRUNZNEJLOUhvMFdxclpfWUZjVVZkTXNPWXJZWXdsMmdZbzJEWDg</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心警告说： “接吻虫”疾病在美国蔓延：我们所知道的- AL.com</title><link>https://www.al.com/news/2025/09/kissing-bug-disease-spreading-across-us-cdc-warns-what-we-know.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ABFPEQ5WY5AMDHJT6IWEEUDN5A"&gt;An emerging, potentially deadly disease is spreading through the United States, particularly in the South. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TNVQ3V74XRBJRDRHGFV44WHTCI"&gt;Chagas disease is caused by parasites in triatomine insects, also known as “kissing bugs” because they &lt;a href="https://www.uclahealth.org/news/article/chagas-disease-which-can-be-deadly-now-considered-endemic-us" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;tend to bite people in the face&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6HOJLLA7PRBWXNVO2LBZOJ36MY"&gt;When kissing bugs bite, they pass the parasite in its feces. When the feces get into the bite wound, a cut, or the eye or mouth, it leads to infection, according to the Alabama Department of Public Health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FKUUE7PIGZAUZKURBGOPI36NAY"&gt;An increase in cases in both humans and animals has led the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention to &lt;a href="https://wwwnc.cdc.gov/eid/article/31/9/24-1700_article" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;declare the disease endemic to the U.S. for the first time&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5Z5AA3DNONGK7FYC7K4OTOK3BU"&gt;Eight states - Texas, California, Arizona, Tennessee, Louisiana, Missouri, Mississippi and Arkansas - have &lt;a href="https://wwwnc.cdc.gov/eid/article/31/9/24-1700_article" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;reported cases in humans&lt;/a&gt;, according to the CDC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5EE67UFFXRBFDPFD5ZJSL3N44Q"&gt;Alabama has reported cases only in animals, according to the CDC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4Q3MSQNSCVB6LCDM73HTN62G6Q"&gt;Kissing bugs occur naturally in the southern half of the country and have been identified in 32 states, including Alabama&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="675G3J5BMZDIDNECSCMPTT6KHM"&gt;“We do have kissing bugs in Alabama, but we also have a lot of other bugs that look like kissing bugs. Although kissing bugs can be found in Alabama, there have been no cases of Chagas Disease reported to ADPH in 2025,” state health officials said in an emailed statement to &lt;a href="https://www.al.com/" rel="" target="_blank"&gt;AL.com&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="32NLQNFFVNCM7MRBRJ4ZU7Q6AI"&gt;Chagas is not a disease that’s required to be reported in Alabama and is not nationally notifiable either. But the Alabama public health agency said that if a physician suspects a patient has the disease, state officials can assist in coordinating tests and identifying the bug. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="A7AGYIJJWJBR3CAQXYY7OLPXD4"&gt;ADPH warned that Chagas can be a very serious disease, especially if not treated early, adding that chronic infection can lead to serious medical issues. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3V5JDLANXFBIPIJ3VNVUHRGWKI"&gt;Along with a bite, Chagas can also be spread through blood transfusions and organ transplants, according to the health department. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WVRIQ2K57BHD3CAPKYQS6BSXYM"&gt;There are no vaccines for the disease, but antiparasitic treatments are available, and early diagnosis and treatment can prevent chronic issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Q73SNFUCDVGFVH5CZYW3NGLQUE"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/chagas/about/index.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;According to the CDC&lt;/a&gt;, about 8 million people globally and 280,000 in the United States have the disease, often without knowing it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AL.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:20:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxQVnZfNUxJNXhNeGRUSjZwRUtsamFWRWNKRWFkdU9YQmJ0czFQbnMyS2JrLXplV196eHF3VXJtenRaM2M3UW9PVWFDWHZFZWQybGlUX1hqMzhrV0lUU2xpc1lTM1BYYTQyQ1JVT3FLaWRMTkppM0lHUXJ2NlRlMEhoSTNUcl83OTlBcW9ObW10NUpLcjEzRWlvZ1JIWTZ6WENN0gG0AUFVX3lxTE5vUUVlVEduSERIalBoSVhBTnRZeHl2RF9UOEVhaEwyQmdkalR5N2JXZzBLMHBKZ3VRbXR4TGFyVUtFNTFvV0NBbGtFVDhiLUphN0NFdGZOS1FVU1pROWl5dl9yeTQtZnAyak4zbG54ZHNHUWllZXRmQnI5dW1MV0k1RDJvT1hLbUxtbU9pejRRcWRMVk1fRTZSaTRDMm5TSTZleWVFN2ZkTENVQ2tySDNGQkU1Vg</guid></item><item><title>2025年拉斯克奖授予细胞生物学和囊性纤维化先驱者-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/11/health/lasker-awards-medicine.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:23:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE1ONURHZTE1TEt2clVrbU03eHJNNkJVVzhlM0lsbDNrT3dReDdXejNyVXFCazNWTjZ3dXN0LVc2ZWFCWTVfdF96a1RvZGxYVi1CZ25hZGZiSUlFV2R4NURtdHk3eTlER0ZkQ01hanUzQ2hPRE9ueXpPcA</guid></item><item><title>您是否能够在西澳大利亚州接种新型冠状病毒疫苗？ -《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/have-you-been-able-to-get-your-updated-covid-vaccine-in-wa/</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirAFBVV95cUxNZmZ6MFlPVlVtSFgtNHdoS21CakxTTjhlMzdVUjU2T3RtTC11UF9RZEw2NU9YZDA4UVYzZ1ExQVo1OU1tVkpGR0c4VUVkbURxa2JwSnNmQ25rS0x0R3dmd2tqVlJ0bi1aMmp3MGNrbXh0ZzItSjlKWTFqTmRuODNPbk9PYWtTNlRycklvRWZTeVJKUTFlUW9nY0IxZkVWd1pGOUo1eUZTN1NIQkRG?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Have you been able to get your updated COVID vaccine in WA?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimAFBVV95cUxQSC0xc0pxVE1mOFZhNDV3cG9qRGlWcFBPMElhelRfMFJsWGdQU1FPMzRUaVNwYXR2VnJ6MVJUWTljRER5NHZGa19ORG0wOFc2aVRvUy1kX3VCQ3dCOXhkbzhlNTNJeEZWWjVWaXJpQTRKOWFXdHZsMDRSemFaalZFdVY0cl8yUjZ2bFdza2U3NnJrVXkzUWVRTg?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Can you get the Covid shot for free? In Washington state, probably&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;KUOW&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxNdmFjLUNEcXNBNUwwRjM3MVZXQkpLMnFIMzFOVk9WalN6SUt6X2U4Uk83TmJuT3F6YUJlRHhLM3JLM1VBNVl0M3ZOcnJLQWhsTE50U2ZBdVVNaTdiRG1UUGlyMVlOekVRME1zN29Kd2l3dHZIN1dZRTBaUW02UFNXRVRFLXVOb2t1aFhxRXFNZU1FUmVPbERCU2F6TlAtOXdo?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;COVID vaccine available to all in WA 6 months and older&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Columbian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipgFBVV95cUxPRWlhczdVUXhuVW84Uk45MnFZUzdNMExfM1A2WEVSRDlKUHdMQ1ZyYXNZRVFxZVQtcW9mbkZNZkJvRGV5Ymd5dTVqMDIxZVVGcTMwNFlzOXl3WWhhcjdHMWtnQ3JiY0w2RHBfTEhncjduRkNNQ2s0VXhPM3BkaWlraWJnVUlCZC1iOGV5UmZoRG94UzZFbWdYYVRMRXZiVE5CcHhGUVpn?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;KPHD board discusses vaccination efforts amid federal uncertainty&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Kitsap Daily News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijwFBVV95cUxNTktjbEhndEgyWnZZZlBYZHVGUjRuQjRTNVVQd1hpVUdIVUZodzZYVWY1RHcteWh5cG40SmQ2R0pGWC1BTFE2c1M2WWZld2ctT2thdlBVR3psMXNPUHlweW03dXpOU2RveW5qdEJzTnJReEZ3Szg4ejRYR29XcWxNODY2UUdUS3lBWktIT2VjYw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;State order removes COVID vaccine restrictions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Vashon-Maury Island Beachcomber&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxNZmZ6MFlPVlVtSFgtNHdoS21CakxTTjhlMzdVUjU2T3RtTC11UF9RZEw2NU9YZDA4UVYzZ1ExQVo1OU1tVkpGR0c4VUVkbURxa2JwSnNmQ25rS0x0R3dmd2tqVlJ0bi1aMmp3MGNrbXh0ZzItSjlKWTFqTmRuODNPbk9PYWtTNlRycklvRWZTeVJKUTFlUW9nY0IxZkVWd1pGOUo1eUZTN1NIQkRG</guid></item><item><title>研究：晚点吃早餐可能对您的健康有害- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/study-eating-breakfast-later-could-113000045.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;Is Eating Breakfast Late Unhealthy?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;ClarkandCompany - Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Hearst Magazines and Yahoo may earn commission or revenue on some items through these links."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’ve all heard the saying that &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/food-nutrition/g35362654/what-to-eat-for-breakfast/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:breakfast;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;breakfast&lt;/a&gt; is the most important meal of the day. Now, new research suggests that the specific timing of eating breakfast and other meals might be pretty important as well, especially as you get older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fs43856-025-01035-x&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.prevention.com%2Ffood-nutrition%2Fa66043546%2Feating-breakfast-late-dangerous-for-health-study%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:decades-long study;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;decades-long study&lt;/a&gt; from researchers at Massachusetts General Hospital and the University of Manchester followed nearly 3,000 adults ages 42 to 94 for an average of 22 years. The team tracked participants’ meal times, lifestyle factors, genetic data, and health outcomes to see how eating schedules shifted with age, as well as what those shifts meant for long-term health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What they found is that as participants got older, they tended to eat their meals later in the day. The time frame in which all meals were consumed each day also narrowed. But perhaps the most important outcome of the study was discovering that eating breakfast later was linked to a higher risk of death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants in the early-eating group had a 10-year-survival rate of nearly 90%, compared to roughly 87% for those among the late eaters. Moreover, each additional hour of delay in breakfast was associated with an 8-11% higher risk of mortality, depending on the statistical model, even after accounting for factors like age, sex, and lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why mealtimes may shift&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers noted that the reasons for participants eating breakfast later were sometimes tied to health challenges. Older adults with fatigue, depression, anxiety, and multiple chronic illnesses were more likely to eat later. Difficulties preparing food and poor sleep quality also factored into delays, as did genetic predisposition to stay up late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the study was observational, this might matter quite a lot. It’s entirely possible that the increased mortality rate in late eaters is connected to the underlying health or genetic issues they faced, and which also caused them to delay their meals. In other words, although there’s a correlation between meal delays and a higher risk of mortality, this study doesn’t prove that the delay itself is the culprit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s also worth noting that the study centered mostly around white British adults and relied on self-reported meal times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Should you eat breakfast early?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, all of this does suggest that keeping mealtimes consistent—especially starting the day with breakfast on the earlier side—could be a marker of better overall health in older adults. Shifts in meal time might not only reflect underlying health problems but could also influence circadian rhythms, which help regulate things like sleep and metabolism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though more research is needed, keeping a consistent breakfast routine could be one simple step toward supporting healthier aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:45:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQVDNKRzlucnVmNjBva19pR1BjS3ExRTB6dmotM3BqNVNyMWg0YzI5N3JtdG5qQzRVemxwOUw4Z0gzX01aeHRNT0lNMzc3b1ljaXRxWlJMRDRfdkE5MHhyaGdGeDcya1VuQzZGS0haV3MwendoUllQRXpLcEk3aF8tcTU1OEM</guid></item><item><title>一项新的研究显示，单次运动可能会减缓癌细胞的生长-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/09/11/exercise-cancer-benefits-prevention-recurrence/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QYKJEJKTLNBRTEPDKY2CIZKWSE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Exercising muscles pumps out substances that can suppress&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;the growth of breast cancer cells, according to an important new study of exercise and cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="IJRARYDOWVETDGV4IB7IIXU2KA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40608178/" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;, published last month, involved 32 women who’d survived breast cancer. After a single session of interval training or weightlifting, their blood contained higher levels of certain molecules, and those factors helped put the brakes on laboratory-grown breast cancer cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:40:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxQUW9qdU5ydHhrQzdFa09MclpmclFMMk1aSHdRam05Z0dFN0RQZGR6YlRHSHk2bEpCZTUxM0hmZTBjSUhOSzRycnVRVUw4WjdoZHhrOGtuVEZka1NNanVvaDEtclFucWM1Nk92ZTdyb3RXejljQVlQSkxnLThCbzB1MjZUN0JFQmxySVJiazZzSGlpS1NzZkFlM3NBanVEREk</guid></item><item><title>根据医生的说法，应避免的补充剂和清洁剂- TODAY.com</title><link>https://www.today.com/health/diet-fitness/never-have-i-ever-liver-supplement-cleanse-rcna228859</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8d58af" class="body-graf"&gt;&lt;em&gt;TODAY’s Never Have I Ever series offers guidance about procedures and practices our trusted health experts would never participate in. Discover why they should be avoided and which healthy practices you should turn to instead.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c94685" class="body-graf"&gt;The liver is a remarkable organ. Among its many functions, it rids our blood of toxins, disposes of old cells, metabolizes nutrients and creates the fluid necessary for digestion. And it rarely needs assistance with any of its hundreds of jobs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-57db7c" class="body-graf"&gt;Still, a host of cleanses and supplements are available online and in stores, with claims they can detoxify the liver, thereby improving its function. But there’s no clinical evidence to support that they work, Dr. Raymond Chung, chief of gastroenterology, hepatology and endoscopy at Mass General Brigham, tells TODAY.com. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3a2597" class="body-graf"&gt;In fact, some have been linked to liver damage and failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-449556" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never Have I Ever: Done a Liver Cleanse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-537b2d" class="body-graf"&gt;“It’s only natural to think that being good to our bodies is to find things like supplements that ostensibly reduce the stress to our livers,” Chung tells TODAY.com. But your liver likely doesn’t need any additional help, which is why he’s never done a liver cleanse or taken a liver supplement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-de45b3" class="body-graf"&gt;Plus, he has safety concerns around the many products that are available. That's in part because the U.S. Food and Drug Administration doesn't vet the safety of dietary supplements before they hit shelves (though it can take action against supplement makers after if a dangerous one reaches the market).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b62db8" class="body-graf"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/diet-fitness/bad-supplements-list-rcna209561" target="_blank"&gt;Certain types of supplements can be especially risky&lt;/a&gt; to liver health, such as black cohosh, kava and vitamin A, TODAY.com previously reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-ac8263" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-056ce5" class="body-graf"&gt;While the liver can incur damage from disease, viruses and lifestyle choices, a detox likely won’t be the fix — and in some cases, they may even make things worse. “Several herbal and dietary supplements have been linked to liver injury, damage or even liver failure,” Chung points out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-aa4bd9" class="body-graf"&gt;“The liver is the ultimate filter and the ultimate detoxifier,” he adds, but taking supplements can actually “overwhelm that detoxification mechanism.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-8a7bec" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to Do Instead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d1cb86" class="body-graf"&gt;If you’ve already taken liver cleanses and supplements, don’t fret. “(The liver) is a sturdy, hardy organ,” with regenerative capacities, says Chung. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-25aec0" class="body-graf"&gt;To keep it functioning at its best, avoid liver supplements and focus on a few lifestyle practices, he advises. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-44d9cf" class="body-graf"&gt;“The good news about the liver is that it is such an extraordinarily forgiving organ,” says Chung. “So even if liver damage somehow occurred during the period of exposure to a supplement, in most cases, with removal of the injurious agent, we will see regression of that injury.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b32468" class="body-graf"&gt;Moving forward, focus on a healthy diet. Chung recommends the &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/diet-fitness/mediterranean-diet-rcna63362"&gt;Mediterranean diet,&lt;/a&gt; which promotes healthy fats, lean protein, antioxidants, whole grains and produce. This diet has been shown to lower the risk of death, lower levels of heart disease and boost digestive health. Chung is a fan because it lessens the accumulation of fat in the liver — a benefit since &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/diet-fitness/fatty-liver-diet-rcna140012"&gt;non-alcoholic fatty liver disease&lt;/a&gt; is the leading cause of liver cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-49cb36" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;He also advises fitting as much movement as you can into your day, and drinking alcohol in moderation, especially if you have liver disease, since it can inflame the liver and destroy its cells. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TODAY.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxQcTYwRzJRS3pWRHRkVXZ1cUF1UER6eXJoZHQtMW1UNHhHUHEyQjk2ZUtpeWZ0cWRVOGJWUmNkeWRBcWNGUGdLdXkyc1E1N24yVFFKVlYtMG01Q1JtWUxsVndqLXBfQzJxUVlJZEpXRmxhRHNRX0ktZW9wT1N2OWdjU1hORjBLazZ5eWxUWGRYc2JMUlpQS1M3M21td9IBVEFVX3lxTE9DVXFyU2RFUS0xeHBlZWxRQmdrdXYwTF9LM1Q3VWFUWjdiNVhFQ284MWNZWE5saWpib1V6S2k1LU80aTBtaWh5N0hXcmoxT0VEallhYg</guid></item><item><title>希腊酸奶有多健康？ -《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/how-healthy-is-greek-yogurt/</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiekFVX3lxTE45UXQ4ZUNVZFNLS1F5SWVjQmxYMGkyNkRhSEFPQzJwbkhyYms1THFENGpST1hxaTRqYkN0VVZ0bjlQRHJrVEtoUzhiVjA0dXlpTFV0Nl8taUNBMnNXMXloUjZpUU11TGNtWmF6ZDNBaVRzN0hnZ1RlVzRB?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;How healthy is Greek yogurt?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:22:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE45UXQ4ZUNVZFNLS1F5SWVjQmxYMGkyNkRhSEFPQzJwbkhyYms1THFENGpST1hxaTRqYkN0VVZ0bjlQRHJrVEtoUzhiVjA0dXlpTFV0Nl8taUNBMnNXMXloUjZpUU11TGNtWmF6ZDNBaVRzN0hnZ1RlVzRB</guid></item><item><title>爱情、毒品和安全套：艾滋病毒感染者身份不同的夫妇面临新的现实-美国国家公共广播电台</title><link>https://www.npr.org/sections/goats-and-soda/2025/09/11/g-s1-77007/hiv-condoms-hiv-positive-u-s-aid-cuts</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-82264" class="bucketwrap image x-large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Robert Ochweda and Millicent Akoth is HIV positive — she caught the virus from her former husband. She is now married to Robert Ochweda, a fisherman who is HIV negative. After the two of them fell in love, he says he was afraid to marry her lest he contract the virus. "I have been able to stay safe by using condoms and PrEP," Ochweda explains, referring to a pill that prevents infection. In the wake of U.S. foreign aid cuts, they say it's become harder to find the pills and condoms that keep them safe.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Julia Gunther for NPR
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Julia Gunther for NPR
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Let's say you fall in love with someone harboring a deadly -- and highly infectious -- virus. And you think … is it crazy to get married?&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Sometimes love conquers all — with the help of modern medicine.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That's the story of serodiscordant couples — the term used when one partner is HIV positive and the other is HIV negative.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Robert Ochweda and Millicent Akoth of Kenya are one such couple. She is HIV positive — she caught the virus from her former husband. He is a fisherman who is HIV negative. After the two of them fell in love, he says he was afraid to marry her lest he contract the virus.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;He was able to overcome his fears.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"I have been able to stay safe by using condoms and PrEP," Ochweda explains, referring to a pill that prevents infection. And The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention writes: "Most condoms are highly effective in preventing HIV."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;His wife takes antiretroviral pills that reduce her viral load, so she does not face the risk of death from AIDS. Those pills also reduce the risk that she will infect her husband.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;This year, couples in this category are especially anxious. They say that, in the wake of the Trump administration's dramatic foreign aid cuts and dismantling of USAID, the agency that supported health-related programs, it's become harder to find the pills and condoms that keep them safe.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;div id="resg-s1-82272" class="bucketwrap image x-large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Caleb Ochieng, who is HIV negative, has been married to DIana Odhiambo, who is HIV positive, for eight years. They have two children. On a recent visit to pick up his PrEP drugs that reduce his risk of infection, he says, "I was told the supply that was available has been reserved for pregnant women."
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Julia Gunther for NPR
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Julia Gunther for NPR
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Caleb Ochieng, who is HIV negative, has been married to Diana Odhiambo, who is HIV positive, for eight years. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Ochieng learned of Odhiambo's HIV status when they went to do an HIV test as they made plans to tie the knot after several years of cohabiting. She believes she contracted the disease from a previous relationship.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We were shocked because at that time we had two children and wanted others. We were advised on preventive measures like condom use and voluntary male circumcision as a way of preventing HIV infection," he says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"I wondered how we would manage," he recalls. "It's not been easy but with love, we have been taking care of ourselves." &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Odhiambo takes pills to suppress the virus; he takes pre-exposure prophylaxis (PrEP) to stay safe. He is tested for HIV every three months. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Taking these precautions, the couple has had two children who are HIV negative. After counseling, Odhiambo has become a peer educator who talks to other couples in the same situation.  The partner who is positive, he reflects, "has a lot of emotions. AS a partner, you should be there for them and support them well."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;On a recent visit to the clinic where he picks up his PrEP drugs, he says, "I was told the supply that was available has been reserved for pregnant women. I traveled to neighboring Busia county and managed to get a small dose that could last a month and a half."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;His experience echoes a memo from the State Department that NPR obtained, stating that if a clinic receives funding through the U.S. program PEPFAR, this preventative medication can "only" be given to "pregnant and breastfeeding women" during the 90-day freeze on foreign aid that the Trump administration instituted — and that is still in effect.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A senior health official with the Kenyan Ministry of Health told NPR that clinics have been rationing medications and other supplies because of the uncertainties about donor funds.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We acquire most of the HIV medication through partners and donors. The exit of U.S. funding means that there is a gap, and until that gap is filled, there is always bound to be friction but the government has done everything to keep operations going," says the official, who asked not to be identified by name because he did not have permission to speak to the press.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Joywine Adek, a programs officer at &lt;a href="https://www.mildmay.org/kenya" target="_blank"&gt;Mildmay Kenya&lt;/a&gt;, an organization that supports HIV patients, is seeing this gap.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Mildmay Kenya is among the organizations that was receiving funding from the U.S. government to support HIV interventions in Kenya, including screening services, distribution of antiretroviral drugs and condoms, and counseling for serodiscordant couples.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"In the current grant that is available after the reduction in funding, there is no support for discordant couples," Adek says, adding that the charity has had to halt many of its services because of the loss of U.S. aid.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We are trying to sort this out by doing what we call integration of HIV care into routine health care," says Fredrick Oluoch, the director of public health in Kenya's Kisumu County.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The lack of condoms is evident. This reporter saw empty dispensers where co Kndoms were once stocked and made available in clinics.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;div id="resg-s1-82267" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Empty condom dispensers at a charity called Mildmay Kenya, which supports people who are HIV positive. According to the United Nations Population Fund, the U.S. cuts in foreign aid have had an impact on the supply of free condoms for those in need.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Julia Gunther for NPR
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Julia Gunther for NPR
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;And even though condoms are inexpensive — as little as $1 or $2 each in the U.S., even less in Kenya — that price could still be daunting in a country where a third of the population lives below the poverty line of about $2 a day in income.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Kenya has previously reported that the supply of condoms was not equal to the demand. But this year, officials say, things are worse than ever in the wake of the U.S. foreign aid shakeup, which has affected some of the suppliers, like the United Nations Population Fund (UNFPA).&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In a statement to NPR, UNFPA noted: "Kenya has historically relied heavily on USAID for its free condom distribution programs. Kenya's annual condom requirement is estimated at 400–450 million units. Condom procurement by UNFPA has been affected indirectly — but nonetheless significantly - by U.S. funding cuts. While UNFPA continues its role in condom programming through funding from other global partners, the U.S. stop work order has contributed to shortfalls in supply, putting more pressure on UNFPA and other providers. Some 9.8 million UNFPA-procured condoms were received at the Kenya Central Stores on August 13, 2025, but funding restrictions from the U.S. and other donors mean there is uncertainty as to whether UNFPA will be able to meet projected condom procurement needs for 2026 and beyond."&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;NPR asked the State Department to respond to these points about U.S. funding and free condom programs but did not receive a response.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The result of this altered aid landscape is that partners with different HIV status are living with newfound uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;div id="resg-s1-82273" class="bucketwrap image x-large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                "The shortage of the drugs and condoms is a major concern for us, and the government is yet to address our concerns," says Erastus Ng'uono, who is HIV positive and married to Winnie Auma Miyare, who is HIV negative. The couple is standing in front of their home with two of their children, a boy named Rain and a baby girl named Rose. Says Ng'uono: "I don't know what the future holds."
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Julia Gunther for NPR
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Julia Gunther for NPR
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Erastus Ng'uono was born with HIV positive status. When he met Winnie Auma Miyare and wanted to start a relationship with her, he asked her if she could love someone who is HIV positive and using ARVs. A few days later, he told her about his HIV status. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;At first she did not want to have anything to do with him. But when he explained how medications could help her ward off infection, she changed her mind. She takes PrEP pills. They have four children who are all HIV negative. Their youngest is six months old. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The news of U.S. aid cuts that could affect the strategies they use has hit them hard. "I encouraged him to have courage and not to worry," she says. "I know the government will intervene." &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"I was very afraid," he says. "I even prayed over it and I know God will see us through."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Still he worries. "The shortage of the drugs and condoms is a major concern for us and the government is yet to address our concerns," says Ng'uono. "I don't know what the future holds."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Viola Kosome is a Kenyan journalist. See more of photojournalist Julia Gunther's work on &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/juliagunther.com/__;!!Iwwt!U8T0yz2hwgnmX_1m42aPsJ22zA2gPchXvncsvL95H7Bz6veQvg35xeVEGgzaX6K1_v9bFlEPLbL4VLU$" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;her website&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; or follow her on Instagram: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/www.instagram.com/juliagunther_photography/__;!!Iwwt!U8T0yz2hwgnmX_1m42aPsJ22zA2gPchXvncsvL95H7Bz6veQvg35xeVEGgzaX6K1_v9bFlEPZJnKJmA$" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;@juliagunther_photography&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:56:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxNZ3BVeURqYnlYTHplbGVnY1F6d2tpSUFNaUliYm13MFl5WjZ4VWNjX0UwSV9IYkMtbFE1eDhaRXA0aGtwR3ZVeHEzRHJXSnUtcG5ITmxFQWFEeGpuODZBOW5lNTd3bXVWdU41MnhOYnZqX0lUR05TNFFLZHA0NVhvQWJsY2VmcURzRG1TOElyRXhBN0paVFVXdDUyYk1XazlsemFUTFNn</guid></item><item><title>“混乱是重点” ：在RFK Jr下部署新冠疫苗助推器的动荡-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/sep/11/covid-vaccine-boosters-rfk</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The first deployment of updated Covid shots under the &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/trump-administration" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Trump administration&lt;/a&gt; has been plagued by access issues and misinformation amid confusion and chaos at US health agencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;People attempting to get the &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/vaccines" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;vaccines&lt;/a&gt; say they have struggled to understand eligibility requirements, book appointments, process insurance claims, battle misinformation from pharmacists and obtain prescriptions from their doctors in some states. Such hurdles will disproportionately affect people of color and low-income people, experts say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SignInGateSelector" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"contentType":"Article","sectionId":"world","tags":[{"id":"world/coronavirus-outbreak","type":"Keyword","title":"Coronavirus"},{"id":"society/vaccines","type":"Keyword","title":"Vaccines and immunisation"},{"id":"us-news/robert-f-kennedy-jr","type":"Keyword","title":"Robert F Kennedy Jr"},{"id":"science/infectiousdiseases","type":"Keyword","title":"Infectious diseases"},{"id":"us-news/healthcare","type":"Keyword","title":"US healthcare"},{"id":"society/health","type":"Keyword","title":"Health"},{"id":"science/science","type":"Keyword","title":"Science"},{"id":"us-news/us-news","type":"Keyword","title":"US news"},{"id":"world/world","type":"Keyword","title":"World news"},{"id":"campaign/email/the-stakes-us-election-edition","type":"Campaign","title":"This Week in Trumpland"},{"id":"type/article","type":"Type","title":"Article"},{"id":"tone/news","type":"Tone","title":"News"},{"id":"tone/features","type":"Tone","title":"Features"},{"id":"profile/melody-schreiber","type":"Contributor","title":"Melody Schreiber"},{"id":"tracking/commissioningdesk/us-news","type":"Tracking","title":"US News"}],"isPaidContent":false,"isPreview":false,"host":"https://www.theguardian.com","pageId":"world/2025/sep/11/covid-vaccine-boosters-rfk","idUrl":"https://profile.theguardian.com","contributionsServiceUrl":"https://contributions.guardianapis.com","editionId":"US"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;These problems come amid turmoil at US health agencies, with top leaders of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) quitting because of reported pressure from the Trump administration to approve unscientific vaccine policies and new limitations placed on the Covid vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="a7ab4d7a-20d2-4cf8-b2fa-b858d7baf041" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":3,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"As Covid surges in the US, Americans can’t get vaccinated: ‘terrified I might kill somebody’","elementId":"a7ab4d7a-20d2-4cf8-b2fa-b858d7baf041","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/sep/08/covid-surge-vaccine-restrictions"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":10,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Anybody can get the booster,” Robert F Kennedy Jr, secretary of the US Department of Health and Human Services (HHS), said at a hearing before a US Senate committee last week – before adding: “It’s not recommended for healthy people.” In an August &lt;a href="https://x.com/SecKennedy/status/1960742897201872969" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; on X, Kennedy said the updated Covid vaccine was approved only for people “at higher risk”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Matt Shipman, a health writer in North Carolina, was eager to receive an updated shot to protect himself against the acute and &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/ofid/advance-article/doi/10.1093/ofid/ofaf533/8244677" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;long-term&lt;/a&gt; risks of a Covid infection, especially as the late-summer &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/cfa-modeling-and-forecasting/rt-estimates/index.html#:~:text=As%20of%20July%2022%2C%202025,not%20changing%20in%2019%20states." data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Covid wave&lt;/a&gt; appears to be reaching its peak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It used to be easy to schedule an appointment at a pharmacy, but now he received a message saying the vaccines will hopefully be available in a few weeks. He had heard some people were getting prescriptions for the shots, but when he called his doctor’s office, they wouldn’t even make an appointment for a prescription.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;North Carolina is one of several states where pharmacists are requiring prescriptions before administering any shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In some states, pharmacists are prevented by law from administering vaccines that are not recommended by the CDC’s advisory committee on immunization practices (ACIP). While doctors have liability protections for Covid vaccines under the Public Readiness and Emergency Preparedness (Prep) Act, pharmacists may not if the vaccines are not approved by the advisory committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some insurers might also opt not to cover the shots until they are recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The independent advisers are expected to take up Covid recommendations at the next meeting in mid-September, but that meeting has been embroiled in controversy. Senator Bill Cassidy, a Republican from Louisiana, called for an &lt;a href="https://www.help.senate.gov/rep/newsroom/press/cassidy-calls-for-vaccine-committee-meeting-to-be-postponed-following-cdc-departures" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;indefinite postponement&lt;/a&gt; given the recent upheaval at health agencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Shipman said: “It’s incredibly frustrating, because this has significant consequences for public health, and there is no reason in the world for this to be happening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It is an entirely manufactured problem that is going to cost people their health and wellbeing and possibly their lives. It is manifestly clear that people who would like the Covid vaccine are not able to access it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Changing the rules to make vaccination easier will depend on the state, said Lindsay Wiley, a professor of law and faculty director of the health law and policy program at UCLA Law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“In several states, governors and health officials are solving the prescription problem pretty swiftly, so it’s a rapidly evolving situation right now. In other states, the legislature may need to take action to fix the problem,” Wiley said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Even states that have tried to combat the confusion still have vaccine challenges. The state of Maryland released &lt;a href="https://governor.maryland.gov/news/press/pages/Maryland-Protects-Access-to-Vaccines-for-All-Marylanders.aspx" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;guidance&lt;/a&gt; last week for all residents to access vaccines – without specifying the need to disclose qualifying conditions. Maryland’s governor, Wes Moore, called the federal changes to vaccine policy “harmful for Marylanders and all Americans”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Yet when Ian Morgan tried to obtain the vaccine in Maryland, the pharmacist said it could only be administered to those over the age of 65 or people with at least one underlying health condition. Morgan tried to make an appointment online, but was told CVS couldn’t schedule his appointment because he did not qualify.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Morgan, a postdoctoral fellow at the National Institutes of &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/health" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; and a union steward of NIH Fellows United-UAW 2750, said the tumult has been caused by Kennedy’s messaging on vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“I think the chaos is the point, and that chaos has consequences,” Morgan said. “Creating this confusion, creating this chaos, trying to discredit scientific experts – and we see that every time [Kennedy] goes out there – that in and of itself is causing problems, and that in itself is harming the American people.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="f1f7cf35-b4f9-47ab-aad7-e55e9cb97247" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Workers log a shipment of Covid vaccines in Horsham, Pennsylvania.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Matt Rourke/AP&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Morgan is one of 1,000 current and former HHS employees who signed a &lt;a href="https://www.savehhs.org/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;letter&lt;/a&gt; calling for Kennedy’s resignation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Vaccine availability for children, especially for those under the age of five, has lagged even further behind adults as pediatricians struggle to understand new limitations and potential legal risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Joanne Hilden, a retired physician, has been searching for the updated vaccines for her four grandchildren, who are between the ages three and 12, in Minnesota. The local health department, where the youngest two kids were vaccinated in 2021, is only offering vaccines for adults over the age of 65. Pharmacies have not received the pediatric doses yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There are also immense structural barriers that make it harder for marginalized people to access the shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Julia Lynch, a professor of political science at the University of Pennsylvania, first made plans to get vaccinated in Oakland, New Jersey, a 45-minute drive from her home in Philadelphia, before the state board of pharmacy gave pharmacies the go-ahead to vaccinate Pennsylvanians.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The CVS pharmacies near her home had no appointments, so she ended up driving to a predominantly white suburb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“I don’t know why it is that the vaccines are getting to those CVSes first,” she said. But that means “if you’re Black or Latino, you are less likely than if you’re white to live close to someplace where you can get a vaccine”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="#EmailSignup-skip-link-27" class="dcr-jzxpee"&gt;skip past newsletter promotion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;aside aria-label="newsletter promotion" class="dcr-av5vqf"&gt;&lt;div class="dcr-10et71f"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-rsfwa"&gt;Sign up to &lt;span&gt;This Week in Trumpland&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-1xjndtj"&gt;A deep dive into the policies, controversies and oddities surrounding the Trump administration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SecureSignup" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"newsletterId":"the-stakes-us-election-edition","successDescription":"A deep dive into the policies, controversies and oddities surrounding the Trump administration"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1eusqlu"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy Notice: &lt;/strong&gt;Newsletters may contain information about charities, online ads, and content funded by outside parties. If you do not have an account, we will create a guest account for you on &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://www.theguardian.com" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;theguardian.com&lt;/a&gt; to send you this newsletter. You can complete full registration at any time. For more information about how we use your data see our &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://www.theguardian.com/help/privacy-policy" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;. We use Google reCaptcha to protect our website and the Google &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://policies.google.com/privacy" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://policies.google.com/terms" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt; apply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p id="EmailSignup-skip-link-27" tabindex="0" aria-label="after newsletter promotion" role="note" class="dcr-jzxpee"&gt;after newsletter promotion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The population of Oakland, for example, is 80% white and had appointments – but neighboring Camden, New Jersey, had no appointments, and its population is 3.5% white.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Transportation is another major issue. Traveling to Oakland by public transit would have taken more than two hours on three buses and one regional train.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Eligibility right now is obviously limited to people who are over 65 or who have at least one medical condition that puts them at high risk,” Lynch said. “These are exactly the people who are most likely to have trouble traveling four-plus hours on a multimodal public transit journey to get their Covid shot.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Not everyone has reliable internet access, the technological knowledge to book appointments, or the ability to take time off work or find childcare to locate and travel to appointments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“For people who are not chronically online, it’s a major undertaking to do all this,” Lynch said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Fighting to have the shots covered by insurance, or paying out of pocket for the uninsured, is another major hurdle, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Rachel, who lives in Pittsburgh and asked to be identified by her first name to protect her health history, has two autoimmune disorders and a genetic blood clotting disorder that puts her at high risk if she gets sick with Covid. She said she would like to get the latest Covid shot, but is planning to wait for a few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“The challenges right now for me are just around information, and actually knowing what is the truth and what is going to happen if I try to get it,” she said. She said she had heard of people being turned away from pharmacies even after the Pennsylvania vaccine announcement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It just sounds like it’s still a shitshow. It’s still challenging to make an appointment here, so I’m going to wait a little bit.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Rachel said it reminded her of 2021, when many people scrambled to get their first Covid shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s just frustrating to me that based on absolutely zero evidence, and in some cases, just making up lies about evidence, [the] HHS has just decided these are so dangerous that we need to limit them,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Sarah, who lives in Westchester county, New York, and asked to be identified by her first name so she is not harassed by anti-vaccine activists, said she was finally able to get the shot after days of effort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In New York, she needed a prescription. That later changed when Kathy Hochul, the governor, &lt;a href="https://www.governor.ny.gov/news/governor-hochul-signs-executive-order-expanding-access-vaccines-amid-uncertainty-washington" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;opened&lt;/a&gt; up access to all New Yorkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The faxed prescription never went through, so her health system had to set up an electronic prescription system. Sarah asked that her doctor prescribe any Covid vaccine; she said she overheard the pharmacist denying one prescription because it was for the Pfizer vaccine and they only had Moderna.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Even after the prescription was received, the pharmacist said he needed verbal confirmation from the doctor by phone as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Sarah said she paid $250 out of pocket, and has since spent hours on the phone with her insurance company to be reimbursed. After she paid, the pharmacist tried to dissuade her from getting the shot, Sarah said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Do you really know what you’re getting into? This is brand new,” she recalls him saying. She responded: “I know – that’s why I want it.” But he told her they “don’t know anything” about the updated vaccines and “we don’t know what’s gonna happen” to her once she received it, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The roadblocks were “wearing me down”, Sarah said. “It’s trying to make it inaccessible, impossible, confusing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Shipman in North Carolina was dogged in his search, even looking at appointments in other states. Eventually, he was able to receive the vaccine at an urgent care center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But not everyone is able to track down the vaccine and overcome these obstacles, Lynch said. “It’s really hard for ordinary people who are very busy and not necessarily paying close attention to this to know what they’re supposed to do to keep themselves or their loved ones safe.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:04:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE5aenlhSG9hSV8zOW5oSWpzUmdXZW9xeGxnRWowV0dieGRicEY0NXhfMk01aEdfSUxqLXVqTUtrXzh1Y2hRWmlEbUs2a2lKaGpVRGJVSDdRTXZQY2JPYlRjcEdkSTlPdnJVVDlwa01fM09URGRhQlRna0NnaDc</guid></item><item><title>Dropping hepatitis B shots for newborns would ignore history and endanger children, scientists warn - statnews.com</title><link>https://www.statnews.com/2025/09/11/newborn-hep-b-vaccine-debate-how-it-started/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the late 1980s and the American plan to combat hepatitis B wasn’t working. A vaccine had been available since 1982 and recommended for those deemed to be at highest risk, such as health care workers and men who have sex with men. But the infection rates had gone up, not down. When epidemiologists at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention dug into the data, they noticed one figure that had stayed alarmingly stable: Between 30% and 40% of hepatitis B patients had no identifiable risk factors at all.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;When they published &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/article-abstract/380888" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;their paper&lt;/a&gt; in 1990, it was subtitled, “Need for Alternative Vaccination Strategies.” The next year, the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices — the CDC body that sets such guidelines — recommended vaccinating all infants. Over the next two decades, case numbers &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/00333549231175548" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;plummeted&lt;/a&gt; by 99% among children and teens. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Now, under the Trump administration, some members of the ACIP have hinted at a desire to reverse course when the committee &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/meetings/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;next&lt;/a&gt; convenes on Sept. 18 and 19, as part of a broader review of childhood vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;At the last meeting in June, after health secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. abruptly &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/06/09/rfk-jr-fires-every-member-of-cdc-vaccine-expert-panel-acip/"&gt;fired&lt;/a&gt; all 17 experts who sat on the committee and &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/06/11/rfk-jr-names-new-acip-members-replaces-cdc-vaccine-experts-he-just-fired/"&gt;replaced&lt;/a&gt; them with his own picks, the new chair, Martin Kulldorff, expressed doubts about the current advice. “Is it wise to administer a birth dose of hepatitis B vaccine to every newborn before leaving the hospital? That’s the question,” he said. “Unless the mother is hepatitis B positive, an argument could be made to delay the vaccine for this infection, which is primarily spread by sexual activity and intravenous drug use.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To people who study, treat, or have hepatitis B, that argument is dangerously misguided, and if adopted, they warn it could lead to a resurgence of the virus as well as the liver disease and cancer it causes. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I’m speechless. It’s a failure to recognize why that strategy was put into place,” said Miriam Alter, the first author of that 1990 study, now retired from the CDC and the University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston. If that argument is taken up by the committee, she went on, “the virus, because it still circulates in the population, will rear its ugly head. We’ll be back in the same situation we were in when we depended upon risk-factor-based screening.”&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;One reason for giving the first vaccine dose on the first day of life, and the next doses soon after, is that infants are exquisitely vulnerable. A newly minted immune system — still learning what’s foreign and what’s self, not yet able to muster certain protective white blood cells — can allow hepatitis B to run amok, replicating continuously. That &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2076-393X/12/4/439" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;happens&lt;/a&gt; to fewer than 10% of people who get infected as adults, to 30% of those who get infected between the ages of 1 and 4, and to a whopping 90% of babies who get infected in the first year. If they’re vaccinated, though, that rate nosedives into the single digits. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“What you need to do is get their bodies the tools they need for the babies to start fighting the virus as soon as they are exposed,” said Chari Cohen, president of the Hepatitis B Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That exposure can take place before an infant has fully entered the world. Hepatitis B is a blood-borne pathogen, and childbirth, be it vaginal or cesarean, is bloody, with a possibility of mother-to-child transmission. While Sen. Rand Paul (R.-Ky.) &lt;a href="https://x.com/RandPaul/status/1962223758896173407" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;recently claimed on X&lt;/a&gt; that there is “no medical need to give newborns Hep B vaccine if mother is not infected” because “all mothers who deliver in a hospital are tested,” he was quickly corrected by his Senate colleague Bill Cassidy (R.-La.), who &lt;a href="https://x.com/SenBillCassidy/status/1962269409642197050" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;posted, “Empirically, this is not true.&lt;/a&gt; Not all mothers have prenatal care. Some get infected between testing in the first trimester and delivery. In some cases, the test is overlooked.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;If infection occurs at birth, there’s a 24-hour window of opportunity. “The vaccine needs to be given immediately to help the newborn develop antibodies to fight off that infection they have just been exposed to,” said John Ward, director of the Coalition for Global Hepatitis Elimination, who led the CDC’s viral hepatitis division from 2005 to 2018. “The longer you wait, then the longer that virus has time to set up shop and resist those antibodies.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But early immunization isn’t only helpful in cases of maternal infection. Hepatitis B is extremely infectious, some 50-to-100 times more easily transmissible than HIV, with more of it typically present in blood, meaning that a smaller speck may suffice for the pathogen to be passed on. Su Wang, a New Jersey physician specializing in hepatitis B, has seen young people with so much virus per milliliter of blood that “the lab test couldn’t even quantify it,” and technicians had to dilute the specimen in order to get a read. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That means that a child’s risk doesn’t end once they come home from the hospital: Transmission can happen in the household or at day care, in the infinitesimal-seeming blood exposure that might stem from a razor nick or shared toothbrush, a bite or scratch from another kid. &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Wang is a case in point. She was diagnosed with hepatitis B in her first year of college, when she signed up to donate blood, and she assumed she’d gotten it from her mom. But when her mom got tested, it came back negative. Her maternal grandparents, on the other hand, tested positive. They’d lived with Wang’s family when she was little, and Wang imagines that they may have been her source of exposure, but can’t be sure. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Those cases of early-childhood transmission are rare in the United States, but the consequences can be dire. Often, the virus lurks silently in the liver. It triggers inflammation that kills cells, which means someone may end up needing a transplant. But it also hijacks the genetic machinery and increases the likelihood of mutations. “We hear these stories all the time. Someone wakes up with tremendous pain in their side, they go to the emergency room, and by the end of the day, they’re told they have liver cancer,” Cohen said. “They don’t find out they have hep B until after they’re diagnosed with liver cancer, and they live for six weeks.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Such horrible outcomes are part of the calculus behind a “birth dose.” While critics of the strategy point out that some countries such as Denmark don’t vaccinate against hepatitis B until later in infancy, American researchers respond that the setting is quite different: Unlike European countries with smaller populations and universal health care systems, the United States has no unified public health apparatus that tracks every baby born and every intervention they receive. Prenatal care falls through the cracks; childhood visits fall through the cracks.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Other issues emerge when trying to screen or vaccinate adults based on their risk, as was recommended in the 1980s. If patients get to the doctor’s office at all, doctors may not think to ask about risk factors. Even if they do, patients might not feel comfortable disclosing their histories of sexual encounters and drug use, for instance, given the potential for stigma. Plus, by then, it might be too late.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“How do you identify individuals before they become ‘at risk’? You can’t,” said Alter. “That’s why immunizing young children was such a successful strategy. Because, by doing that, you immunize the population before they develop risk factors, whatever those risk factors might be.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Plus, hundreds of millions of people have received the hepatitis B vaccine worldwide, and follow-up studies have shown that it is remarkably safe, with the most common side effects being fever, redness and soreness at the injection site, and vomiting. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It’s easy to forget, when discussing statistics and stratifications of risk, that real people’s lives are at stake. There are antivirals that can help control hepatitis B, but there is no cure. Once people have it, they have it for life. If their immune systems become suppressed, it can roar out of hiding. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;After she was diagnosed at 21, during a routine screening before a college semester abroad, Wendy Lo sometimes couldn’t bring herself to go to her appointments. She’d likely been infected from her mom at birth; every visit was a painful reminder of the stigma she’d inherited. “Monitoring was doing a number to my psychology,” said Lo, 52, a former tech professional who now works as a fitness coach and hepatitis B advocate. “It’s just telling me I have this blemish. It’s kind of like a scarlet letter, this stain.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;She eventually did seek care, but at every stage, the virus shadowed her life. She canceled her study abroad program. The need to disclose her status made dating a minefield. Even the mildest of social drinking was off limits, given her elevated risk of liver failure. When she got married, her husband was protected by vaccines but she was terrified of giving the disease to her children. When doctors reassured her, saying that her babies would be safe with the administration of vaccines and other protective proteins, she worried that she might leave them without a mom. “Premature death, that is a very real and perpetual anxiety,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The fear was heightened as her uncle died of liver failure caused by hepatitis B. There were jobs and promotions Lo didn’t accept because she worried the stress might be too much for her health, or because the new health insurance wouldn’t cover the hepatitis drugs she needed. There are all sorts of medications she’s avoided so as not to burden her liver. In her 40s, when she was diagnosed with scarring of the liver, she became so anxious she couldn’t eat or sleep or make even the most quotidian decision. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;She’d been born years too early. But she can’t help but splice those two time frames together, and imagine what might’ve happened if she hadn’t gotten the virus, if she’d gone to do that semester abroad in Nanjing, if she’d stayed in China to start her career as planned — all of the worries and complications and curveballs she could have sidestepped with a vaccine. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 08:34:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxOVlhwOGJXdkxWeDFieWY2Z0t2Q0NkWlBuVGdFWnB5LWdHdVFYWDZRMGZINlBCLVYzdmdiUmZoU0ZVTktUR3NoNmlDZEpqSlc4eTRfR3FWX0FKSjFHWDBiaGdzX3ZmSXZEb3ZXR2c1bk5ORWkwRFhBcUNxcGswOC1DQVhLVTRYTEU</guid></item><item><title>简单的维生素可以逆转世界上最常见的肝病吗？ - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/could-a-simple-vitamin-reverse-the-worlds-most-common-liver-disease/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content cf entry-content content-spacious"&gt;

		
				
		&lt;figure id="attachment_493743" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-493743" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Liver-Human-Body.jpg"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-493743" src="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Liver-Human-Body-777x437.jpg" alt="Liver Human Body" srcset="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Liver-Human-Body-777x437.jpg 777w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Liver-Human-Body-400x225.jpg 400w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Liver-Human-Body-768x432.jpg 768w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Liver-Human-Body-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Liver-Human-Body-150x84.jpg 150w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Liver-Human-Body-450x253.jpg 450w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Liver-Human-Body-1200x675.jpg 1200w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Liver-Human-Body.jpg 2000w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-493743" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Researchers have identified a genetic trigger of fatty liver disease and found that vitamin B3 may hold the key to suppressing it. The discovery offers a promising pathway toward targeted therapies using a familiar, already approved drug. Credit: Shutterstock&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MiR-93 promotes fatty liver disease, but vitamin B3 can counteract its effects. This discovery suggests a new treatment approach.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roughly 30% of people worldwide are affected by metabolic-associated fatty liver disease (MASLD), a condition that until recently lacked targeted therapies. In an important breakthrough, scientists have identified a genetic factor that worsens the disease, and notably, the FDA-approved compound shown to be most effective against this factor is vitamin B3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A global first was achieved by a collaborative research group led by Professor Jang Hyun Choi of the Department of Life Sciences at UNIST, together with Professor Hwayoung Yun from the College of Pharmacy and Research Institute for Drug Development at Pusan National University (PNU) and Professor Neung Hwa Park from Ulsan University Hospital (UUH). Their work revealed the critical role of microRNA-93 (miR-93), a molecule expressed in the liver, as a genetic regulator influencing the onset and progression of MASLD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Role of miR-93 in liver function&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MiR-93 is a type of &lt;span class="glossaryLink" aria-describedby="tt" data-cmtooltip="&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemTitle&amp;gt;RNA&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemBody&amp;gt;RNA, or ribonucleic acid, is a single-stranded molecule involved in coding, decoding, and regulating gene expression. It acts as a messenger between DNA and protein synthesis and plays crucial roles in both genetic function and viral replication. Variants like mRNA, tRNA, and rRNA support different stages of protein assembly.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;" data-gt-translate-attributes='[{"attribute":"data-cmtooltip", "format":"html"}]' tabindex="0" role="link"&gt;RNA&lt;/span&gt; found in hepatocytes that suppresses the activity of specific target genes. Researchers detected unusually high levels of miR-93 in both human patients with fatty liver disease and in experimental animal models. Molecular studies showed that miR-93 drives lipid buildup, inflammation, and fibrosis by blocking the expression of SIRT1, a gene essential for regulating lipid metabolism in liver cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When scientists used gene-editing techniques to block miR-93 production in mice, they observed major reductions in liver fat accumulation, along with improved &lt;span class="glossaryLink" aria-describedby="tt" data-cmtooltip="&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemTitle&amp;gt;insulin&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemBody&amp;gt;Insulin is a hormone produced by the pancreas, crucial for regulating blood glucose levels. It helps cells in the body absorb glucose from the bloodstream and convert it into energy or store it for future use. Insulin production and action are essential for maintaining stable blood sugar levels. In people with diabetes, the body either does not produce enough insulin (Type 1 diabetes) or cannot effectively use the insulin it does produce (Type 2 diabetes), leading to elevated levels of glucose in the blood. This can cause various health complications over time, including heart disease, kidney damage, and nerve dysfunction. Insulin therapy, where insulin is administered through injections or an insulin pump, is a common treatment for managing diabetes, particularly Type 1. The discovery of insulin in 1921 by Frederick Banting and Charles Best was a landmark in medical science, transforming diabetes from a fatal disease to a manageable condition.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;" data-gt-translate-attributes='[{"attribute":"data-cmtooltip", "format":"html"}]' tabindex="0" role="link"&gt;insulin&lt;/span&gt; sensitivity and liver function markers. In contrast, mice engineered to overexpress miR-93 displayed more severe impairments in liver metabolism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Vitamin B3 as a therapeutic candidate&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, screening 150 FDA-approved drugs revealed that niacin (vitamin B3) most effectively suppresses miR-93. Mice treated with niacin showed a significant decrease in hepatic miR-93 levels and a notable increase in SIRT1 activity. The activated SIRT1 restored disrupted lipid metabolism pathways, thereby normalizing liver lipid homeostasis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research team explained, “This study precisely elucidates the molecular origin of MASLD and demonstrates the potential for repurposing an already approved vitamin compound to modulate this pathway, which has high translational clinical relevance.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They added, “Given that niacin is a well-established and safe medication used to treat hyperlipidemia, it holds promise as a candidate for combination therapies targeting miRNA pathways in MASLD.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference: “Hepatic miR-93 promotes the pathogenesis of metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease by suppressing SIRT1” by Yo Han Lee, Jinyoung Lee, Joonho Jeong, Kieun Park, Bukyung Baik, Yuseong Kwon, Kimyeong Kim, Keon Woo Khim, Haneul Ji, Ji Young Lee, Kwangho Kim, Ji Won Kim, Tam Dao, Misung Kim, Tae Young Lee, Yong Ryoul Yang, Haejin Yoon, Dongryeol Ryu, Seonghwan Hwang, Haeseung Lee and Jang Hyun Choi, 12 April 2025, &lt;i&gt;Metabolism&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.metabol.2025.156266"&gt;DOI: 10.1016/j.metabol.2025.156266&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This research was supported by various including the National Research Foundation of Korea (NRF) and the Korea Research Institute of Bioscience and Biotechnology (KRIBB).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Never miss a breakthrough: &lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/newsletter/"&gt;Join the SciTechDaily newsletter.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				
		
		
		
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 08:16:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPUm5BNUJ4U3lycmh3MjFHOTVPQjhLaFhhSU1nUFlQNG1CNWZxTW9QaGY5dHFKMTRnczJLYTdDdDVhVm9QdWVTT1dOcjJUemgtOXlEZU01SGZuc0dycDcwdDRZLWRvakhvT0p1cExxZFc0SzRoR0tqaUozRUZQZkhkWko1UVJRZHc0c0hYcE1SY1BCWjc1MzJ3eg</guid></item><item><title>致命真菌在医院蔓延引发欧洲警报- Bloomberg.com</title><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-09-11/candidozyma-auris-warning-as-deadly-fungus-spreads-in-europe-hospitals</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="box main"&gt;
                &lt;h2 class="main__heading"&gt;We've detected unusual activity from your computer network&lt;/h2&gt;
                &lt;p class="continue"&gt;To continue, please click the box below to let us know you're not a robot.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p id="px-captcha"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/section&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bloomberg.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxPVmExTXRwY2RUOXNuS0ZIc3FMelRpb2dRNEtMUFZRMkduQ25fNGZLM1RpWEpNdFFPOGZzTjhTRy1URVZmTDdtR3BINnI5TmxyT3MzdmdvbFR5Z2VOX3hhRm5xWXIzMmRyNHNBVTB0Zjh0V19jUmRma1plTXBzTU5fbmMyb3gxdGN4TU1VQTdaeU9WMTRaU0V4RThGWjNEcHBnLWFGa0lCeUlOeTJxUzBSV3lYX2FkVFgyMlM1OUpn</guid></item><item><title>改变阿尔茨海默氏症诊断的临床试验在英国启动- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trial-to-transform-alzheimers-diagnosis-launched-in-uk</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;UK researchers on Wednesday &lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/news/2025/sep/uk-trial-launches-transform-alzheimers-diagnosis-simple-blood-test"&gt;announced the trial&lt;/a&gt; of a blood test for  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="173862" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;, which it is hoped will transform the diagnosis of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers at University College London (UCL) will assess whether the test could improve the accuracy of diagnosis from 70 percent to over 90 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medics say &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-fastball-test-could-assess-alzheimers-risk-in-just-3-minutes"&gt;early diagnosis is critical&lt;/a&gt; with Alzheimer's, which is the most common cause of dementia, as the earlier treatment is started, the more effective it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/unexpected-link-between-menthol-and-alzheimers-found-in-mice"&gt;Unexpected Link Between Menthol And Alzheimer's Found in Mice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 1,100 people will be recruited through some 20 memory clinics to take part in the trial, which will assess how well the test can work in the UK's National Health Service (NHS).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer's disease is linked to the build-up of two key proteins in the brain called amyloid and tau.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/AlzheimersTauTangleIllustration.jpg" alt="Trial to Transform Alzheimer's Diagnosis Launched in UK" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Tangles of tau proteins can trigger the death of neurons, leading to Alzheimer's disease. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MADerDrK0Vs/"&gt;selvanegra/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new blood test measures the protein p-tau217, which is considered an effective biomarker of the presence of both the rogue proteins in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the test has already proven effective in finding p-tau217, scientists want to investigate whether administering it when memory issues are first assessed can help diagnosis and treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts believe blood tests such as plasma p-tau217 can detect the presence of amyloid and tau as accurately as current –  but more invasive – methods such as PET scans and lumbar punctures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trial is part of the Blood Biomarker Challenge, a multimillion-pound research project supported by UK Alzheimer's charities hoping to make breakthroughs in the use of blood tests to diagnose Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jonathan Schott, a professor of neurology at UCL's Dementia Research Centre who is co-leading the trial, &lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/news/2025/sep/uk-trial-launches-transform-alzheimers-diagnosis-simple-blood-test"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; he hoped it would "take us a step forward in revolutionizing the way we diagnose dementia".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early diagnosis would become even more important in coming years "as a new generation of treatments emerge that can slow down the decline of memory and thinking," he &lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/news/2025/sep/uk-trial-launches-transform-alzheimers-diagnosis-simple-blood-test"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Timely diagnosis will be key to ensuring these advances reach the people who need them most," he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;© &lt;a href="terms-and-conditions"&gt;Agence France-Presse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 05:46:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNcndPUTYtcDJvYjdyMDlNRkxDckZ4dEY0b2lTRHlsSjRjUXZRV2Y0enh6TUNGZ0FUVTRRQTJyMXJLOWhUSEpHdzBHbG9VMV95TU1TLVE1eGNoVV9TYlZpTU1ITkJFdHJpYk56eHNLN29lNm9rcXd4anYyRnlVUUl1MFVuWXowNGlwc3pGalFxOXRUYnV2eHpv</guid></item><item><title>言论自由和医疗错误信息之间的界限模糊不清-《金融时报》</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/0be45570-a889-44f4-a2e2-e099b8e1d15d</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="card-content css-1onnxdk"&gt;&lt;p class="o-grid-row o3-type-body-highlight css-1rea6b9"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="o3-visually-hidden"&gt;was &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="crossed-out-price css-lhfuqt"&gt;$540&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o3-visually-hidden"&gt;now &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="price css-79fz17"&gt;$319&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; for your first year&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="o-grid-row details-section o3-type-body-base css-pmzbjb"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Save now on essential digltal access to quality FT journalism on any device. Saving based on monthly annualised price.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="expander-content-recommendedOffers-Recommended Offers-standard" class="expander__content css-1n99znb" aria-hidden="true" data-offer-type="standard"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li class="css-i7yamd"&gt;&lt;span src="https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https://barrier-page-components.s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/assets/icons/global_news.svg?source=next-barrier-page&amp;amp;format=svg" alt="" class="css-5w798v"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o3-type-body-base"&gt;Global news &amp;amp; analysis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="css-i7yamd"&gt;&lt;span src="https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https://barrier-page-components.s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/assets/icons/expert_opinion.svg?source=next-barrier-page&amp;amp;format=svg" alt="" class="css-gai379"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o3-type-body-base"&gt;Expert opinion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="css-i7yamd"&gt;&lt;span src="https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https://barrier-page-components.s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/assets/icons/ft_logo_android_ios.svg?source=next-barrier-page&amp;amp;format=svg" alt="" class="css-koy9w6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o3-type-body-base"&gt;FT App on Android &amp;amp; iOS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="css-i7yamd"&gt;&lt;span src="https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https://barrier-page-components.s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/assets/icons/ft_edit_app.svg?source=next-barrier-page&amp;amp;format=svg" alt="" class="css-1ki4xuj"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o3-type-body-base"&gt;FT Edit: Access on iOS and web&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="css-i7yamd"&gt;&lt;span src="https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https://barrier-page-components.s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/assets/icons/first_ft.svg?source=next-barrier-page&amp;amp;format=svg" alt="" class="css-hdxmz4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o3-type-body-base"&gt;FirstFT: the day's biggest stories&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="css-i7yamd"&gt;&lt;span src="https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https://barrier-page-components.s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/assets/icons/mail_icon.svg?source=next-barrier-page&amp;amp;format=svg" alt="" class="css-1f3rsb0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o3-type-body-base"&gt;20+ curated newsletters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="css-i7yamd"&gt;&lt;span src="https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https://barrier-page-components.s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/assets/icons/my_ft.svg?source=next-barrier-page&amp;amp;format=svg" alt="" class="css-ziqj0d"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o3-type-body-base"&gt;Follow topics &amp;amp; set alerts with myFT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="css-i7yamd"&gt;&lt;span src="https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https://barrier-page-components.s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/assets/icons/videos_and_podcasts.svg?source=next-barrier-page&amp;amp;format=svg" alt="" class="css-sqib2a"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o3-type-body-base"&gt;FT Videos &amp;amp; Podcasts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="css-i7yamd"&gt;&lt;span src="https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https://barrier-page-components.s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/assets/icons/additional_articles.svg?source=next-barrier-page&amp;amp;format=svg" alt="" class="css-96k0qz"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o3-type-body-base"&gt;10 monthly gift articles to share&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Financial Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 04:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE9rZmRHRHBZS2VJX1hkbTA4N01KdzZITmRSME93QnN2dXc4VTAtemFsZG5WYjEzZmVZWURIQUNYdTlxb3I3WkJTcllXWmdfMXlMQkpKMlM2WHhnVFRCQXM3RUpNSDZlLWF6bjNFOVMxNlo</guid></item><item><title>全球慢性病死亡人数下降，但美国的进展停滞不前-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/10/well/chronic-disease-deaths.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 01:29:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTFBaamU1VU90VHd6MW94S0lJaERVd3MyMFBDV1FEbHBEcnZHcnJsVFAxWl94MDdwc0VrZTgyZ19KZXhfNjBlUnA0eXlDNnEwLXdNMk15c291cUo3SlRtVnA4RW82TENRVXhnWGQ4V1pnVE5FbVU5VXc</guid></item><item><title>压力以及如何管理： Xand van Tulleken博士的五个关键提示- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cg42zq7nqxwo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Dr Xand: Stress is normal. Here's how to manage it better&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-c4820dd1-0 cYDsPh"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-c4820dd1-11 bxdaHR"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;Dr Xand van Tulleken&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;Morning Live expert&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 kSquvq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-86c96223-1 evkFpM"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250905-110137-f27f908f49-web-2.29.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-86c96223-0 iMuqLZ hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Shot of a stressed out businesswoman surrounded by colleagues needing help. Businesswoman feeling stressed out in a demanding office environment at work. Photo of businesswoman under strain as colleagues request various things from her. Businesswoman feeling overwhelmed by her colleagues in the office. Frustrated businesswoman having a headache while her colleagues are demanding her to work on many things in the office. Stress, anxiety and multitasking businesswoman with headache from workload and laptop deadline in office." class="sc-86c96223-0 fHZDyi"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-86c96223-2 hqrvRC"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;September's back-to-it energy can leave us feeling overwhelmed and stressed&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Summer's over, the holidays feel like a distant memory and suddenly the world is back at full speed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;And that back-to-it energy can leave many of us feeling stretched thin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Stress, in small doses, can help us stay sharp but left unchecked, it can chip away at our health, mood and relationships.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Cortisol, often labelled as the stress hormone has become a bit of a wellness buzzword but it's worth remembering that it isn't the enemy - it's what helps us wake up, stay alert, and handle challenges. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The trick is keeping it in balance, not eliminating it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Here are five simple, science-backed ways to manage stress and get back in control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;1. Stop stressing about it&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 geRyoc"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-86c96223-1 evkFpM"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250905-110137-f27f908f49-web-2.29.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-86c96223-0 iMuqLZ hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A young woman is sitting on the sofa at home with her head in her hands" class="sc-86c96223-0 fHZDyi"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-86c96223-2 hqrvRC"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ironically, worrying about the effects of stress can make it worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The more we talk about how much harm stress does, we start to think 'agh now I'm stressed and I know it's doing me lots of harm', so try not to worry about how you're feeling. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Stress is a normal part of life and is unavoidable especially during major challenges like grief, caring for loved ones, looking after young children or navigating job uncertainties. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Instead of panicking about being stressed, accept that it happens and remind yourself it won't last forever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;2. Move your body&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 geRyoc"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-86c96223-1 evkFpM"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250905-110137-f27f908f49-web-2.29.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-86c96223-0 iMuqLZ hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Mature Man Exercising in a Park in the Morning " class="sc-86c96223-0 fHZDyi"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-86c96223-2 hqrvRC"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The best way to physically manage stress is to exercise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Exercise does the same thing to your body as stress does - it raises your heart rate, puts your blood pressure up, makes you breather faster and releases adrenaline and cortisol. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;By exercising, your body is learning to manage the cortisol spikes and handle those surges so you're better equipped to manage life's bigger stresses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;If you're getting stressed thinking about what exercise you're going to do or what gym to join, remember that any form of exercise is great. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It doesn't have to be anything too time consuming or high pressured - a simple walk, jog or any activity you enjoy will do the trick. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;3. Prioritise sleep&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 geRyoc"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-86c96223-1 evkFpM"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250905-110137-f27f908f49-web-2.29.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-86c96223-0 iMuqLZ hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Woman in depression closed face with hands and crying in bed." class="sc-86c96223-0 fHZDyi"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-86c96223-2 hqrvRC"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Try and get into bed earlier and wake up at roughly the same time in the morning so your body gets into a routine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;If you find yourself tossing and turning at night and not being able to fall asleep, don't worry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Your body can function on less sleep occasionally and over time your natural rhythms will recalibrate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;4. Focus on yourself&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 geRyoc"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-86c96223-1 evkFpM"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250905-110137-f27f908f49-web-2.29.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-86c96223-0 iMuqLZ hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Happy young woman mixing bowl of fresh salad." class="sc-86c96223-0 fHZDyi"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-86c96223-2 hqrvRC"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Managing stress isn't just about avoiding the negatives, it's also about actively building yourself up.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Make sure you're eating well with plenty of fruits, vegetables, whole foods and good-quality proteins to fuel your body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Try and also carve out some quality alone time where you can relax and recharge. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Mindfulness can also help - it's not about using a meditation app or sitting in silence, it's about being intentional in how you approach your life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Take a few minutes to think about the day or week ahead of you, what might be challenging and how you can pace yourself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;For me, it's about planning ahead with batch cooking as that can relieve some stress in the evening after work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;5. Talk it out&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 geRyoc"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-86c96223-1 evkFpM"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250905-110137-f27f908f49-web-2.29.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-86c96223-0 iMuqLZ hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Two women sitting in armchairs and talking. Female coach, psychotherapist, psychologist, advisor and patient, client " class="sc-86c96223-0 fHZDyi"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-86c96223-2 hqrvRC"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;I get terribly anxious about all kinds of things and everyone worries about money, jobs and families. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Those worries can quickly spiral when kept bottled up so sharing your concerns with someone you trust lightens the load and gives perspective, even if they can't solve the problem for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Sometimes just saying it out loud makes the problem feel more manageable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;i id="additional-reporting-by-yasmin-rufo" class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt;Additional reporting by Yasmin Rufo&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:30:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9JQ0dNR2tGSTdCQUd0TUVnTjJvWkdhYmlQNlYxV0VoSzkxejVRWGtTYkNxMGd0OS1OOTBvRzVzRjEzaHFNb1Z6VFhqT0JxbU5uckJ1MXBzQ0lOUQ</guid></item><item><title>压力以及如何管理： Xand van Tulleken博士的五个关键提示- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cg42zq7nqxwo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Dr Xand: Stress is normal. Here's how to manage it better&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-c4820dd1-0 cYDsPh"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-c4820dd1-11 bxdaHR"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;Dr Xand van Tulleken&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;Morning Live expert&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 kSquvq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-86c96223-1 evkFpM"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250905-110137-f27f908f49-web-2.29.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-86c96223-0 iMuqLZ hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/b1af/live/0dcd84d0-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Shot of a stressed out businesswoman surrounded by colleagues needing help. Businesswoman feeling stressed out in a demanding office environment at work. Photo of businesswoman under strain as colleagues request various things from her. Businesswoman feeling overwhelmed by her colleagues in the office. Frustrated businesswoman having a headache while her colleagues are demanding her to work on many things in the office. Stress, anxiety and multitasking businesswoman with headache from workload and laptop deadline in office." class="sc-86c96223-0 fHZDyi"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-86c96223-2 hqrvRC"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;September's back-to-it energy can leave us feeling overwhelmed and stressed&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Summer's over, the holidays feel like a distant memory and suddenly the world is back at full speed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;And that back-to-it energy can leave many of us feeling stretched thin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Stress, in small doses, can help us stay sharp but left unchecked, it can chip away at our health, mood and relationships.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Cortisol, often labelled as the stress hormone has become a bit of a wellness buzzword but it's worth remembering that it isn't the enemy - it's what helps us wake up, stay alert, and handle challenges. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The trick is keeping it in balance, not eliminating it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Here are five simple, science-backed ways to manage stress and get back in control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;1. Stop stressing about it&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 geRyoc"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-86c96223-1 evkFpM"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250905-110137-f27f908f49-web-2.29.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-86c96223-0 iMuqLZ hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/73d8/live/34a6bd60-8d78-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A young woman is sitting on the sofa at home with her head in her hands" class="sc-86c96223-0 fHZDyi"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-86c96223-2 hqrvRC"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ironically, worrying about the effects of stress can make it worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The more we talk about how much harm stress does, we start to think 'agh now I'm stressed and I know it's doing me lots of harm', so try not to worry about how you're feeling. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Stress is a normal part of life and is unavoidable especially during major challenges like grief, caring for loved ones, looking after young children or navigating job uncertainties. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Instead of panicking about being stressed, accept that it happens and remind yourself it won't last forever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;2. Move your body&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 geRyoc"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-86c96223-1 evkFpM"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250905-110137-f27f908f49-web-2.29.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-86c96223-0 iMuqLZ hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/04e4/live/608b1e40-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Mature Man Exercising in a Park in the Morning " class="sc-86c96223-0 fHZDyi"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-86c96223-2 hqrvRC"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The best way to physically manage stress is to exercise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Exercise does the same thing to your body as stress does - it raises your heart rate, puts your blood pressure up, makes you breather faster and releases adrenaline and cortisol. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;By exercising, your body is learning to manage the cortisol spikes and handle those surges so you're better equipped to manage life's bigger stresses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;If you're getting stressed thinking about what exercise you're going to do or what gym to join, remember that any form of exercise is great. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It doesn't have to be anything too time consuming or high pressured - a simple walk, jog or any activity you enjoy will do the trick. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;3. Prioritise sleep&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 geRyoc"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-86c96223-1 evkFpM"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250905-110137-f27f908f49-web-2.29.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-86c96223-0 iMuqLZ hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0b9e/live/2fb39bd0-8d77-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Woman in depression closed face with hands and crying in bed." class="sc-86c96223-0 fHZDyi"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-86c96223-2 hqrvRC"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Try and get into bed earlier and wake up at roughly the same time in the morning so your body gets into a routine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;If you find yourself tossing and turning at night and not being able to fall asleep, don't worry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Your body can function on less sleep occasionally and over time your natural rhythms will recalibrate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;4. Focus on yourself&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 geRyoc"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-86c96223-1 evkFpM"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250905-110137-f27f908f49-web-2.29.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-86c96223-0 iMuqLZ hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/76bb/live/ed13a3b0-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Happy young woman mixing bowl of fresh salad." class="sc-86c96223-0 fHZDyi"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-86c96223-2 hqrvRC"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Managing stress isn't just about avoiding the negatives, it's also about actively building yourself up.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Make sure you're eating well with plenty of fruits, vegetables, whole foods and good-quality proteins to fuel your body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Try and also carve out some quality alone time where you can relax and recharge. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Mindfulness can also help - it's not about using a meditation app or sitting in silence, it's about being intentional in how you approach your life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Take a few minutes to think about the day or week ahead of you, what might be challenging and how you can pace yourself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;For me, it's about planning ahead with batch cooking as that can relieve some stress in the evening after work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;5. Talk it out&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 geRyoc"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-86c96223-1 evkFpM"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250905-110137-f27f908f49-web-2.29.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-86c96223-0 iMuqLZ hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3dff/live/f2eb2740-8d76-11f0-a337-d7a51974c55f.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Two women sitting in armchairs and talking. Female coach, psychotherapist, psychologist, advisor and patient, client " class="sc-86c96223-0 fHZDyi"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-86c96223-2 hqrvRC"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;I get terribly anxious about all kinds of things and everyone worries about money, jobs and families. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Those worries can quickly spiral when kept bottled up so sharing your concerns with someone you trust lightens the load and gives perspective, even if they can't solve the problem for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Sometimes just saying it out loud makes the problem feel more manageable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;i id="additional-reporting-by-yasmin-rufo" class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt;Additional reporting by Yasmin Rufo&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:30:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9JQ0dNR2tGSTdCQUd0TUVnTjJvWkdhYmlQNlYxV0VoSzkxejVRWGtTYkNxMGd0OS1OOTBvRzVzRjEzaHFNb1Z6VFhqT0JxbU5uckJ1MXBzQ0lOUdIBX0FVX3lxTE1jUUF4c1YzWUxsQndZdlM1Ykh4SmtDUXZqbU1Ob0hfeW5ZaFkzS09lMjVNdUFTUnduSk1FWVgteTZwRHdhVHV3WC1EMm8xbWx0RFVxTWVFcGtXQnFLZjZj</guid></item><item><title>如果您居住在这些国家，您死于慢性病的风险已经下降—自然</title><link>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02905-z</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__teaser" data-test="access-teaser"&gt; &lt;figure class="figure"&gt;&lt;picture class="embed intensity--high"&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-02905-z/d41586-025-02905-z_51434352.jpg?as=webp 767w, //media.nature.com/lw319/magazine-assets/d41586-025-02905-z/d41586-025-02905-z_51434352.jpg?as=webp 319w" sizes="(max-width: 319px) 319px, (min-width: 1023px) 100vw,  767px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" alt="Sign attached to a street post indicating a no smoking district in a downtown area in California." loading="lazy" src="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-02905-z/d41586-025-02905-z_51434352.jpg"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="figure__caption u-sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span class="mr10"&gt;Public-health policies that restrict smoking have helped to reduce the chance of people dying from non-communicable diseases such as lung cancer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Credit: Smith Collection/Gado/Getty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chance of dying from chronic illnesses such as heart disease, &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-023-02075-w" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-023-02075-w" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;cancer &lt;/a&gt;and &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-023-00676-z" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-023-00676-z" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; declined in four out of five countries between 2010 and 2019, finds a study of 185 countries published in &lt;i&gt;The Lancet&lt;/i&gt; today&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR1" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nindia.2019.60" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/nindia.2019.60" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;Non-communicable diseases&lt;/a&gt; (NCDs) are the leading cause of death globally. The United Nations has set the goal of reducing deaths from these diseases by one-third by 2030.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;article class="recommended pull pull--left u-sans-serif" data-label="Related"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-00862-1" class="u-link-inherit" data-track="click" data-track-label="recommended article"&gt;&lt;img class="recommended__image" alt="" src="//media.nature.com/w400/magazine-assets/d41586-025-02905-z/d41586-025-02905-z_50860700.jpg"&gt;&lt;p class="recommended__title u-serif"&gt;154 million lives and counting: 5 charts reveal the power of vaccines&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest study is the first to investigate the change in NCD mortality across countries. It finds that, from 2010 to 2019, the probability of dying from an NCD before the age of 80 fell in 152 countries for women and in 147 countries for men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these gains, more than half of the countries saw slower declines in the 2010s compared with the previous decade. “Around the beginning of the millennium, we saw significantly lowered mortality rates, but despite political attention suddenly over the last decade, things are not doing as well as before,” says Majid Ezzati, a co-author and global-health researcher at Imperial College London.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2019, women in Japan and men in Singapore had the lowest risk of dying from a NCD among the countries studied, while women in Afghanistan and men in Eswatini had the highest (see ‘Risk of dying from chronic disease’).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="figure"&gt;&lt;picture class="embed intensity--high"&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-02905-z/d41586-025-02905-z_51437432.jpg?as=webp 767w, //media.nature.com/lw319/magazine-assets/d41586-025-02905-z/d41586-025-02905-z_51437432.jpg?as=webp 319w" sizes="(max-width: 319px) 319px, (min-width: 1023px) 100vw,  767px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" alt="Most and least improved: Graphic displaying data showing that among 25 high-income countries, the chance of dying from a non-communicable disease between 2001 and 2019 declined the most in Denmark, whereas the United States recorded the smallest decline." loading="lazy" src="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-02905-z/d41586-025-02905-z_51437432.jpg"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="figure__caption u-sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Source: Ref. 1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;All 25 high-income countries in the data set saw declines in NCD mortality between 2010 and 2019, with Denmark recording the largest drop for both sexes and the United States the smallest (see ‘Most and least improved’). China, Egypt, Nigeria, Russia and Brazil had a reduction in chronic-disease deaths, whereas India and Papua New Guinea experienced an increase in NCD deaths over the same period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="figure"&gt;&lt;picture class="embed intensity--high"&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-02905-z/d41586-025-02905-z_51437822.jpg?as=webp 767w, //media.nature.com/lw319/magazine-assets/d41586-025-02905-z/d41586-025-02905-z_51437822.jpg?as=webp 319w" sizes="(max-width: 319px) 319px, (min-width: 1023px) 100vw,  767px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" alt="Most and least improved: Graphic displaying data showing that among 25 high-income countries, the chance of dying from a non-communicable disease between 2001 and 2019 declined the most in Denmark, whereas the United States recorded the smallest decline." loading="lazy" src="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-02905-z/d41586-025-02905-z_51437822.jpg"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="figure__caption u-sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Source: Ref. 1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Veronica Le Nevez, a public-policy specialist at the George Institute for Global Health in Sydney, Australia, says that the report finds the biggest drivers of improvements in death rates were embedding better treatments and preventions in health-care systems, the widespread adoption of statins and hypertensives to lower the risk of heart attack and stroke and the development of vaccines for hepatitis and &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-00862-1" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-00862-1" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;cervical cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Government restrictions on tobacco and alcohol have also helped to reduce mortality from diseases linked to their use, such as lung cancer and alcohol-use disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Nature</author><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:11:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiX0FVX3lxTFA5WjJ4WDc2aXUxbmJtMEcyY0dFMmJHOUs3UXE5OW9QUkx0UXZJY3VxWmV4YXl1Ynl5V2g4WkZUYXJ2UFExeGRGUk5KTVJidlN1cmhUTzIyQmNjMkRMRml3</guid></item><item><title>一种纤维可能具有类似于Ozempic的减肥益处- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/a-type-of-fiber-may-have-weight-loss-benefits-similar-to-ozempic</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Research on the microbes living in our digestive tract has triggered a '&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC9503711/"&gt;revolution&lt;/a&gt;' in nutritional science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the last few years, dietary fiber has become the "&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/inulin-is-being-added-to-many-foods-but-it-could-be-causing-stomach-problems"&gt;new protein&lt;/a&gt;", added to foods &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-create-invisible-fiber-that-can-make-cakes-and-pizzas-better-for-you"&gt;in abundance&lt;/a&gt; to feed our gut's microbiome and boost our health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, a study on mice published in 2024 suggests that not all fiber supplements are equally beneficial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/eating-fiber-could-protect-you-from-infections-heres-why"&gt;Eating Fiber Could Protect You From Infections. Here's Why.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A form that is readily found in oats and barley, called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oat_beta-glucan"&gt;beta-glucan&lt;/a&gt;, can control blood sugar and assist in weight loss among mice fed a high-fat diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers at the University of Arizona (UA) and the University of Vienna found it decreased a mouse's fat content and body weight within 18 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other fibers they tested, including wheat dextrin, pectin, resistant starch, and cellulose, had no such effect, despite shifting the makeup of the mouse microbiome significantly compared to mice fed no fiber supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We know that fiber is important and beneficial; the problem is that there are so many different types," &lt;a href="https://news.arizona.edu/news/how-your-morning-oats-could-help-you-manage-your-weight"&gt;explained&lt;/a&gt; biomedical scientist Frank Duca from UA in July last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We wanted to know what kind of fiber would be most beneficial for weight loss and improvements in glucose homeostasis so that we can inform the community, the consumer, and then also inform the agricultural industry."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dietary fibers are the &lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/proceedings-of-the-nutrition-society/article/interactions-between-dietary-fibre-and-the-gut-microbiota/0BEF28B809F38D02AC0B1D4E4990210C"&gt;main source of energy&lt;/a&gt; for bacteria living in our guts, and &lt;a href="https://www.nih.gov/news-events/nih-research-matters/health-benefits-dietary-fibers-vary"&gt;yet less than 5 percent&lt;/a&gt; of people in the US consume the &lt;a href="https://www.ucsfhealth.org/education/increasing-fiber-intake"&gt;recommended 25–30 grams (0.9–1 ounce)&lt;/a&gt; of fiber a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_133570" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-133570" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/OatsAndABowl.jpg" alt="A bowl of oats and some oat grains " class="size-full wp-image-133570" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/OatsAndABowl.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/OatsAndABowl-600x374.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-133570" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Beta-glucan is found in oats and barley. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MADat1fdGi4/"&gt;ArxOnt/Canva Pro&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;To make up for this, fiber supplements and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-create-invisible-fiber-that-can-make-cakes-and-pizzas-better-for-you"&gt;'invisible fiber'-infused foods&lt;/a&gt; are &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/inulin-is-being-added-to-many-foods-but-it-could-be-causing-stomach-problems"&gt;growing in popularity&lt;/a&gt;. But fibers are extremely diverse, so which do we choose?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some fibers, like oat beta-glucans and wheat dextrin, are water-&lt;a href="https://www.webmd.com/diet/compare-dietary-fibers"&gt;soluble&lt;/a&gt;, meaning they are easily fermented by gut bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others, like cellulose and resistant starch, are less soluble or insoluble, meaning they &lt;a href="https://health.clevelandclinic.org/whats-the-difference-between-soluble-and-insoluble-fiber"&gt;stick to other materials to form stool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until now, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.tjnut.2024.05.003"&gt;writes&lt;/a&gt; biomedical scientist Elizabeth Howard from UA and her colleagues, "there is no study that has investigated the role of various fibers in one cohort."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To make up for this, the current study tested several forms of fiber in one cohort of mice. Only beta-glucan was found to increase the number of &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ileibacterium"&gt;Ileibacterium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; in the mouse intestine. Other &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/jn/nxy011"&gt;studies on mice&lt;/a&gt; have linked this bacterium to weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sure enough, long before the 10-week marker, mice fed beta-glucan showed reduced body weight and body fat content compared to mice fed other forms of fiber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings align with another recent &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12986-023-00767-8"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; by Duca, which fed barley flour, rich in beta-glucan, to rodents. Even though the rats continued eating just as much of their high-fat diet as before, their energy expenditure increased and they lost weight anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A similar outcome was observed in mice fed beta-glucan in the new study. These animals also showed increased concentrations of butyrate in their guts, which is a metabolite made when microbes break down fiber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Butyrate induces the release of glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1), which is the natural protein that synthetic drugs like &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-ozempic-and-why-are-people-saying-its-a-sad-way-to-lose-weight"&gt;Ozempic&lt;/a&gt; mimic to stimulate insulin release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_124692" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-124692" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/04/FingersHoldOzempicPen-642x260.jpg" alt="Fingers Hold Ozempic Pen" class="size-medium wp-image-124692" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/04/FingersHoldOzempicPen-642x260.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/04/FingersHoldOzempicPen-768x311.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/04/FingersHoldOzempicPen-600x243.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/04/FingersHoldOzempicPen.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-124692" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Ozempic and other semaglutide drugs mimic the effects of GLP-1. (imyskin/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Part of the benefits of consuming dietary fiber is through the release of GLP-1 and other gut peptides that regulate appetite and body weight," &lt;a href="https://news.arizona.edu/news/how-your-morning-oats-could-help-you-manage-your-weight"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; Duca.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"However, we don't think that's all of the effect. We think that there are other beneficial things that butyrate could be doing that are not gut peptide related, such as improving gut barrier health and targeting peripheral organs like the liver."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Far more research is needed before these results can be extended to humans, but the findings suggest that some fibers may be better suited to weight loss and insulin control than others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in the &lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.tjnut.2024.05.003"&gt;Journal of Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in July 2024.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 23:41:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxQbkJ5UzRDRGdoRTdjWVJhSzc3Q0x2N2RrYWNuNmJrOXFDYy04cHlpM1gzdENOQnBDTy1lVVhLOWVZUG8teE5mYkx0Ymg1Qk5tT1BNaFQ0XzhfVFVYOUNLcjdCVlRyZkN1MXA4UjRVdTlQTE4ySUtOcDNlckdrMko2LUhhWW4xWDBIaFJXRml1MTA0MDFOV3FrNw</guid></item><item><title>长期失眠？新的研究表明，这可能会导致你的大脑老化。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/09/10/chronic-insomnia-sleep-brain-aging/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CBOJZLSJLNHRNDH2PT2MAJ3GWM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Persistent sleeplessness may be far worse than a passing annoyance — gradually unraveling memory and mental sharpness, according to new research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YZS6PIGMSREMTHBN3ZPZKS2GZQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A study published Wednesday in &lt;a href="https://n.neurology.org/lookup/doi/10.1212/WNL.0000000000214155%20[press.aan.com]" target="_blank"&gt;Neurology&lt;/a&gt;, the journal of the American Academy of Neurology, identifies a troubling link: Older people who have chronic insomnia appear more likely to experience accelerated aging of the brain. These changes are revealed in both cognitive tests and imaging scans showing the altered structure of the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 23:01:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxNeEpBOURoRWZBU2RjMWFJYmtEUC1USTJnVGFjYUd4YWtNS3hNeF9nYmZHQWVsejloQzg3ZVZ6WVJKcHdNUDZ3ZTlmN1FaRFMzYS1HdG4yR2ZxMHA3TkxlQURmdEdjamdQQ0twOS0xTGh0dmZJTlRpd3J0YmkxQzJBb1Y5aWtJYzAwSjdGbQ</guid></item><item><title>2024年，新冠肺炎疫情从美国十大死亡原因中脱颖而出-美国国家公共广播电台</title><link>https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/09/10/nx-s1-5537078/u-s-death-rates-covid-2024</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-88078" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Activists gather during a vigil in Lafayette Park for nurses who died during the COVID-19 pandemic on January 13, 2022, in Washington, DC. (Photo by Brendan Smialowski / AFP) (Photo by BRENDAN SMIALOWSKI/AFP via Getty Images)
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    BRENDAN SMIALOWSKI/AFP/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        BRENDAN SMIALOWSKI/AFP/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;COVID-19 is no longer one of the top 10 causes of death in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Early data on deaths in 2024, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/data/vsrr/vsrr039.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;published by&lt;/a&gt; the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, show that COVID dropped from the list for the first time since the start of the pandemic. It became the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/products/databriefs/db456.htm" target="_blank"&gt;third leading cause of death&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. in 2020, and remained among the leading causes until now.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"COVID is still in the top 15 leading causes of death, so it hasn't disappeared," says Farida Ahmad, a health scientist at the CDC's National Center for Health Statistics and lead author on the publication.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Since its &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/products/databriefs/db456.htm" target="_blank"&gt;peak in 2021&lt;/a&gt;, when more than 463,000 people died from COVID, it has been moving steadily down the list. Last year, it was a factor in around &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/nvss/vsrr/covid19/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;47,000&lt;/a&gt; U.S. deaths.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;Overall, deaths last year were down 4% from the previous year, and it was the third consecutive year of that downward trend, Ahmad says. The declines extend across the board, to most age groups and to people of all races and ethnicities, and can be attributed to a number of factors, such as fewer deaths from COVID and from drug overdoses, she says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The leading causes of death included suicide, diabetes, kidney disease, and unintentional injury. Heart disease and cancer — both chronic diseases — remained the top two leading causes of death, as they have been for more than a decade, and were responsible for more than 40% of U.S. deaths in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Death rates were higher for men than women, for older adults, and for Black Americans compared with other racial and ethnic groups.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The fact that we're seeing people living into older and older age and dying of chronic diseases is a sign that we've been successful at dealing with infectious diseases," says Kathleen Ethier, a former CDC official at the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nccdphp/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;National Center for Chronic Disease Prevention and Health Promotion&lt;/a&gt;, who left the agency in January and was not involved in this paper.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Tackling chronic diseases takes a different strategy, Ethier says: "These are things that develop over time, that are highly impacted by our behavior and environments and genetics."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;With heart disease, for instance, a person may have higher risks if they have a family history of the condition, if they live in &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/CIRCRESAHA.123.323613" target="_blank"&gt;stressful or polluted environments&lt;/a&gt;, if they mainly eat &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/05/25/1178163270/ultra-processed-foods-health-risk-weight-gain" target="_blank"&gt;ultraprocessed foods&lt;/a&gt;, and if they have spotty access to health care. "What kinds of food can people afford? Do they have insurance and money to pay for services? Those are difficult, entrenched things for public health to impact," Ethier says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Earlier this week, Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. released a report titled "Make Our Children Healthy Again," which &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/09/09/nx-s1-5534412/rfk-maha-report-childrens-health" target="_blank"&gt;drew mixed reviews&lt;/a&gt; from public health advocates, who note that its goals clash with other recent moves by the Trump Administration, including cuts to food assistance, scientific research, Medicaid programs and changes that limit access to vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"What this administration is doing is going to make the top ten causes of death worse," says Ethier. She notes that President Trump's &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Fiscal-Year-2026-Discretionary-Budget-Request.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;FY 2026 budget&lt;/a&gt; targets the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nccdphp/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;CDC division&lt;/a&gt; that's focused on preventing chronic diseases for elimination in. This includes the &lt;a href="https://www.tobaccofreekids.org/press-releases/2025_05_05_administrations-budget-would-devastate-cdc-efforts-to-fight-chronic-disease-and-tobacco-use" target="_blank"&gt;office that deals with smoking&lt;/a&gt;, a major risk factor for heart disease, stroke and some cancers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 22:43:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxOTzd2RnpZMDdlTDQwUThRYzF0bFROVWMyUzFSR24xTDl3T0RmLTVqNGZlVGhTcF9ObEJFdk5BVDY1NGI1ZnNBRmdQSGQwUkZZdHNzdl9RVVFiVVdBOThKc29kdUFFeHRQZE9Dci14WGY5NDBWWmh4S2J3ay05UEt3SlN2cGpsYmRRcnBlWk5teEw3VFBJbjFTSmREMWZvRVU</guid></item><item><title>新研究发现，在高收入国家中，美国在降低慢性疾病死亡风险方面进展最慢- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/10/health/chronic-disease-deaths-global-study-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/action-bar/instances/cmfebu2hf006l28qj9727bu7w@published" data-label-id-prefix="action-bar-start-of-article" class="action-bar" data-dynamic-breakpoint-placement='{"extraLarge":{"placement":".layout-article-elevate__left"}}' data-expand-conditions='{"follow":{"extraLarge":{"alwaysExpand":true}},"shareOptions":{"large":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"medium":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"extraLarge":{"withAction":"follow","maxNumOfActions":2}}}'&gt;
    &lt;p class="action-bar__overlay"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet" tabindex="-1"&gt;
        
            
            &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet--action" data-title="share options"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/social-share/instances/cmfebu2hf006o28qjh1wfgc0r@published" class="social-share_labelled-list"&gt;
    &lt;div class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links vossi-social-share_labelled-list" data-type="share-links"&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.facebook.com/dialog/share?app_id=80401312489&amp;amp;href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F10%2Fhealth%2Fchronic-disease-deaths-global-study-wellness&amp;amp;display=popup" data-type="facebook" aria-label="share with facebook" title="Share with Facebook"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-facebook-circle" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.04139 1.33301C11.7458 1.33301 14.7488 4.33601 14.7488 8.04042C14.7488 11.3884 12.296 14.1632 9.08943 14.6663V9.97928H10.6523L10.9497 8.04042H9.08943V6.78225C9.08943 6.25182 9.34934 5.73475 10.1825 5.73475H11.0283V4.08409C11.0283 4.08409 10.2607 3.95309 9.52685 3.95309C7.99476 3.95309 6.99336 4.88165 6.99336 6.56269V8.04042H5.29031V9.97928H6.99336V14.6663C3.78677 14.1632 1.33398 11.3882 1.33398 8.04042C1.33398 4.33601 4.33699 1.33301 8.04139 1.33301Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Facebook&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F10%2Fhealth%2Fchronic-disease-deaths-global-study-wellness" data-type="x" aria-label="share with x" title="Share with X"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-x-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.99386 8.11503L0 0.666992H4.74756L8.44753 5.27039L12.4004 0.687719H15.0151L9.71175 6.84331L16 14.667H11.2666L7.2603 9.6887L2.98317 14.6532H0.354296L5.99386 8.11503ZM11.9565 13.287L2.91105 2.04698H4.0571L13.0912 13.287H11.9565Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Tweet&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;a class="social-share_labelled-list__share" href="mailto:?subject=CNN%20content%20share&amp;amp;body=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A%0Ahttps%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F10%2Fhealth%2Fchronic-disease-deaths-global-study-wellness" data-type="email" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="share with email" title="Share with email"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-email-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 24 24" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M2 6C2 4.89543 2.89543 4 4 4H20C21.1046 4 22 4.89543 22 6V18C22 19.1046 21.1046 20 20 20H4C2.89543 20 2 19.1046 2 18V6ZM4 6H20V9.11604L12 11.9396L4 9.11604V6ZM4 11.237V18H20V11.237L12.3328 13.943C12.1174 14.019 11.8825 14.019 11.6672 13.943L4 11.237Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Email&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/10/health/chronic-disease-deaths-global-study-wellness" data-type="copy" aria-label="copy link to clipboard" title="Copy link to clipboard"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-hyperlink" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.64373 10.3574C5.38338 10.0971 5.38338 9.67496 5.64373 9.41461L9.88637 5.17197C10.1467 4.91162 10.5688 4.91162 10.8292 5.17197C11.0895 5.43232 11.0895 5.85443 10.8292 6.11478L6.58654 10.3574C6.32619 10.6178 5.90408 10.6178 5.64373 10.3574Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M4.22952 8.94321L5.64373 7.52899C5.90408 7.26865 5.90408 6.84654 5.64373 6.58619C5.38338 6.32584 4.96127 6.32584 4.70092 6.58619L3.28671 8.0004C1.98496 9.30215 1.98496 11.4127 3.28671 12.7144C4.58846 14.0162 6.69901 14.0162 8.00075 12.7144L9.41497 11.3002C9.67532 11.0399 9.67532 10.6178 9.41497 10.3574C9.15462 10.0971 8.73251 10.0971 8.47216 10.3574L7.05795 11.7716C6.2769 12.5527 5.01057 12.5527 4.22952 11.7716C3.44847 10.9906 3.44847 9.72426 4.22952 8.94321Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.94356 4.22916L7.52935 5.64338C7.269 5.90373 6.84689 5.90373 6.58654 5.64338C6.32619 5.38303 6.32619 4.96092 6.58654 4.70057L8.00075 3.28635C9.3025 1.98461 11.4131 1.98461 12.7148 3.28635C14.0165 4.5881 14.0165 6.69865 12.7148 8.0004L11.3006 9.41461C11.0402 9.67496 10.6181 9.67496 10.3578 9.41461C10.0974 9.15426 10.0974 8.73215 10.3578 8.4718L11.772 7.05759C12.553 6.27654 12.553 5.01021 11.772 4.22916C10.9909 3.44812 9.72461 3.44811 8.94356 4.22916Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Link&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__open" data-type="open" aria-label="open social share" title="Open social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-share-os" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19 12c.394 0 .714.32.714.714v8.572c0 .394-.32.714-.714.714H4.714A.715.715 0 014 21.286v-8.572a.715.715 0 011.429 0v7.857h12.857v-7.857c0-.394.32-.714.714-.714zm-7.664-9.79a.73.73 0 011.024 0l.076.075 4.916 4.854c.183.18.27.449.188.69a.734.734 0 01-1.216.314L12.57 4.5v11.786c0 .357-.357.714-.714.714s-.714-.359-.714-.714V4.5L7.372 8.143a.73.73 0 01-1.102-.091c-.21-.289-.149-.694.106-.946l4.884-4.821z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__close" data-type="close" aria-label="close social share" title="Close social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-close" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19.787 18.758l-6.792-6.781 6.746-6.735a.728.728 0 00-1.028-1.03l-6.747 6.737-6.711-6.7a.728.728 0 00-1.028 1.03l6.71 6.698-6.723 6.712a.727.727 0 101.027 1.03l6.725-6.714 6.793 6.782a.725.725 0 001.028 0 .727.727 0 000-1.03"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebu2hf006n28qjhooq33cd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Among all high-income Western countries, the United States has shown the worst performance in reducing the probability of dying from chronic diseases, a new study finds.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvyce00043b6ngt3q0w0d@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            From 2010 to 2019, deaths due to chronic diseases declined in most age groups in the US but increased among adults 20 to 45, “a rare phenomenon in high-income western countries,” according to the study, published Wednesday in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(25)01388-1/fulltext" target="_blank"&gt;The Lancet&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvyce00053b6njctdoh28@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The study, led by researchers at Imperial College London, analyzed data on 185 countries and territories and found that, from 2010 to 2019, the probability of dying by age 80 from a noncommunicable disease — such as cancer, heart disease and stroke — declined in most of those countries, but the decline&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;had slowed compared with&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;the previous decade.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvyce00063b6nild6cgho@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The risk of dying – or what we call probability in the paper – from chronic diseases in most countries in the world is coming down,” said Majid Ezzati, the study’s senior author and a professor in the School of Public Health at Imperial College London and Imperial Global Ghana.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvyce00073b6necpuru5j@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “But we were doing better before,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvyce00083b6nz5rda8n1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Among the 25 high-income Western countries in the study, Denmark had the largest decline in chronic disease deaths, while the United States had the smallest, and Germany did only slightly better than the United States.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvyce00093b6nqn9mrc75@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The US is the slowest, but it’s by no means the exception,” Ezzati said. “Germany is doing nearly as badly.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000a3b6nuznk8at0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Among the high-income Western countries, there were small to moderate declines in the probability of dying from a chronic disease by age 80 from 2010 to 2019&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;overall. But the researchers noted that a possible reason why the declines were not larger as a group is that in many countries, neuropsychiatric conditions such as dementia increased and contributed unfavorably to the trends.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000b3b6nt75iqwnh@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The new study included data from the World Health Organization’s &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/data/global-health-estimates" target="_blank"&gt;Global Health Estimates&lt;/a&gt;, and the team of researchers analyzed deaths between time periods, countries and by age groups: young adults 20 to 45, working-age adults 45 to 65, and older adults 65 to 80.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000c3b6n7sccev1z@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The data showed that from 2010 to 2019, chronic disease deaths declined in about 80% of the world’s countries, home to more than 70% of the global population.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000d3b6nazce3hrr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The reasons for widespread decline in chronic disease mortality could be tied to improvements in diagnosing and treating chronic diseases, according to the study. For instance, there have been changes in clinical guidelines as well as increases in the use of certain medications and the early detection of certain cancers.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000e3b6nchlfuy6c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But in about 60% of countries, either the decline in chronic disease deaths from 2010 to 2019 was smaller than it had been in the preceding decade or there was a reversal of an earlier decline, the data showed.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000f3b6nzrshd1ia@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The countries that did really well did well both in older and working ages. Countries that did really badly did badly in both older and working ages,” Ezzati said. “And then there was some tradeoff between these. Some places never slowed down in older ages, but they have in working ages, and vice versa.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000g3b6ndumo1prx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            From 2010 to 2019, Finland, Norway and Denmark all had a slower decline in chronic disease deaths among older ages than they had in the previous decade. But they still maintained significant progress in reducing the risk of chronic disease deaths overall because that slower decline among older adults was countered by faster declines among working-age adults.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000h3b6n2nyupit9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In the United States, small reductions in mortality among older adults were combined with a stagnation among working-age adults and increases in mortality among young adults, leading to the nation’s poor performance compared with other high-income Western countries.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000i3b6nndxkmozs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The study did not analyze why some countries had greater improvements than others in reducing the probability of chronic disease deaths, but Ezzati had some ideas.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000j3b6nxtz69a9w@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In both high-income Western countries that performed poorly compared with their peers – the United States and Germany – there are segments of the population in which there has been less investment in public health, he noted, and these disparities in investment can lead to broad barriers to accessing care.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000k3b6nw55t9kn7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For instance, a barrier can be not having a primary care physician in your local area, which can lead to the delayed screening for and diagnosis of chronic conditions, Ezzati said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000l3b6nnw91guzz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Many Americans live in areas where critical-care services are lacking. It’s estimated that &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2017/08/03/health/hospital-deserts"&gt;nearly 30 million Americans don’t live within an hour of trauma care&lt;/a&gt;. And a CNN analysis has found that people living in 16% of the mainland United States are 30 miles or more from the nearest hospital.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000m3b6n5o94sfdp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The United States also has had a rise in the probability of dying from neuropsychiatric conditions, such as dementia and alcohol use disorders, which did not appear to offset continued declines in deaths from cancers and cardiovascular diseases – and these trends could have contributed to the nation’s poor performance in reducing chronic disease mortality, according to the researchers.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000p3b6nr7214aud@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The new study was published a day after the Trump administration released the &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/09/health/make-america-healthy-again-maha-report"&gt;Make America Healthy Again Commission&lt;/a&gt;’s action plan on reducing &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/maha-commission-report-childhood-disease-strategy.html" target="_blank"&gt;childhood chronic diseases&lt;/a&gt; in the United States.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000q3b6n1dbgpobx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            US Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has made tackling chronic diseases a primary focus. In an &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/bretbaier/reel/DOZjGEPj3c3/" target="_blank"&gt;interview Tuesday on Fox News&lt;/a&gt;, Kennedy noted that the share of &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pcd/issues/2025/24_0539.htm" target="_blank"&gt;US adults with at least one chronic condition is 76.4%&lt;/a&gt;, according to data from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000s3b6nxakxnxm9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Elena Ladas, a professor of global integrative medicine at Columbia University and an expert on noncommunicable diseases in young people, said she is optimistic the United States is heading toward embracing wellness as a prevention tool to reduce chronic disease deaths, but she wants to see a clear implementation plan.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000t3b6n69djci5b@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “They’re talking about the right things: Ultraprocessed foods need to really be minimized, and exposures to pesticides and environmental contaminants,” Ladas said of the MAHA report. “They’re talking about what I think a lot of epidemiologists and clinicians have been saying for a very long time. But how they’re going to implement that remains to be seen.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000u3b6nta4i7ft8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Ladas, who was not involved in the new study but has done public health work in nearly two dozen countries, said the United States should “think about wellness comprehensively” to reduce the burden of chronic disease.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000v3b6n9brmur57@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Wellness approaches include good nutrition. We need to make healthy food reasonably priced. A lot of times, farmer’s markets are more expensive than the grocery store. You don’t see that in Europe. In Europe, farmer’s markets are far less expensive than grocery stores,” Ladas said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfebvycf000w3b6nxyp4yfic@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “And mental health can include meditation and deep-breathing,” she added. “There are more holistic wellness approaches to include for a lot of these chronic conditions versus being only medication-based resolutions. You need both.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOQVM1UGQ1aFRpM0dGSFdoTGRESzJvcXdsQmxkbk9QYkRhQ0FVZV93cW9xQTE3OFNWc052VFN0U3Y1YmF6ZG5FaHRCWFh2Z09qczR1a0x0eWVCMnRtYWJXNXRPQ1lWdl9uNVQwbW5jODQtbzJZckRVYUpmV2piUG9xTVZld1J1LUVwZHc</guid></item><item><title>新泽西州是扩大获取最新新冠疫情疫苗的最新州--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/10/nyregion/new-jersey-covid-vaccine-pharmacies.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 22:11:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxNRVFEQ3BCWFNUUUdhNGNmNE1TVkQ3ckNHSWNJQmZ5YXVaWHBKcEh2NFUzcmtLQzNZemRCMGpXV0ZldklpX3NGRWhJeTJxN3M5SHlyS3RhbjZQVmFhQ2xVUzJQSkxQR1hPbzY2dTlNc3diLXlxUzFma2hPY3U4cmFwY1ZONnpSRVZ6SjFvUA</guid></item><item><title>1500年的谜团解开：科学家重写世界第一次大流行的起源- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/1500-year-old-mystery-solved-scientists-rewrite-the-origins-of-the-worlds-first-pandemic/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content cf entry-content content-spacious"&gt;

		
				
		&lt;figure id="attachment_118753" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-118753" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Virus-Pandemic.jpg"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-118753 size-large" src="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Virus-Pandemic-777x518.jpg" alt="Virus Pandemic" srcset="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Virus-Pandemic-777x518.jpg 777w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Virus-Pandemic-400x267.jpg 400w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Virus-Pandemic-768x512.jpg 768w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Virus-Pandemic-1536x1024.jpg 1536w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Virus-Pandemic.jpg 2000w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-118753" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Researchers have finally identified genetic traces of the plague bacterium at the heart of the Byzantine Empire, providing long-sought proof of the microbe behind history’s first pandemic. Credit: Stock&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;USF and FAU researchers identify bacterium behind 1,500-year-old pandemic mystery.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the first time, scientists have obtained direct genomic evidence of the bacterium responsible for the Plague of Justinian, the earliest known pandemic in recorded history. The outbreak, which struck the Eastern Mediterranean nearly 1,500 years ago, has now been firmly tied to &lt;em&gt;Yersinia pestis&lt;/em&gt;, the pathogen that causes plague.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An international team led by researchers at the University of South Florida and Florida Atlantic University, working with partners in India and Australia, identified &lt;em&gt;Y. pestis&lt;/em&gt; in human remains from a mass grave at the ancient city of Jerash in Jordan, close to the heart of the pandemic. This pivotal discovery confirms the bacterium’s role in the Justinian Plague (AD 541–750), resolving a mystery that has lingered for centuries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_493351" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-493351" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Rays-Jiang-1-scaled.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-493351" src="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Rays-Jiang-1-777x519.jpg" alt="Rays Jiang" srcset="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Rays-Jiang-1-777x519.jpg 777w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Rays-Jiang-1-400x267.jpg 400w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Rays-Jiang-1-768x513.jpg 768w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Rays-Jiang-1-1536x1025.jpg 1536w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Rays-Jiang-1-2048x1367.jpg 2048w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Rays-Jiang-1-150x100.jpg 150w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Rays-Jiang-1-450x300.jpg 450w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Rays-Jiang-1-1200x801.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-493351" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Rays Jiang, PhD, University of South Florida. Credit: USF Health&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Filling historical gaps with genetic proof&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For hundreds of years, scholars debated the origins of the catastrophic outbreak that killed tens of millions, reshaped the Byzantine Empire, and altered the trajectory of Western history. Although written accounts hinted at plague, no biological proof had been available, leaving a critical gap in the narrative of pandemics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, two newly released papers led by USF and FAU provide that missing proof, offering fresh insight into one of humanity’s most transformative health crises. The findings also highlight plague’s continued presence today: although uncommon, &lt;em&gt;Y. pestis&lt;/em&gt; still circulates globally. In July, a resident of northern Arizona died from pneumonic plague, the deadliest form of the disease and the first U.S. fatality since 2007, followed just a week later by a confirmed case in California.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_493348" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-493348" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Tooth-With-Roots-scaled.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-493348" src="https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Tooth-With-Roots-777x378.jpg" alt="USF Researcher Holding Excavated Human Tooth With Roots" srcset="https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Tooth-With-Roots-777x378.jpg 777w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Tooth-With-Roots-400x194.jpg 400w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Tooth-With-Roots-768x373.jpg 768w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Tooth-With-Roots-1536x747.jpg 1536w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Tooth-With-Roots-2048x996.jpg 2048w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Tooth-With-Roots-150x73.jpg 150w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Tooth-With-Roots-450x219.jpg 450w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Tooth-With-Roots-1200x583.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-493348" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Tooth from the Jerash architectural site. Credit: University of South Florida&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This discovery provides the long-sought definitive proof of &lt;em&gt;Y. pestis&lt;/em&gt; at the epicenter of the Plague of Justinian,” said Rays H. Y. Jiang, PhD, lead PI of the studies and associate professor with the USF College of Public Health. “For centuries, we’ve relied on written accounts describing a devastating disease, but lacked any hard biological evidence of plague’s presence. Our findings provide the missing piece of that puzzle, offering the first direct genetic window into how this pandemic unfolded at the heart of the empire.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Evidence of widespread mortality&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Plague of Justinian was first documented in Pelusium (modern-day Tell el-Farama) in Egypt, before sweeping across the Eastern Roman, or Byzantine, Empire. Although remnants of &lt;em&gt;Y. pestis&lt;/em&gt; had been detected in small villages in western Europe thousands of miles away, no genetic evidence had ever been uncovered within the empire itself or close to the pandemic’s center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Using targeted ancient &lt;span class="glossaryLink" aria-describedby="tt" data-cmtooltip="&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemTitle&amp;gt;DNA&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemBody&amp;gt;DNA, or deoxyribonucleic acid, is a molecule made of two long strands of nucleotides twisted into a double helix. It serves as the hereditary material in humans and nearly all other organisms, encoding the genetic instructions used for development, functioning, and reproduction. Most DNA resides in the cell nucleus (nuclear DNA), while a smaller portion is found in mitochondria (mitochondrial DNA or mtDNA).&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;" data-gt-translate-attributes='[{"attribute":"data-cmtooltip", "format":"html"}]' tabindex="0" role="link"&gt;DNA&lt;/span&gt; techniques, we successfully recovered and sequenced genetic material from eight human teeth excavated from burial chambers beneath the former Roman hippodrome in Jerash, a city just 200 miles from ancient Pelusium,” said Greg O’Corry-Crowe, PhD, co-author and a research professor at FAU Harbor Branch Oceanographic Institute and a National Geographic Explorer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_493347" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-493347" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/images/The-Ancient-DNA-Lab-at-Florida-Atlantic-University.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-493347" src="https://scitechdaily.com/images/The-Ancient-DNA-Lab-at-Florida-Atlantic-University.jpg" alt="The Ancient DNA Lab at Florida Atlantic University" srcset="https://scitechdaily.com/images/The-Ancient-DNA-Lab-at-Florida-Atlantic-University.jpg 777w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/The-Ancient-DNA-Lab-at-Florida-Atlantic-University-400x240.jpg 400w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/The-Ancient-DNA-Lab-at-Florida-Atlantic-University-768x461.jpg 768w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/The-Ancient-DNA-Lab-at-Florida-Atlantic-University-150x90.jpg 150w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/The-Ancient-DNA-Lab-at-Florida-Atlantic-University-450x270.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-493347" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The Ancient DNA lab at Florida Atlantic University. Credit: FAU&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The arena had been repurposed as a mass grave during the mid-sixth to early seventh century, when written accounts describe a sudden wave of mortality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Genomic analysis revealed that the plague victims carried nearly identical strains of &lt;em&gt;Y. pestis&lt;/em&gt;, confirming for the first time that the bacterium was present within the Byzantine Empire between AD 550-660. That genetic uniformity suggests a rapid, devastating outbreak consistent with historical descriptions of a plague causing mass death.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The Jerash site offers a rare glimpse of how ancient societies responded to public health disasters,” said Jiang. “Jerash was one of the key cities of the Eastern Roman Empire, a documented trade hub with magnificent structures. That a venue once built for entertainment and civic pride became a mass cemetery in a time of emergency shows how urban centers were very likely overwhelmed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Broader evolutionary patterns&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2076-0817/14/8/797"&gt;companion study&lt;/a&gt;, also led by USF and FAU, places the Jerash discovery into a wider evolutionary context. By analyzing hundreds of ancient and modern &lt;em&gt;Y. pestis &lt;/em&gt;genomes — including those newly recovered from Jerash — the researchers showed that the bacteria had been circulating among human populations for millennia before the Justinian outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team also found that later plague pandemics, from the Black Death of the 14&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; century to cases still appearing today, did not descend from a single ancestral strain. Instead, they arose independently and repeatedly from longstanding animal reservoirs, erupting in multiple waves across different regions and eras. This repeated pattern stands in stark contrast to the &lt;span class="glossaryLink" aria-describedby="tt" data-cmtooltip="&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemTitle&amp;gt;SARS-CoV-2&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemBody&amp;gt;SARS-CoV-2 is the novel coronavirus that causes COVID-19, first identified in Wuhan, China, in late 2019. It primarily spreads through respiratory droplets and has infected hundreds of millions worldwide. The virus has undergone multiple mutations, resulting in variants with differing transmission and immune escape characteristics.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;" data-gt-translate-attributes='[{"attribute":"data-cmtooltip", "format":"html"}]' tabindex="0" role="link"&gt;SARS-CoV-2&lt;/span&gt; pandemic (&lt;span class="glossaryLink" aria-describedby="tt" data-cmtooltip="&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemTitle&amp;gt;COVID-19&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemBody&amp;gt;COVID-19 is an infectious disease caused by the novel coronavirus SARS-CoV-2, first identified in late 2019. It led to a global pandemic, disrupting economies, healthcare systems, and daily life worldwide. Transmission occurs primarily through respiratory droplets and aerosols, and symptoms range from mild to severe.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;" data-gt-translate-attributes='[{"attribute":"data-cmtooltip", "format":"html"}]' tabindex="0" role="link"&gt;COVID-19&lt;/span&gt;), which originated from a single spillover event and evolved primarily through human-to-human transmission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_493350" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-493350" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Greg-OCorry-Crowe.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-493350" src="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Greg-OCorry-Crowe-777x1021.jpg" alt="Greg O’Corry Crowe" srcset="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Greg-OCorry-Crowe-777x1021.jpg 777w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Greg-OCorry-Crowe-400x525.jpg 400w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Greg-OCorry-Crowe-768x1009.jpg 768w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Greg-OCorry-Crowe-1169x1536.jpg 1169w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Greg-OCorry-Crowe-150x197.jpg 150w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Greg-OCorry-Crowe-450x591.jpg 450w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Greg-OCorry-Crowe-1200x1576.jpg 1200w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Greg-OCorry-Crowe.jpg 1559w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-493350" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Greg O’Corry-Crowe, PhD, Florida Atlantic University. Credit: G. Divoky&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together, the landmark findings reshape the understanding of how pandemics emerge, recur and spread, and why they remain a persistent feature of human civilization. The research underscores that pandemics are not singular historical catastrophes, but repeating biological events driven by human congregation, mobility and environmental change — themes that remain relevant today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Shared humanity across pandemics&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This research was both scientifically compelling and personally resonant. It offered an extraordinary opportunity to delve into the study of human history through the lens of ancient DNA at a time when we ourselves were living through a global pandemic,” said O’Corry-Crowe. “Equally profound was the experience of working with ancient human remains — individuals who lived, suffered, and died centuries ago — and using modern science to help recover and share their stories. It’s a humbling reminder of our shared humanity across time and a moving testament to the power of science to give voice to those long silent.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_493349" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-493349" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Molar-Tooth-scaled.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-493349" src="https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Molar-Tooth-777x378.jpg" alt="USF Researcher Holding Excavated Human Molar Tooth" srcset="https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Molar-Tooth-777x378.jpg 777w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Molar-Tooth-400x194.jpg 400w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Molar-Tooth-768x373.jpg 768w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Molar-Tooth-1536x747.jpg 1536w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Molar-Tooth-2048x996.jpg 2048w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Molar-Tooth-150x73.jpg 150w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Molar-Tooth-450x219.jpg 450w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/USF-Researcher-Holding-Excavated-Human-Molar-Tooth-1200x583.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-493349" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;A researcher holds a Jerash tooth used to help identify the origin of the first plague. Credit: Greg O’Corry FAU&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While very different from COVID-19, both diseases highlight the enduring link between connectivity and pandemic risk, as well as the reality that some pathogens can never be fully eradicated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’ve been wrestling with plague for a few thousand years, and people still die from it today,” Jiang said. “Like COVID, it continues to evolve, and containment measures evidently can’t get rid of it. We have to be careful, but the threat will never go away.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Building on the Jerash breakthrough, the team is now expanding its research to Venice, Italy, and the Lazaretto Vecchio, a dedicated quarantine island and one of the world’s most significant plague burial sites. More than 1,200 samples from this Black Death-era mass grave are now housed at USF, offering an unprecedented opportunity to study how early public health measures intersected with pathogen evolution, urban vulnerability, and cultural memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference: “Genetic Evidence of Yersinia pestis from the First Pandemic” by Swamy R. Adapa, Karen Hendrix, Aditya Upadhyay, Subhajeet Dutta, Andrea Vianello, Gregory O’Corry-Crowe, Jorge Monroy, Tatiana Ferrer, Elizabeth Remily-Wood, Gloria C. Ferreira, Michael Decker, Robert H. Tykot, Sucheta Tripathy and Rays H. Y. Jiang, 31 July 2025, &lt;i&gt;Genes&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/genes16080926"&gt;DOI: 10.3390/genes16080926&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Never miss a breakthrough: &lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/newsletter/"&gt;Join the SciTechDaily newsletter.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				
		
		
		
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 22:10:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxPSklHY09Id3QwaHY2R1FSY2c1SjZqSjRSczNCZXRjSjdmNjR2TldhZkNDbWhQR01adV9kbUlvbEtEazJ2d241UkVMbC1sQ2NaRlo5Q0phckNFRU9rRlZBNVVMLXRsSU0yX3F1YkRFb1FKU3ZQZjNhLUI0RkVJYlB4TGhMbU9mZ215MjAxZ3BSUWVvaEg2T0dxOFNmZEtodThDYnBENHgtdFp5SWcybzJOMGdzX1k</guid></item><item><title>西尼罗河病毒病例高于正常水平，引发健康警告-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/west-nile-cdc-d0fe355b8351f52b39ca4d39046da9de</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — West Nile virus infections are intense so far this year, with case counts running 40% higher than normal, health officials say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 770 cases, including about 490 severe cases, were reported as of early September, according to Centers for Disease Control and Prevention &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.cdc.gov/west-nile-virus/data-maps/current-year-data.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;data posted this week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. About 550 cases — 350 of them severe — are usually reported by this time of year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials are ramping up warnings to the public, because most cases of the mosquito-borne disease are reported in August and September.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“West Nile virus can be a very serious disease and its presence in mosquitoes remains high right now in Massachusetts,” said the state’s public health commissioner, Dr. Robbie Goldstein, in a statement last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People can protect themselves by wearing long-sleeved shirts and pants when possible, and using an EPA-registered &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/mosquito-repellent-cdc-recommends-e47c0c35ffe49d6f36b39d03f1b95e06"&gt;insect repellent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; when spending time outdoors, health officials say.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;West Nile virus was first reported in the United States in 1999 in New York, and then gradually spread across the country. It &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.cdc.gov/west-nile-virus/data-maps/historic-data.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;peaked&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in 2003, when nearly 10,000 cases were reported. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scientists say many people — perhaps tens of thousands each year — are infected but don’t know it because they have no symptoms, or only mild ones such as headaches, body aches, joint pain, vomiting, diarrhea and rashes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In severe cases, damage to the central nervous system causes inflammation of the brain or spinal cord, and even death.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;In the last decade, health officials have fielded reports of 2,000 cases annually on average, including 1,200 life-threatening neurological illnesses and approximately 120 deaths. Deaths are on pace to be higher this year, CDC officials said, but they declined to discuss specifics, saying mortality statistics are too preliminary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem is not that there are more mosquitoes this year, but rather that a higher proportion of the bugs are carrying the virus, CDC officials said. Mosquito infection rates can be affected by such factors as temperature, rainfall, the amount of insect control going on, and how many nearby birds are infected.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Colorado, which tends to see more West Nile virus, has reported about 150 of the nation’s cases — more than double what other states are reporting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fort Collins is a hot spot. Monitoring last month in an area in the southwest part of the city found that 35 out of every 1,000 female mosquitoes were infected — far higher than the 8 per 1,000 that would be expected for that time of year — said Roxanne Connelly, a CDC entomologist who lives there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s not clear why, but she noted it’s been a wet and warm year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 22:06:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE1pTno4QzNlWmpwTFgzbDJaWFBsQWFHX2dSUy05THA1eGZKYldSQzV4UDBLN013cVlIRnpJUENVQUZYNG9iQlBUb0RDNjQ0VlJwTnhTdFRQb0VjV0plYjN1SEFUekdKN1l4QXdWN01XMmhnT2taenA4a09sVy1TQQ</guid></item><item><title>新的研究揭示了更年期期间人类声音的变化- Northeastern Global News</title><link>https://news.northeastern.edu/2025/09/10/menopause-voice-change-research/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-constrained wp-container-core-post-content-is-layout-575ec271 wp-block-post-content-is-layout-constrained"&gt;






&lt;p&gt;Most conversations about menopause health revolve around things like hot flashes and brain fog, but new research points to another less discussed but no less impactful change to women’s health: voice changes.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;All women undergo menopause, which occurs, on average, around age 52 at the point when menstruation stops occurring. In a comprehensive review of existing literature on menopause, researchers shine a spotlight on how menopausal vocal changes are both less understood and potentially more significant for certain women.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Voice changes during menopause are subtle [and] gradual but for those who use their voice a lot — voice super users — these have massive implications on their daily life and also their profession,” says &lt;a href="https://ai.northeastern.edu/our-people/rupal-patel" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Rupal Patel&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of communication sciences and disorders and director of the Voice of Women Lab at Northeastern University. “Many times the other symptoms of menopause have more attention but voice changes, because they’re subtle and gradual, are not necessarily given the same importance in terms of affecting the individual’s life.”&lt;/p&gt;






&lt;p&gt;During menopause, estrogen levels decrease, which changes tissue in the vocal folds. The end result is women’s voices get deeper and hoarser, and it can even get harder to project the voice.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In reviewing the literature around menopause, Patel and collaborators found that these changes are not well studied and “not necessarily well understood” in part because they are so gradual that most women might not notice them unless someone else draws attention to it. However, for women who use their voice a lot — teachers, reporters or voice actors, for example — these changes have much more of an impact, Patel notes.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://news.northeastern.edu/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Rupal_Patel.jpg?w=1100" alt="Portrait of Rupal Patel." class="wp-image-277502" srcset="https://news.northeastern.edu/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Rupal_Patel.jpg 1400w, https://news.northeastern.edu/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Rupal_Patel.jpg?resize=800,533 800w, https://news.northeastern.edu/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Rupal_Patel.jpg?resize=768,512 768w, https://news.northeastern.edu/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Rupal_Patel.jpg?resize=1100,733 1100w, https://news.northeastern.edu/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Rupal_Patel.jpg?resize=196,130 196w, https://news.northeastern.edu/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Rupal_Patel.jpg?resize=335,223 335w, https://news.northeastern.edu/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Rupal_Patel.jpg?resize=1200,800 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1100px) 100vw, 1100px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;The other symptoms of menopause might get more of the spotlight but vocal changes are worth studying and understanding, says Rupal Patel, a professor of communication sciences and disorders and director of the Voice of Women Lab at Northeastern University. Photo by Ruby Wallau/Northeastern University&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“If you’re a teacher or in any one of these professions that uses the voice a lot, it can actually mean a difference between taking days off of work and being productive or not,” Patel says. “Voice-over actors who are females often complain that they’re no longer desirable voices.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It’s actually a big issue because most of the voice super users, 75% of them are women,” Patel adds. “If you think about teachers, 75% of teachers are women. If you think about voice-over artists, there’s just a high predominance of women.”&lt;/p&gt;






&lt;p&gt;Another reason very little attention has been paid to menopausal vocal changes is that they have historically been conflated with other conditions. As much as Patel and her Voice of Women Lab, or VOxx Lab, are trying to analyze the voice as a marker for certain health conditions, she notes that the human voice is a “sensitive kind of cue.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“If someone’s voice changes, we don’t know if it’s due to these hormonal changes or due to a neurological change,” Patel says. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;However, Patel and her lab aim to fill the knowledge gap around these vocal changes that all women will go through in their lives. New technology, like artificial intelligence, has unlocked the potential to study the human voice in even more subtle ways.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Previously, Patel, through the company she founded, VocaliD, cloned the voices of female voice-over artists with their permission, partially as a way of preempting some of the issues women face later in their careers.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“They knew that people would have less interest in their voice as they aged, and they thought that would be an insurance policy,” Patel says. “If they banked their voice ahead of time, created their synthetic voice, they could still speak as their younger selves with their synthetic voice and then as their voice ages take on other roles.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Finding the gaps that have existed in previous research has spurred new lines of research that Patel and her collaborators are in the early stages of pursuing. They include an examination of how hormone replacement therapy can help improve women’s voices later in life and even a study of how menopausal changes to the oral cavity can trigger sleep apnea in women.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The end goal of all this work, Patel says, is to better understand, and potentially remedy, something that for far too long has been understudied and underdiscussed, despite being a factor in half of the population’s lives.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“How can this be ignored for so long when 100% of women, regardless of whether you’ve had a child or not, are going to go through menopause?” Patel says.&lt;/p&gt;






&lt;div class="recirc-layout has-2-cols alignwide alignwide wp-block-nunews-recirculation-quick-and-dirty" id="recirc-layout__outer-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="recirc-layout__content" id="recirc-layout__inner-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Northeastern Global News</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:40:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE5UT1pGSVFoVHBFUi1yWHlsdkc4OC1zOWcydWN5MVhMMEkzN2lUS3YtN09XUVJwNFdhUWxZbDVESkhTb25MWGQtaVNTdEpydWhieERLNVFhakdPZVNQQXVxRWVuOHViR29qdGI2aUtvLXhyWGtzeFdWczEwRml0QQ</guid></item><item><title>沃尔格林表示，由于加利福尼亚州新冠肺炎发病率飙升，疫苗无需“证明”。- SFGATE</title><link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/walgreens-covid-vaccine-california-21041231.php</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;For weeks, COVID-19 activity has been circulating in California, with &lt;a href="https://skylab.cdph.ca.gov/calwws/" data-link="native" class=""&gt;wastewater &lt;/a&gt;showing high levels of the virus since June. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, hospitalizations are spiking in the state, rising 144% since early July through the end of August, although hospitalization levels are still significantly lower than the COVID-19 spikes California saw in the winter of 2020 and 2021. And while overall levels in the Bay Area are no longer spiking, they are still increasing in most San Francisco test sites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlikely previous years, the Food and Drug Administration has put more limits on who qualifies for the COVID-19 vaccine. Adults under the age of 65 only &lt;a href="https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/covid-19-flu-vaccine-explainer-21033342.php" data-link="native" class=""&gt;qualify for a COVID-19 vaccine&lt;/a&gt; if they have an &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/covid/hcp/clinical-care/underlying-conditions.html" data-link="native" class=""&gt;underlying condition&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a statement to SFGATE, a Walgreens official confirmed that many adults under 65 do not need a prescription if they want the shot. The spokesperson said the COVID-19 vaccine is available for people who qualify, and no extra “proof” is needed if people confirm they have an underlying condition such as diabetes, asthma or depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Patients may self-attest to their qualifying condition—no proof or additional documentation is required,” Walgreens spokesperson Brigid Sweeny told SFGATE in an email. “We encourage anyone with questions about their eligibility or personal risk factors to speak directly with our pharmacists, who are available to provide guidance and support.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new restrictions from the FDA have been &lt;a href="https://publications.aap.org/aapnews/news/33053/AAP-FDA-COVID-vaccine-recommendations-are-deeply" data-link="native" class=""&gt;criticized &lt;/a&gt;by medical groups. These groups, including the&lt;a href="https://www.aafp.org/news/media-center/statements/aafp-announces-fall-immunization-recommendations-reaffirming-commitment-to-vaccine-safety-and-public-health.html" data-link="native" class=""&gt; American Academy of Family Physicians&lt;/a&gt;, recommend all adults get a COVID-19 shot regardless of whether they have an underlying condition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Monica Gandhi, an infectious disease physician at UC San Francisco, said the different advice from the FDA compared with major medical groups is confusing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The issue is that vagaries in the guidance is going to make it more difficult for people to get the vaccine,” Gandhi told SFGATE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SFGATE</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:17:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxQTFdFQ2s3Rlk2dW1EUEpKTGVzcnRnTnV6d3BueHBENUhBN1hLUXFScnM4NzF2U2l4Z2RxMjFaV0JXR3gxMmFRYkhZZnBsNEp6UFlLOS13MDllbi1XRUYtMi1neUtEdEQtV3ZVMWc0NVFBMW5kSU5iMklVMVYwSVBvOG90OFJoOU83MklCOHQyWQ</guid></item><item><title>发现控制饮食冲动的大脑“拨号” -神经科学新闻</title><link>https://neurosciencenews.com/amygdala-bnst-eating-29678/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;Researchers have uncovered a brain circuit in mice that acts as a “dial” for consumption, controlling the urge to eat sweets, fats, salt, and other foods. The circuit links the amygdala to the BNST, a region tied to feeding and reward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stimulating this pathway could drive mice to eat even when full, while suppressing it blocked consumption even in hungry animals. The findings could inspire treatments for eating disorders, cancer-related appetite loss, and obesity by precisely tuning this brain circuit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brain Dial:&lt;/strong&gt; The BNST regulates appetite for sweets, fats, salt, and overall food.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dual Role:&lt;/strong&gt; Stimulating it boosts consumption, while suppressing it curbs appetite.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Medical Potential:&lt;/strong&gt; Could help manage cachexia in chemotherapy or improve weight-loss therapies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Zuckerman Institute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; It’s natural to crave sugar when you feel tired and want a boost of energy. Now scientists at Columbia University’s Zuckerman Institute have linked a brain area in mice to the drive to consume not just sweets, but fats, salt and food. The findings show this area serves as a kind of dial that can amplify or repress consumption. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This discovery, detailed today in &lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt;, may inform novel treatments for both overeating and undereating. For instance, the results suggest that finding ways to modulate this brain circuit may help treat people suffering from the severe loss of appetite and muscle wasting often seen in large numbers of chemotherapy patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-112761"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows a brain surrounded by food." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/09/brain-eating-dial-neuroscience-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Each of those neurons possessed branches that reached into a brain region called the bed nucleus of the stria terminalis (BNST), which prior work found was associated with feeding and responses to rewards. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The relationship between something that stimulates the appetite, such as fat or sugar, and its capacity to drive us to consume it has been an open question in neuroscience,” said Charles S. Zuker, PhD, the study’s corresponding author, a principal investigator at Columbia’s Zuckerman Institute and a Howard Hughes Medical Institute investigator. “This work provides exciting new insights and identifies a brain center that orchestrates a unified control over consummatory behaviors.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Zuker and his colleagues started by analyzing the brain circuit in mice that responds to sweet tastes. Their goal was to explore how a sensation that can stimulate the appetite spurs the urge to consume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists first investigated the amygdala, the brain’s emotion center, which also helps judge whether various sensations feel good or bad. They identified neurons, a type of brain cell, in the central amygdala that were activated by sweetness. Each of those neurons possessed branches that reached into a brain region called the bed nucleus of the stria terminalis (BNST), which prior work found was associated with feeding and responses to rewards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the researchers stimulated neurons connected to the BNST, they showed that mice that had recently fed until they were full could now be driven to continue to consume sweets. Conversely, suppressing the BNST neurons greatly suppressed sweet consumption even in animals that were very hungry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists went on to show that this brain region was associated with the urge to consume not just sweets, but also salt, fat, food and other substances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our discovery far exceeded our expectations,” said Li Wang, PhD, the study’s co-lead author and a postdoctoral fellow in the Zuker lab. “We did not expect this brain region to be so important and involved with such a broad range of consummatory behaviors in such a general way.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists uncovered anatomical connections between the BNST and other parts of the brain that underscore its role in consumption. For example, they found links between the BNST and brain circuits sensing an animal’s internal states, such as the need to eat when hungry or to consume salt when their body’s salt levels become dangerously low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We now have a better understanding of how the brain integrates specific internal needs with sensory signals in order to elicit appropriate consummatory responses,” said José A. Cánovas, PhD, the study’s co-lead author&lt;a href="https://www.pew.org/en/projects/pew-latin-american-fellows/directory-of-latin-fellows/2016/jos--c-novas"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;and a postdoctoral fellow in the Zuker lab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This discovery of a “brain dial” for consumption might one day help cancer patients undergoing chemotherapy, who often experience cachexia, a condition that can lead to a dangerous loss of appetite and weight. When mice were given a chemotherapy drug that can trigger a cachexia-like state, the researchers found that stimulating the BNST could protect them from weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Chemotherapy drugs are amazing in that they can kill cancer, but they also suppress the motivation to eat, which becomes a big problem,” Dr. Wang said. “Maybe stimulating this brain area can help address this issue.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the flip side, the researchers discovered that inhibiting the BNST resulted in substantial weight loss in mice. The scientists also found the weight-loss drug semaglutide (sold under brand names such as Ozempic and Wegovy) targets neurons in the BNST, shedding light on how it may work to help people reduce consumption. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Taking semaglutide can lead to nausea and other negative side effects,” Dr. Cánovas said. “Perhaps a better understanding of the BNST may lead to therapies that help suppress consumption without these effects.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this neuroscience research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#bcd2d9cbcffcc6d592dfd3d0c9d1ded5dd92d9d8c9" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Zuckerman Communications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://zi.columbia.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Zuckerman Institute&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Zuckerman Communications – Zuckerman Institute&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research:&lt;/strong&gt; Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2025.08.021" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;A Brain Center that Controls Consummatory Responses&lt;/a&gt;” by Charles S. Zuker et al. &lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstact&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Brain Center that Controls Consummatory Responses&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The innate attraction to sweet mediates appetitive and consummatory responses. Here, we dissected the circuit driving responses to sweet and showed that amygdala neurons tuned to sweet connect to the bed nucleus of the stria-terminalis (BNST) to promote sweet-evoked consumption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, we demonstrate that the BNST functions as a central hub, transforming appetitive signals into consumption and linking sensory inputs to the internal state, not only for sweet but also for other stimuli such as salt or food, to flexibly regulate consummatory behaviors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using single-cell functional imaging, we show that ensemble activity in the BNST encodes stimulus identity and the animal’s internal state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, we demonstrate that manipulating BNST activity can bidirectionally transform consummatory responses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Together, these findings illustrate how the internal state modulates sensory responses, characterize a general brain dial for consumption, and provide fresh insights into sites of action of GLP1R agonists and a strategy to help promote weight gain in pathological states.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:23:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZ0FVX3lxTE8xTzBseFpjRnFWSHNQVF9wYVhfSk5iclkwRzNkTC1acWg5NElyRzh0WnY4MlZTakNFTGczN3BWUkJobkhvYkR0REdFZVQ0WlNnMGtLQTNWSmY1VFpKTzBOVG02bWxfZTg</guid></item><item><title>SAMHSA战略重点- SAMHSA (.gov)</title><link>https://www.samhsa.gov/about/strategic-priorities</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p&gt;  The specified URL cannot be found. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SAMHSA (.gov)</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:22:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiXkFVX3lxTFBqSm42ejlCQVl6WF9kN2FTbERLclkyTEJjODB2X1p6bXFMYS1tVGlNaFJObHlZWU9vellBd1ZUNVI3VVVmY3U2b21rdDgxU0hUb2dGU0xoMlRyWkZBNnc</guid></item><item><title>美国死亡率降至2020年以来的最低水平， COVID不再是主要原因- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/us-death-rate-2024-covid-cdc/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The mortality rate in the United States declined by 3.8% in 2024, and COVID-19 was no longer among the 10 leading causes of death, according to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/data/vsrr/vsrr039.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;a federal report&lt;/a&gt; released Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using provisional death certificate data, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention's National Center for Health Statistics estimates there were 3,072,039 deaths last year, which equates to about 722 deaths per 100,000 people compared to 750.5 per 100,000 in 2023. This is the lowest death rate since 2020, the authors of the report note.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And for the first time since 2020, COVID-19 was not one of the 10 leading causes of death. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The top three causes of death were heart disease with 683,037 deaths, cancer with 619,812 and unintentional injury with 196,488. The other leading causes were stroke, chronic lower respiratory disease, Alzheimer's disease, diabetes, kidney disease, chronic liver disease and cirrhosis, and suicide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the overall death rate decline, deaths for both heart disease and cancer, the two leading causes, increased from 2023. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Broken down by demographics, death rates were highest for males, older adults and Black people, the data shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings are limited due to the use of provisional data, but the estimates still give "researchers and policymakers an early signal about shifts in mortality trends," the authors said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While heart disease is the leading cause of death in the U.S., &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/heart-disease-risk-factors/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;a survey from the Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; earlier this year found many Americans are unaware of the &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/video/watch-out-for-these-top-heart-disease-risk-factors/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;risk factors&lt;/a&gt;, including things like tobacco use and air pollution. And the risk doesn't appear to be slowing anytime soon — &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/61-percent-us-adults-cardiovascular-disease-2050-american-heart-association/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;a 2024 report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; from the American Heart Association projected more than six in 10 U.S. adults, about 61%, will have some type of cardiovascular disease by 2050.&lt;/p&gt;

      

                    
        
      
        
    

    &lt;aside class="component list recirculation component--type-recirculation component--type-recirculation-collection"&gt;
                    
                                            
        &lt;div class="component__heading-wrapper"&gt;
          &lt;h3 class="component__title"&gt;Coronavirus Pandemic
                          &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/feature/coronavirus/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="component__view-more component__view-more--lg" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                More
                &lt;svg viewbox="0 0 32 32" class="icon__caret-right" aria-hidden="true"&gt;
                  &lt;use xlink:href="#icon-caret-down"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                &lt;/svg&gt;
              &lt;/a&gt;
                      &lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;

        
                    &lt;/aside&gt;



    
      
    
  

          
  
        
      &lt;div class="content-author"&gt;
      &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/team/sara-moniuszko/" class="content-author__name" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Sara  Moniuszko&lt;/a&gt;

      &lt;div class="content-author__bio"&gt;
        &lt;div class="content-author__full-information"&gt;
          &lt;p class="content-author__text"&gt;Sara Moniuszko is a health and lifestyle reporter at CBSNews.com. Previously, she wrote for USA Today, where she was selected to help launch the newspaper's wellness vertical. She now covers breaking and trending news for CBS News' HealthWatch.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/section&gt;

  
  

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:21:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE9kMGRvNmlKVjhxeGpERzAxYlFYSzBldTQwaEZ4aFdZX1NXQnRCby1oNktSRWZOelJnUm95LS16R1R2cXh4ODg2NjQxbUN0MXFUR3ZWaFZaZkZkeFRKbkVvLVNpWVZEWnNUaGfSAW9BVV95cUxOQm42ZVNnT0hJeVJORjFZN2paSFluOXAyNXhITWZ4T29zYktEMUZvMDhOTTZUZFlTWWpNUmo2VHZJUTd5SU5lVVE3OW5XTFNhc21FX3lhWUV0SlZUOXUxM1ZaSEdnNFVlM2lrdmZQR28</guid></item><item><title>宾夕法尼亚大学的研究人员发现杀死休眠的“睡眠”乳腺癌细胞可以防止复发- WHYY</title><link>https://whyy.org/articles/sleeper-dormant-breast-cancer-cells/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="flexible-content-container wysiwyg-styles"&gt;
                    &lt;h2&gt;Reducing anxiety and providing reassurance for patients&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team at Penn is currently enrolling patients in &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/research/participate/clinical-trials-search/v?id=NCI-2021-12420"&gt;two ongoing&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/research/participate/clinical-trials-search/v?id=NCI-2021-06208"&gt;large-scale studies&lt;/a&gt; that could help support their findings. Trial sites are located across the country, including &lt;a href="https://www.med.upenn.edu/acc-cancer-research/breast-cancer-tce/"&gt;at the University of Pennsylvania&lt;/a&gt; in Philadelphia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ultimate goal, Chodosh said, is to not only identify and treat those who are at a higher risk of recurrence, but to be able to offer reassurance to survivors who don’t have dormant cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The goal would be to get a test that’s so good that, if you’re negative with this test, you could confidently say your risk of recurring is extremely low over the course of your lifetime,” he said. “That would have such a big benefit.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers are also following breast cancer survivors who don’t ever test positive for dormant cancer cells in order to compare their long-term survival outcomes to those who get treated for sleeper cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some clinicians and experts were worried about whether participation in these kinds of trials would cause more distress in survivors, DiMichele said. But her team studied that, too, and found it to be the opposite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Regardless of the answer, whether the patient found out they were positive or negative, overall their anxiety went down,” she said. “And we think it’s because, and what patients tell us is, ‘Look, at least I’m doing something.’ It was the not doing something, not knowing, that was so anxiety-provoking.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the years, LaScala has become more involved in research efforts and now serves as a patient advocate on research boards at Penn, where she can help shape studies and participant guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Among breast cancer survivors, she said there has always been passion and an eagerness for &lt;a href="https://whyy.org/articles/breast-density-cancer-mammogram-counseling/"&gt;advancing testing&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/breast-cancer/treatment.html"&gt;treatment options&lt;/a&gt; for everyone — survivors, people actively battling disease and those who may one day get a diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s so energizing,” LaScala said. “To be around the research and to be able to participate … it’s incredible.”&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WHYY</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:03:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE05M0YxNG9fYk5qVVVacFhfUmZuNlBHZ1Z1aVd2QjBPdW9yZEhkajVITEpiLW5DVFkxRXQ5MWczYWVvM3YzRkI4enpKRWRjcVBYRmhmeG5BaUk3eC1DdlBCbWFjeURDVUFPd3lXVGNIaw</guid></item><item><title>莱姆病的未经批准的测试和替代疗法正在增殖- PBS</title><link>https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/unapproved-tests-and-alternative-treatments-for-lyme-disease-are-proliferating</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-text"&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Lyme disease can cause serious harm, but so can bogus tests and treatments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The complexity of diagnosing the tick-borne disease has given rise to an entire industry of unapproved tests and unproven alternative treatments that experts say should be avoided, including lasers, herbal remedies and electromagnets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It really is a buyer-beware situation,” said Dr. Robert Smith, a Lyme specialist at MaineHealth Institute for Research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no one-size-fits-all approach to diagnosing Lyme. Doctors use a combination of visual clues, information reported by their patients and the standard medical test, which has a number of limitations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When patients show the classic symptoms — including a bull’s eye rash, fever and fatigue — a short course of antibiotics usually resolves them. But a subset of patients will go on to experience months or even years of arthritis, pain and fatigue — poorly understood symptoms that overlap with a number of other medical conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That has left an opening for so-called “nonstandard” Lyme tests and treatments. Interest in those products has been amplified by influencers and a growing list of celebrities attributing various health problems to the disease, most recently Justin Timberlake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That might lead patients to spend hundreds or thousands of dollars on bogus tests, which aren’t covered by insurance, followed by unapproved treatments that may do more harm than good. And it’s possible some of them may not have had Lyme at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a recent consensus report from the National Academies of Sciences, Engineering, and Medicine, Smith and other experts called for more funding and research into the chronic symptoms experienced by some Lyme patients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The key thing is that these people are suffering and we need to come up with strategies to alleviate that suffering, whatever the trigger was,” Smith said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the same time, Smith and his colleagues warn that “profiteering entities” are pushing Lyme products that are “costly, may not work and may cause harm.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s a look at the established approach for testing and treating Lyme and how to spot unproven alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The standard Lyme test comes with limits&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First identified 50 years ago, Lyme disease takes its name from the Connecticut town where the earliest cases were diagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The challenge of diagnosing it begins with the standard laboratory test, which comes with a number of caveats that must be carefully weighed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bacteria that causes Lyme, carried by certain ticks in the Northeast and Midwest, doesn’t circulate throughout the body. Often it stays in the skin near the tick bite, making it hard to detect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead, Lyme tests look for antibodies, proteins that help fight off foreign invaders, which usually only appear in the blood several weeks after an infection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WATCH: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/show/what-more-can-be-done-to-treat-lyme-disease-and-its-potential-long-term-effects"&gt;What more can be done to treat Lyme disease and its potential long-term effects&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s the best approach available, but experts acknowledge its shortcomings: If the test is given too early it will come back negative because antibodies haven’t yet appeared.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s one of the problems,” Smith says. “We can’t say for sure in the first couple of weeks that it’s Lyme disease or not based on these tests.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, these antibodies continue to circulate in the blood long after the infection. That means the test can return a positive result years or even decades later — making it difficult to distinguish between a new case and an old one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Medical guidelines deal with this ambiguity by recommending doctors diagnose and start antibiotics in all patients who have the signature bull’s eye rash associated with Lyme. But as many as 30% of those infected never get the rash, causing further uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Unproven options for testing are plentiful&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The limitations of the approved test has opened the door to alternative tests, ranging from over-the-counter kits to specialty laboratories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The more expensive tests are often ordered by self-described “Lyme literate” physicians and health providers, who may have backgrounds in fields unrelated to infectious disease, like homeopathy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spotting unproven Lyme tests is relatively easy, since only antibody blood tests are approved by the Food and Drug Administration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any Lyme test available for sale at a drugstore or website is unapproved, says Andrea Love, a microbiologist and director of the American Lyme Disease Foundation. Another red flag is the use of saliva, urine or other bodily fluids besides blood to detect Lyme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When you see these other tests appear on the market, it’s very likely that they’re not accurate and haven’t done their due diligence, which should make people skeptical” Love says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Patients will bear most of the costs for unapproved tests, which may provide inaccurate information and derail a diagnosis for other conditions that are sometimes mistaken for Lyme, such as rheumatoid arthritis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While acceptance of post-treatment Lyme is growing, Love and some other experts recommend caution when approaching the topic. Studies estimate that 10% to 20% of people treated for Lyme will have ongoing symptoms that can’t be clearly explained. But she and others point to startlingly high numbers of people reporting such problems in regions that have no documented history of Lyme, such as Australia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The sheer number of people who believe they have these post-treatment Lyme symptoms is orders of magnitude higher than what you would expect among people who legitimately have Lyme,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Serious risks with alternative Lyme treatments&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the downsides of ineffective Lyme tests are considerable, experts say they are often the gateway to even riskier therapies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A recent medical paper documented nearly 120 clinics across the U.S. offering unproven Lyme treatments, some with consultation fees as high as $3,000.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treatments include electrical stimulation, “ozone-based therapy” and hyperbaric oxygen therapy, procedures that aren’t covered by insurance and can carry price tags as high as $6,000.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Love and other doctors say the most worrisome approach involves long-term intravenous use of antibiotics — sometimes multiple drugs for years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While antibiotics are effective for quickly killing Lyme bacteria, multiple large studies have shown no benefits to their long-term use for chronic Lyme symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smith and other experts have reported cases of patients who spent years getting regular antibiotic infusions, only to develop life-threatening gut infections after the drugs killed off healthy bacteria needed to support the digestive tract.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There is clearly harm being done to people who are suffering and who, out of desperation, take on these great expenses or can be harmed by treatments that are not proven effective,” Smith said.&lt;/p&gt;

                                            &lt;div class="inline-invite inline-invite-type__funding inline-invite-style__default"&gt;
        
                    &lt;div class="inline-invite-funding__box"&gt;
                &lt;figure class="invite__logo"&gt;
                    &lt;svg class="svg"&gt;&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#pbs-newshour-horiz-refresh"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
                &lt;/figure&gt;
                &lt;p class="invite_heading"&gt;
                    We're not going anywhere.
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p class="invite_body"&gt;
                    Stand up for truly independent, trusted news that you can count on!
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://give.newshour.org/page/85597/donate/1?ea.tracking.id=nh_july_2025_rescission_article&amp;amp;supporter.appealCode=N2507QW07000AA" class="donation-link ga-click-funding ga-click-ender-funding"&gt;
                    &lt;button class="donate-button"&gt;Donate now&lt;/button&gt;
                    &lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="#000000" class="bi bi-arrow-right-short" version="1.1" id="svg1" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:svg="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;
                    &lt;defs id="defs1"&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;
                    &lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" d="M4 8a.5.5 0 0 1 .5-.5h5.793L8.146 5.354a.5.5 0 1 1 .708-.708l3 3a.5.5 0 0 1 0 .708l-3 3a.5.5 0 0 1-.708-.708L10.293 8.5H4.5A.5.5 0 0 1 4 8z" id="path1"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
                    &lt;/svg&gt;
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;


                                    &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PBS</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:48:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxNeTRIMTlRM0lEVE9DRXVQS2JjSi01VDZPNG5ER3I4Z2xzVFpDVDE0X2IzSVk4QVNHcHBLa1dzOXRqcXFtZ29Mek1Hak1Ndi1kOE5WdXpaX3ExaVdSMWlZYXc2N3N2TXpENXhNUGdGUnFlaU53VGR4MWJNSHdDVFdBN3hPazdzaXJJeGZoNFFVSUtnZkhRTEUtZkFmLUZKVlVweHRNNExuRWZyYTc3TFFkWVo2R0vSAboBQVVfeXFMUFNvZzk0MVRrc2VEenlldkhEazkxVWMwd2JRaGlqQmlmN3d0RVdiRk9MRjJVSlNXeVc1ektuNlRNOU9nb0VWYnVNeV9RNjllcGtDSFM3bDQwNzBqOFlXWV9kOEVJV3gyNFFNTE5xeDFtTFZhLUpXaWlVREowalh4RmZIcjRLamlOUVRTX0h1N3RLS1k5YUZxRFZWWURGZnEydXdRdHdSS2lGN0RpS0lJcGw3M2dhTmpHTkJ3</guid></item><item><title>新泽西州成为扩大COVID-19疫苗接种的最新州- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/new-jersey-latest-state-expand-access-covid-19/story?id=125444856</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;New Jersey has become the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.nj.gov/health/news/2025/approved/20250909a.shtml" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;latest state to sign orders&lt;/a&gt; expanding access to COVID-19 vaccines, breaking with guidance from federal health agencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The state Department of Health issued an executive directive on Tuesday allowing anyone aged six months or older to receive an updated COVID-19 vaccine, in time for the upcoming respiratory virus season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The agency issued a separate order directing pharmacists to administer COVID-19 vaccines without a prescription to those who are three years and older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"At a time when COVID-19 cases are increasing across the country and as part of my Administration's dedication to evidence-based public health action, I am committed to ensuring everyone in New Jersey who wants to receive a COVID-19 vaccination can receive a dose this fall from trusted health professionals," Gov. Phil Murphy said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In a statement to ABC News, Andrew Nixon, spokesperson for the Department of Health and Human Services (HHS), said, "Democrat-run states that pushed unscientific school lockdowns, toddler mask mandates, and draconian vaccine passports during the COVID era completely eroded the American people's trust in public health agencies."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;He added that the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention's (CDC) vaccine advisory committee "remains the scientific body guiding immunization recommendations in this country, and HHS will ensure policy is based on rigorous evidence and Gold Standard Science, not the failed politics of the pandemic."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;In this Jan. 9, 2024, file photo, New Jersey Governor Phil Murphy delivers his State of the State address to a joint session of the Legislature at the Statehouse in Trenton, N.J.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Matt Rourke/AP, FILE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;It comes two weeks after the Food and Drug Administration &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/fda-approves-updated-covid-vaccines-restrictions-receive/story?id=125032817" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;approved updated COVID-19 vaccines&lt;/a&gt; with restrictions. The vaccines were approved for use in all adults aged 65 and older and younger Americans with at least one underlying condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;New Jersey health officials said in a press release that the changes to COVID-19 vaccine access, announced by HHS Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. on &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://x.com/SecKennedy/status/1960742897201872969" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;social media&lt;/a&gt;, "bypassed the normal scientific review process, creating confusion and uncertainty, especially because they conflicted with previous CDC recommendations."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Following the FDA's approval, CVS, the nation's largest pharmacy chain, said it would continue to offer COVID-19 vaccines for those who fall under the new FDA authorization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;But in another 13 states, people will need a prescription to get a COVID shot, even if they are older or high-risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Walgreens, another large pharmacy chain, said it would give shots where it was legally able to do so, but didn't specify which states would have which rules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In response, states, including New York and Minnesota, issued executive orders in an effort to protect vaccine access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz issued an &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://content.govdelivery.com/attachments/MNGOV/2025/09/08/file_attachments/3381381/Executive%20Order%2025-09.pdf" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;executive order&lt;/a&gt; directing the state epidemiologist to issue a standing order – a written protocol allowing health care professionals to perform specific tasks or provide certain treatments for the COVID-19 vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Walz's office said in a &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://mn.gov/governor/newsroom/press-releases/#/detail/appId/1/id/704332" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; that this will "provide greater flexibility for health care providers and pharmacists to provide the vaccine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;New York's &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.governor.ny.gov/executive-order/no-52-declaring-disaster-state-new-york-due-federal-actions-related-vaccine-access" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;order&lt;/a&gt; allows physicians and nurse practitioners to issue patient-specific or non-patient-specific orders to pharmacists to administer COVID-19 vaccines among patients aged three and older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;A pharmacy manager administers a patient with a COVID-19 vaccine at a CVS Pharmacy in Miami, Sept. 9, 2025.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Rebecca Blackwell/AP&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The order also expands permits pharmacists to prescribe COVID-19 vaccines themselves for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"I promised New Yorkers that their family would be my fight. In the absence of federal leadership, we must do everything we can to ensure that New Yorkers have access to the vaccines and preventative healthcare they have come to rely on," Gov. Kathy Hochul said in a &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.governor.ny.gov/news/governor-hochul-signs-executive-order-expanding-access-vaccines-amid-uncertainty-washington" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;statement.&lt;/a&gt; "By signing this executive order, we are sending a clear message that when Washington Republicans play politics with public health, New Yorkers can still get the care they need, close to home, from trusted providers in their own communities."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Meanwhile, states on the West Coast and several on the East Coast are forming geographic coalitions to offer their own consistent vaccine guidelines, which they say are backed by evidence and informed by major national medical groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;ABC News' Cheyenne Haslett contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxNTjV3T3RZanNNX1B5a1VMNGpmaWxUczZfN0Y4bF8xTkpjMjU4T0s0VmhMM0g2VmZaXzFfZW1qQXNkakxUcndVMlNQLVZXakVNdDJLdDlkTW14NkhXenFRcEpfODExSXE0UVB2MTlRY0ViQ2RyaWVLWU1RRjNWb2M1RElycGJsZGFOU01uTVg2WXNCeGxvMGZRLVhDVdIBoAFBVV95cUxQelZNQmVXTWI2eFkxM0VDVEh2aDBWMjJEN2dJdkRUSjI3LVRENFJEZWFZNGI0d0w1UnFMbWFteHI1aURCUXFyR3RfUTNvWXlFckkxOTQ2d21SZlllYUNsajUyZjFyTkRxV2ZrWDhfVDB3b1Y1ekhhNFhaLWVZa2toNU90MFMxNm8tblhGTkQ3VFRxQWV5dnlEZ2swOFVwVUFt</guid></item><item><title>研究人员说， “接吻虫”疾病现在在美国流行。您需要了解的信息。- KUSA.com</title><link>https://www.9news.com/article/news/nation-world/kissing-bug-disease-chagas-disease-now-endemic-in-us-researchers-say/507-6557279f-b15b-434c-b2be-2bc128d9e3fd</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Access Denied&lt;/h1&gt;
 
You don't have permission to access "http://www.9news.com/article/news/nation-world/kissing-bug-disease-chagas-disease-now-endemic-in-us-researchers-say/507-6557279f-b15b-434c-b2be-2bc128d9e3fd" on this server.&lt;p&gt;
Reference #18.1db74d68.1757546809.f23e31ec
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://errors.edgesuite.net/18.1db74d68.1757546809.f23e31ec&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KUSA.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:37:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7gFBVV95cUxNVmNSRVVsalFIVVZFbGFFM0Y4WldTYzF3NHhuX2YtTGUyUk84X2UwaHRIMjA5RlRveWtzWU5fcm5aWDBGdTF4SmNuWlpUYXlUdGlTRlhpQl8zUS1NWXRzUnFTTUxPdHRmZno5NklHeEtVOXktN0IyaHZuTTVrY0tmeGVBZkJKNzRyaklEclFIdTRhVVFBVF83TlIwbEYzSjMwZDdZUDM4dlhZVFR3QkthVXhVMm5EOTFBS1RjaGdvd2JwLVZyUmZTdDkwa1QtYldSei1sSFpHN1dhTUFhb3c4RmNqa2NxQzhvbGQxekF3</guid></item></channel></rss>