<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>数千年来一直有效的草药背后的科学-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2026/01/13/ginger-nausea-pregnancy-chemotherapy/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DXZIJNPLVZAQZEORGGGQSSUPN4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Does ginger really help an upset stomach?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:31:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxON3FsdlZnd3pGeDhqemdkbVVNUHdtSE40U0VTbG95bHA0bGtKVWJ1UWlCLUFMVzJSc29IN1E0d1Nfa2xhT01uRVRiWWVPSTRKQzliVUJXZy04UHNodEp2NmVjWTVERzNOYlROdGo5bE5yUndmbjUwWkFtYTNmSFJ0SXk5UER4TmFnZEItVlBJY3hCdw</guid></item><item><title>意见|不要效仿特朗普的阿司匹林榜样-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2026/01/13/aspirin-recommendations-trump-heart-attack-stroke/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KHVPTF7YN5HFNFGD7OHN3UQVKM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;President Donald Trump, in a &lt;a href="https://www.wsj.com/us-news/as-signs-of-aging-emerge-trump-responds-with-defiance-769c5dcd"&gt;wide-ranging interview&lt;/a&gt; with The Wall Street Journal  earlier this month, revealed that he takes a high-dose aspirin pill every day despite his doctors encouraging him to switch to a lower dose. “They say aspirin is good for thinning out the blood, and I don’t want thick blood pouring through my heart,” he said. “I want nice, thin blood pouring through my heart.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:31:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQUHJmTTRINTZVS2pJOGk3cVVDMF8yaUtYV0hTZmF1SmVPRktFYzN0Y0p3MkdJZVVCV1Z1bnFqYVFTZE1hNTRVVGF4dTNwcTF3cktJM2VBWUNyWWgxQnY5TnpEWWtsRVJpZUNJM05TS3hyNkJ3eXA0cENBWXFvVGdSSEZsaFB3Z00wMXVhR2RXbi1mejBRZWgzajJOUkRra1B0YVVJ</guid></item><item><title>“在某些时候，没有它你无法呼吸” ：鼻腔喷雾器-《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/at-some-point-you-cant-breathe-without-it-the-nasal-spray-trap/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-content" class="article-content entry-content"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BERLIN — Decongestant nasal sprays can save you from a restless night when a cold clogs up your nose, but pharmacists warn this aid can be a slippery slope. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The leaflet that comes with it will – if you read it – tell you that a decongestant spray should not be used for longer than seven days in a row.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pharmacist Alexander Schmitz advises even more caution. He said anyone with a blocked nose should give it up after four to five days and use a moisturizing seawater-based spray instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reason is that the nasal mucosa quickly adapts to decongestant active ingredients, which cause the blood vessels in the lining to constrict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“At some point you can’t breathe without the spray, so you have to make sure you always have it with you,” says Schmitz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pharmacist said he repeatedly encounters people who have developed a nasal spray dependency. Coming off it can be hard, he says. “After all, everyone wants to be able to breathe.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using a nasal spray after your cold has gone also has other unwanted effects. Over time, decongestant sprays dry out the nasal mucosa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This not only risks bleeding, but also greater susceptibility to infection, because pathogens can penetrate more easily,” Schmitz explains. Important protective functions of the nose then work only to a limited extent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to wean the nasal lining off decongestant sprays? The classic tip is to switch first to a children’s version, which contains less active ingredient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once the nose has adjusted to the lower dose, the next step is to switch to a seawater nasal spray that contains no active ingredient at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This plan does not always work. “Many have had this adaptation for years. Then those are steps that are too big,” said Schmitz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In that case he advised seeking help at a pharmacy. “We can dilute the nasal spray. Then you wean yourself off in really tiny steps until you eventually reach 0.0%, that is the seawater nasal spray.” How long this takes depends on the person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike with decongestant sprays, seawater sprays don’t bring the risk of the nasal lining becoming dependent, since these simply have a moisturizing effect.&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;p id="userMessagingIn-story"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        
&lt;p&gt;©2026 dpa GmbH. Distributed by &lt;a href="https://tribunecontentagency.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Tribune Content Agency, LLC.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxNXzlyS25HOEJRUEZReDJUZmNvbmI3MkF4bXYzbGRlU3gwdlRESFJwMnpBanl3NThSWG9ta21DblVNdmVsazFGRG5xQW9zSEIzN20yYk9XbEVOdFZSMWhNWnJMWFBxYTUyRWtZZXIxdXVTYjBsZG14RnlfdEFpMloyZW14NFktU0dhNDkyeGx4UnZaTGU5cnNiVllLRXFEd2dVSng4aEc2YUM</guid></item><item><title>癌症抗争的一个新里程碑：十分之七的患者现在可以存活五年以上- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/cancer-survival-rate-five-years-7-in-10-patients-rcna253089</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-517706" class="body-graf"&gt;The U.S. has reached a watershed moment in the fight against cancer: Seven in 10 people now survive five years or more after diagnosis, according to the latest annual report from the American Cancer Society. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7cd1ea" class="body-graf"&gt;That’s a big improvement since the 1970s, when only half of those diagnosed lived at least five years. In the mid-1990s, the rate was 63%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-92f642" class="body-graf"&gt;The 70% figure is based on diagnoses from 2015 to 2021. The findings were published Tuesday in the American Cancer Society’s medical journal, CA: A Cancer Journal for Clinicians.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-6b3fae" class="body-graf"&gt;Five years is the most common benchmark for measuring cancer survival, since the risk of certain cancers’ recurring declines significantly if the cancers haven’t come back within that time.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3a09bc" class="body-graf"&gt;Thanks to &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/cancer-patients-immunotherapy-may-way-skip-surgery-chemo-rcna203038" target="_blank"&gt;improved treatment options&lt;/a&gt; over the last decade, many cancers have gone from death sentences to chronic diseases, according to the report’s lead author, Rebecca Siegel, the American Cancer Society’s senior scientific director of surveillance research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a649fa" class="body-graf"&gt;“It takes decades for research to understand and develop these more effective treatments, and now we’re seeing the fruits of those investments,” Siegel said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7cd0ff" class="body-graf"&gt;The report estimates that 4.8 million cancer deaths were prevented from 1991 to 2023, largely because of better treatments, earlier detection methods and reductions in smoking.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-86dfd3" class="body-graf"&gt;Siegel said scientists have a greater understanding of &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/fat-cells-breast-cancer-tumors-triple-negative-risk-overweight-rcna225598" target="_blank"&gt;how cancer develops and spreads&lt;/a&gt;, allowing them to engineer the immune system to stop or slow cancer growth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d185f9" class="body-graf"&gt;She highlighted immunotherapies as one of the biggest advances — the treatments help the immune system find and attack cancer cells. Immunotherapy has been “game changing” for myeloma, Siegel said. The five-year survival rate for the blood cancer, which is twice as common among Black people as in white people in the U.S., rose to 62% from 32% in the mid-1990s. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-475727" class="body-graf"&gt;Targeted therapy, which targets specific genes or proteins that help cancer cells grow, has been &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/cancer-fighting-antibodies-inject-chemo-directly-tumor-cells-upping-ef-rcna153773" target="_blank"&gt;another major advancement&lt;/a&gt;, as such treatments cause less damage to healthy cells and come with fewer side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3f51dc" class="body-graf"&gt;“Staying on treatment longer allows patients to live longer, and these less toxic treatments allow more sequences of therapy,” said Dr. Christopher Flowers, head of cancer medicine at MD Anderson Cancer Center in Houston, who wasn’t involved in the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-6c3e2c" class="body-graf"&gt;Flowers said targeted therapies and immunotherapies have improved survival outcomes for lung cancer, which kills more people than any other cancer in the U.S. The five-year survival rate for regional lung cancer — which is found in the lung and nearby structures or lymph nodes — is now 37%, up from 20% in the mid-1990s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-73f5d7" class="body-graf"&gt;However, further progress could be made by &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/ultra-processed-foods-linked-increased-risk-precancerous-polyps-study-rcna243574" target="_blank"&gt;addressing major risk factors for cancer&lt;/a&gt;, said Dr. Clark Gamblin, a gastrointestinal surgeon at the Huntsman Cancer Institute and chief of surgical oncology at the University of Utah.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-043a73" class="body-graf"&gt;“Our country has an epidemic of obesity, and cancers follow that,” said Gamblin, who wasn’t involved in the report. “So we’re not winning on every front.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0edb7c" class="body-graf"&gt;Colorectal cancer rates are &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/cancer-rates-rising-young-people-deaths-diagnosis-rcna233805" target="_blank"&gt;rising in people under age 50&lt;/a&gt;, and overall breast cancer rates are &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/cancer-cases-increasing-women-declining-men-report-rcna187586" target="_blank"&gt;rising among women&lt;/a&gt;. Obesity can be a risk factor for both cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-081f56" class="body-graf"&gt;Overall, the American Cancer Society estimates there will be more than 626,000 cancer deaths and more than 2.1 million newly diagnosed cases in the U.S. this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-91112f" class="body-graf"&gt;Siegel said she is concerned about scientists’ ability to study new methods of prevention, detection and treatment, given recent cuts to cancer research by the Trump administration. An &lt;a href="https://www.sanders.senate.gov/wp-content/uploads/HELP-Committee-Minority-Report-Trumps-War-on-Science.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;analysis from Democrats&lt;/a&gt; on the Senate Health, Education, Labor, and Pensions Committee found a 31% decline in cancer research grant funding in the first three months of 2025, compared with the same period in 2024. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-2a6713" class="body-graf"&gt;“Other threats to progress are the enormous gap that we see in the cancer burden in people of color, specifically Native American people and Black people,” Siegel said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f3fb2f" class="body-graf"&gt;The same populations are among the most affected by &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/congress-leaves-town-2026-no-health-care-deal-forcing-premium-hikes-rcna249817" target="_blank"&gt;the expiration of Affordable Care Act insurance subsidies&lt;/a&gt;, which could reduce access to cancer drugs, Siegel said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e8eb17" class="body-graf"&gt;Disruptions to cancer screening during the Covid pandemic could also have further effects, including late-stage diagnoses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-223f85" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“The screening for [asymptomatic] cancer largely stopped during that time period, and I don’t know that we’ve seen the tail of that yet,” Gamblin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxPaGtvQlhiUTF1SEF2TUZwdGQ2TkhnRFBwU3B1dTladFJrdzNwVFpmdldhWGNReGNFRDlZeHdwVWp0MFN5RVk1UkZqZ3hIb2VjN3RmNldwOW1yY0thZ1dRRXRKVElhbEotMWpjVXBkc0Z6VTQ5ZGlrOEpJNEtveTNudWVDNkRLa2xZQnBmd2tzbzhDQVl0cXNheTNDalNydw</guid></item><item><title>根据一位研究简单习惯如何预防疾病的营养师的说法， 3种健康食品交换可以保护您的心脏- Business Insider</title><link>https://www.businessinsider.com/heart-healthy-food-swaps-dietitian-studies-simple-habits-prevent-disease-2026-1</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="post-body-content post-story-body-content" data-component-type="post-body-content" data-load-strategy="exclude" data-track-content="" data-post-type="story" data-track-marfeel="post-body-content"&gt;
            
                &lt;p&gt;A nutrition researcher and dietitian who studies &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/essential-healthy-habits-for-your-twenties-thirties-longevity-advice-2023-12" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;how simple habits&lt;/a&gt; can protect our hearts shared three simple food swaps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardiovascular disease is the No. 1 cause of death in the US, but research has found that eating a &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/mediterranean-diet-best-healthy-eating-longevity-rankings-2025-1" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Mediterranean-style diet&lt;/a&gt; and being physically active can help lower the risk. The American Heart Association's dietary guidelines recommend prioritizing fresh produce, whole grains, lean proteins such as fish, and limiting &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/scientists-uncover-processed-foods-fuel-colon-cancer-how-offset-damage-2024-12" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;ultra-processed foods&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;and refined sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That may sound like a lot, but Matthew Landry told Business Insider  that you don't necessarily need to overhaul your diet to improve your heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Landy, an assistant professor at the University of California, Irvine, suggested considering: "how can we make simple swaps with our diet? How can we engage in more physical activity, and do very simple things that all add up to help prevent a heart attack later?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are his three suggestions:&lt;/p&gt;
              
            
              
            &lt;h2 id="f1426ea8-76ac-4bb4-9967-f82aaa75bb88" data-toc-id="f1426ea8-76ac-4bb4-9967-f82aaa75bb88"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1) Switch from cooking with butter to olive oil&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Olive oil contains heart-healthy fats.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Lazy_Bear/Getty Images
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Landry's first swap relates to the type of fat used for cooking. He suggests switching butter or lard for heart-healthy fats like olive oil or avocado oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We're not necessarily changing the food, we're just changing how we're sometimes preparing it," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Animal products and &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/government-eat-more-butter-full-fat-milk-dietary-guidelines-dairy-2026-1" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;full-fat dairy products&lt;/a&gt; like beef tallow, butter, and cream contain saturated fat, which can drive up our LDL or "bad cholesterol levels, Landry said. If a person has too much LDL cholesterol in their blood, it can form a sticky plaque in their arteries, putting them at greater risk of heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We need fat as part of a balanced diet, but unsaturated fats, found in foods such as avocados, fatty fish, nuts, and olive oil, don't raise our LDL cholesterol nearly as much as saturated fat, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="92ff2c6c-ba8f-4601-94f3-06f8a5c0fe3b" data-toc-id="92ff2c6c-ba8f-4601-94f3-06f8a5c0fe3b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2) Switch from red meat to poultry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Red and processed meats are linked to a higher risk of cardiovascular disease.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Johner Images/Getty Images
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;There's one finding that keeps cropping up in Landry's research: reducing red meat consumption lowers the risk of cardiovascular disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Landry worked on a 2023 study in which 22 pairs of identical twins were assigned either a vegan or an omnivorous diet for eight weeks. It was the focus of a Netflix documentary titled "You Are What You Eat: A Twin Experiment."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the end of the study, the &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/omnivore-vs-vegan-diet-vegan-lost-more-weight-lower-cholesterol-2024-1" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;vegan twins&lt;/a&gt; had lower LDL cholesterol and insulin levels, and had lost more weight, another risk factor for cardiovascular disease, according to the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This doesn't mean you have to cut out meat entirely, Landry said, but he recommended swapping red and processed meats, including beef, pork, and sausages, for leaner options like poultry, such as chicken and turkey, or fish, which are lower in saturated fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's also a good idea to add plant-based protein sources to your diet. "Eventually, I would love for folks to even move further than that and start consuming some plant-based proteins, some beans, lentils, tofu, tempeh. Those are great things for our heart as well," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="f2310b17-c86f-481d-9b8f-929fd5162d13" data-toc-id="f2310b17-c86f-481d-9b8f-929fd5162d13"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3) Swap white carbs for whole-wheat versions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Swap out white toast for wholemeal or seeded bread.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              zimmytws/Getty Images
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Fiber is great at keeping &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/nutritionist-lowered-cholesterol-4-simple-ways-eat-more-fiber-2026-1" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;cholesterol levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;u&gt; &lt;/u&gt;"nice and stable," Landry said, but most Americans don't eat enough. Ninety percent of women, and 97% of men, don't meet the recommended 30 grams of fiber a day, according to the 2020 to 2025 Dietary Guidelines for Americans. The 2025 to 2030 guidelines recommend two to four servings of whole grains a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whole grains such as brown rice, quinoa, and whole-wheat bread are good sources of fiber and can easily replace their white counterparts, which tend to be low in fiber. One cup of brown rice, for example, contains 3.5 grams of fiber, while a cup of white rice contains 0.6 grams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We can still have bread, we can still have rice," Landry, said, "but the whole grain version."&lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            &lt;/section&gt;
            
            
            
            
            
            
    
    
    
    
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Business Insider</author><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxOUTNDOElPNHZOamV2YktsRWVNTFBUOUV0NmhDWmtRMEYzOGJocHJHZDd2LUFleDZpQnUzVlozYWRkRnpjTUJUaFE4QkdNakFSTEQ3N1dtc3BOb2Z2cDVwelVwLWw4eWdSREZZYlVURU00RHdWS3pOTU4tRUZNUDlaOWFLS3ZMeHVwUjJMcHZxeTBwVFBmVGg4QmlyUHhCYUFZaGJrRk1oOVBJVFBzaDZjZA</guid></item><item><title>保持健康所需的最少运动量是多少？ -《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/13/well/move/minimum-exercise-advice.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:00:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE9naEdrWkdLaW9lSHdkLW5McmYySVVpanViV3A5eGcxR2sxTnBjX0hOMFM3MUFhMnVXOFM2a1BUWEpNeVJ3bW5sejNWWWJzRTdWZ2NuWW1DeFE5dXZVNkc3Q2pRQ3FLWHpLQmRWbmZJUllyQU1INkdrVFpJbVhhQQ</guid></item><item><title>这些药物对痴呆症患者有风险。无论如何，医生都会开处方。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/12/dementia-patients-risky-medications/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="C0M2TPA5257TH89A5W9905D990" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;An estimated quarter of traditional Medicare beneficiaries with dementia are prescribed risky, brain-altering drugs despite years of clinical guidelines cautioning against the practice, a new study shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 07:51:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNekwwajM5ZS1kTW1LUWZ0QXRRTWVmNGJMZHpPQ1lXd3g3YTdJWkdndjVsczlKVWo1MzBCM1FkeG9wMHkyUVZ6NFoyV3A1UVJibXplQnUyQ0huUGRwdGdkWnhhc0FhdjlxSGdWeWNKN1I3YjNEOHRxZUVFX1dXUVIxakdPVFNNQ1YzcXBVUmZB</guid></item><item><title>您的生物钟对晚年的大脑健康很重要–甚至可能与痴呆症风险有关- The Conversation</title><link>https://theconversation.com/your-body-clock-matters-for-brain-health-in-later-life-and-could-even-be-linked-to-dementia-risk-272838</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="grid-ten large-grid-nine grid-last content-body content entry-content instapaper_body inline-promos" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Inside the body, a 24-hour rhythm, known as the circadian rhythm, quietly coordinates when we sleep, wake, eat and recover. This internal timing system helps keep organs and hormones working in sync. When it becomes disrupted, the effects may extend well beyond poor sleep, with growing evidence suggesting consequences for long-term brain health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A large 2025 study of more than 2,000 people with an average age of 79 found that those with a strong &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/circadian-rhythms-94"&gt;circadian rhythm&lt;/a&gt; had an almost halved risk of developing dementia. Circadian rhythms regulate daily processes including sleep timing, hormone release, heart rate and body temperature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over three years of follow-up, people with weaker or more disrupted circadian rhythms were more likely to develop dementia than those with stronger, more stable daily rhythms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disrupted circadian rhythms are often associated with poor &lt;a href="https://www.ucd.ie/nnsc/t4media/Dietary%20and%20lifestyle%20habits%20and%20the%20associated%20health%20risks%20in%20shift%20workers..pdf"&gt;sleep&lt;/a&gt;. For decades, poor sleep has been suspected to contribute to both dementia and heart disease, which share several underlying risk factors. In &lt;a href="https://www.neurology.org/doi/10.1212/WNL.0000000000214513"&gt;the 2025 study&lt;/a&gt;, worse &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12281244/"&gt;heart health&lt;/a&gt; and high blood pressure, both commonly linked to sleep disruption, were accounted for in the analysis. Sleep apnoea, however, was not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sleep apnoea is a common condition in which breathing repeatedly stops and starts during sleep, reducing oxygen supply to the brain and raising blood pressure. Its relationship with dementia remains debated, largely because sleep apnoea is more common in people who already have &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8226698/"&gt;established dementia risk factors&lt;/a&gt; such as obesity, diabetes, smoking and alcohol misuse. This overlap makes it difficult to determine whether sleep apnoea itself increases dementia risk or whether it reflects broader metabolic and cardiovascular vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
            &lt;p class="placeholder-container"&gt;&lt;iframe class="native-lazy" loading="lazy" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/I5JEH4TzvD8?wmode=transparent&amp;amp;start=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            
          &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8226698/"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; suggested that addressing physical inactivity linked to fatigue from disrupted sleep may be a promising approach. Increasing activity could reduce obesity, improve sleep quality and support brain cell health, potentially lowering dementia risk through several pathways at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other explanations may also help clarify the link between disrupted circadian rhythms and dementia. One involves the immune system, which is influenced by circadian rhythms as well as sleep and plays a role in both heart disease and neurodegeneration. Another is &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.1241224"&gt;the theory that&lt;/a&gt; sleep supports the removal of toxic proteins from the brain, including amyloid plaques that characterise Alzheimer’s disease, through a waste clearance system that appears to be more active during sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this clearance hypothesis is widely discussed, evidence remains mixed. Some animal studies, including &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11156584/"&gt;those in mice&lt;/a&gt;, have shown reduced rather than increased toxin clearance during sleep. Animal findings must be interpreted cautiously, as sleep patterns in mice &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7255885/"&gt;differ substantially&lt;/a&gt; from those in humans, particularly in later life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Lancet commission &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(24)01296-0/fulltext"&gt;update&lt;/a&gt; on dementia prevention concluded that sleeping for longer or shorter durations is unlikely to be a true independent risk factor for dementia. One reason for this conclusion is that evidence from real-world sleep disruption does not clearly point to sleep duration as the main driver of risk. Although shift work &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9978382/"&gt;is associated with&lt;/a&gt; increased dementia risks, studies &lt;a href="https://bmjopen.bmj.com/content/9/5/e027027"&gt;do not consistently show&lt;/a&gt; higher risk in night shift workers compared with day shift workers. If sleep disruption alone were responsible, night shifts would be expected to carry a greater risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This suggests that circadian disruption may matter independently of sleep duration. However, shift work is also associated with unhealthy &lt;a href="https://www.ucd.ie/nnsc/t4media/Dietary%20and%20lifestyle%20habits%20and%20the%20associated%20health%20risks%20in%20shift%20workers..pdf"&gt;lifestyle patterns&lt;/a&gt;, including poorer diet, smoking, alcohol use and variable physical activity. Chronic stress, lack of routine, hormonal disruption, raised blood pressure, reduced opportunities for leisure and social isolation also cluster around shift work. Each of these factors is independently linked to dementia, heart disease and poor sleep, complicating attempts to isolate the effects of circadian disruption alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
            &lt;p class="placeholder-container"&gt;&lt;iframe class="native-lazy" loading="lazy" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YzmQtsoyyBc?wmode=transparent&amp;amp;start=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            
          &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Lancet authors also argued that if amyloid clearance does occur in humans, it likely happens during the first two hours of sleep, when deep sleep is most prominent. Deep sleep tends to be preserved even when total sleep duration falls below seven hours. They therefore suggested that fragmented sleep and disrupted biological rhythms may be early consequences of dementia-related brain changes, rather than causes. The toxic plaques may accumulate in brain regions that regulate sleep and wakefulness long before memory problems become apparent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So should sleep be deprioritised in dementia prevention? The Lancet advice was not to restrict sleep. Evidence linking long sleep, defined as more than eight hours, to dementia risk was not supported when broader data were considered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanhl/article/PIIS2666-7568(24)00161-2/fulltext"&gt;A recent trial&lt;/a&gt; tested a personalised programme combining several approaches, such as light exposure, sleep scheduling, daytime activity and caregiver support, to improve sleep in people with dementia. After eight months, sleep improved in the intervention group, although sleep also improved with usual care. The overall effect was small to moderate, and there was no improvement in dementia-related behaviours or overall health. These approaches may benefit carers by supporting routines, but their impact for people with dementia appears limited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both acute and chronic sleep deprivation, particularly loss of deep sleep and REM sleep, &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-01732-y"&gt;can impair memory&lt;/a&gt;. Whether long-term disruption of restorative sleep increases dementia risk later in life, and whether treating sleep problems can prevent dementia, remains uncertain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because improving sleep is often seen as a potential prevention strategy, medications used to treat insomnia also deserve scrutiny. Sedative drugs such as benzodiazepines have been linked to increased &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37888096/"&gt;dementia risk&lt;/a&gt;, as well as daytime drowsiness, falls and accidents. &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1087079222001058"&gt;Melatonin&lt;/a&gt;, while used by many, has not shown consistent benefits for improving sleep in adults.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That said, there are evidence-based ways to &lt;a href="https://issuu.com/marketing-web/docs/sleep_hygiene_booklet"&gt;improve sleep&lt;/a&gt; and support healthy circadian rhythms. Regular moderate &lt;a href="https://www.sleepfoundation.org/insomnia/exercise-and-insomnia"&gt;exercise&lt;/a&gt;, around 30 minutes a day, particularly outdoors and before midday, is one of the most effective. As a bonus, physical activity is also one of the strongest protective factors against heart disease and &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40962877/"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt;. So wrap up warm and get walking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Correction: This article was updated on 13 January 2026 to clarify findings from a 2025 study on circadian rhythms and dementia risk. An earlier version mischaracterised how dementia risk differed between participants with stronger versus weaker circadian rhythms.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

        

        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Conversation</author><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:18:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiywFBVV95cUxPb2VpQzcwdFZiSnEyZExHRUVOS2hZNDAxcnlpeklJc2NuN3RsaFJUWk1oQVk0eFRRUTF4WHV5ejdwNy1ONGhUb0ZKU2wya3VRZ0Vrc1M4bjB1TXpwRHNJdnZFb3BtQVgwMkFMem1oSWRvMEFEa0ViM2ZCekZPWXh0VG14TzZsV1RNejJ3ZFllWmNmdTlzNVlsbDFjcHZvaEVZNHdUQmxha2ZGUWFWdWtBSHVyekpvQklrYUVTZG5URHdmdzNjcFdKM2NmUQ</guid></item></channel></rss>