<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>预计专家将对英国大多数男性常规前列腺癌筛查提出建议- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/live/clykgr941ddt</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article data-testid="content-post" id="asset:75418b78-36e4-478d-886d-aa601450cfd2" class="ssrcss-1wmuay-ContentPost e6wdqbx1"&gt;&lt;header class="ssrcss-1p40248-Header e14e9ror5"&gt;&lt;span class="ssrcss-1de7kuz-HeadingContainer e14e9ror1"&gt;&lt;h3 type="normal" class="ssrcss-ad2rmd-Heading e10rt3ze0"&gt;&lt;span role="text" class="ssrcss-189b1h2-HeadlineWrap e14e9ror2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;David Cameron reveals treatment for prostate cancer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ssrcss-etauer-ServerSideTime e14e9ror0"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="timestamp" class="ssrcss-umer6k-Timestamp ekpio9q4"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="accessible-timestamp" class="visually-hidden ssrcss-1f39n02-VisuallyHidden e16en2lz0"&gt;published at 12:36 GMT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="ssrcss-8ksoz0-Wrapper ekpio9q3"&gt;&lt;span aria-hidden="true" class="ssrcss-crgz56-Time ekpio9q2"&gt;12:36 GMT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/header&gt;
      &lt;figure class="ssrcss-12gl1u2-StyledFigure e34k3c22"&gt;&lt;div class="ssrcss-ab5fd8-StyledFigureContainer e34k3c21"&gt;&lt;span class="ssrcss-5zsoxt-Placeholder etlorgc0"&gt;&lt;img alt="David Cameron standing in front of out of focus foliage, wearing a shirt and fleece" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/ace/standard/640/cpsprodpb/vivo/live/images/2025/11/27/5f9f64bd-c285-4d66-bfdc-44b0d6d5e101.jpg.webp" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/ace/standard/240/cpsprodpb/vivo/live/images/2025/11/27/5f9f64bd-c285-4d66-bfdc-44b0d6d5e101.jpg.webp 240w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/ace/standard/320/cpsprodpb/vivo/live/images/2025/11/27/5f9f64bd-c285-4d66-bfdc-44b0d6d5e101.jpg.webp 320w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/ace/standard/480/cpsprodpb/vivo/live/images/2025/11/27/5f9f64bd-c285-4d66-bfdc-44b0d6d5e101.jpg.webp 480w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/ace/standard/624/cpsprodpb/vivo/live/images/2025/11/27/5f9f64bd-c285-4d66-bfdc-44b0d6d5e101.jpg.webp 624w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/ace/standard/800/cpsprodpb/vivo/live/images/2025/11/27/5f9f64bd-c285-4d66-bfdc-44b0d6d5e101.jpg.webp 800w" class="ssrcss-11yxrdo-Image edrdn950"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span role="text" class="ssrcss-2z7a81-StyledFigureCopyright e34k3c20"&gt;&lt;span class="visually-hidden ssrcss-1f39n02-VisuallyHidden e16en2lz0"&gt;Image source, &lt;/span&gt;PA Media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph e1jhz7w10"&gt;Earlier this week former Prime Minister David Cameron revealed he has been treated for prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph e1jhz7w10"&gt;Cameron, 59, told the Times newspaper his wife had insisted he go for a check-up after they listened to a BBC radio interview with entrepreneur Nick Jones, who was campaigning for more men to be tested after being diagnosed himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph e1jhz7w10"&gt;"I sort of thought, well, this has happened to you, and you should lend your voice to it... I had a scan. It helped me discover something that was wrong. It gave me the chance to deal with it," Cameron said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph e1jhz7w10"&gt;Cameron had a prostate-specific antigen (PSA) test earlier this year, followed by an MRI scan and a biopsy. He was then treated with focal therapy, which targets the area where the tumour is present using methods such as ultrasound waves to destroy cancer cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph e1jhz7w10"&gt;He told the newspaper he wanted to use his platform to support a call by Prostate Cancer Research, a charity which counts Mr Jones - founder of private members' club chain Soho House - as a trustee, for screening to be offered to high-risk men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph e1jhz7w10"&gt;The National Screening Committee is expected to advise against most men being screened for the cancer.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:31:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiVEFVX3lxTFB1eVVZbUJZa3ZrMnBWaUNMYjE0WXhLY0I2R1JvME8xNzJmQWRLUkRGTnF4MGU4Y3JNb3RaYjdhRHFmdzZSZDRNaWZ6Q2dZRHZTOU1ROQ</guid></item><item><title>糖与锯齿：肠道医生，帕尔博士对精制白色晶体之间更健康的选择进行了现实检查-经济时报</title><link>https://m.economictimes.com/magazines/panache/sugar-vs-jaggery-gastro-doctor-dr-pal-gives-a-reality-check-on-healthier-choice-between-refined-white-crystals-and-traditional-indian-sweetener/articleshow/125546725.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-brcount="20" class="artText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A familiar debate resurfaced this week after &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/gastroenterologist" target="_blank"&gt;gastroenterologist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; Dr Pal Manickam shared a detailed comparison of sugar and jaggery on Instagram. While the traditional sweetener often enjoys a reputation for being the healthier pick, the doctor urged viewers to understand what actually happens once these foods enter the bloodstream. His explanation was featured in a video highlighted by an Instagram post, where he broke down myths attached to both ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Pal began by addressing a common belief that brown sugar and jaggery are fundamentally different from white sugar. Referring to his demonstration in the video, he explained that brown sugar loses its dark colour when placed in water because the molasses drains out. He emphasised that the body treats most sweeteners the same way. Whether one consumes white sugar, brown sugar, jaggery or any organic variant, the bloodstream converts them into glucose, causing similar spikes in blood sugar levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-newpos-mgid="mgid_125546725" id="div-mgid-mid-newpos-125546725"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="E_3" class="etoro"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Palm Jaggery Gets Some Extra Points&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;The discussion, however, did not end with a blanket comparison. Dr Pal noted that palm jaggery has a slight advantage over refined white sugar. As cited from the video, he highlighted that palm jaggery has a lower &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/glycemic-index" target="_blank"&gt;glycemic index&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. This means it raises blood sugar more gradually, offering steadier energy levels. He added that palm jaggery is also more eco friendly because palm trees use less land and water than sugarcane. Its micronutrient content provides an additional edge, though he stressed that this benefit should not be overstated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-vdoai="vdoai_125546725" id="div-vdoai-mid-125546725"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Clearing Up Confusion About Impurities&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;The video also attempted to put rumours to rest regarding jaggery turning lighter in colour when dissolved. Dr Pal clarified that the whitening is simply the result of impurities dissolving and not evidence of adulteration. He added that this process does not wash away minerals and does not make jaggery unsafe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID_INTL_300" data-loc="100" id="div-gpt-ad-858478126-1-125546725" class="country_specAD"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="2" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-125546725" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="5" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-125546725" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="3" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-125546725" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Moderation Still Rules&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite acknowledging that jaggery is traditional, flavourful and slightly better than white sugar when consumed in equal amounts, Dr Pal issued a reminder that it remains a form of sugar. People should avoid treating it as a health food. He noted humorously that many avoid white sugar but freely indulge in jaggery, often consuming more than recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Pal Manickam, widely known for simplifying medical science through his signature blend of humour and explanation, is a board certified gastroenterologist and Director of Preventive Gastroenterology at a California based practice. His work often focuses on gut health, plant based diets and time restricted eating. With a strong social media presence, his content aims to inform the public through an approach that merges comedy with evidence based guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional guidance from nutrition experts underscores that both sugar and jaggery originate from sugarcane and offer similar calorie loads, despite jaggery’s reputation as a natural alternative. According to a recent Redcliffe Labs report, jaggery retains small amounts of minerals, but its high glycemic index means it can still raise blood sugar significantly, making moderation essential for everyone, including people with diabetes. Specialists advise that neither sweetener should be viewed as inherently healthier, and limiting overall intake remains the safest approach.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;meta content="cms.article3" name="cmsei-article3"&gt;&lt;div class="inSideInd"&gt;&lt;div data-ga-action="Preference Banner InArticle Widget" data-ga-impression="Preference Banner InArticle Widget#Impressions | Preference Banner | Articleshow#url" class="Pbanner"&gt;&lt;div class="Pbannertext"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img alt="ET Logo" src="https://img.etimg.com/photo/123467569.cms"&gt;&lt;p&gt; as a Reliable and Trusted News Source&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Economic Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:15:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwJBVV95cUxNbndCekdUVFlZM3JJeWJYRklEZmdNQTdxOXVZOXJkLUJSSExNQU0ySnZBRGpLX1RGNXNqRzdjQzQ3STZ3cGdvNGl0UXVHWDZxdTZOWV9qZDB1SFhGdXlMRG9JUGRBUF9kUHcybHBBcEZKbm9fNzMzOUpCTjd2MXJKODlXMmVHRjNhczdKUUZKS0o0bk80elF4TkZjckJSdWU1aHBld1ZDYXMySmhiN2tTZGtZd3hoNzVTR0NfY3BQMDZiS3U3eFZ0ZVVUQ01FX3lSeVQyM0tfa2RsYU9UNldmUnZVUVhHUHZwajNhZkU1VlZRT2pMdWx4aWdiNWh1RVdicGRJdWYtYnBJZ3p1VHJIbmc3YVdpMGUtNk9oOG40S19PNzhBdkU5YjZXVWdVMllobFUyOHJ1RTcyS1HSAcACQVVfeXFMTXF5cF9JcV91WWhBN1FFZ0VJS1dGT1V3V3FSb0wxRVlXU0pZTUg3Ulp5OHhISW1SSmlaQW8xOFQ0aE5sMmZqb3dvXzJvWWpaRTFKUVBuNklRSVZFSE5yeGJJZTI1Y01wR2ZTTHY0RHZQdzRabTIzaFZvd1djcDZoZWtxX2dfZ0tBSGlXWXZQNm1nbkJOZnZDcGJYVUk2bnp5SVBRSTRqaTdkRTJtcmY0ZEdvWHlka1FCSENBSnZOVExMMW4yV2pFWHh2V0JBSW51V1ZRbTNVaUlmWUNaN0I3OTVPZkhuMHRjQVBnY0JaS3UxVTNuYXQ3aDVKcWxvbU9nSlI3M2N1SFlpRDhTVVFodlREemJQOG1pd214MlRkTlZxMmh4OUtSN0NDWEJqbFFlQTZxOU11YVpsTlFZSzlOZTI</guid></item><item><title>麻疹病例激增是“火灾警报” ，警告其他疾病可能是下一个- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/surging-measles-cases-are-fire-alarm-warning-diseases-rcna246035</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-090f34" class="body-graf"&gt;The surging number of measles cases around the world is a stark warning sign that outbreaks of other vaccine-preventable diseases could be next, the World Health Organization warned Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3372bd" class="body-graf"&gt;“It’s crucial to understand why measles matters,” said Dr. Kate O’Brien, director of the WHO’s Department of Immunization, Vaccines and Biologicals. “Its high transmissibility means that even small drops in vaccine coverage can trigger outbreaks, like a fire alarm going off when smoke is detected first.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b8f2f4" class="body-graf"&gt;That is, measles is often the first disease to pop up when vaccination rates overall drop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-424c91" class="body-graf"&gt;"When we see measles cases, it signals that gaps are almost certainly likely for other vaccine-preventable diseases like diphtheria or whooping cough or polio, even though they may not be setting off the fire alarm just yet," O'Brien said at a media briefing Monday, ahead of the release of the WHO's Progress Toward Measles Elimination report, published Friday in its &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/journals/weekly-epidemiological-record" target="_blank"&gt;Weekly Epidemiological Record&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b9fc10" class="body-graf"&gt;Indeed, whooping cough cases are also rising in the United States and are on track to be the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/php/surveillance/pertussis-cases-by-year.html" target="_blank"&gt;most in a decade&lt;/a&gt;. More than 20,000 whooping cough cases have been reported so far in 2025, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-789004" class="body-graf"&gt;In 2024, there were an estimated 11 million measles infections worldwide, according to the report, nearly 800,000 more than were recorded in 2019. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8ed4bb" class="body-graf"&gt;Last year, 59 countries reported large measles outbreaks. In 2025, the United States joined the list of countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-492538" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Elimination status threatened&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a41910" class="body-graf"&gt;The ongoing outbreaks threaten the so-called measles elimination statuses of some countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-efcaa5" class="body-graf"&gt;Elimination means a virus has stopped spreading in a specific country or region. (Only one virus — smallpox — has been eradicated, or wiped out permanently, worldwide.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d4b03d" class="body-graf"&gt;In total, 81 countries had reached elimination status in 2024, according to the WHO. Canada eliminated measles in 1998. Two years later, the United States did the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-40cb1f" class="body-graf"&gt;Elimination status means a country has the capacity to stop an outbreak when measles cases arrive from abroad, O'Brien said. If vaccination rates are high enough, the virus won't have enough unvaccinated people to infect, halting an outbreak in its tracks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-08eca5" class="body-graf"&gt;But vaccination rates in the United States are falling: An &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/data-investigation-childhood-vaccination-rates-are-backsliding-us-rcna228876" target="_blank"&gt;NBC News investigation&lt;/a&gt; revealed that since 2019, 77% of counties and jurisdictions have reported declines in the number of kids getting routine childhood vaccinations like the measles-mumps-rubella shots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9de51f" class="body-graf"&gt;The key determining factor for a country to lose its measles elimination status is the ongoing spread of the same strain of the virus for a full year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c4aacd" class="body-graf"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/canada-loses-measles-elimination-status-will-us-rcna242630" target="_blank"&gt;Canada met that threshold&lt;/a&gt; this month. The United States could be next if scientists can trace current cases to a Texas outbreak that began in January.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4fda67" class="body-graf"&gt;Nearly all of the samples analyzed from those early cases were identified as a genotype of measles called D8, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7414a1.htm" target="_blank"&gt;CDC report&lt;/a&gt; published in April.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-ac3b8a" class="body-graf"&gt;The D8 genotype was recently detected in a South Carolina outbreak. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-14fe9d" class="body-graf"&gt;Preliminary results from specimens sent from South Carolina to CDC labs "are the same type, D8, that is seen in other settings in the United States," Dr. Linda Bell, state epidemiologist for the South Carolina Department of Public Health, said at a news briefing Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4a478e" class="body-graf"&gt;Additional genetic sequencing is needed to make a definitive link between the Texas outbreak and the one in South Carolina, as well as outbreaks in Utah and Arizona. A South Carolina Department of Public Health spokesman said the agency "expects those results in the next few weeks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-31fe1c" class="body-graf"&gt;Bell said that as of Tuesday, 58 cases had been reported in South Carolina, mostly in Spartanburg County in the northwest part of the state. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-dbed05" class="body-graf"&gt;An &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/amp/rcna240592" target="_blank"&gt;outbreak along the border of Arizona and Utah&lt;/a&gt; continues to grow. The &lt;a href="https://www.azdhs.gov/preparedness/epidemiology-disease-control/measles/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;Arizona Department of Health Services&lt;/a&gt; reported 153 cases this week, nearly all in Mohave County. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8239eb" class="body-graf"&gt;Cases in Utah have reached 102, according to the &lt;a href="https://epi.utah.gov/measles-response/" target="_blank"&gt;state Department of Health and Human Services&lt;/a&gt;. While the bulk of those cases are linked to the cluster at the Utah-Arizona border, case numbers are also rising near Salt Lake City. &lt;a href="https://www.ksl.com/article/51410730/measles-confirmed-in-8-students-at-wasatch-high-utahs-total-eclipses-100-infections" target="_blank"&gt;NBC affiliate KSL&lt;/a&gt; reported that eight students at a high school in Wasatch County had been diagnosed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f54f56" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;As of Wednesday, the CDC had reported 1,798 confirmed measles cases in 42 states in 2025. Three people, an adult in New Mexico and two little girls in Texas, have died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxPb1FUZHVCN0NjMTR6WFRfS051UXE4Q2pSSFhqeU8wRmJNaUZZN1VGSkEzaEtvQlotT2NpNlpuSHRyNnZEb2JsVE15Y3VDU1NGODdUTVdHcWwyZ3RRSEVGRC0yRGhVZmRHRXIxaGluU2ZvWHg5UDlsNkVEaVZCQlJISmtueWhPX18xUXlfMVliX0dQSmhkR1BKc0VYTDc1eFpuTjl4Y3U1MnpIVzjSAVZBVV95cUxPLTZXaHYxV0NTdVR3NU1SM29LNjBOOHAwb2R3dmFXRjB6VG1FOGV5TUM0Wk1hb0RONFdmTG9sQThBOXhpZjNZVG9MZkgzbDYzaXZBa09iZw</guid></item><item><title>科学说我们的大脑有五个“时代” ，这就解释了为什么我直到三十多岁才觉得自己是一个真正的成年人-独立报</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/adult-thirties-brain-32-study-b2872890.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 bxpovR sc-jbiisr-1 sc-1wfc891-0 fooWDH" id="main"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="big-letter"&gt;W&lt;/span&gt;hen you think about it, the ages at which we decide a human being has crossed the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/life-style/adulting-utility-bills-adulthood-rubbish-tip-maturity-wine-family-children-credit-card-a8196601.html"&gt;threshold from childhood to adulthood&lt;/a&gt; are as strange as they are arbitrary. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first accepted turning point in British culture comes at 16, when you can get a full-time job, leave school, buy a lottery ticket and consent to have sex. Then there’s the legal transformation into an adult at 18: you can live alone, buy alcohol and cigarettes, vote, gamble and get tattoos and piercings without anyone else’s say so. And finally, 21, when nothing much happens at all – unless you’re particularly keen on adopting a child, holding a minibus or pilot’s licence and getting pissed in North America – but which has, nevertheless, been deemed a final step into maturity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet not one of these milestones is particularly reflective of our neurological development. Neuroscience has long shown that our &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/life-style/health-and-families/writing-mental-health-resilience-b2871463.html"&gt;prefrontal cortex&lt;/a&gt;, responsible for impulse control, decision-making, planning and problem-solving, doesn’t fully develop until around the age of 25. But now a &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-025-65974-8"&gt;new study&lt;/a&gt; has uncovered a whole new benchmark. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on brain scans of nearly 4,000 people, the research mapped evolving neural connections to identify five distinct “epochs”, or eras, for the brain, with changes occurring at four key ages: nine, 32, 66 and 83. Despite our ingrained societal ideas around when someone becomes a grown-up, these latest findings suggest that “adult mode” only kicks into gear &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/news/science/adult-brain-30s-teenagers-crime-mental-health-research-a8828681.html"&gt;in our early thirties&lt;/a&gt;. That’s when the architecture of our brains stabilises and coincides with a “plateau in intelligence and personality”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m not at all surprised by this; if anything, I feel vindicated. Though lead researcher Alexa Mousley was quick to point out that they’re “definitely not saying that people in their late twenties are going to be acting like teenagers… It’s really the pattern of change,” the notion that I was an “adult” – responsible or otherwise – in my teens or twenties is risible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-us-premium-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Granted, I was always a late bloomer. At 16, I was still far too busy making up elaborate routines to the &lt;em&gt;Centre Stage &lt;/em&gt;soundtrack with my friends to contemplate coitus. At 18, I may have gone off to university, but I was also shamefully clueless (during a “how to cook pasta” lesson with my mother before leaving home, I really did respond with, “But how can I tell?” when told to wait until the water was boiling). At 21, I dressed up as a dolphin for my birthday party in a grotty nightclub, snogged a stranger, vomited copiously and turned up to my all-year lecture the next day still drunk and singing sea shanties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="2" class="sc-awdjp1-0 dfOhoE"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.the-independent.com/2025/11/26/12/20/iStock-1312770451.jpg" srcset="https://static.the-independent.com/2025/11/26/12/20/iStock-1312770451.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;crop=3%3A2%2Csmart&amp;amp;trim=0%2C0%2C0%2C0&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.the-independent.com/2025/11/26/12/20/iStock-1312770451.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;crop=3%3A2%2Csmart&amp;amp;trim=0%2C0%2C0%2C0&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Embrace the ‘hot mess’ era of your twenties" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-110239"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Embrace the ‘hot mess’ era of your twenties&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’d like to say that my twenties saw me develop some semblance of sophistication – and indeed, at the tail-end of that decade, I did finally find my way onto a more solid career path and started my first adult-feeling relationship. But, in all honesty, that period was mostly typified by hapless stumbling between dramas. There was the morning I slept through my alarm and turned up 90 minutes late to run a workshop for 500 young people; the day I got to the station and realised I didn’t have enough money to buy a train ticket to work; the time I accidentally &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/life-style/bills-life-admin-tasks-bank-b2605589.html"&gt;built up thousands of pounds in debt&lt;/a&gt; when I moved out of a shared flat and forgot to cancel all the direct debits. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I won’t even get into the romantic mishaps – we don’t have that kind of time – but suffice to say they were plentiful and ran the gamut from chaotic to embarrassing. “Making good decisions” was as alien a concept as flossing my teeth at that age. It would have been my “hot mess” era, had I actually been hot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1wzq3bw-0 sc-1wzq3bw-2 kqnNdl mbxVq"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-i07cwn-0 dvtoxw"&gt;&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" id="7b73b88eb27c89ab" viewbox="0 0 80 47"&gt;&lt;path fill="#eb1426" d="M21.18 46.99c9.4 0 17.18-7.73 17.18-17.13 0-9.46-7.72-17.12-17.12-17.12A17.2 17.2 0 0 0 3.99 29.86c0 3.74 1.29 7.47 3.48 10.5l-.13.12A23.6 23.6 0 0 1 1.29 24.4c0-12.75 10.36-23.3 23.1-23.3a24 24 0 0 1 11.53 2.89l.57-.96A26 26 0 0 0 24.33 0 24.3 24.3 0 0 0 0 24.4c0 14.09 9.72 22.59 21.18 22.59m41.47 0c9.4 0 17.18-7.73 17.18-17.13 0-9.46-7.72-17.12-17.12-17.12a17.2 17.2 0 0 0-17.25 17.12c0 3.74 1.29 7.47 3.48 10.5l-.13.12a23.6 23.6 0 0 1-6.05-16.08c0-12.75 10.36-23.3 23.1-23.3a24 24 0 0 1 11.53 2.89l.58-.96A26 26 0 0 0 65.8 0a24.33 24.33 0 0 0-24.33 24.4c0 14.09 9.72 22.59 21.18 22.59"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The notion that I was an adult – responsible or otherwise – in my twenties is risible&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I look back, the watershed moments that marked my transition into being a proper grown-up person with her s*** together are undeniable – and nearly every single one happened at around the time identified by the study. At the age of 31, I got a job at this very publication, the first time I really felt like I was intentionally steering my career in the desired direction. At 32, I &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/life-style/how-to-make-friends-new-town-b2310941.html"&gt;identified the coastal town where I wanted to build my life&lt;/a&gt; as an adult. At 33, I &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/life-style/taylor-swift-breakup-thirties-women-joe-alwyn-b2532689.html"&gt;broke up with my long-term partner&lt;/a&gt; because we both realised it wasn’t right – and that, in many ways, we’d always felt like adolescents playing house together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My generation, millennials, have long been accused of refusing to grow the heck up. We’re buying homes, getting married and &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/life-style/babies-birth-rate-decline-fertility-b2605579.html"&gt;having children later&lt;/a&gt;, while continuing to cling on to childhood obsessions with Disney and Harry Potter. But aside from all the socio-economic factors that have led to this perceived arrested development, maybe we didn’t have it so wrong after all. Maybe “kidulthood” isn’t something to be denigrated but a completely natural phase of life, embodying the chaotic whirlwind of our twenties before we wise up, settle down and get comfortable in our own skin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's not to say we should stay Peter Pans forever. Just that your twenties are for making mistakes, learning from them and figuring out who you want to be. So the next time you miss your train, mess up your finances or go home with someone questionable, just apologise, shake it off – and explain that science made you do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 10:07:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxPRlBERGdWd3NyVmlfLXJsNFlXRTJLUGhXV1poSVJ1VVBIemE0aUtSc2U4bWpJT2d1UlZ4QUctcFVhSDlUZXhsRlJiYUF1SUVWMWZiMFk1aGhabmVvVkxGQ1JTcHNoUC0wR1ZWMWNmdnBYV3RJMVB5OHhLbFRYalVHY3dQUElmSmxPSlRNcQ</guid></item><item><title>全球健康专家揭示促进消化系统健康的10种方法-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/global-wellness-expert-reveals-10-ways-to-boost-digestive-health/articleshow/125628109.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Improving digestion involves not just what goes onto the plate but how, when, and in what state it's eaten. Functional medicine doctors, like Dr. Eric Berg, often discuss such simple daily habits that can turn bloating, gas, heaviness, and sluggish bowels into a lighter, more comfortable gut experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Eat in a relaxed state&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Digestion starts in the brain. The "fight-or flight" mode shunts blood away from the digestive tract, stomach acid falls, and motility slows. A few deep nasal breaths, a quick prayer-or pause of screens before meals flips on the parasympathetic "rest and digest" system and puts the gut in a better position to process incoming food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;The Importance of a Strong Digestive Fire for Holistic Health in Ayurveda&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Chew properly and eat slowly&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chewing mechanically reduces the size of the food and mixes it with saliva that contains digestive enzymes such as amylase. The longer you chew, the more head start the stomach and small intestine have, and thus less work for the rest of the gastrointestinal tract. Eating slowly also allows time for the hormones cholecystokinin and GLP‑1 to signal fullness-which naturally prevents overeating and heaviness following a meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Support stomach acid when needed&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Low stomach acid is more common than people often think, especially in older adults or in anyone with chronic stress. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Small amounts of diluted apple cider vinegar, lemon water-or bitter herbs before meals are gentle approaches many practitioners recommend to support stomach acid and enhance protein and mineral absorption. Anyone currently taking an acid‑suppressing medication or experiencing reflux or ulcers should always discuss this with a doctor first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Stimulate a healthy flow of bile&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It emulsifies fats and helps to carry toxins out of the body. Traditionally, the use of bitter foods-lemon, dandelion greens, beetroot, arugula, and methi leaves-is to stimulate the production and flow of bile from both the liver and the gallbladder. A plate that regularly includes these bitter vegetables, in addition to healthy fats, can make fatty meals feel lighter and reduce symptoms such as floating stools or greasy residue in the toilet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Use digestive enzymes judiciously&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Supplementing one's diet with digestive-enzyme supplements has become very popular for symptoms such as fullness, gas, or-undigested food in stool. These supplements provide additional amylase, lipase, protease, or plant enzymes such as bromelain and papain. While they could be helpful with short-term support-for example, when one has to eat heavier meals, or during the recovery phase of any gut issues-they are best used under medical supervision rather than as a permanent crutch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Feed gut microbes with fermented foods&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diversity in the microbiome enhances motility, immunity, and even mood. Conventional fermented foods like curd, yogurt, kefir, kimchi, homemade pickles, sauerkraut, kanji, or idli/dosa batter introduce live bacteria and their beneficial metabolic products, such as short‑chain fatty acids. Gradual introduction in small quantities can help the intestines get used to them, thereby minimizing bloating or discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Include omega‑3 fats and healthy-oils&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good fat does no harm to digestion but helps regulate bile and reduce inflammation along the gut lining. Fatty fish, flaxseed, chia, walnuts, and cold-pressed oils in moderation assist the easy passage of foods through the intestines, nourishing the intestinal cells. To the contrary, seed oils repeatedly heated and trans fatty acids increase inflammation and could exacerbate reflux or irritable bowel symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Space meals and allow an overnight fast&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The migrating motor complex is a housekeeping wave that sweeps any residue of food and bacteria through the small intestine between meals. If one is grazing all day, this system never functions optimally. Leaving four to five hours between meals-and allowing for a 12–14‑hour overnight gap (for example early dinner and slightly later breakfast)-allows time for the MMC to function, reducing small intestinal bacterial overgrowth and post‑meal bloating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Practice light movements after dinner&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Light movement after meals aids circulation and peristalsis, and normalizes blood sugar. A ten‑-to twenty‑minute easy walk after lunch or dinner, a few gentle stretches, or household activity can markedly reduce heaviness and reflux compared with lying down immediately. It is better to save high‑intensity exercise for other times of the day so the gut is not deprived of blood flow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Hydrate smartly and manage stress, sugar-and late nights&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adequate water helps prevent constipation by keeping the stool soft, while it also supports the production of saliva and mucus along the digestive tract. Sipping water throughout the day is more effective than taking large gulps with your food, which for some sensitive individuals can dilute stomach acid. Avoid refined sugar, ultraprocessed foods-and late-night heavy dinners to give time for your digestive system to rest and repair. Chronic stress, too little sleep-and rushing around day after day blunts vagal tone and keeps the body stuck in survival mode, showing up as indigestion, cramps-and irregular bowels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5wFBVV95cUxNSncwbnFNVjNuMmljcWlXbXNvakFmS0tXNGs1R01WUTdhRUZUSmVCakdmLWJqOE9KRHVWUldzV3dUSlBWLUhadThLZDFRei1lanhNbEFnY1pQNFlhLVNBRWZqQjU0TEN1U242WEN3bDR3bnlnQl9fMUFZTDVCSWhjQWtmSmdZaFBDQlNCSjZKdWc1a2N5X3pfMEVXMVQ1WVcxcVlOV2QwamFxeGZRVjBtX0FEZkhQN1V6TWxwWXRXZ1pVQXdaUmY0V1h6bEp5bjlMd1dURmJOMzYydHZBOEhWbkZvQWxXSnM</guid></item><item><title>根据科学家的说法，这种“奇迹植物”可以帮助治疗阿尔茨海默病-SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/according-to-scientists-this-miracle-plant-could-help-treat-alzheimers-disease/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 02:11:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxQdFFJeEhJbGZuUE45QnJaeUVkWFlxVjZaRVkwRHRLRjZEMmpQNjdPWEF2cEtBQWhZSEFlN0F2eWI3cUJsbTR5dzNNZGRDQktNd0pzR2NISy1DWTlYd0hsUFBmOG0wQ283OWVoYWNvdFJpcHhySXpPdl9CeER3SlcxN3pUUlJMbjVyOFE3U2wtTi1sTUpjaHpyMExiODE0TFpab0NOLXYyNA</guid></item><item><title>这种常见药物似乎可以对抗最致命的脑癌之一- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/this-common-drug-seems-to-fight-one-of-the-deadliest-brain-cancers</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hydralazine"&gt;Hydralazine&lt;/a&gt; has been used to treat &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-blood-pressure-guidelines-mean-you-may-now-have-hypertension"&gt;high blood pressure&lt;/a&gt; for many decades, even though it's never been exactly clear how it works. Now a new study answers some key questions about the medication – and adds an intriguing new link to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-7-warning-signs-of-brain-cancer-you-might-easily-miss"&gt;brain cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a closer look at the effects of hydralazine on human and mouse cells, researchers led by a team from the University of Pennsylvania found that it blocks a particular enzyme called 2-aminoethanethiol dioxygenase (ADO).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That same enzyme, as it happens, is thought to play a role in aggressive &lt;a href="https://www.cancerresearchuk.org/about-cancer/brain-tumours/types/glioblastoma"&gt;glioblastoma brain cancers&lt;/a&gt;. This new understanding of hydralazine could lead the way to new  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="182732" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; treatments, as well as improve the drug's effectiveness for its current targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/serotonin-could-play-an-unexpected-role-in-cancer-scientists-discover"&gt;Serotonin Could Play an Unexpected Role in Cancer, Scientists Discover&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hydralazine is one of the earliest vasodilators ever developed, and it's still a first-line treatment for preeclampsia – a hypertensive disorder that accounts for 5-15 percent of maternal deaths worldwide," &lt;a href="https://penntoday.upenn.edu/news/penn-chemistry-serendipitous-find-leads-lifesaving-discoveries"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; physician-scientist Kyosuke Shishikura, from the University of Pennsylvania.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It came from a 'pre-target' era of drug discovery, when researchers relied on what they saw in patients first and only later tried to explain the biology behind it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_182735" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-182735" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/CancerDiagram.jpg" alt="Cancer action diagram" class="wp-image-182735 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/CancerDiagram.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/CancerDiagram-600x415.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-182735" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The ADO enzyme catalyzes reactions that produce hypotaurine, which increases cancer growth. (Shishikura et al., &lt;em&gt;Sci. Adv.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers describe ADO as an "alarm bell" that alerts the body to dropping oxygen levels. It triggers a chain reaction, tightening blood vessels by destroying so-called RGS proteins (short for &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Regulator_of_G_protein_signaling"&gt;regulators of G-protein signaling&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41420-020-00398-5"&gt;Previous studies&lt;/a&gt; have shown that glioblastoma tumors are often high in ADO, hijacking it to produce a chemical called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hypotaurine"&gt;hypotaurine&lt;/a&gt;, which helps the cancer cells spread, survive for longer, and tolerate stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But no ADO inhibitors were known prior to this study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hydralazine effectively mutes ADO, the team found: RGS proteins aren't attacked, blood vessels aren't squeezed, and blood pressure drops. In experiments with human &lt;span&gt;glioblastoma&lt;/span&gt; cells, hydralazine halted &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/breast-cancer-spreads-more-aggressively-at-night-startling-new-study-finds"&gt;tumor growth&lt;/a&gt; by blocking ADO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's very early days – t&lt;span&gt;he effects of hydralzine still need to be tested in people with &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-deadliest-kind-of-brain-cancer-may-have-a-promising-new-treatment"&gt;glioblastoma&lt;/a&gt; in clinical trials – &lt;/span&gt;but these are promising findings that could unlock a way to control the spread of these &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/nasal-drops-could-help-fight-a-common-and-deadly-brain-cancer"&gt;notoriously hard-to-treat&lt;/a&gt; brain tumors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The newly uncovered mechanism also explains why hydralazine is an effective treatment for preeclampsia, a high blood pressure condition in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pregnancy-ages-a-persons-cells-but-some-may-undergo-an-unexpected-rejuvenation"&gt;pregnant women&lt;/a&gt;. That means the drug can be better engineered and personalized, to reduce side effects and improve results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Understanding how hydralazine works at the molecular level offers a path toward safer, more selective treatments for pregnancy-related hypertension – potentially improving outcomes for patients who are at greatest risk," &lt;a href="https://penntoday.upenn.edu/news/penn-chemistry-serendipitous-find-leads-lifesaving-discoveries"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; chemist Megan Matthews, from the University of Pennsylvania.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The discoveries here mean better drugs for both &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-blood-pressure-guidelines-mean-you-may-now-have-hypertension"&gt;high blood pressure&lt;/a&gt; and brain cancer can now be developed, carefully balancing the need to hit particular pathways in cells while minimizing harm to healthy parts of the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And since hydralazine is already widely used, understanding its mechanism of action gives scientists something of a head start if they want to build more treatments based on the compound.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further down the line, we might be able to take out one of the key defenses of glioblastoma, adding to the treatments &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/breakthrough-therapy-obliterates-deadly-brain-tumor-in-days"&gt;already in development&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's rare that an old cardiovascular drug ends up teaching us something new about the brain," &lt;a href="https://penntoday.upenn.edu/news/penn-chemistry-serendipitous-find-leads-lifesaving-discoveries"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Matthews, "but that's exactly what we're hoping to find more of – unusual links that could spell new solutions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/sciadv.adx7687"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Science Advances&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 02:02:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxPZlNsc05JMmJLb1dlQjRJejMyajFkbnF0VndOQlJIZExoVHV0MklWcnZRbE9mTkFMUWNMRTdTampHczZSVEdCMXpxZHk3SVVtUHhzaXJTSHNEQzBEVzNOaXdQUUdJU0Vnb2tra29OMVlCOTdCRDYtT01MNWtjUFBFbmc0dW54Vjd6Tzdmcjdka1ZmQ2lzRGFDRU9Iaw</guid></item><item><title>Nature's Ozempic ： 5种可食用的食物， “模仿”流行的减肥药物，具有天然益处-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/weight-loss/natures-ozempic-5-edibles-that-mimic-the-popular-weight-loss-drug-with-natural-benefits/photostory/125627258.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an era where weight loss is a wellness trend and seeking quick weight-loss solutions is part of conforming to that trend, prescription medications like Ozempic have become household names. The drug that originally came into the picture mainly as a treatment for type 2 diabetes and heart disease has now been turned into a mere fat-loss jab. What’s more? After the FDA approval, Ozempic has gotten the much-coveted endorsement — from celebrities, influencers, and many more people who have the power and position to influence common people. In fact, as American singer-songwriter-rapper Lizzo pointed out, there is an Ozempic boom happening now that’s erasing plus-size women from the mainstream spaces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For patients at risk of heart disease or diabetes, Ozempic is a necessary prescription medication — yes. But what if there were gentler, more natural ways to tap into some of that drug’s metabolic magic — not with injections or pills, but with everyday foods and herbs?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers at Heliopolis University (Egypt) have drawn attention to a set of plant-based foods and compounds that appear to influence the same gut-hormone pathways targeted by Ozempic. According to their review, ingredients such as ginger, cinnamon, wheat protein, fermented green tea, and the plant compound berberine may help stimulate the release or expression of a hormone called GLP-1 (glucagon-like peptide-1), which plays a key role in appetite control, digestion speed, and blood-sugar regulation — the very effects for which Ozempic is prized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s spill the beans, shall we?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:46:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAJBVV95cUxNZXVaaW1XTk1vU2tpMzVhenN6XzN4QzZJdVYzbHJnNDlwbGEyUmZTeEhSM0JfSmNxMFZ5OE1QbUNmNDRMUHlCWkZQaVRPUEd6NW9jenlrQVJHR0ZyRWV4eUs0aFlrSzQtRS1UODlOUDRlSDAzM3hEaEw1MmZtdUMyRVFHR1d6dmNsYUpPcHA2dUxEMDZUZnBnZGotdzJTaURRNy1pQVl3aGdrTWhiWmkweHI1UnVQX2dvTVBsaGhWWGVuN2t4b1I2VUh0ajZYNVA5NGM0eEhOa00tQ2dWWVR4X0p5M3VXMVFoUVI3TC1FU1ctdG4xUi1sYXFuV1l4aDctVEJ2YVhwbGFhbVAtUVN6U1htNHHSAZwCQVVfeXFMTzlzcHFRXzhPVEpMOE8yS25SeWJScC1tNC1WWC1Md1lOOWphR3VtLVh2dHNrRFZ5b1dzckpvSW0yb0ZQZ18xZ29YZUk2LWV4MEUzVjk5Q1FkZDIwUndQbmUyWWRFdXhKS2VSc2l1MXpoS3BCRHZBNHluTWxaRTJkN0lqanA0ME04QUxDbVRTV0tNR1M2WXo2cEhNZk5SVmllMVIyc2loTm42cDdqODhFMzR3TFZrSGF5R1lkUF9mYXpVWWlMNXdzYVMxNlV1Ny1UYVNrLTdnR2lIeHFrQVk1RkcwMTlIaF9xSmZSXzZLczdJNlVMQVZlTU9lbHk1SmhlX2E5VHVaVndlQW9XS2RiRGRxZVdMa3NScUwzWGs</guid></item><item><title>减肥：研究发现饮食，运动组合可能最有效-今日医学新闻</title><link>https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/diet-exercise-study-best-strategy-reducing-belly-fat-weight-loss</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-12va8w7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="css-7j3c6j"&gt;&lt;span class="css-rwmw5v"&gt;&lt;span class="css-mjp0j9"&gt;&lt;picture class="css-16pk1is"&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/exercise-diet-collage-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 1190px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/exercise-diet-collage-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 990px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/exercise-diet-collage-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 879w" media="(min-width: 768px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="eager" src="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/exercise-diet-collage-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg" alt="A collage of two photos depicting a healthy diet with bowls of fruits, nuts and seeds, and a woman stretching on a mat with her dog" class="css-1jytyml"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;hl-share-overlay class="css-1mqo1cs"&gt;&lt;a class="icon-hl-pinterest css-11oz8gb" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" data-event="Any Page|Image Pinterest Click|Icon Clicked" data-element-event="OPEN|CONTENTBLOCK|Any Page|Article Body|BUTTON|Image Widget Pinterest Click|" href="https://www.pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicalnewstoday.com%2Farticles%2Fdiet-exercise-study-best-strategy-reducing-belly-fat-weight-loss&amp;amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.post.rvohealth.io%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fsites%2F3%2F2025%2F11%2Fexercise-diet-collage-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg&amp;amp;description=Fat%20loss%3A%20Study%20finds%20diet%2C%20exercise%20combination%20may%20be%20most%20effective" title="Share on Pinterest" data-pin-custom="true" data-share-url="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/exercise-diet-collage-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg"&gt;&lt;span class="css-z1zfa"&gt;Share on Pinterest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-share-overlay&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;figcaption class="css-1nzy6lj css-whkgel"&gt;A new study explores the effects of diet and exercise in preventing weight gain. Design by MNT; Photography by Nadine Greeff/Stocksy &amp;amp; BONNINSTUDIO/Stocksy&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Over the last few years, research has shown that having too much visceral fat can be very harmful to a person’s health.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Past studies have shown that having an unhealthy amount of visceral fat may increase a person’s risk of several health conditions.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A new study found that improving both diet and exercise levels simultaneously may be more effective in preventing weight gain, particularly of visceral fat.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the last few years, research has shown that having &lt;span&gt;excessive &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/320929" target="_blank" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;visceral fat&lt;/a&gt; — the fat surrounding the abdominal area that protects internal organs — can be detrimental&lt;/span&gt; to a person’s health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Abdominal weight gain is a major public health concern,” &lt;a href="https://www.ndph.ox.ac.uk/team/shayan-aryannezhad" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Shayan Aryannezhad&lt;/a&gt;, MD, MPH, PhD, doctoral graduate of the MRC Epidemiology Unit at the University of Cambridge, and clinical research fellow at the Nuffield Department of Population Health at the University of Oxford, in the United Kingdom, told &lt;em&gt;Medical News Today&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Nearly 3 billion people worldwide are living with overweight or obesity. Weight gain usually happens slowly, over many years, and we still have limited evidence on how everyday behaviors can help prevent the build-up of fat in different body compartments over the long term. Fat that builds up deep in the abdomen around internal organs, known as visceral fat, is especially harmful. It raises the risk of cardiometabolic diseases and premature death. Finding effective ways to prevent this type of fat gain is therefore very important.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;— Shayan Aryannezhad, MD, MPH, PhD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aryannezhad is the first author of a new study published in the journal &lt;hl-trusted-source source="JAMA" rationale="Highly respected journal,Expert written journal,Peer reviewed journal"&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2841742" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;JAMA Network Open&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt;, which found that improving both diet and exercise levels at the same time may be more helpful in preventing weight gain, especially of visceral fat, than focusing on only one of those healthy lifestyle choices. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this study, researchers analyzed the health data of more than 7,000 study participants in the U.K.-based &lt;a href="https://studies.mrc-epid.cam.ac.uk/fenland" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Fenland study&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Study participants were at an average age of about 49 at the start of the Fenland study, which followed participants for an average of 7 years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participant follow-up included measuring physical activity energy expenditure for at least 72 hours, a &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/324553" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;DEXA scan&lt;/a&gt; to assess body fat, and an evaluation of participants’ adherence to the &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/324221" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Most long-term studies look at diet and physical activity separately, but people do not live their lives in isolated behaviors,” Aryannezhad said. “Evidence shows that clearer and more consistent links with health outcomes appear when we assess changes in both behaviors at the same time.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This may be because people often make compensatory changes,” he added. “For example, becoming more active may lead someone to eat more, or vice versa. Studying the behaviors together gives a more realistic understanding of how they influence long-term adiposity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the study’s conclusion, researchers found that participants who simultaneously improved their diet and physical activity levels had the highest reduction in body fat, while changing only one of those lifestyle choices was linked to moderate body fat improvements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists also discovered that after adjusting for &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/323586" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;body mass index (BMI)&lt;/a&gt;, the correlation of diet and physical activity changes resulted in significant changes to visceral fat levels, showing that visceral fat was specifically responsive to these healthy changes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Researchers reported that participants who improved diet and exercise at the same time increased on average about 1.9 kilograms (kg) less total body fat and 150 grams (g) less visceral fat than those who did not make both lifestyle improvements. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is a meaningful difference,” Aryannezhad explained. “Gaining 1.9 kg less total body fat represents about 7% of the average body fat in this population.“&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Previous research shows that around 10% increase in body fat is associated with an 11% higher risk of all-cause mortality. The additional 150 g less visceral fat is also important, as visceral fat is the most harmful type. This is approximately 16% of (the) total visceral fat of this population,” he emphasized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Improving both diet quality and physical activity was linked not only with less weight gain, but also with a healthier pattern of body fat distribution,” Aryannezhad continued. “Addressing both behaviors together appears to offer greater benefits than improving either one alone. These health behaviors should be seen as complementary strategies, not competing ones.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; spoke with &lt;a href="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/mir-b-ali" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Mir Ali&lt;/a&gt;, MD, a board certified general surgeon, bariatric surgeon, and medical director of MemorialCare Surgical Weight Loss Center at Orange Coast Medical Center in Fountain Valley, CA, about this study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ali, who was not involved in the research, commented that he thought this was a good study that showed the benefits of combining exercise and a healthy diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Visceral fat (around the abdomen) has been shown to increase the risk of diabetes, cardiovascular disease, and many other conditions,” he explained.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Any method that can reduce visceral fat is beneficial to the patient,“ said Ali. “More research into defining the optimal diets and exercises to eliminate and maintain visceral fat loss would be helpful.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; also spoke with &lt;a href="https://doctors.hackensackmeridianhealth.org/provider/seth-michael-kipnis/1316514" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Seth Kipnis&lt;/a&gt;, MD, FACS, FASMBS, director of bariatric and robotic surgery at Hackensack Meridian Jersey Shore University Medical Center in New Jersey, about this research, who said that this study provides evidence for the advice he gives to his patients every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Often, patients come frustrated, having tried to focus on just diet or just exercise without seeing the results they want, especially around their midsection,” Kipnis, who was not involved in the research, explained. “This study demonstrates that the combination of improving diet quality and increasing physical activity is the most effective strategy.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What’s particularly compelling is the use of advanced imaging like DEXA scans to differentiate between types of fat. I frequently explain to patients that the ‘belly fat’ we are most concerned about isn’t the fat you can pinch (subcutaneous fat), but the deeper visceral fat surrounding their organs. This study’s finding that a combined approach is especially effective at reducing this dangerous visceral fat. It is not just about the number on the scale but the overall body composition.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;— Seth Kipnis, MD, FACS, FASMBS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The finding that individuals who were overweight or inactive at the start of the study saw the greatest benefits is also very encouraging,” Kipnis added. “It provides a hopeful and motivating message for the very patients who often feel the most discouraged.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical News Today</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:32:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxPX09oRnk1S2ZxZWx6Yy1lVzVqeWs0TkFaeDIwbEVsU0hRMlJodFJDa0ZsN0ZwU1E5TWw1amVQdWRvRWJBeHNIcWhKQl80cnplSXlsUzZfeFVJQm1XQXBDTG9sYl9vaHJPZnhnanpYTUpMUXN6amJQMDNnUTNUNGRwOVpRZndpRHNMZFVxMGxmeDVvTXlUbHVaSjR1cWFfMEI2eXJHdi1ySk5tZw</guid></item><item><title>为什么你的身体需要额外的睡眠：揭示睡眠过度的7个隐藏原因-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/why-your-body-wants-extra-sleep-7-hidden-causes-of-oversleeping-revealed/articleshow/125618289.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oversleeping, defined as sleeping nine or more hours in 24 hours, can seem harmless, especially after a tiring week, but consistently sleeping too much often signals that something deeper is affecting your health. While sleep is essential for restoring energy, supporting immunity, and maintaining cognitive function, excessive sleep can leave you feeling groggy, unfocused, and unusually tired during the day. Many people who oversleep also experience headaches, low motivation, or the need for frequent naps, showing that the body may not be getting truly restorative rest. Oversleeping can be influenced by lifestyle habits, environmental disruptions, medical conditions, mental health issues, medications, or underlying sleep disorders. Understanding why you’re sleeping too much is the first step toward improving sleep quality, boosting daytime energy, and restoring a healthier sleep routine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;7 common causes of excessive sleep and daytime tiredness&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Drug and alcohol use &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain substances directly interfere with the brain chemicals responsible for alertness. When someone stops using stimulants like amphetamines or cocaine, the body enters a “rebound” phase. During this phase, the nervous system slows down to recover, creating intense sleepiness and longer sleep durations. A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39631226/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study published in PubMed Central&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; found that alcohol reduces restorative REM sleep and disrupts sleep architecture, leading to poor-quality rest, morning fatigue, and increased daytime sleepiness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Fix Your Sleep Naturally! Sadhguru’s 5-Step Routine for Deep Rest&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alcohol also has a complicated effect on sleep. It may help you fall asleep faster, but it reduces deep and REM sleep, the stages that restore energy and cognitive function. As a result, people often wake feeling unrefreshed and may sleep longer to compensate. Chronic alcohol use can disrupt brain signalling and worsen daytime tiredness, leading to unintentional dozing and difficulty staying awake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Environmental factors affecting sleep duration&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your environment and daily responsibilities can push your sleep schedule out of balance. For example, people caring for infants, older adults, or sick family members often get fragmented or insufficient sleep, causing their bodies to demand longer rest when possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Irregular routines such as late-night screen use, long work hours, or inconsistent bedtimes can confuse the body’s internal clock. Shift workers are especially affected because their sleep occurs at times when the brain naturally expects light or activity. This mismatch between work demands and biological rhythms can lead to chronic fatigue and oversleeping on off-days as the body tries to recover. Over time, this disruption may also increase stress, weaken immunity, affect mood, and impair cognitive function, making it harder to maintain consistent energy levels and overall health despite attempts to rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Illnesses that cause prolonged sleep&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you are sick, the immune system releases chemicals called cytokines that increase sleepiness to help the body heal. This is why respiratory infections such as flu, colds, or COVID-19 often make you sleep more than usual. However, even long hours of sleep during illness may not feel refreshing because the body is directing energy toward fighting infection. Fever, inflammation, and general weakness raise the need for rest, so extra sleep becomes the body’s natural response to promote recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Lack of sleep and sleep debt&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleep debt builds up when you consistently get less sleep than your body needs. Whether due to long workdays, late-night studying, travel, or stress, the body eventually reaches a point where it demands extra sleep to restore balance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While catching up on sleep can temporarily relieve exhaustion, it can also disrupt your sleep cycle if done frequently. Oversleeping after sleep deprivation may lead to irregular bedtimes, low morning energy, and difficulty falling asleep the next night, creating an ongoing cycle of poor sleep quality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Medications that lead to excessive sleep&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many medications contain compounds that slow down brain activity or nervous system responses. Antihistamines, for example, block alertness-related receptors, while some antidepressants and antipsychotics reduce brain stimulation, making you feel more tired. Pain medications, muscle relaxants, tranquillisers, and sleeping pills can also deepen or lengthen sleep beyond normal needs. A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37422714/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study published in Published in PubMed Central&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; concluded that many antidepressant medications alter sleep architecture, some with sedative effects that can prolong sleep or cause excessive daytime drowsiness. If you notice increased sleepiness after starting a new medication, it may indicate that your body is sensitive to its sedative effects, and a doctor can help adjust the dose or suggest alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Physical and mental health conditions linked to oversleeping&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oversleeping can be an early sign of underlying health conditions. Disorders like hypothyroidism slow down metabolism, causing fatigue and the need for more sleep. Diabetes, fibromyalgia, chronic pain, and chronic fatigue syndrome strain the body and reduce energy levels, making longer sleep periods common.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mental health conditions, especially depression, can significantly alter sleep patterns. Depression often leads to hypersomnia, where people sleep long hours but still feel exhausted because emotional stress interferes with restorative sleep. Anxiety can cause mental burnout and tension, which may lead to oversleeping as the body tries to cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Sleep disorders that cause excessive sleep&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain sleep disorders directly affect how long and how well you sleep:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Circadian rhythm sleep-wake disorders: These develop when your internal body clock falls out of sync with natural light-dark cycles. As a result, you may sleep at irregular times, struggle to wake up, or feel the need to oversleep to cope with the mismatch.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hypersomnolence disorder (hypersomnia): This condition causes persistent daytime sleepiness even after a full night’s sleep. People with hypersomnia often sleep much longer than usual, yet still wake up feeling unrefreshed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Narcolepsy: This neurological disorder leads to sudden and uncontrollable episodes of falling asleep during the day. These “sleep attacks” can happen during routine activities, making daytime functioning difficult.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Obstructive sleep apnoea: This condition repeatedly blocks or restricts airflow during sleep, causing brief awakenings and poor sleep quality. The constant disruption leads to extreme fatigue and a tendency to oversleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Restless leg syndrome: This disorder creates uncomfortable, tingling, or creeping sensations in the legs, especially at night. Because it interrupts sleep, the body tries to compensate with longer sleep periods or daytime sleepiness.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because these conditions affect sleep structure, the brain does not get the deep, restorative rest it needs, resulting in prolonged sleep times. Oversleeping is more than just sleeping late; it can signal an imbalance in the body, lifestyle, or overall sleep health. By understanding the underlying causes, whether environmental, medical, psychological, or behavioural, you can take steps to improve energy levels and restore healthy sleep patterns. If oversleeping persists or disrupts your daily life, consulting a healthcare professional can help identify and treat the root cause, leading to more balanced and restorative sleep&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for general informational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the guidance of a qualified healthcare provider regarding any medical condition or lifestyle change.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="72"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also Read: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/6-overnight-habits-that-stress-your-kidneys-and-affect-long-term-health/articleshow/125608700.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;6 overnight habits that stress your kidneys and affect long-term health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggJBVV95cUxPWW0yRzZVUTBOdEVyUkNESEZTS09INFUtamdfTmFjRlVpbWRoc0hfWHh0MEJTMFVMS2pfVHJYNklsMEZGVkw5dGFZdVJ5S0ZONXhwLWd3RkRnTWF3NXpaMm85dVRXOUVOZ0xDbXNSWERXWXpLWXlWN1QtRUJ3eFRpUEtyd0dJQnY0Y3gzV25PdjFVZm9MZmxmc3pLcVhWRzVEYk1RM1p1SWlGZlU0azJTb3lMLWpDbkhXRlNQVVdpWmhTc3c2RkJIMUpLTU50aFlwaXVwdFdCTXJLWlE1VklUZEFFWXNIZ1lOM1lzQW03djBoYUhlVVRLN1lqZUQ5Wlctb2fSAYcCQVVfeXFMTjdvY0ZSQU5JVHlrTV90dzM5aGRpdFhjYm5wQ0MwTzhvU2d0dlNtRXRqV0V0eHVBaDJhQWVFR0VnYTJlNUg3N0VLdDh5RzBZOHNINjQzVVU5djBPdkd5N2N2N2dMSzI2emx5OTZYOUpwSWp2elhhSGxNSnRyVTd6Vk5UUnhMU01VOGVyanVrbTJXa2ZoenAyYTNhOFducmtJamdHc1UzMG5UY0ZuOTdIMXlBUHRLM2tJVkVHTkxGZUwzWVI0XzAtdE9FUXhHSVhPZlloNzRkaV9IVXJ1RWpnVkRudWxUeFBYYllJeDNWX09JVkdPOUxpZ2FyYXkxQm9BWVBnY3Vfd0k</guid></item><item><title>Scorpion Venom可能提供下一个乳腺癌突破-好消息网络</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/scorpion-venom-may-provide-the-next-breast-cancer-breakthrough/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_226057" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-226057" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-226057" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/a-scorpion-credit-Marino-Linic-1024x616.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/a-scorpion-credit-Marino-Linic-1024x616.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/a-scorpion-credit-Marino-Linic-326x196.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/a-scorpion-credit-Marino-Linic-768x462.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/a-scorpion-credit-Marino-Linic-696x419.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/a-scorpion-credit-Marino-Linic-1068x642.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/a-scorpion-credit-Marino-Linic-698x420.jpg 698w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/a-scorpion-credit-Marino-Linic-530x319.jpg 530w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/a-scorpion-credit-Marino-Linic.jpg 1247w" sizes="(max-width: 696px) 100vw, 696px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-226057" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;– credit Marino Linic&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientists in Brazil are currently testing to see if the venom of an Amazonian scorpion could be used to poison breast cancer tumors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers at the University of São Paulo’s Preto School of Pharmaceutical Sciences (FCFRP-USP) have long worked to clone and express proteins from rattlesnake and scorpion venom with hopes of transforming these powerful compounds into medicines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, their work identified that venom of the scorpion &lt;em&gt;Brotheas amazonicus&lt;/em&gt; appears to attack breast cancer cells in a way similar to a widely used chemotherapy medication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These early findings were generated through a collaboration with scientists from the National Institute for Amazonian Research (INPA) and the Amazonas State University (UEA).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Through bioprospecting, we were able to identify a molecule in the species of this Amazonian scorpion that is similar to that found in the venoms of other scorpions and that acts against breast cancer cells,” &lt;a href="https://sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/11/251117095658.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; Eliane Candiani Arantes, a professor at FCFRP-USP and the coordinator of the project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arantes and her team identified two neurotoxins in scorpion venom with immunosuppressive effects. Working with collaborators at INPA and UEA, they found a peptide named BamazScplp1 in the venom of &lt;em&gt;Brotheas amazonicus&lt;/em&gt; that appears to have anti-tumor potential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ALSO CHECK OUT: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Laboratory tests showed that the peptide’s impact on breast cancer cells was comparable to paclitaxel, a commonly prescribed chemotherapy treatment. It primarily triggers necrosis, a form of cell death previously associated with molecules from other scorpion species.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arantes and her team have isolated other components of venoms from scorpions and from snakes that have been used to help develop other clinical applications, including an internal wound sealant that mimics the body’s natural clotting and scaffolding processes. It’s undergoing trials for use in nerve repair, bone healing, and restoring movement following spinal cord injury.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next time you see a scorpion, and think it a nasty creepy crawly that will send you to the hospital, show a bit of grace; they might help save a woman’s life some day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SHARE This Unlikely Focus Of Oncology With Your Friends… &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:30:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxQY3U4ZWVvYS1jN1hENDhlaHhlRmJ3cXpsTkFHOWRCdVR0MzZGRzl0WFRSbkFMbmZwYkdWbmMxazA3YjBvd1p6MGlaSngyMWs0WHlmbFQtZ2NJQ3NPbjZGOXZfYWJTNE9IU18tR2FMX1dmSnhUMDVoYmFhQUhHZV91aEJ1YzQ5X2lRTzNWNXNLSkpTU0dDVkl2ZVEzdw</guid></item><item><title>“Ozempic 2.0”即将推出，可以彻底改变减肥药物- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/ozempic-weight-loss-pills-fda-approval-387539-20251127</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p class="loading-bar_loader__2fNms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;main&gt;&lt;template id="B:0"&gt;&lt;/template&gt;&lt;p class="article-page-skeleton_background__h2J4n"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/main&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:29:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPSTFEdmlfQ0RCM0lPN1ZjN0tLVDdUc0pxVkZ2eTFHVDJpeDJwRDlzUkJFY2JSd2FldFExUGNnSEU0R3JSZTZXSE1XcE5ya0lvX0pSVFJVMTgzQVJXbXFjbzExazVPcTNfazdpVFQzdUxmSF90RFZQRGM1VHU5SlQyN3RUM1U3UW1CWVFkWC04M1pvMWRXREE</guid></item><item><title>调查陪审团发现， 12岁的女孩在医院失败后死亡-英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c058ppym6m2o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Girl, 12, died after hospital failings - inquest&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 gXJgDY"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 gqeTMs"&gt;Hayley Coyle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 bIfajQ"&gt;Sheffield Medico-Legal Centre&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251120-101800-81b2dab7dc-web-2.34.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/fea7/live/08936610-c9fa-11f0-b3d5-a53e36530b68.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/fea7/live/08936610-c9fa-11f0-b3d5-a53e36530b68.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/fea7/live/08936610-c9fa-11f0-b3d5-a53e36530b68.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/fea7/live/08936610-c9fa-11f0-b3d5-a53e36530b68.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/fea7/live/08936610-c9fa-11f0-b3d5-a53e36530b68.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/fea7/live/08936610-c9fa-11f0-b3d5-a53e36530b68.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/fea7/live/08936610-c9fa-11f0-b3d5-a53e36530b68.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/fea7/live/08936610-c9fa-11f0-b3d5-a53e36530b68.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Family handout Mia Lucas laughing" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Family handout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Mia Lucas died while being detained under the Mental Health Act on 30 January 2024&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A 12-year-old girl who took her own life while being detained under the Mental Health Act died following a series of failings by hospital staff, an inquest jury has found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Mia Lucas was found dead at the Becton Centre at Sheffield Children's Hospital on 30 January 2024 while suffering from an acute psychotic episode, partly triggered by an underlying brain disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Following a nine-day inquest, jurors found that inadequate testing by staff at Nottingham's Queen's Medical Centre (QMC) meant the condition had gone undetected and had "possibly contributed to Mia's death".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Speaking after the hearing Mia's mother Chloe Hayes said she would "never forgive" those responsible for the "failure to provide appropriate care to her in her time of need."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The inquest heard how Mia, from Arnold in Nottinghamshire, began to behave strangely over Christmas 2023 - hallucinating and hearing voices telling her to harm herself and her family - and was taken to QMC on New Year's Eve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Whilst there she was found to be experiencing an "acute psychotic episode" and was sectioned under the Mental Health Act.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The jury of five women and four men heard that blood tests and an MRI scan were carried out but came back negative and doctors ruled out a physical cause of Mia's psychosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, a lumbar puncture, which may have revealed she was suffering from the rare disorder autoimmune encephalitis which would have caused the acute psychosis, was not carried out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The jury said this meant "potential indicators... were missed".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Manjeet Shehmar, Medical Director at Nottingham University Hospitals NHS Trust, said: "I would like to offer my heartfelt condolences to Mia's family for the loss of their daughter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We accept the coroner's outcome in court today and apologise to Mia's family for not identifying autoimmune encephalitis while she was in our care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"While this is an incredibly rare condition and initial tests were negative, we recognise that further testing may have had an impact on her future, for which we are truly sorry."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251120-101800-81b2dab7dc-web-2.34.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/1c2a/live/86026a60-ca13-11f0-b881-37f4ac070994.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/1c2a/live/86026a60-ca13-11f0-b881-37f4ac070994.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/1c2a/live/86026a60-ca13-11f0-b881-37f4ac070994.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/1c2a/live/86026a60-ca13-11f0-b881-37f4ac070994.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/1c2a/live/86026a60-ca13-11f0-b881-37f4ac070994.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/1c2a/live/86026a60-ca13-11f0-b881-37f4ac070994.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/1c2a/live/86026a60-ca13-11f0-b881-37f4ac070994.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/1c2a/live/86026a60-ca13-11f0-b881-37f4ac070994.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Family handout Mia Lucas, wearing a riding helmet, stands next to a horse." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Family handout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Mia loved horses and spoke about her plans to become a vet, her mother said&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Mia was transferred on 9 January to the Becton Centre, one of the only mental health units in the country suitable for children aged 13 and under. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, the jury found the information passed between QMC and the Becton Centre "provided an inappropriate level of assurance that organic causes had been ruled out".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;While there Mia tried to harm herself four times, including on the morning of her death - an incident which failed to be logged in the shift handover notes - and was described as being "changeable and distressed". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But on the night of Mia's death Ms Hayes said she was told she was "settled".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, she received a phone call just after midnight to tell her Mia had self-harmed again and it was found that she did not have a pulse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The jury said while at the unit "insufficiently robust communication and management of risk had led to a failure to respond adequately to Mia's risk of self harm".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251120-101800-81b2dab7dc-web-2.34.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/e56e/live/605ebd30-c3d4-11f0-bdbe-6f7df1044786.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/e56e/live/605ebd30-c3d4-11f0-bdbe-6f7df1044786.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e56e/live/605ebd30-c3d4-11f0-bdbe-6f7df1044786.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/e56e/live/605ebd30-c3d4-11f0-bdbe-6f7df1044786.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/e56e/live/605ebd30-c3d4-11f0-bdbe-6f7df1044786.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/e56e/live/605ebd30-c3d4-11f0-bdbe-6f7df1044786.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/e56e/live/605ebd30-c3d4-11f0-bdbe-6f7df1044786.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e56e/live/605ebd30-c3d4-11f0-bdbe-6f7df1044786.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Family handout Mia pictured with her mother Chloe Hayes, both smiling with long hair." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Family handout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Mia pictured with her mother Chloe Hayes, who attended the inquest with other family members&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ms Hayes said: "It has been devastating to listen to how, when she needed specialist healthcare, for the first time in her life, she was so badly let down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"She was let down at the Queen's Medical Centre in Nottingham, who wrongly decided there was no underlying physical cause of her psychosis, and failed to carry out appropriate testing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I believe they simply dismissed her and looked to pass her onto mental health services as quickly as possible, which led to her transfer to the Becton Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Her mental health spiralled deeper out of control there, as she was not being treated for her condition, and the many failings and lack of care meant sadly she wasn't properly protected from harming herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"My beautiful little girl has lost her life and I will never forgive the Queen's Medical Centre or the Becton Centre for failing her."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She added: "I have never believed for a moment that Mia ever wanted to take her own life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"She was always a happy, healthy child and had so much to live for."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A spokesperson for Sheffield Children's NHS Foundation Trust said: "The inquest has been important to understand fully the circumstances surrounding Mia's death. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We will now carefully reflect on the evidence heard and the coroner's conclusions to ensure we continue to provide safe and compassionate care."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The inquest heard how since Mia's death the Becton Centre has made a number of changes to the facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Due to these "substantial and robust" changes, senior coroner Tanyka Rawden did not issue a Prevention of Future Deaths report. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She said she would also not be issuing one for the Queen's Medical Centre either, giving it six months to implement its changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However Mrs Rawden said she would be writing to Health Secretary Wes Streeting to raise her "concerns" regarding national guidelines into autoimmune encephalitis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 djqsWD"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:19:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9UOTFqcTlIaVZ0dk5CN2RUWWJVZEt5WXhQVGRldkstc1JiTmczaW1XSnl6RFJsRm9DVjZVMk14Tm13dUg4N013bENJamJTWDFHc1BxUGZjeHNEQdIBX0FVX3lxTE5zZzFJb1BNaG5HUjZaTWkzcEctUVdPYXVjM1VDd0N4bVVYS2xNUVNyZjBKYTEwemFEU0hlbzZYX1g4XzBNbUIzdHZjb2E0RFJDRTh4QzZBNUdMTE53SHBB</guid></item><item><title>抑制衰老的主调节因子在小鼠中再生关节软骨- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-inhibiting-master-aging-regenerates-joint.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOQXh4VFpIZC1UOG0zTnpILU9ObjVuOGdMdTJjTkdJSzJCM2ZYZnJwbXRRYnlKMzZ0QWc3STFObTE5SWpNQXRYNGRQcmZXTHc2ZEdLSkthRUxsNE9EblN0MVo1aGFkSUdHU3VIbWE5d1gwNzlLTFIxU1FGQjM5NDZHMjlzTmF1VG1QQzlVR3B3</guid></item><item><title>发烧有助于身体抵御病毒：但它是如何运作的？ - NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/11/27/nx-s1-5620766/fevers-viruses-cold-flu</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-99555" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Fever is part of the immune system's response to a pathogen, one that's shared with many animal species.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Cavan Images/iStockphoto/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Cavan Images/iStockphoto/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;For centuries, the nature of a fever — and whether it's good or bad — has been hotly contested.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In ancient Greece, the physician Hippocrates thought that fever had useful qualities, and could cook an illness out of a patient. Later on, around the 18th century, many physicians regarded fever as a distinct illness, one that could actually cook the patient, and so should be treated.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;These days, researchers understand that fever is part of&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2025/11/12/nx-s1-5580487/immune-health-test-immunome-precision-medicine" target="_blank"&gt; the immune system's response&lt;/a&gt; to a pathogen, one that's shared by many animal species. And while there's accumulating evidence that fevers can help kick an infection, precisely how they can help remains mysterious.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"There's a cultural knowledge that there's this relationship between temperature and viruses, but at a molecular level, we're quite unsure how temperature might be impacting viruses," says Sam Wilson,&lt;a href="https://www.immunology.cam.ac.uk/staff/professor-sam-wilson" target="_blank"&gt; a microbiologist at the University of Cambridge&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;There are two main ideas, he says. The heat of a fever itself could be harming the virus, akin to Hippocrates' hypotheses. Alternatively, the heat is a means to an end, either stoking our immune system to work better, or simply a regrettable, but unavoidable byproduct of fighting off an infection.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The fact that there weren't definitive answers to these questions piqued my interest," says Wilson. That interest &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.adq4691?adobe_mc=MCMID%3D82649840174138400580474904999936302642%7CMCORGID%3D242B6472541199F70A4C98A6%2540AdobeOrg%7CTS%3D1764178729" target="_blank"&gt;led to a study, published Thursday&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;em&gt;Science&lt;/em&gt;, that suggests — at least in mice — that elevated temperature alone is enough to fight off some viruses.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Reaching this conclusion was tricky, says Wilson, since it's very difficult to disentangle the effects of a fever itself from the immune response that usually comes with it. "The stars had to align," he says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;To put this question to the test, Wilson and his colleagues first needed a pathogen. They settled &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/11/06/nx-s1-5600125/bird-flu-risk-outbreak-trump-administration" target="_blank"&gt;on bird flu&lt;/a&gt;, because birds run hotter than humans.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The influenza A viruses that infect birds target their guts, which are a few degrees warmer than the airways favored by human influenza viruses. "This means that bird flus are adapted to replicate at a higher temperature, a temperature equivalent to that of a human fever," says Wilson.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;The researchers pinpointed a part of the bird flu genome that helps the virus thrive in this warm environment, called PB1. They then inserted this heat-tolerant snippet into a human flu virus. This gave them two nearly identical versions of influenza, a normal human one, and a heat-tolerant one.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;Those two strains allowed the researchers to ask what impact this ability to replicate at different temperatures might have on disease. They needed an animal to test the question, and laboratory mice turned out to be ideally suited.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It just so happens mice don't mount their own fever to an influenza infection," says Wilson.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So the team simulated one by housing some mice at slightly elevated temperatures. Then they exposed the mice to either the normal human influenza virus, or the heat-tolerant version.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Under normal laboratory temperatures, mice infected with both strains got sick.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But when the team turned up the heat, a key difference emerged. Mice infected with the heat-resistant strain got sick, but those infected with the normal strain seemed relatively unscathed, suggesting the heat itself helped fight off the flu.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"This study reinforces the idea that temperature alone is an important and effective," part of the body's attempt to respond to infection, says Daniel Barreda, &lt;a href="https://apps.ualberta.ca/directory/person/dbarreda" target="_blank"&gt;a microbiologist at the University of Alberta&lt;/a&gt; who wasn't involved in the research. But he says the study doesn't rule out that fever also helps the immune system work better, which could be important for fighting off viruses that aren't as sensitive to temperature as influenza.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Joe Alcock,&lt;a href="https://vivo.health.unm.edu/display/n7040" target="_blank"&gt; an emergency physician and researcher&lt;/a&gt; at the University of New Mexico, also praises the study. But he points out that we shouldn't assume fevers work the same way in humans as they do in mice.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Still, Alcock says the study adds to the growing body of evidence that fever evolved for a reason. As a physician trained by a health care system that's often quick to treat fevers, that gives him pause.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"We treat fevers as almost like a knee jerk reaction, giving medicines like acetaminophen or tylenol," he says. Of course, in many circumstances treating fever is appropriate, since those high temperatures can damage human cells, too. But he says it should raise questions about when we should reach for Tylenol or ibuprofen when we've got a viral cold.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Is it possible that by taking Tylenol or ibuprofen for a viral infection, that I might be actually making it tougher for my body to get rid of the infection?" says Alcock. "That's as yet an unanswered question."&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   
   

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE1pTkc4Z3UyYUk4WEZPdWRaSjZtdm1lRm1sZFdGNXBtQXpGQldKcFVyNWthazBjN0x2Q1hXWkw5YVRrNGdrWDRxSXQyZk5Ha2IxM2VKZ09tRjJJbmZWblRJejRFem1WY2VvMmloY1Bodmdoc2pzTDVn</guid></item><item><title>据报道，美国将不再纪念世界艾滋病日--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/nov/27/world-aids-day</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;For the first time since 1988, the US government will no longer commemorate World Aids Day, according to reports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The state department has directed its employees and grant recipients not to use US government funds to mark the event – which falls annually on 1 December – and not to promote the day publicly. The news was first reported by the &lt;a href="https://www.substack.com/home/post/p-179940743" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;journalist&lt;/a&gt; Emily Bass and confirmed in an email viewed by &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/26/health/trump-us-world-aids-day.html?smid=nytcore-ios-share&amp;amp;referringSource=articleShare" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the New York Times&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Employees and grantees could still “tout the work” on Aids being done through various programs “to counter this dangerous disease and other infectious diseases around the world”, the email reportedly said. They may also attend events related to the commemoration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But they should “refrain from publicly promoting World Aids Day through any communication channels, including social media, media engagements, speeches or other public-facing messaging”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The email also reportedly said the government’s policy is “to refrain from messaging on any commemorative days, including World AIDS Day”, even though &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/donaldtrump" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Donald Trump&lt;/a&gt; has issued proclamations &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/proclamations/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;for dozens of other observances&lt;/a&gt;, including World Intellectual Property Day and National Manufacturing Day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“An awareness day is not a strategy,” a state department spokesperson, Tommy Piggott, told the New York Times. “Under the leadership of President Trump, the state department is working directly with foreign governments to save lives and increase their responsibility and burden sharing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Every year since 1988, the &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;US&lt;/a&gt; has marked 1 December as World Aids Day to honor those who have lost their lives to the disease, to recognize and highlight efforts to contain the epidemic, and to raise awareness among the general public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Last year, in a cermony on the South Lawn, &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/joebiden" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Joe Biden&lt;/a&gt; hosted the first White House display of Aids memorial quilt panels memorializing more than 110,000 lives lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Since returning to the White House, Trump has &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/feb/26/trump-usaid-cuts" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;cancelled&lt;/a&gt; foreign aid programs that &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/feb/28/usaid-funding-health-development-hiv-aids-antiretroviral-mothers-lgbt-sex-workers-south-africa" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;combat&lt;/a&gt; HIV and Aids, scrapped &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/mar/31/trump-administration-hiv-research-grant-cuts" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; and prevention resources, and restricted &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/mar/17/hiv-aids-pepfar-christians-trump" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;funding&lt;/a&gt; under the two-decade-old President’s Emergency Plan for Aids Relief, or Pepfar, the government’s global HIV program established under the Republican president George W Bush, which is estimated to have &lt;a href="https://www.state.gov/results-and-impact-pepfar" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;prevented 25 million early deaths&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;World Aids Day is usually when the state department shares Pepfar data about cumulative and annual progress with Congress. It’s not clear if the department still plans to send it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The state department has not yet replied to a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="0539cc37-42c4-4e66-a3a6-121838973f16" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.GuideAtomBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="GuideAtomWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props="{&amp;quot;id&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;ea05a110-2f0f-41ea-ba0a-8d9189dbddb7&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Contact us about this story&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;html&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The best public interest journalism relies on first-hand accounts from people in the know.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you have something to share on this subject, you can contact us confidentially using the following methods.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Secure Messaging in the Guardian app&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Guardian app has a tool to send tips about stories. Messages are end to end encrypted and concealed within the routine activity that every Guardian mobile app performs. This prevents an observer from knowing that you are communicating with us at all, let alone what is being said.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you don't already have the Guardian app, download it (&amp;lt;a href=\&amp;quot;https://apps.apple.com/app/the-guardian-live-world-news/id409128287\&amp;quot;&amp;gt;iOS&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;/&amp;lt;a href=\&amp;quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.guardian\&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Android&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;) and go to the menu. Select ‘Secure Messaging’. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;SecureDrop, instant messengers, email, telephone and post&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you can safely use the Tor network without being observed or monitored, you can send messages and documents to the Guardian via our &amp;lt;a href=\&amp;quot;https://www.theguardian.com/securedrop\&amp;quot;&amp;gt;SecureDrop platform&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Finally, our guide at &amp;lt;a href=\&amp;quot;https://www.theguardian.com/tips\&amp;quot;&amp;gt;theguardian.com/tips&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;lists several ways to contact us securely, and discusses the pros and cons of each.&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;image&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://i.guim.co.uk/img/media/ae475ccca7c94a4565f6b500a485479f08098383/788_0_4000_4000/4000.jpg?width=620&amp;amp;quality=85&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;fit=max&amp;amp;s=45fd162100b331bf1618e364c5c69452&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Illustration: Guardian Design / Rich Cousins&amp;quot;}"&gt;&lt;div data-atom-id="ea05a110-2f0f-41ea-ba0a-8d9189dbddb7" data-atom-type="guide" class="dcr-13gln72"&gt;&lt;details data-atom-id="ea05a110-2f0f-41ea-ba0a-8d9189dbddb7" data-snippet-type="guide" class="dcr-g1vsnw"&gt;&lt;summary&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1ypwo6h"&gt;Quick Guide&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h4 class="dcr-1fa5dcn"&gt;Contact us about this story&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-55zfp0"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-3j53am"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-41evle"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="-3 -3 30 30" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" focusable="false" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="m10.8 13.2.425 9.8h1.525l.45-9.8 9.8-.45v-1.525l-9.8-.425-.45-9.8h-1.525l-.425 9.8-9.8.425v1.525z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Show&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.guim.co.uk/img/media/ae475ccca7c94a4565f6b500a485479f08098383/788_0_4000_4000/4000.jpg?width=620&amp;amp;quality=85&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;fit=max&amp;amp;s=45fd162100b331bf1618e364c5c69452" alt="" class="dcr-1vs4o7z"&gt;&lt;div class="dcr-17vpao5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best public interest journalism relies on first-hand accounts from people in the know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have something to share on this subject, you can contact us confidentially using the following methods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secure Messaging in the Guardian app&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Guardian app has a tool to send tips about stories. Messages are end to end encrypted and concealed within the routine activity that every Guardian mobile app performs. This prevents an observer from knowing that you are communicating with us at all, let alone what is being said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you don't already have the Guardian app, download it (&lt;a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/the-guardian-live-world-news/id409128287"&gt;iOS&lt;/a&gt;/&lt;a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.guardian"&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt;) and go to the menu. Select ‘Secure Messaging’. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SecureDrop, instant messengers, email, telephone and post&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you can safely use the Tor network without being observed or monitored, you can send messages and documents to the Guardian via our &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/securedrop"&gt;SecureDrop platform&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, our guide at &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/tips"&gt;theguardian.com/tips&lt;/a&gt; lists several ways to contact us securely, and discusses the pros and cons of each. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="dcr-1ujsssp"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="-3 -3 30 30" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" focusable="false" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;path d="M12 2C6.467 2 2 6.467 2 12s4.467 10 10 10 10-4.467 10-10S17.533 2 12 2m1.133 13.933v.49c-.11.088-.266.155-.422.244a13 13 0 0 1-.511.2 2.4 2.4 0 0 1-.533.133 4 4 0 0 1-.511.044c-.356 0-.578-.066-.712-.2a.58.58 0 0 1-.222-.444c0-.178.022-.356.045-.533.022-.178.066-.356.11-.578l.934-4.245-.867-.2v-.466c.134-.045.312-.111.556-.178.222-.067.467-.111.733-.156.267-.044.511-.088.756-.11.244-.023.467-.045.667-.045l.244.155-1.244 5.89zm.423-7.466c-.2.177-.49.266-.823.266q-.465 0-.8-.266a.88.88 0 0 1-.31-.69c0-.31.11-.555.31-.733q.3-.266.8-.266c.356 0 .623.089.823.266s.31.423.31.734c-.022.289-.11.51-.31.689"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;p&gt;Illustration: Guardian Design / Rich Cousins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/details&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 18:03:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE55QlFLZFd0THF1R0hrX1pFRDMtSWVMeEFleGdmM0twVnI0b2w5Z1hHYWxHU2FlcFdPSkN2ck93QlhYaV9vOXNtUmZTTGtwRXpjNDFITlBiY1h6MU9KZVJaTGVTUnFKNDEzVW8wYl9ZYw</guid></item><item><title>常见的妊娠并发症可能会增加儿童自闭症的风险：新研究-纽约邮报</title><link>https://nypost.com/2025/11/27/health/pregnancy-complication-may-increase-risk-of-autism-in-children/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom"&gt;
							


&lt;p&gt;Move Over, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/health/what-the-science-says-about-tylenol-autism-ahead-of-rfk-jr-report/"&gt;Tylenol&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/jcem/advance-article/doi/10.1210/clinem/dgaf596/8339900?login=false" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;New research&lt;/a&gt; suggests that a common — but often overlooked — pregnancy complication may increase your chances of having a child with &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/07/09/health/the-4-new-subtypes-of-autism-explained/"&gt;autism spectrum disorder&lt;/a&gt; (ASD).&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The good news? If you treat it, the risk doesn’t seem to rise. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Researchers are exploring how various prenatal conditions might affect the risk of autism.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;pressmaster – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In the study, researchers looked at more than 51,000 women in Israel who gave birth between 2011 and 2017. Of them, 4,409 had abnormal thyroid hormone levels — some before pregnancy, some during and some both. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="connatix-outstream-video"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team followed the women through January 2021 and found that thyroid dysfunction before and during pregnancy more than doubled the chances of their child having autism.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;An estimated &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/autism/data-research/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;1 in 31 children age 8 and older in the US&lt;/a&gt; has been diagnosed with ASD, a disorder affecting learning, behavior, communication and social interaction.  &lt;/p&gt;


	



&lt;p&gt;The researchers also discovered that the longer the thyroid problems lasted, the higher the likelihood of autism became. For example, children whose mothers had low thyroid hormone levels through all three trimesters faced more than three times the risk of being diagnosed with autism.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But there’s a silver lining: when thyroid problems were properly controlled during pregnancy, the risk didn’t rise significantly.  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“We found that while adequately treated chronic thyroid dysfunction was not associated with increased autism risk in offspring, ongoing imbalance across multiple trimesters was,” &lt;a href="https://www.idanme.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Dr. Idan Menashe&lt;/a&gt;, a senior lecturer at Ben-Gurion University of the Negev and one of the study’s authors, said in &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1106734" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;a statement&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Hyperthyroidism occurs when the gland is overactive and produces too many hormones, whereas hypothyroidism occurs when it produces too few. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;amazing studio – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The thyroid is a small, butterfly-shaped gland at the front of your neck, just below the Adam’s apple. It produces hormones that regulate your metabolism, energy levels and other vital functions.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Those hormones are also critical for fetal brain development, especially early in pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;They help neurons grow, move and form connections, which is essential for communication in the brain. Thyroid hormones also support the development of brain structures and the production of myelin, the fatty coating that helps nerve signals travel quickly. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Thyroid disease — an umbrella term for conditions that affect the gland’s ability to produce hormones — is the second most common endocrine disorder among women of reproductive age. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;When left untreated during pregnancy, thyroid problems have been linked to miscarriage, pre-eclampsia, premature birth, low birth weight and potential long-term effects on the child.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Yet in the US and many countries, routine thyroid testing isn’t part of standard pregnancy care, according to &lt;a href="https://www.palomahealth.com/learn/tylenol-vaccines-maternal-hypothyroidism-adhd-autism?srsltid=AfmBOor9ZS32uuxEScUiyWLc7LY590y_Bk0YVVphuztRE_9RdGx1pEVH" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Paloma Health&lt;/a&gt;, a virtual clinic specializing in patients with thyroid conditions.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Autism is a developmental disorder that can lead to social, communication and behavioral challenges.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;ÃÂ¡ÃÂ²ÃÂµÃâÃÂ»ÃÂ°ÃÂ½ÃÂ° ÃÅÃÂ¸Ãâ°ÃÂµÃÂ½ÃÂºÃÂ¾ – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Doctors usually only check if a woman has risk factors — like a personal or family history of thyroid problems, autoimmune conditions or past pregnancy complications — or if she shows symptoms like fatigue, weight changes or a rapid heartbeat. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That leaves a lot of women flying under the radar. In fact, up to 60% of people with thyroid disease don’t even know they have it, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.thyroid.org/media-main/press-room/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;American Thyroid Association&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;As a result, many moms-to-be may have untreated thyroid problems, which could put their child at a higher risk for autism.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“These findings underscore the need for routine monitoring and timely adjustment of therapy to maintain normal thyroid hormone levels throughout pregnancy,” Menashe said. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="comments-inline-cta" data-comment-count data-prompt="What do you think?"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Untreated thyroid issues during pregnancy have also been linked to other neurodevelopmental disorders, like &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/05/23/health/1-in-9-us-children-diagnosed-with-adhd/"&gt;ADHD&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.thieme-connect.com/products/ejournals/abstract/10.1055/s-0040-1717073" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;large US study in 2020&lt;/a&gt; found that children whose mothers had underactive thyroids with low hormone levels shortly before or early in pregnancy were 24% more likely to develop ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Our findings make clear that thyroid health likely has a much larger role in fetal brain development and behavioral disorders like ADHD than we previously understood,” Dr. Morgan R. Peltier, a professor at NYU Long Island School of Medicine and the study’s lead author, said in &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/news/reduced-hormone-supply-pregnant-mothers-linked-adhd-their-children"&gt;a statement&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;

												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:42:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxPTnI0SVVLMjEtd3h0R1BnYm9mQ0hjV1lxTFVSQl92cHNoZDhUeHNwYkNCNVN0ZW1Hd25FeFFvaXNsTDhUTVpKaWV5VG9tNFFPT0NjXzFueENiNWREd1lQWHBRUXZKYmdHX2xVVnRQblM3U2JxQ0RkajhQd1JZWl9JRzdlQjVkOUM4MW03N3Z4c1p4WlBsRkdDaXFNczhaRFB0WGc</guid></item><item><title>医疗专业人士正在分享他们希望更多人知道的“拯救生命的秘密” - BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/abbyzinman/nurses-life-saving-medical-secrets</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-20
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="cleaning" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139708141" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title  "&gt;
    
      &lt;span class="subbuzz__number"&gt;9.&lt;/span&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;"Nurses are not obligated to put our health or safety on the line for our jobs. No exceptions. Spare me your martyrdom/hero fetish."&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;–&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/ImmaculateDecepti0n/" target="_blank"&gt;ImmaculateDecepti0n&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My body is not your jungle gym to ruin all because you need help getting up to the bathroom. I am not lifting you up to stand, you are using as much of your own power as you can and I am making up the difference. Yes, I may be a big, strong human, but that doesn't mean my back doesn't get hurt."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;–&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/AnytimeInvitation/" target="_blank"&gt;AnytimeInvitation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:01:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE1BZUNCUGk0WHJ0WEtsQ1B3eXJmZjNWd1JYVGFLVUg0U0pVb0oyUjRKTThVRWdoVC15amJHVzQ4Y2JzWXNtd19xSVlQZkMxcVBHbEJ3Wk5VeHNxckhPTzZ6ODNfY2lRYVl3WVVuT1VGNUR2VkZtc24tV2Zn</guid></item></channel></rss>