<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>生酮饮食与奇怪的瘙痒皮疹有关-但没有人知道为什么- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/health/2026/01/a-weird-itchy-rash-is-linked-to-the-keto-diet-but-no-one-knows-why/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
          
          
&lt;h2&gt;Diet downsides&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, the keto diet is popular among people trying to lose weight, particularly those trying to lose visceral fat, like the man in the case study. Anecdotal reports promote the keto diet as being effective at helping people slim down relatively quickly while also improving stamina and mental clarity. But robust clinical data supporting these claims are lacking, and medical experts have raised concerns about long-term cardiovascular health, among other things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are also clear downsides to the diet. Ketones are acidic, and if they build up too much in the blood, they can be toxic, causing ketoacidosis. This is a particular concern for people with type 1 diabetes and for people with chronic alcohol abuse. For everyone else, there’s a list of &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK499830/"&gt;common side effects&lt;/a&gt;, including nausea, vomiting, constipation, diarrhea, bad breath, headache, fatigue, and dizziness. Ketogenic diets are also linked to high cholesterol and kidney stones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there’s one side effect that’s well established but little known and still puzzling to doctors: the “keto rash” or &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK599559/"&gt;prurigo pigmentosa&lt;/a&gt;. This rash fits the man’s case perfectly—red, raised, itchy bumps on the neck, chest, and back, with areas of hyperpigmentation also developing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rash was first identified in Japan in 1971, where it was mostly seen in women. While it has been consistently linked to metabolic disorders and dietary changes, experts still don’t understand what causes it. It’s seen not only in people on a keto diet but also in people with diabetes and those who have had bariatric surgery or are fasting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1155/drp/1993385"&gt;a review this month&lt;/a&gt;, researchers in Saudi Arabia noted that a leading hypothesis is that the high levels of ketones in the blood trigger inflammation around blood vessels driven by a type of white blood cell called neutrophils, and this inflammation is what causes the rash, which develops in different stages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the condition remains poorly understood, effective treatments have at least been worked out. The most common treatment is to get the person out of ketosis and give them an antibiotic in the tetracycline class. Antibiotics are designed to treat bacterial infections (which this is not), but they can also dampen inflammation signals and thwart the activity of neutrophils.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the man’s case, doctors gave him a two-week course of doxycycline and told him to ditch his keto diet. A week later, the rash was gone.&lt;/p&gt;


          
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                  
          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:00:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNOTgwd1dsUW1pSTAtUXROb3M5QTF6c09QdTVwdXVyZVVyWlFKQmxhWmMxU3NLaDZXWVZOMUUtVVFnS0lHcGd0dmR3OEtmckNweXRoLTdRSnoxX2FnajJkOU1hSmRwNUFSeEVfQ3NQU2VjMGNCWGpYMlpKUmg0ZmtnMFdQVEJsNV9KdDhzQXFDakYyY0YzMU5xSWk3MTRDRnJLclU2QnhDYUdFdw</guid></item><item><title>关于医学和医疗保健的6个播客-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/24/arts/podcasts-medicine-health-science.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:00:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxOd1h5RVF1VnhjR1JEY2hDNTJxTWttcDJxMW9CVnIwOWtuLWI3SzdRYXE3THlBSHBVMkVKRGlINGUzb1ZNdUlsMmx6MHJhUG9xRjZ2Rk5QLU1YNTdhenRBeHlUM0VraFE1VjRoQjBaQk9KQWZPSG9URkd1dkJwbTFfc1ljNA</guid></item><item><title>随着年龄的增长，忘记肌肉质量，专注于力量-纽约时报</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/24/well/move/muscle-strength-versus-mass.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:00:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNTFpnUUNCMl9IamxhdzF3Y042WW10VmNJazMtN0g0NXJnd2Nia3QyTnBqeXNXM0c3SnBNSVptYnlHRmRfZGFocjkxUGlkYS00ejFpeW5FeHkya05QRnEtVEdMZTRGd1FzdFNLTHFCUFJ0OFI5RDQwMmc3UjBYMlg3ZllqVQ</guid></item><item><title>专家说，即使你锻炼身体，这种日常习惯也会缩短你的寿命--《独立报》</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/health-and-fitness/sitting-work-heart-disease-risk-live-longer-b2897509.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 gIQPHK sc-jbiisr-1 sc-1wfc891-0 fooWDH" id="main"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="big-letter"&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;re you sitting comfortably? Probably. According to the NHS, many UK adults spend upwards of nine hours each day sitting down. But too much sitting could seriously damage your health, according to &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.brunel.ac.uk/news-and-events/news/articles/Sitting-for-long-stretches-raises-heart-and-diabetes-risks"&gt;new research&lt;/a&gt; from Brunel University – even if you meet weekly &lt;a href="/topic/exercise"&gt;exercise&lt;/a&gt; recommendations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We reviewed the published evidence available regarding associations between sedentary behaviour [sitting or lying down] and different risk markers for &lt;a href="/topic/heart-disease"&gt;cardiovascular disease&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="/topic/diabetes"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; in people aged 60 and above,” says sedentary behaviour specialist Dr Daniel Bailey who is, perhaps predictably, stationed at a standing desk during our video call. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The review found that people who sat down for large chunks of their day were far more likely to have a higher waist circumference and body fat levels. They also recorded worse readings for several biomarkers linked to heart disease and diabetes, such as blood pressure, glucose levels, triglycerides and cholesterol. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Those risks were there regardless of the amount of physical activity these older adults were engaging in,” he adds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How much sitting is too much?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people spend upwards of eight hours at a desk each day. Add in the journey home from work and sofa time watching telly, and it’s easy to see how daily sitting times are so high for many of us. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Over the past few decades, we’ve seen all of this technology come into play, which gives us more opportunities to sit down,” Dr Bailey says. “With that, we have seen a massive increase in obesity and the diseases that come with it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data suggests older populations are the most sedentary group, and it is this demographic that will likely experience the greatest benefits from cutting down their daily sitting time. However, Dr Bailey adds, “It is an important consideration for all ages,” with studies on children and working-age adults also linking excessive sitting to increased health risks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Some studies show the threshold is somewhere between seven and 10 hours of sitting per day being too much,” Dr Bailey tells me. “That’s where your risk of early mortality and several different diseases really starts to increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/strength-training-for-longevity-b2826608.html"&gt;The science-backed exercise method that can help fight the effects of ageing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obviously, if you move less, you burn less energy during the day, which can contribute to weight gain. Muscles can lose strength when unused, joints can become stiff, and because you are asking less of your heart and lungs each day, fitness can fade away. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 bcLYNA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2019/11/08/16/woman-work-desk.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2019/11/08/16/woman-work-desk.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2019/11/08/16/woman-work-desk.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Many people spend nine hours or more of their day sitting down, according to the NHS" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-264724"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Many people spend nine hours or more of their day sitting down, according to the NHS&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research shows that the negative effects of excessive sedentary time are linked to the amount of time you spend sitting down at a time. “There have been a number of studies that show the benefits of breaking up your sedentary time every 30 to 60 minutes,” explains. Dr Bailey added that the mechanism behind this is not yet fully understood. He describes it as a series of “metabolic switches that help regulate blood sugar, glucose levels and cholesterol levels.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you’re not doing regular muscular contractions, these metabolic switches switch off. That’s when we get higher levels of glucose in the blood, higher cholesterol in the blood, and our blood pressure isn’t as well regulated.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/10000-steps-walking-workout-heart-health-b2886117.html"&gt;If you struggle to walk 10,000 steps a day, a scientist recommends trying this instead&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to fight back&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The primary ways to fight the negative effects of sitting down is to do less of it, and to ensure you are getting regular muscular contractions – ie using your muscles and moving. Based on his research, Dr Bailey prescribes trying to move in some form every 30 to 60 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 bHmhpR"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/24/13/iStock-2210705103.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/24/13/iStock-2210705103.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/24/13/iStock-2210705103.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Regular muscular contractions – through moving or simply standing up – can combat the negative effects of too much sitting" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-264725"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Regular muscular contractions – through moving or simply standing up – can combat the negative effects of too much sitting&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Every movement counts,” he says. “We’ve published a lot of studies in our group that show how regular, short bouts of light activity keep these metabolic switches turned on, and your blood sugar levels and cholesterol stay lower throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It doesn’t need to be structured exercise. Simply standing up seems to be beneficial in people that are overweight, obese or have type two diabetes. We’ve also looked at slow walking – people can get these metabolic benefits from things we do in our everyday lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Every half an hour, get up, move around for a few minutes, and that should help reduce your risk of the different diseases we’ve discussed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/exercise-snacking-workouts-heart-health-b2859776.html"&gt;The science-backed two-minute daily workouts for improving heart health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another easy change Dr Bailey suggests is reorganising your workstation to encourage more movement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Changing your setup so not everything is at hand can help,” he explains. “If you need a pen, to print something or put something in the bin, having those things located away from your desk might encourage you to move more often. And rather than sending a colleague an email, go and talk to them at their desk.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 iLHiBm"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/17/15/12/iStock-2194826147.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/17/15/12/iStock-2194826147.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/17/15/12/iStock-2194826147.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Dr Daniel Bailey recommends moving for a few minutes every half an hour where possible" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-264726"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Dr Daniel Bailey recommends moving for a few minutes every half an hour where possible&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;You could also make a conscious effort to move after you finish certain tasks at your computer, he adds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Sometimes you might ignore an alert to move from your wearable or an app because you are working on something. Instead, wait until the end of a task, then use that as your cue to get up and move around. If you’re working from home, you could spread your housework across the day rather than doing it in one big chunk, and use these opportunities to do it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Reap the benefits &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is that the results of reducing your daily sitting time and making even these small tweaks are pretty remarkable. “If we can limit our sedentary time and be physically active, we’re going to live a longer and healthier life, which is what I think we’re all striving for,” says Dr Bailey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Benefits you might see and feel quite quickly are [a] better mood, more energy and less fatigue. Then, in the longer term, you might start to see reductions in body fat or body weight because you are burning more calories from movement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The deeper impacts won’t be as obvious, but you could benefit from a reduction in blood sugar levels and a reduction in blood pressure. That will help reduce your risk of heart disease, stroke, diabetes and some cancers as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/heart-health-attack-cardio-exercise-b2785415.html"&gt;A cardiac nurse says these five daily behaviours can reduce your risk of heart disease&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxQM3ZmU291bUhjUFRiX0kwQUJsTDUtVFJybVlJR2MxbUlENW1yTnRQUENtZlMwYVBSMkRUWE5xeUUyMWlVcURISU5HUTkwNjk3dVFfNm15SFBNMWFRYmEybkxwYk55WmFkYkRySW1RS0FoaUVJMlM3dGRzOTR5VHU2WTNwSFRhZ2lLWXhUcWdtMkhWN09rWk51SDRlNzFqM2lTS0RKNjA2VXpGQQ</guid></item><item><title>官员说，感染麻疹的成年人在传染期间访问了克拉克县的高中- kptv.com</title><link>https://www.kptv.com/2026/01/24/adult-with-measles-visited-high-school-clark-county-while-contagious-county-officials-say/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body | article w-100"&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;RIDGEFIELD, Wash. (KPTV) - Clark County Public Health says an adult with a confirmed case of measles was at a local high school while they were contagious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Health officials say the person, whose vaccination status is unverified, was at Ridgefield High School from January 14 through January 16 while they were contagious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Anyone who was at Ridgefield High School during those days and has not been vaccinated or has not had measles in the past are at risk of getting sick, according to the department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Clark County Public Health says they are working with Ridgefield School District to identify students and staff who are not protected against measles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="w-100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;No other public locations have been identified as possible exposure sites in this case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Community members who gave questions about the vaccine or are unsure if they’re protected should contact their healthcare provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Vaccination records are also available through Washington’s &lt;a href="https://links.us1.defend.egress.com/Warning?crId=697439c7e1768fa5cf912299&amp;amp;Domain=gray.tv&amp;amp;Threat=eNpzrShJLcpLzAEADmkDRA%3D%3D&amp;amp;Lang=en&amp;amp;Base64Url=eNrLKCkpKLbS18-tzCzKzU_KzEnVS87P1QcAad4IoQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;@OriginalLink=myirmobile.com" rel="" title="https://links.us1.defend.egress.com/Warning?crId=697439c7e1768fa5cf912299&amp;amp;Domain=gray.tv&amp;amp;Threat=eNpzrShJLcpLzAEADmkDRA%3D%3D&amp;amp;Lang=en&amp;amp;Base64Url=eNrLKCkpKLbS18-tzCzKzU_KzEnVS87P1QcAad4IoQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;@OriginalLink=myirmobile.com"&gt;MyIR Mobile system&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="copyright |"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Copyright 2026 KPTV-KPDX. All rights reserved.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>kptv.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:33:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxPdHhCUE1RWXl5aDZacE1ka1hqRXppYlhtalRaN284MnJjUHVJLUJZaFlHMkhiek9yRUd0M2NSblBOV19WNHhPeG1kYzBrXzVZRVVab3BqVWt2QkwxM19kVE5KdjVDd1V1a1RUSkR3ekFzN2hSUC12bTYwaWwyYmpMcEx1TXYtSGtnNXdUOE1zNVlDQWV3OUVYNWUwVC1TdEM4UkswU2h6NEdyTzhiR3JMbGxzLTBSb2lpZjF0OGkzSQ</guid></item><item><title>美国疫苗小组负责人质疑脊髓灰质炎建议-路透社</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-vaccine-panel-head-questions-polio-recommendation-2026-01-23/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Reuters</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:04:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPODk1VnVxYTlXWTI2bjZKY21kWExoaV9HdlZRand3SlZrSnhxeGM5cFVnaFNYZGdrS09BY3VKN2YzTWw5SDU1eVMwc1JIX3Q0eURadlhpc2h0dVhsdng3UWV0S0I1WXFBSFpzX1ItYVRnUFEtV09CMnlJMEo5cmEzc3ZrcEpSU2pIZjFnaTI0WW1LQWl3TlZaX0dGdS1uQXMxQm1CVkZpNjFieE9ya2R1S1RYQkw2bzJ1TW9ncUlpN05WUQ</guid></item><item><title>研究揭示了您每周需要进行多少运动来控制血压- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/study-reveals-how-much-exercise-you-need-weekly-to-control-blood-pressure</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;When it comes to exercising for your heart's sake, you don't want to peak too early in life. Research suggests that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/turning-point-in-heart-health-occurs-at-1-key-age-its-younger-than-youd-think"&gt;to protect yourself&lt;/a&gt; against high blood pressure in your twilight years, you need to keep your exercise levels up through middle age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But according to a study of more than 5,000 people across four US cities, social factors can make this more difficult for some people than others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Teenagers and those in their early 20s may be physically active but these patterns change with age," epidemiologist Kirsten Bibbins-Domingo from the University of California, San Francisco (UCSF) &lt;a href="https://www.ucsf.edu/news/2021/04/420281/want-be-robust-40-plus-meeting-minimum-exercise-guidelines-wont-cut-it"&gt;explained&lt;/a&gt; in April 2021, when the research was published.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-simple-daily-habit-could-help-lower-your-blood-pressure"&gt;This Simple Daily Habit Could Help Lower Your Blood Pressure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Numerous studies have shown that exercise lowers blood pressure, but the 2021 research suggests that "maintaining physical activity during young adulthood – at higher levels than previously recommended – may be particularly important," Bibbins-Domingo &lt;a href="https://www.ucsf.edu/news/2021/04/420281/want-be-robust-40-plus-meeting-minimum-exercise-guidelines-wont-cut-it"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_96226" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-96226" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2023/05/ExerciseScienceWeightLoss-642x260.jpg" alt="Older man running on street wearing orange t-shirt." class="wp-image-96226 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2023/05/ExerciseScienceWeightLoss-642x260.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2023/05/ExerciseScienceWeightLoss.jpg 1024w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2023/05/ExerciseScienceWeightLoss-768x311.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2023/05/ExerciseScienceWeightLoss-600x243.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-96226" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Maintaining physical activity could be even more important than we knew. (South_agency/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hypertension, also known as high blood pressure, is a serious condition affecting billions of people worldwide. It can lead to heart attacks and stroke; it's also a risk factor for &lt;a href="study-suggests-diabetes-and-high-blood-pressure-might-also-be-affecting-your-mind" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;developing dementia in later life&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-blood-pressure-guidelines-mean-you-could-now-have-hypertension"&gt;New Blood Pressure Guidelines Mean You Could Now Have Hypertension&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upwards of one in four men and about every fifth woman has hypertension, &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/health-topics/hypertension/#tab=tab_1"&gt;according to the World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;. But most people with high blood pressure don't even know they have it – hence why it's often called the "silent killer".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet there are ways to turn high blood pressure around: exercise is the focus of this study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over 5,100 adults were recruited for the study, which tracked their health over three decades through physical assessments and questionnaires on exercise habits, smoking status, and alcohol intake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At each clinical assessment, blood pressure was measured three times, 1 minute apart, and, for data analysis, participants were grouped into four categories by race and gender.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/castingcall?utm_source=SA_website&amp;amp;utm_medium=article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=casting_call"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg" alt="Audition now for ScienceAlert's Casting Call" class="alignnone wp-image-189354 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-1200x509.jpg 1200w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1.jpg 1266w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across the board – amongst men, women, and in both racial groups – levels of physical activity slumped from 18 to 40 years of age, with rates of hypertension rising and physical activity falling over subsequent decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the researchers, this suggests that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-simple-change-to-your-standing-desk-could-make-workdays-healthier"&gt;young adulthood is an important window for intervening&lt;/a&gt; to prevent midlife hypertension with health promotion programs designed to boost exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-5-minute-workout-each-day-can-still-make-a-huge-health-difference"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A 5-Minute Workout Each Day Can Still Make a Huge Health Difference&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Nearly half of our participants in young adulthood had suboptimal levels of physical activity, which was significantly associated with the onset of hypertension, indicating that we need to raise the minimum standard for physical activity," &lt;a href="https://www.ucsf.edu/news/2021/04/420281/want-be-robust-40-plus-meeting-minimum-exercise-guidelines-wont-cut-it"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; lead author Jason Nagata, a UCSF expert in young adult medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_80404" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-80404" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2022/11/DumbbellExercise-642x260.jpg" alt="Someone lifting a dumbbell behind their head" class="wp-image-80404 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2022/11/DumbbellExercise-642x260.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2022/11/DumbbellExercise.jpg 1024w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2022/11/DumbbellExercise-768x311.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2022/11/DumbbellExercise-600x243.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-80404" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Physical activity often declines with age, but this can have consequences for your health. (Watchara Piriyaputtanapun/Moment/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the researchers looked at people who had done 5 hours of moderate exercise a week during early adulthood – double the minimum amount currently recommended for adults – they found that this level of activity lowered the risk of hypertension considerably, especially if people maintained their exercise habits until age 60.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Achieving at least twice the current minimum adult [physical activity] guidelines may be more beneficial for the prevention of hypertension than simply meeting the minimum guidelines," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.amepre.2020.12.018"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; in their paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it's not easy to step up physical activity each week amid life-changing decisions and growing responsibilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This might be especially the case after high school when opportunities for physical activity diminish as young adults transition to college, the workforce, and parenthood, and leisure time is eroded," &lt;a href="https://www.ucsf.edu/news/2021/04/420281/want-be-robust-40-plus-meeting-minimum-exercise-guidelines-wont-cut-it"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; Nagata.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/not-all-sitting-is-equal-one-type-was-just-linked-to-better-brain-health"&gt;Not All Sitting Is Equal. One Type Was Just Linked to Better Brain Health.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for another sobering truth, the study also showed how Black men and Black women experience starkly different health trajectories compared to their White counterparts. At 40 years of age, physical activity levels plateaued among White men and women, whereas activity levels in Black participants continued to decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By age 45, Black women surpassed White men in rates of hypertension, while White women in the study experienced the lowest rates of hypertension through midlife.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And by age 60, between 80 and 90 percent of Black men and women had hypertension, compared with just below 70 percent for White men and around half of White women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team attributed these well-known racial disparities to a multitude of social and economic factors; however, these factors were not assessed in this study, although high school education was noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although Black male youth may have high engagement in sports, socioeconomic factors, neighborhood environments, and work or family responsibilities may prevent continued engagement in physical activity through adulthood," Nagata &lt;a href="https://www.ucsf.edu/news/2021/04/420281/want-be-robust-40-plus-meeting-minimum-exercise-guidelines-wont-cut-it"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.amepre.2020.12.018"&gt;American Journal of Preventive Medicine.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in April 2021.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:03:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxQQTFuMkRieWFxdkQydVpHSUFiS2NJSi0zQ3Y0V3pvNlJjUHlwV1BFa3dTclpLNGZSMktTQ3IzNk5PTEwzbjhSbXNySFdxTTVoUWpCU0lFUU5oOXIwUkdvSXQ2NDhnV1hPcEVMNlpWR1lXSl9GVnVRRkVVdEs2YWw2OTdZYkliYkNGS1hZRUt4ZnpRdlhpNm9xcmxQVXBtRG5CQTM2RA</guid></item><item><title>未接种疫苗的儿童标志着湾区县十多年来首例麻疹病例- SFGATE</title><link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/unvaccinated-child-bay-area-measles-21311776.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>SFGATE</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:59:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxQVmh4MXJjaXhITDkxTzF0T0ZZOC1MMlc3VVJEOU1WZDY3cG5NcXJJT3ZhZ3hRVmM0bjJmcURYVFJLUC1nbHIxM3VQaTNTa3BfbDVyb1dCQlZqRTVBT3FGcG51b3QzT0NCWTBBdE1BNDN3bUhULWJWMWUwQi13RTZKRms5RWpiT0tHS25iTGlfdks</guid></item><item><title>科学家可能已经找到了复活旧细胞的蓝图- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-may-have-found-a-blueprint-to-revive-old-cells</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Many of the body's processes slow down or falter as we get older, including &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/body-resurrects-cells-marked-for-death-solving-a-50-year-mystery"&gt;tissue regeneration&lt;/a&gt;. In a new study, researchers detail a promising method to get this vital repair work back up to speed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, from a team at the University of California, San Francisco, identified four &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transcription_factor"&gt;transcription factors&lt;/a&gt; – proteins that control the activity of other genes – that have a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-discover-a-way-to-recharge-aging-human-cells"&gt;rejuvenating effect&lt;/a&gt; on cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the researchers boosted production of one of these transcription factors in the liver cells of elderly mice, they noticed numerous benefits: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/5-daily-habits-could-be-causing-your-liver-serious-harm"&gt;fat and scarring&lt;/a&gt; were significantly reduced, and glucose tolerance improved – all signs of a more youthful organ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/blood-of-exceptionally-long-lived-people-reveals-crucial-differences"&gt;Blood of Exceptionally Long-Lived People Reveals Crucial Differences&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team also tinkered with the levels of all four transcription factors in lab-grown human &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fibroblast"&gt;fibroblast cells&lt;/a&gt;. Fibroblasts make up connective tissue and provide scaffolding around other cells and organs. Again, multiple signs of youthfulness were spotted as a result, including increased cell division and boosted energy levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"By altering gene expression using the transcription factors we identified, old fibroblasts behaved as if they were younger, and improved the health of old mice," &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1112231"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; biochemist Hao Li.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_188901" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188901" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/LiverScarring.jpg" alt="Liver scarring diagram" class="wp-image-188901 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/LiverScarring.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/LiverScarring-600x419.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-188901" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Increasing the expression of EZH2 (bottom row), one of four transcription factors identified, reduced liver scarring (blue stain) in older mice compared to controls (top row). (Sengstack et al., &lt;em&gt;PNAS&lt;/em&gt;, 2026)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;To identify the four key transcription factors, the researchers first compared old and young human fibroblast cells using a computational model to see how &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/hundreds-of-genes-act-differently-in-male-vs-female-brains-scientists-discover"&gt;gene expression&lt;/a&gt; differed with age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having drawn up a shortlist of 200 transcription factors that could be controlling the 'youthfulness' of cells, they began systematically toggling them on and off – changing the transcription factors produced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results of this tinkering led the researchers to the final four transcription factors that they tested in more detail: E2F3, EZH2, STAT3, and ZFX. Altering the levels of these factors in liver cells of mice and human fibroblast cells grown in plastic dishes shifted the cells &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-restore-aging-blood-stem-cells-to-a-more-youthful-state-in-mice"&gt;towards a younger mode&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/castingcall?utm_source=SA_website&amp;amp;utm_medium=article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=casting_call"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg" alt="Audition now for ScienceAlert's Casting Call" class="alignnone wp-image-189354 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-1200x509.jpg 1200w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1.jpg 1266w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fact that these proteins had an effect across two different species and cell types suggests we could be looking at a universal blueprint of sorts, one that could be broadly applied to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/young-immune-cells-partly-reverse-alzheimers-symptoms-in-mice"&gt;reactivate youthful states&lt;/a&gt; in older cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These results suggest a shared set of molecular requirements for cellular and tissue rejuvenation across species," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.2515183123"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's still early days for this research, and we're not yet talking about &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/gains-in-human-life-expectancy-may-have-already-passed-their-peak"&gt;extending lifespans&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/axolotl-discovery-brings-us-closer-than-ever-to-regrowing-human-limbs"&gt;replacing limbs&lt;/a&gt; or rejuvenating the whole body. We only have the results from a few cell types.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long-term safety needs to be considered, too. The experiments in mice lasted only a few weeks, so we still don't know what effects rejuvenating cells in this manner might have over extended periods. Too much cell growth connected to EZH2 has been &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.1933744100"&gt;linked with cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, with a global population that's growing older and living longer, potential ways of keeping our bodies &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-reveal-turning-point-when-your-bodys-aging-accelerates"&gt;healthier for longer&lt;/a&gt; should warrant further investigation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our work opens up exciting new opportunities to understand and ultimately reverse aging-related diseases," &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1112231"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; biochemist Janine Sengstack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.2515183123"&gt;&lt;em&gt;PNAS&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:01:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxNTXBBVWxDUTBCNjZFbXlOZGliOVVib0ZrdjFOOTVSSjV6SFd5c0hjQ1RNVkVYZDIwdElkdXU1VEdtUkN1aDR5VGN2QjdaNVF0V2hrckpmQldQTmNEcFlEN0VILXhyMlU2SXl1ZFNhZ2N2alA4c1I0UGlmTDNIZkwzSGpTTi03X091Z3Zkcjhxbw</guid></item><item><title>卫生官员表示，新不伦瑞克省没有神秘脑部疾病的证据- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cy4qwyp3gpno</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A report by Canadian officials has found no evidence of a new disease after hundreds of reports of neurological symptoms led to claims of a mystery brain condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The results of the investigation by New Brunswick's Chief Medical Officer of Health add to a growing body of research that suggests patients may have diagnosable illnesses instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;About 500 people in New Brunswick and other provinces have been identified by neurologist Dr Alier Marrero as having unexplained neurological symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Officials said they also found no evidence to support Marrero's claims that patients' symptoms were caused by elevated levels of herbicides and heavy metals. The BBC has contacted Marrero for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Regardless of the findings of our investigation, the fact remains there are patients who are very ill and need support," said New Brunswick's chief medical officer of health Dr Yves Léger on Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c623r47d67lo" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;BBC report published earlier this month&lt;/a&gt; questioned the legitimacy of the cluster of patients and asked whether hundreds may have been misdiagnosed by Marrero, and had suffered instead from known neurological illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The BBC report also revealed that at least one cluster patient had opted for death via medically assisted dying – with the mystery disease cited as the cause on the death certificate – and that at least one other patient was considering medically assisted dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The provincial study published on Friday examined the cases of 222 of Marrero's patients and reviewed results of extensive testing he had ordered on the patients which he said showed elevated levels of herbicides and heavy metals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;After comparisons with test results from among the broader population in the Atlantic Canada region, the province's findings showed that the herbicide levels among the cluster patients were normal, officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A small number of patients did show higher than expected levels of heavy metals, the report found, but officials said it was difficult to confirm the results because of issues with the way they had been tested and they said there was no clear evidence to suggest the elevated levels could have led to adverse neurological health effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Officials said the provincial review was limited by several factors, including that some of Marrero's initial testing had not been done according to correct guidelines and that most patients had not been regularly retested to establish a pattern of elevated levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The report also found that close to 60% of patients in the group had also been seen by a second neurologist, and that none of the other neurologists had raised concerns to health authorities regarding the patients' conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In response to the report's findings, health officials said that any patient referred to the province with an unexplained neurological condition would now have to be examined by two separate specialists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Léger told reporters on Friday that there was "mounting evidence that these patients have diagnosable conditions", adding that the province was "certainly concerned about that and about patient care".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He said the province's findings would be shared with Marrero, and that it was important the neurologist "understand what we've found from our analysis".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The data will also be shared with the Public Health Agency of Canada, Leger said, which will conduct a further review.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Sarah Nesbitt, a patient in the cluster and an environmental advocate, said she was concerned about the limitations of the study and that some patients did prove to have elevated levels of metals in their system. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But Nesbitt told the BBC she is hopeful that this a step towards helping patients, especially those with elevated levels, get more answers and additional support for their illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"At the end of the day, it's about finding the problem with the patients, helping them heal or cure or symptom manage," she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Friday's study is the second conducted by the province into the purported mystery illness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Results of the previous study, which examined the first 48 patients in the cluster, was published in 2022 and similarly found no common exposures and concluded the patients were likely suffering from a range of different illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Last year, a separate research paper published by the JAMA neurology journal echoed the conclusions of the 2022 provincial report. The paper, based on a review of 25 cluster cases, found that the patients had all suffered from known and diagnosable illnesses including cancer and dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The lead author of the JAMA paper, Dr Anthony Lang, told the BBC on Friday that the provincial report "confirms our suspicion or belief that there was no environmental factor that could have accounted for such a broad range of neurological problems". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"There was no consistent neurological disease that we had seen in this small group of patients we described," Lang added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"So this just confirms exactly what we've suspected and really emphasises the suffering and pain that patients and families have had."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Nesbitt and other patients have rejected accusations that Marrero has misdiagnosed patients, and said he rightfully raised concerns about their test results of elevated metals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She added some patients have expressed they do not want to see another neurologist "because they don't trust anybody anymore".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"He's a kind man, he's intelligent, he does due diligence," Nesbitt said, adding that he has done a considerable amount of testing on patients to help give them answers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero did not immediately reply to a request for comment about Friday's report. In September, he told the BBC that other senior federal and provincial scientists had also believed there was a novel syndrome in New Brunswick and that he was now being portrayed as the sole purveyor of the idea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They are trying to present me as it," he said. "I was part of it, but I was not it. The only difference is, when the table was empty, I stayed."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:01:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1VMzBWT2dPdmFsTTlfbUhfc3ZncVlEMlV3NGRhS3J3SU10TGkxRERiLXp1RVFzN1NPRzVBUnlKQmVkRmdZQ2JMdmM0ZWc2bHIxMjdBWmI5a3RPd9IBX0FVX3lxTFBwTFVWUjFHV0tkUG43M3NyRVFjc0d6N3c0aWU4ZF9xVU5BSWMtUjhib1ZYUC1hOEEtOW96Rk83cEZIQkRpN1NoNEY4YWpFYTE1bnBaUnFPU0JIZlEtdTlz</guid></item><item><title>旧金山报告本季首例流感死亡病例，加利福尼亚州各地病例呈上升趋势--《旧金山纪</title><link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/health/article/san-francisco-flu-deaths-21311591.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>San Francisco Chronicle</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:15:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxPOWhkbl8tM0NUd214MUJjeS1FTi05UVEyb2F4a3JJVnZleEd6bVIyOExGb2hmMUY3c1FjbzA1Wnoyb0NER0pCbzh0X09IQ0VMSXZGeEg1Y280bGQweUo5aXJ6cnR0b2lBLUNtTWIwcFk0ZGV0UkJrNV9FaWRBVzRfSHR5N3NLOGc</guid></item><item><title>死于流感的2岁儿童的家人威胁要起诉送他回家的新泽西州医院- nj.com</title><link>https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2026/01/family-of-2-year-old-who-died-of-the-flu-threatens-to-sue-nj-hospital-that-sent-him-home.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NDQ7U7JDIBBWPBASFS4VRT7K4E"&gt;A New Jersey family is threatening to sue Morristown Medical Center for $25 million after their &lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2026/01/2-year-old-with-beautiful-smile-identified-as-first-child-flu-death-this-season-in-nj.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2026/01/2-year-old-with-beautiful-smile-identified-as-first-child-flu-death-this-season-in-nj.html"&gt;2-year-old son was discharged and died from complications of the flu&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5KDDXK2JK5BQ3HW4FQE7QIS3VQ"&gt;Isais Castillo IV, who died Jan. 6, wasn’t vaccinated for the flu. He was scheduled to get a shot later this month, his family said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VCAGNCOE6JGWRERIRCSQS65CLA"&gt;His mom &lt;a href="https://abc7ny.com/post/nj-child-flu-death-mom-speaks-2-year-old-son-was-sent-home-morristown-medical-center/18392336/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://abc7ny.com/post/nj-child-flu-death-mom-speaks-2-year-old-son-was-sent-home-morristown-medical-center/18392336/"&gt;told ABC7 &lt;/a&gt;that he had a fever and they took him to the emergency room, but he died one day after being sent home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EOJKBVMQAZE6JDTSCB2EWPLK5Y"&gt;Morristown Medical Center staff allegedly “deviated from accepted standards of care” when they discharged Isais on Jan. 5, causing his death the next day, according to a notice of tort claim filed against the hospital. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="N6VB3IK2INDZXMFGS44UT5U4XU"&gt;The legal notice claims $25 million in damages, which include “emotional distress, suffering, loss of enjoyment of life, extraordinary medical expenses, economic damages and loss of child’s services.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CPXH7EE5OVCQDMK5UY4S537GMQ"&gt;Darryl L. Zaslow, the family’s attorney, told NJ Advance Media on Friday that “the tragedy here is unimaginable.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="L7GMLZFPVJAGXNDKK5CIJZXLWA"&gt;“I will be doing a thorough investigation upon receiving the medical records and then I’ll determine if a lawsuit will be filed,” said Zaslow. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Z545SCSJBZFU3L3JAVR5TGLICM"&gt;Spokespeople for Atlantic Health, which owns Morristown Medical Center and is also named in the legal notice, did not immediately respond Friday to requests for comment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VK22N72QCJGY3EFYZOHSK6G75U"&gt;Giselle Castillo described her son’s death as “the biggest loss of our lives,” in a public Facebook post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DSXPM5WOSFERLJKH3XYUE364UA"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/support-for-the-castillo-familys-healing" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.gofundme.com/f/support-for-the-castillo-familys-healing"&gt;GoFundMe campaign&lt;/a&gt; created to support the family has raised more than $18,000 as of Friday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="72V2MUBXXFGEXNOHY4QZ6JVHAM"&gt;Isais was the &lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2026/01/child-dies-from-the-flu-in-nj-marking-first-pediatric-case-as-infections-increase.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2026/01/child-dies-from-the-flu-in-nj-marking-first-pediatric-case-as-infections-increase.html"&gt;first pediatric flu death in New Jersey&lt;/a&gt; this season. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FJ3IMGCICVHXJOUA455YSTB4MU"&gt;There have been 104 total flu-related deaths in New Jersey since the fall, most of which were people 65 and older, according to state data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3LAK2UTGARG4DAWNRDZNMRHMHI"&gt;However, the flu can cause severe illness and death in anyone, including children. Last year, the state reported five pediatric flu deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:IGXK2EJOF5ELPCPCMKDVBWN26U" data-fusion-component="IGXK2EJOF5ELPCPCMKDVBWN26U"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:IGXK2EJOF5ELPCPCMKDVBWN26U" data-fusion-component="IGXK2EJOF5ELPCPCMKDVBWN26U"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>nj.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:07:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiygFBVV95cUxPbG82RDc4OFV5R1hTZVJJaTl3Nm12SENfVHJFb2VpSUNOTV9PMk5MdklKNWVDREZfZ0J6QnVWOERMUkFoSThhMDJlRVM4RGJvdXpHVE1tVmJxOVRfMk1Jd3ZYVmVUbUU4TC1VUVdYLWp3d081NHRUcWxsN19mWkpaQUNkVHRISldZOTY4czVDeHhSWWJVbWpHcS16bGpmUkNZT3JEM2JGNkwzdEUzRTZtdk1oMHRfTDRkdFRuUWhaZDJISENKd0lTVnlB</guid></item><item><title>超薄无线视网膜植入物为安全恢复视觉信号带来希望- Phys.org</title><link>https://phys.org/news/2026-01-ultra-thin-wireless-retinal-implant.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:00:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE96cFhidVMyejRmRnRhY1JMdGhvUEFOeVlmRFFFVS1uM1Q4NUxHdkZpSThQUlFuS2p3cHlITENhU0wyUGZaVVY1b2VsX2ZmbzVJYTNCeXU4bE1lTkNINENQOTVaazNaM1pkaWkxY2xIaDhhVDBaVHA0SFJ3</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，在家中燃烧木材会在冬季造成危险的空气污染- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-wood-homes-dangerous-air-pollution.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxNRV9SNFJRN0RQaTZBRHNaXy0yOU5KdFFGUzg0MnMzbEhFbEpVNUhuNlRpSUFCbEEzZ2NfcG1ORnBkdjJyUFpZdnRISHRlV1FyYmpDRXBKR2xSdVZvNEhXRWhRSERvaVAxcVUtN05Tb1Ficjl2Q1BZWU04WlFPb3p6VlJCYUY</guid></item><item><title>Baptist Health在杰克逊维尔确认2例小儿麻疹病例- news4jax.com</title><link>https://www.news4jax.com/news/local/2026/01/23/baptist-health-confirms-two-pediatric-measles-cases-in-jacksonville/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 fURyTV iQviKm articleBody" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JACKSONVILLE, Fla. &lt;/strong&gt; – Baptist Health has confirmed two pediatric measles cases in Jacksonville.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;According to a press release from the health system, the two children, who live in the same household, sought emergency care at Baptist Health’s main campus on Jan. 16.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Hospital officials said both children received appropriate treatment and were sent home without needing hospital admission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Baptist Health shared this statement:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;&lt;i&gt;“Baptist Health remains deeply committed to the safety and well-being of our patients and team members. We have shared the names of anyone who may have been exposed with the Department of Health (DOH). The DOH will contact those individuals directly.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;&lt;i&gt;We want to assure you that the risk of infection from exposure within our facility is very low, because our team of pediatric Emergency Center specialists is expertly prepared and ready to care for these children and our community.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__FlexBase-sc-1fnzlkn-1 jGlKin adWrapper" aria-label="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Measles is an airborne infection that can spread when an infected person coughs or sneezes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Symptoms typically appear 7 to 14 days after exposure, including high fever, cough, runny nose, and watery eyes. Then, a rash of tiny red spots appears. It starts at the head and spreads to the rest of the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;The Florida Department of Health in Duval County said it cannot comment on the specifics of an ongoing epidemiological investigation, but shared the following with News4JAX:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 bqJyUE iQviKm block-quote"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 ewwUYq"&gt;When a communicable disease is reported in the county, DOH-Duval immediately initiates an epidemiological investigation to protect the public’s health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 ewwUYq"&gt;If an individual is experiencing symptoms of measles, they are advised to not abruptly visit a health care provider without contacting them ahead of time. Instead, they should contact their health care provider or local county health department to receive instructions on how to safely seek medical attention without exposing others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;cite class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 fwWldV"&gt;Florida Department of Health in Duval County&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Dr. Shalika Katugaha, system medical director of infectious diseases at Baptist Medical, explained that measles symptoms can be more severe in children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;“Children younger than 5 years are at the highest risk for complications and death. So children do experience it more severely than adults,” Katugaha said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Infants younger than 12 months face significantly higher risks for severe complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Katugaha explained why this is the case. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__FlexBase-sc-1fnzlkn-1 jGlKin adWrapper" aria-label="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;“The mom’s antibodies wane in these children, and they are ineligible for routine vaccines before 9 to 12 months of age,” she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Measles is highly contagious and can be contracted by other family members, including children and adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;To help protect families, the local Department of Health is offering immunizations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;DOH-Duval will hold a “Pop-Up” Immunization Clinic on Sunday, Feb. 1, from 9 a.m. to 12 p.m. at the Regency Library, 9300 Regency Square Boulevard. Vaccines available include MMR, influenza, and hepatitis A.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Immunizations are also available Monday through Friday, 8 a.m. to 5 p.m., at these locations:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 kDvXdO font_openSans articleList"&gt;&lt;li class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 ecGWWE iQviKm"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 hxqFXA fYWDEy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 6 6" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" aria-hidden="true" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;circle cx="3" cy="3" r="3" fill="#212121"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;span class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 gJUqRf"&gt;515 W. 6th Street, Jacksonville, FL 32206&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 ecGWWE iQviKm"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 hxqFXA fYWDEy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 6 6" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" aria-hidden="true" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;circle cx="3" cy="3" r="3" fill="#212121"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;span class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 gJUqRf"&gt;3225 University Blvd. South, Jacksonville, FL 32216&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Walk-ins are welcome, or appointments can be made by calling 904-253-1130.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) recommends that children receive two doses of the MMR (measles, mumps, rubella) vaccine: the first at 12–15 months of age and the second at 4–6 years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;For infants aged 6–11 months who will be traveling internationally, the CDC recommends one MMR dose before departure, followed by two additional doses after the child’s first birthday (according to the routine schedule).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__FlexBase-sc-1fnzlkn-1 jGlKin adWrapper" aria-label="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 nALdY copyright"&gt;Copyright 2026 by WJXT News4JAX - All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>news4jax.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:59:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxObUswOVd3cEFKc1J4MmhFb0xYdzd1clVlUngxaDZwM1BYUV92MEZOSFJsOXhFZTc2dUxKZXhOWm9sbWNxM0xtZmZ1MzNkbmVRX0diSW5pRGFHa1lObEtqUGlrWVBKaE12eXFwb2JLV2h0MEhXUDRGUmFyMkNwa1JsZEszV1pJX1c0ZXJhQlB6OE1LbnRpRHZlUHVMcXpXUDZROTM0cktxcG9vbk9QR0I3RS1pU09lUQ</guid></item><item><title>7天高蛋白高纤维饮食计划- Skinnytaste</title><link>https://www.skinnytaste.com/7-day-high-protein-high-fiber-diet-meal-plan-3/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content clear" data-ast-blocks-layout="true"&gt;

		
		
&lt;span id="dpsp-post-content-markup" data-image-pin-it="true"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="content-disclaimer-text disclaimer-location-top"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post may contain affiliate links. Read my &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/legal/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;disclosure policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A free, 7-day &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-protein/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;high protein&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-fiber-recipes/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;high fiber&lt;/a&gt; diet meal plan including &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/recipes/breakfast-brunch/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;breakfast&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/recipes/lunch/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;lunch&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/recipes/dinner-recipes/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;dinner ideas&lt;/a&gt; and a shopping list. All recipes include &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/what-are-macros/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;macros&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/smart-points/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Weight Watchers&lt;/a&gt; points.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" src="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Week_525_Jan-26-Feb-1_High-Protein.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-158151" srcset="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Week_525_Jan-26-Feb-1_High-Protein.jpg 1200w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Week_525_Jan-26-Feb-1_High-Protein-500x625.jpg 500w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Week_525_Jan-26-Feb-1_High-Protein-550x688.jpg 550w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Week_525_Jan-26-Feb-1_High-Protein-600x750.jpg 600w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Week_525_Jan-26-Feb-1_High-Protein-150x188.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading has-text-align-center"&gt;7 Day High-Protein High-Fiber Diet Meal Plan&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/holiday-recipes/superbowl-recipes/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Game days&lt;/a&gt; are all about big plays, loud cheers, and even better food. Whether you’re hosting a football watch party or pulling up to a sports-filled weekend with friends, these party &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/recipes/appetizers/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;apps&lt;/a&gt; prove you don’t have to choose between great flavor and hitting your &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-protein/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;protein&lt;/a&gt; goals. Perfect for sharing (or keeping all to yourself),  these &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/mini-bell-pepper-loaded-turkey-nachos/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Mini Bell Pepper Loaded Turkey Nachos&lt;/a&gt; (18g protein), &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/air-fryer-chicken-wings/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Air Fryer Chicken Wings&lt;/a&gt; (25.5g protein) or &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/guacamole-recipe/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Best Guacamole Recipe&lt;/a&gt; (4g fiber) are sure to be crowd-pleasers—bringing feel-good fuel to every celebration. Because the best game-day spreads let you enjoy every bite and the win!&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;span id="more-158113"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;


&lt;div id="callout-box-block_8de5bb252b0c1a2ad0ab188737abb1ae" class="callout-box-block callout-box-style-1"&gt;&lt;p class="callout-box-tag"&gt;&lt;h2 class="callout-box-title"&gt;Update About New WW Points Plan&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="callout-box-content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all my WW friends, WW added new 0 point foods (yay for oatmeal!) but it will take time for me to update my recipes. So far I have everything from 2025 to 2018 updated. The great news is every recipe on my site is linked to WW recipe builder (only works from your phone) so it will automatically give you the new points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Why High Protein?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As many of you know, I’ve been following a &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-protein/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;high-protein&lt;/a&gt; diet for the past few years for muscle gain, and it’s been a total game changer for me! I feel stronger and more satisfied, which keeps me from reaching for sweets or chips between meals or at the end of the day. I know a lot of you struggle with hitting your protein goals, so I was inspired to create this &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-protein/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;high-protein&lt;/a&gt; meal plan for the week. If you enjoy it, I’ll share 1 or 2 each month. Plus, I’m working on a high-protein cookbook, so stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To reach my protein goals, I typically divide it across three meals. For example, if my goal is 120 grams of protein per day, I aim for at least 30 grams per meal, plus 10 to 30 grams with each snack. If you’re not sure how much protein you should eat in a day, this &lt;a href="https://examine.com/guides/protein-intake/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow external" data-wpel-link="external"&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; may be helpful.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;How It Works&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;If you’re new to my &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/meal-plans/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;meal plans&lt;/a&gt;, these are meant as a guide, with &lt;strong&gt;plenty of wiggle room&lt;/strong&gt; for you to &lt;strong&gt;add more food&lt;/strong&gt;, coffee, beverages, fruits, &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/recipes/snacks/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;snacks&lt;/a&gt;, dessert, etc. or swap recipes out for meals you prefer, you can search for &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/recipes/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;recipes&lt;/a&gt; by course in the &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/recipes/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;index&lt;/a&gt;. Depending on your goals, you should aim for at least 1500 calories* per day. There’s no one size fits all, this will range by your goals, your age, weight, etc. Always talk to your nutritionist or dietician for your specific needs.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Note&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Those with kidney or liver disease, gout, specific metabolic disorders, or older adults with reduced kidney function may need to limit protein to avoid complications. It’s always best to consult a healthcare provider or dietitian before significantly increasing protein intake, especially if you have any underlying health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Lastly, if you’re on Facebook join my &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/1934885496754505/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow external" data-wpel-link="external"&gt;Skinnytaste Facebook Community&lt;/a&gt; where everyone’s sharing photos of recipes they are making, you can join here. I’m loving all the ideas everyone’s sharing! If you wish to get on the email list, you can subscribe here so you never miss a meal plan!&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div id="callout-box-block_676ad29253934f2635e272fe8b2f2a6e" class="callout-box-block callout-box-style-2"&gt;&lt;p class="callout-box-tag"&gt;&lt;h3 class="callout-box-title"&gt;&lt;span class="callout-box-icon webicon-diamond"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Ultimate Skinnytaste Meal Planner&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="callout-box-content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignleft wp-image-79975 size-full" src="" alt="Skinnytaste Ultimate Meal Planner" data-lazy-src="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Skinnytaste-UltimateMealPlanner-125.png"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignleft wp-image-79975 size-full" src="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Skinnytaste-UltimateMealPlanner-125.png" alt="Skinnytaste Ultimate Meal Planner"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get the Skinnytaste Ultimate Meal Planner! The 52 week spiral bound meal planner has weekly meal planning grids you can tear out and put on your fridge if you wish, a 12-week meal plan, 30 (15 new) recipes, and tear-out grocery lists. I love starting my week with gratitude, affirmations and intentions, so I included a space for that as well. I hope you will love this as much as I do!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;figure class="wp-block-image"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt="Skinnytaste Ultimate Meal Planner" class="wp-image-111022" data-lazy-srcset="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-scaled.jpeg 2560w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-500x375.jpeg 500w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-550x412.jpeg 550w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-1536x1152.jpeg 1536w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-2048x1536.jpeg 2048w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-600x450.jpeg 600w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-1200x900.jpeg 1200w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-150x112.jpeg 150w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" data-lazy-src="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-scaled.jpeg"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-scaled.jpeg" alt="Skinnytaste Ultimate Meal Planner" class="wp-image-111022" srcset="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-scaled.jpeg 2560w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-500x375.jpeg 500w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-550x412.jpeg 550w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-1536x1152.jpeg 1536w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-2048x1536.jpeg 2048w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-600x450.jpeg 600w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-1200x900.jpeg 1200w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/image-150x112.jpeg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Buy the Skinnytaste meal planner here:&lt;/h2&gt;







&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;High Protein Diet Meal Plan:&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Breakfast and lunch Monday-Friday, are designed to serve 1 while dinners and all meals on Saturday and Sunday are designed to serve a family of 4. Some recipes make enough leftovers for two nights or lunch the next day. The grocery list is comprehensive and includes everything you need to make all meals on the plan. Add some &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-protein-snacks/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;high protein snacks&lt;/a&gt; to help you reach your protein goals.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MONDAY (1/26)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;B: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-protein-zucchini-omelet-for-one/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;High Protein Zucchini Omelet for One&lt;/a&gt; with 2 chicken breakfast sausage links and 1 slice whole grain toast&lt;br&gt;L: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/tuna-and-white-bean-salad/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Tuna White Bean Salad&lt;/a&gt; and 2 tablespoons raw almonds&lt;br&gt;D: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/greek-tofu-bowl/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Greek Tofu Bowls&lt;/a&gt; (recipe x 2) with &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/roasted-cauliflower-and-chickpeas-with/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Roasted Cauliflower and Chickpeas with Minted Yogurt&lt;/a&gt; (½ recipe)&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Total Calories: 1,568* Protein: 120.5 g Fiber: 30 g&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TUESDAY (1/27)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;B: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/high-protein-zucchini-omelet-for-one/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;High Protein Zucchini Omelet for One&lt;/a&gt; with 2 chicken breakfast sausage links and 1 slice whole grain toast&lt;br&gt;L: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/tuna-and-white-bean-salad/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Tuna White Bean Salad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;D: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/ground-turkey-tacos/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Ground Turkey Tacos&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/quick-and-deliciouso-cuban-style-black/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Quick and Delicioso Cuban Style Black Beans&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/cilantro-lime-cauliflower-rice/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Cilantro Lime Cauliflower Rice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Total Calories: 1,477* Protein: 120 g Fiber: 34 g&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WEDNESDAY (1/28)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;B: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/carrot-banana-protein-smoothie/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Carrot Banana Protein Smoothie&lt;/a&gt; with ¼ cup low fat plain Greek yogurt&lt;br&gt;L: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/microwave-salmon-rice-bowl/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;5-Minute Microwave Salmon Rice Bowl&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;D: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/chicken-marbella/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Chicken Marbella&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/farro-with-feta-cucumbers-and-sun-dried/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Farro Salad with Feta, Cucumbers and Sun-Dried Tomatoes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;Total Calories: 1,431* Protein: 129 g Fiber: 25 g&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THURSDAY (1/29)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;B: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/carrot-banana-protein-smoothie/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Carrot Banana Protein Smoothie&lt;/a&gt; with ¼ cup low fat plain Greek yogurt&lt;br&gt;L: LEFTOVER &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/chicken-marbella/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Chicken Marbella&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/chickpea-salad/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Chickpea Salad with Cucumbers&lt;/a&gt; (1/2 recipe)&lt;br&gt;D: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/spicy-whole-wheat-linguini-with-sausage/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Spicy Whole Wheat Linguini with Sausage and Roasted Peppers&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/arugula-with-pomegranates-blue-cheese/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Arugula with Pomegranates, Blue Cheese and Pistachios&lt;/a&gt; (recipe x 2)&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Total Calories: 1,406* Protein: 131 g Fiber: 26 g&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FRIDAY (1/30)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;B: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/15-minute-protein-chia-seed-cereal/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;15-Minute Protein Chia Seed Cereal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;L: LEFTOVER &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/chicken-marbella/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Chicken Marbella&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/chickpea-salad/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Chickpea Salad with Cucumber&lt;/a&gt;s&lt;br&gt;D: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/broiled-tilapia-with-tomato-caper-sauce/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Broiled Fish with Tomato Caper Sauce&lt;/a&gt; with 1 cup whole wheat orzo and &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/roasted-broccoli-and-cauliflower/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Roasted Broccoli and Cauliflower&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Total Calories: 1,417* Protein: 122.5 g Fiber: 31 g&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SATURDAY (1/31)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;B: ⅛ &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/breakfast-casserole-with-spinach-and-sausage/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Breakfast Casserole with Sausage and Spinach&lt;/a&gt; and an orange&lt;br&gt;L: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/asian-lettuce-wrap-chicken-chopped-salad/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Asian Chicken Chopped Salad&lt;/a&gt; with ¼ cup shelled edamame&lt;br&gt;D: DINNER OUT&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Total Calories: 745* Protein: 56.5 g Fiber: 10 g&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUNDAY (2/1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;B: LEFTOVER &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/breakfast-casserole-with-spinach-and-sausage/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Breakfast Casserole with Sausage and Spinach&lt;/a&gt; and a pear&lt;br&gt;L: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/chicken-quesadillas/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Chicken Quesadilla&lt;/a&gt; with 1 ounce avocado&lt;br&gt;D: &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/french-onion-pot-roast/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;French Onion Pot Roast&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/garlic-mashed-potatoes-3-ww-points/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;Garlic Mashed Potatoes&lt;/a&gt; and 1 cup steamed green beans&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Total Calories: 1,452* Protein: 127 g Fiber: 33.5 g&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;*This is just a guide, women should aim for around 1500 calories per day. &lt;a href="https://www.myplate.gov/myplate-plan" target="_blank" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener"&gt;Here’s a helpful calculator to estimate your calorie needs.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt="" class="wp-image-158134" data-lazy-srcset="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249.png 802w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-500x298.png 500w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-550x328.png 550w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-800x478.png 800w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-600x358.png 600w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-150x89.png 150w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 802px) 100vw, 802px" data-lazy-src="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249.png"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249.png" alt="" class="wp-image-158134" srcset="https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249.png 802w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-500x298.png 500w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-550x328.png 550w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-800x478.png 800w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-600x358.png 600w, https://www.skinnytaste.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Screenshot-2026-01-22-203249-150x89.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 802px) 100vw, 802px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;*&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1WH_rdx5PsjY-sK9Fw4HwoyotL2pBgirH2uSTLTts5oU/edit?usp=sharing" target="_blank" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener"&gt;Google doc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="print-this-wrapper ggnoads"&gt;&lt;p class="print-this-button-wrapper"&gt;&lt;button class="print-this-button submitbutton"&gt;Print Shopping List&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="print_this_6973f42b1c86a" class="print-this-container"&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shopping List&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Produce&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 medium (ripe) banana&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;4 medium oranges (any variety)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;4 medium pears (any variety)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (6-ounce) container raspberries or blackberries&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small pomegranate (or container of seeds)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium mango&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;4 medium lemons&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;4 medium limes&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small (5-ounce) PLUS 1 medium (6-ounce) Hass avocados&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;3 medium heads garlic&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 medium shallots&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (2-inch) piece fresh ginger&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium jalapeno&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;3 small PLUS 1 medium red bell peppers&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 medium zucchini&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;4 Persian (mini) cucumbers (can sub 1 medium English, if desired)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 medium cucumbers&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium head baby bok choy&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 ½ pounds green beans&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 medium carrots&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small bag baby carrots&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium PLUS 1 large head cauliflower (can sub 1 pound pre-riced for medium head, if desired)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;¾ pound broccoli florets&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 pounds (4 medium) Yukon Gold potatoes&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small bunch scallions&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small bunch/container fresh thyme&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small bunch/container fresh dill&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small bunch/container fresh mint&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium bunch fresh cilantro&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small bunch fresh Italian parsley&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 (5-ounce) clamshell/bag baby spinach&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (1-pound) clamshell/bag baby arugula&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium head Boston or Bibb lettuce&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small head Romaine lettuce&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small head Iceberg lettuce (can sub a small bag pre-shredded, if desired)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium plum tomato&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;3 medium vine-ripened tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 dry pint cherry or grape tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small container Pico de Gallo (or &lt;a href="https://www.skinnytaste.com/pico-de-gallo-salsa-0-pts/" data-wpel-link="internal" target="_self" rel="follow"&gt;ingredients to make your own&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small PLUS 1 medium red onion&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small PLUS 3 medium yellow onions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meat, Poultry and Fish&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 small package chicken breakfast sausage links (can buy frozen, if desired)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;¾ pound ground turkey breakfast sausage&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 pound hot Italian chicken sausage&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 pound ground chicken&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 pound boneless, skinless chicken breasts&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 ½ pounds bone-in, skin-on chicken thighs&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 pound 93% lean ground turkey&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (6-ounce) salmon fillet&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 ½ pounds (4) tilapia, flounder or grouper fillets&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (2 ½-pound) boneless beef chuck roast&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Condiments and Spices&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extra virgin olive oil&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Canola oil&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Cooking spray&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Olive oil spray (or get a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Misto-Brushed-Aluminum-Olive-Sprayer/dp/B00004SPZV/ref=sr_1_1?s=grocery&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1515181085&amp;amp;sr=8-1&amp;amp;keywords=misto&amp;amp;th=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow sponsored external noopener" data-wpel-link="external"&gt;Misto&lt;/a&gt; oil mister)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Kosher salt (I like &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0011BPMUK/ref=as_li_qf_sp_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=1094004-20&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B0011BPMUK&amp;amp;linkId=de126591a74a25f41428f89bbb2986da&amp;amp;th=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow sponsored external noopener" data-wpel-link="external"&gt;Diamond Crystal&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Pepper grinder (or fresh peppercorns)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Turmeric&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Dijon mustard&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Sweet red chili sauce&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Sriracha sauce&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Sesame oil&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Rice vinegar&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Honey&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Hoisin sauce*&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Reduced sodium soy sauce*&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Cumin&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Garlic powder&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Oregano&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Onion powder&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Red wine vinegar&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Curry powder&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Taco seasoning (or buy paprika and chili powder and make your own with ingredients in list)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Bay leaves&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Balsamic vinegar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dairy &amp;amp; Misc. Refrigerated Items&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 (8-ounce) bottle pomegranate juice&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;2 (14-ounce) packages extra-firm tofu&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 18-pack large eggs&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 pint liquid egg whites&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (12-ounce) container skim milk&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 pint unsweetened almond milk&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 pint whole or reduced fat milk&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (5.3-ounce) container low fat (2%) plain Greek yogurt&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (16-ounce) container nonfat plain Greek yogurt&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small tub light sour cream&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small tub whipped butter&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (8-ounce) bag shredded reduced fat Mexican cheese blend&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (8-ounce) bag part-skim mozzarella cheese&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 block feta cheese&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package crumbled blue cheese&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 medium wedge fresh Parmesan cheese&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small wedge Pecorino Romano (can sub 2 tablespoons Parmesan in Spicy Linguine, if desired)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grains*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 package dry whole wheat orzo&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 package dry whole wheat linguine&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 package dry pearled farro&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 package seasoned breadcrumbs&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 package plain panko breadcrumbs&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package all-purpose flour&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small loaf slice whole grain bread (I like Dave’s Killer Bread)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 package burrito size low carb whole wheat flour tortillas (such as La Tortilla Factory)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package corn tortillas or crunchy corn shells (your choice)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Canned and Jarred&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 (3-ounce) packets tuna in water&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (8-ounce) can water chestnuts&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (15-ounce) can low sodium navy beans&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (15-ounce) can black beans&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (15-ounce) can chickpeas&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small jar pitted Spanish green olives&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 large jar capers&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (12-ounce) jar roasted peppers&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 jar sundried tomatoes in oil&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (15-ounce) can tomato sauce&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (15-ounce) can crushed tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (16-ounce) carton beef bone broth&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (32-ounce) carton low sodium chicken broth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frozen&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 small package shelled edamame&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package pre-cooked brown rice (or a single serve shelf stable package)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Misc. Dry Goods&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 single-serve package unflavored protein powder&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 single-serve package vanilla protein powder&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package ground flax (meal)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package chia seeds&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package unsalted cashews (if buying from bulk bin, you need 2 tablespoons)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package shelled pistachios (if buying from bulk bin, you need ¼ cup)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package raw almonds (if buying from bulk bin, you need 2 tablespoons)&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package granulated sugar&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package brown sugar&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small package pitted prunes&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 single serve bottle Pinot Grigio&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 small bottle sherry wine&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;1 (1 ¼-ounce) package dry onion soup mix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;*You can buy gluten free, if desired&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="print-this-button-wrapper"&gt;&lt;button class="print-this-button submitbutton"&gt;Print Shopping List&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


		
		
			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Skinnytaste</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:59:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxNOGc4azVWcC1KWHlJMWhLMTE1V0gxSkdtWUpWSzk2bHZhN0R5SUM4TWtvZmNhT3JjaVdfNUk4aENKUTh4UC03NmVrQkVQY0ExaHY0aVNuYjI1aHlINzlLaXRMNkVRRUJvN3M4eTAwNVMxMlg5aWVpNnNPQ2hpWk53Mw</guid></item><item><title>正如最近的一项研究所表明的那样，肉食者真的比非肉食者更有可能活到100岁吗？ -对话</title><link>https://theconversation.com/are-meat-eaters-really-more-likely-to-live-to-100-than-non-meat-eaters-as-a-recent-study-suggests-273861</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="grid-ten large-grid-nine grid-last content-body content entry-content instapaper_body inline-promos" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;People who don’t eat meat may be less likely than meat eaters to reach the age of 100, according to a recent study. But before you reconsider your plant-based diet, there’s more to these findings than meets the eye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0002916525007282?via%3Dihub"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; tracked over 5,000 Chinese adults aged 80 and older who participated in the Chinese Longitudinal Healthy Longevity Survey, a nationally representative study that began in 1998. By 2018, those following diets that don’t contain meat were less likely to become centenarians compared with meat eaters. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the surface, this appears to contradict decades of research showing that plant-based diets are good for your health. Vegetarian diets, for example, have been consistently linked to lower risks of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s00394-022-02942-8"&gt;heart disease and stroke&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.numecd.2011.07.004"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2337/dc08-1886"&gt;obesity&lt;/a&gt;. These benefits come partly from higher fibre intake and lower saturated fat consumption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what’s going on? Before drawing any firm conclusions, there are several important factors to consider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Your body’s needs change as you age&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This study focused on adults aged 80 and older, whose nutritional needs differ markedly from those of younger people. As we age, physiological changes alter both how much we eat and what nutrients we need. &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2818133/"&gt;Energy expenditure drops&lt;/a&gt;, while &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/jcp.25001"&gt;muscle mass, bone density&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1017/S1041610203008779"&gt;appetite&lt;/a&gt; often decline. These shifts increase the risk of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S0140-6736(22)02612-5"&gt;malnutrition&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jamda.2016.12.074"&gt;frailty&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most evidence for the health benefits of diets that exclude meat comes from studies of younger adults rather than frail older populations. Some research suggests older non-meat eaters face a higher risk of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12916-020-01815-3"&gt;fractures&lt;/a&gt; due to lower calcium and protein intake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In later life, nutritional priorities &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s13668-023-00473-0"&gt;shift&lt;/a&gt;. Rather than focusing on preventing long-term diseases, the goal becomes maintaining muscle mass, preventing weight loss and ensuring every mouthful delivers plenty of nutrients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The study’s findings may, therefore, reflect the nutritional challenges of advanced age, rather than any inherent problems with plant-based diets. Crucially, this doesn’t diminish the well-established health benefits of these diets for younger and healthier adults.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="align-center "&gt;
            
            &lt;figcaption&gt;
              &lt;span class="caption"&gt;Maintaining muscle mass in older age is important, and that requires protein.&lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;span class="attribution"&gt;&lt;a class="source" href="https://www.shutterstock.com/image-photo/older-people-lifting-weights-gym-596085842?trackingId=%7B%22app%22%3A%7B%22module%22%3A%22image-search-results%22%2C%22name%22%3A%22next-web%22%2C%22page%22%3A%22ecomm%22%7D%2C%22providers%22%3A%5B%7B%7D%5D%2C%22svc%22%3A%22recommendation-api%22%2C%22strategy%22%3A%7B%22name%22%3A%22INTENT%22%2C%22version%22%3A%221.0%22%7D%2C%22uuid%22%3A%22d5fb547f-f844-42bf-9c8f-c945d838d814%22%7D&amp;amp;listId=searchResults"&gt;CCISUL/Shutterstock.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;
          &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a crucial detail: the lower likelihood of reaching 100 among non-meat eaters was only observed in underweight participants. No such association was found in older adults of healthy weight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being underweight in older age is already strongly linked with increased risks of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.archger.2024.105467"&gt;frailty&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/aje/kwj114"&gt;death&lt;/a&gt;. Body weight therefore appears to be a key factor in explaining these findings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s also worth remembering that this was an observational study, meaning it shows associations rather than cause and effect. Just because two things occur together doesn’t mean one causes the other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The findings also align with the so-called &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu15071780"&gt;“obesity paradox”&lt;/a&gt; in ageing, where a slightly higher body weight is often linked to better survival in later life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Notably, the reduced likelihood of reaching 100 observed among non-meat eaters was not evident in those who included fish, dairy or eggs in their diets. These foods provide nutrients that are essential for maintaining muscle and bone health, including high-quality protein, vitamin B12, calcium and vitamin D.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Older adults following these diets were just as likely to live to 100 as meat eaters. The researchers suggested that including modest amounts of animal-source foods may help prevent undernutrition and loss of lean muscle mass in very old age, compared with strictly plant-based diets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What this means for healthy ageing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than focusing on whether one diet is universally better than another, the key message is that nutrition should be tailored to your stage of life. Energy needs decline with age (due to decreased resting energy expenditure), but some nutrient requirements increase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Older adults still require adequate protein, vitamin B12, calcium and vitamin D – especially to preserve muscle mass and prevent frailty. In older adulthood, preventing malnutrition and weight loss often becomes more important than long-term chronic disease prevention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plant-based diets can still be healthy choices, but they may require careful planning and, in some cases, supplementation to ensure nutritional adequacy, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s13668-017-0194-x"&gt;particularly in later life&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bottom line is that our nutritional needs at 90 may look very different from those at 50, and dietary advice should reflect these changes across the lifespan. What works for you now might need adjusting as you age – and that’s perfectly normal.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

        

        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Conversation</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:31:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizAFBVV95cUxPVmlFREJkV20zOWhEdUZrcFlBTFI1aGRCRmNzOGZHbXdMdzgzTEdWeW9yeF80YVBjUVNJbzZTdDVxZlNZTjZtOVdkTl9vWHo3dlgtMzZTMWx0Yjgwb3QtUFR4SHU2Tm43bFc0OHVFZjNneDBsWmFFZldvMTN5U3VvMUNmdWJkN2NmVFNUeWllWHd6VXNjU0NXNmVuY2tJeEdaSWsyOG9kMXlUZm4wR3ZRN0V6akl6OTBTNmtpTlRXV0p2eWpkRHh0UlE0c1E</guid></item><item><title>美国14个州麻疹感染病例超过400例：美国疾病控制与预防中心-美国广播公司新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/us-measles-cases-surpass-400-infections-14-states/story?id=129415270</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;At least 245 new measles cases have been reported in the U.S., according to &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;newly updated data&lt;/a&gt; from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The CDC said on Friday that a total of 416 cases have been reported in 14 states, including Arizona, California, Florida, Georgia, Idaho, Kentucky, Minnesota, North Carolina, Ohio, Oregon, South Carolina, Utah, Virginia and Washington. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Only three measles cases this year were from international visitors, CDC data shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;About 94% of cases are among people who are unvaccinated or whose vaccination status is unknown, the CDC said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Meanwhile, 3% of cases are among those who have received just one dose of the measles, mumps, rubella (MMR) vaccine and 3% of cases are among those who received the recommended two doses, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;CDC data shows that the majority of cases occur among patients under 19. About 2% of all measles patients in the U.S. have been hospitalized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;It comes as a measles outbreak, which began last year, continues to spread across South Carolina. The South Carolina Department of Public Health (DPH) reported &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://dph.sc.gov/diseases-conditions/infectious-diseases/measles-rubeola/2025-measles-outbreak" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;54 new cases of measles&lt;/a&gt; on Friday, bringing the total number of cases in the state to 700.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;There are currently 485 people in quarantine and 10 in isolation with the latest end of quarantine being Feb. 14, according to state health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Dr. Kristin Moffitt, an infectious diseases physician at Boston Children's Hospital, said she is "very alarmed" by the increase in measles cases in the U.S. over the last year or two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"I'm very worried about our current year already," she told ABC News. "Exceeding 2,000 cases in the last year is indeed alarming [and] ... I am worried that even our current year is off to a very concerning start."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Signs point the way to measles testing in the parking lot of the Seminole Hospital District across from Wigwam Stadium, February 27, 2025 in Seminole, Texas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Jan Sonnenmair/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Moffitt said that declining vaccination rates across the U.S. are behind the recent increase in measles cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"This is entirely due to declining vaccination rates," she said. "It's very clear based on where these outbreaks are occurring."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The CDC currently &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/vaccines/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;recommends&lt;/a&gt; that people receive two doses of the MMR vaccine, the first at ages 12 to 15 months and the second between 4 and 6 years old. One dose is 93% effective, and two doses are 97% effective against measles, the CDC says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;However, federal data shows vaccination rates have been lagging in recent years. During the 2024-2025 school year, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/schoolvaxview/data/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;92.5% of kindergartners received the MMR vaccine&lt;/a&gt;, according to data. This is lower than the 92.7% seen in the previous school year and the 95.2% seen in the 2019-2020 school year, before the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"What our concern is, is that as you have lower vaccination rates each year, you're gonna get a bigger and bigger population of people that are not immune, and so it's gonna increase your likelihood of having outbreaks," Dr. Robert Frenck, a professor of pediatrics in the division of infectious diseases of Cincinnati Children's Hospital, told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The national trends mirror those see in counties across the U.S. A &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/new-map-shows-spot-measles-risk-level-zip/story?id=129179712" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;recent map from ABC News&lt;/a&gt; -- a collaboration with researchers from Boston Children's Hospital, Harvard School of Medicine and Icahn School of Medicine at Mt. Sinai that allows people to type in their ZIP code and see the measles risk in their area -- found a wide range of risks in areas across the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Some counties and ZIP codes fell into the "lowest risk," with 85% or more of children under 5 years old receiving one or more measles vaccine dose to "very high risk" with fewer than 60% of children under age 5 receiving one or more measles vaccine dose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Moffitt explained that many counties are below the 95% vaccination threshold needed to achieve herd immunity, which occurs when enough people are vaccinated in a community so vulnerable people are protected and the virus has few people to infect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"So, one in five children, and it is absolutely school-age children who are representing the burden of these cases," she said. "So, if these numbers continue to increase, we could see significant surges, and they will be very local surges in hospital admissions for measles and complications of the measles."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;Richard Zhang, MD, MA, is a child and adolescent psychiatry fellow at Yale School of Medicine and a member of the ABC News Medical Unit.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;ABC News' Youri Benadjaous contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:08:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxNakhVZkJEVWtxU3htSTRQTEw1YkVEd2VXUGZRdFFya211UkpDNEhERlhXM1o3NEEybXlpSFhoUkRKUVdsd3JBVUtjc1c0NV9oUU1Cc3N5aVNZZk01aWRkZ0tMUzFCdURiSFpYdVZ6NUxTWWJ1eDlUYUIxaVBGNG5sQWI3LTUwQkRWSkotektFWDZTMWJYd3E1Zm1RdlRJYk3SAaQBQVVfeXFMTjBUYWRwVEliT1ROQzhWc2ZWOUhzc2ZnS0M3b1FyQjZreFVhY2lNeXppOVhXM2E0M0ZzajRwS2RNemRVdl95aGlwUmVOY3RfYjhTOTNGbEdvUG1leTBRbExyWUVDcFJDcWUtQjRUaEY4TW5wV3ByOVRpY2p5LXlYVzBkQzM5ZFktUjdURGNwQWhqYzFaVlBsTy1iV0R1UHNJUEJLMEM</guid></item><item><title>疫苗小组主席表示，脊髓灰质炎和其他疫苗应该是可选的，拒绝数十年的科学-纽约时报</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/23/health/milhoan-vaccines-optional-polio.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:51:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxPWG5nVkFJeDN1SFdUNTBGMkRGclAxeVVud1FiWHViMmNNRW1KSkV1QWxYMFdFUkl5MHhQZ0UyemE4QzVoUFktR2haUk9PUDlSbE5ocU5sY3BQcnhvWElNS3Zva0Vldi1jblAzcVZPTnJzUFBHU2ZDZVN6QzhTRE8wN011SDc</guid></item><item><title>科学家在海洋中发现了一个巨大的洞，里面充满了1700种神秘病毒-银河日报</title><link>https://dailygalaxy.com/2026/01/giant-hole-ocean-filled-mysterious-viruses/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content dynamic-entry-content" itemprop="text"&gt;
			
&lt;p&gt;Far out in the South China Sea, a massive underwater sinkhole plunges&lt;strong&gt; nearly 1,000 feet straight down&lt;/strong&gt;. It’s called the &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dragon Hole&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, and it’s a strange, silent world where oxygen vanishes and sunlight never reaches. Yet somehow, deep inside, life finds a way, just not the kind we’re used to. First charted by Chinese scientists in 2016, the &lt;em&gt;Sansha Yongle Blue Hole&lt;/em&gt; quickly drew attention for being one of the deepest known sinkholes on Earth. But its real mystery lies inside. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Deeper than Deep and Built to Last&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;At &lt;strong&gt;301 meters (998 feet) deep&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;162.3 meters (535 feet) wide&lt;/strong&gt;, the Dragon Hole is one of the largest ocean sinkholes ever recorded. As reported in a study &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-018-35220-x#Abs1" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;published in &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, researchers believe it formed during a period when sea levels were much lower. Rainwater slowly dissolved the limestone below, carving out steep walls in a kind of underwater stair-step shape. Later, when sea levels rose, the hole flooded and became what it is today.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;What makes the Dragon Hole truly unusual is how still it is. Because the opening is narrow and the sides are steep, the usual ocean mixing doesn’t happen. Water from the surface doesn’t reach the bottom, and fresh oxygen doesn’t make it in. Chinese researchers from the &lt;em&gt;First Institute of Oceanography&lt;/em&gt; found that oxygen levels drop sharply below the surface and vanish completely well before the midpoint. This creates several distinct zones in the water, each with its own chemistry and life forms.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Location-and-external-morphology-of-the-Sansha-Yongle-Blue-Hole-1200x564.webp" alt="Location And External Morphology Of The Sansha Yongle Blue Hole." class="wp-image-118418" srcset="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Location-and-external-morphology-of-the-Sansha-Yongle-Blue-Hole-scaled.webp 1200w, https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Location-and-external-morphology-of-the-Sansha-Yongle-Blue-Hole-420x198.webp 420w, https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Location-and-external-morphology-of-the-Sansha-Yongle-Blue-Hole-520x245.webp 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;sup&gt;Location and external morphology of the Sansha Yongle Blue Hole. Credit: Nature&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Life Without Oxygen Or Light&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Below 100 meters, everything changes. No fish, algae or plants survive past that point. But according to &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1186/s40793-025-00778-3" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environmental Microbiome&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, bacteria fill the gap, thriving in complete darkness by using chemical reactions to produce energy. In the first deep layer, known as &lt;strong&gt;Anoxic Zone I&lt;/strong&gt;, sulfur-oxidizing bacteria are everywhere. Two types, &lt;em&gt;Thiomicrorhabdus&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Sulfurimonas&lt;/em&gt;, make up&lt;strong&gt; nearly 90 percent of all microbial life &lt;/strong&gt;in this section.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Deeper still, &lt;strong&gt;past 140 meters&lt;/strong&gt;, researchers identified &lt;strong&gt;Anoxic Zone II&lt;/strong&gt;. In this area, nitrate disappears and hydrogen sulfide begins to build up. The &lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2025/12/nasa-discovers-bacteria-playing-dead-to-survive-extreme-space-conditions/" data-type="post" data-id="111924"&gt;bacteria &lt;/a&gt;there shift to a new kind of metabolism known as &lt;strong&gt;sulfate reduction&lt;/strong&gt;. Species like &lt;em&gt;Desulfatiglans&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Desulfobacter&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Desulfovibrio&lt;/em&gt; become dominant. Green sulfur bacteria such as &lt;em&gt;Prosthecochloris&lt;/em&gt; also appear, along with other rare microbes like &lt;em&gt;Chloroflexi&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Parcubacteria&lt;/em&gt;. Each group is specially adapted to the harsh, oxygen-free conditions.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/structural-features-of-the-Dragon-Hole-revealed-through-underwater-imaging-and-3D-mapping-1160x1200.webp" alt="Structural Features Of The Dragon Hole Revealed Through Underwater Imaging And 3d Mapping." class="wp-image-118416" srcset="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/structural-features-of-the-Dragon-Hole-revealed-through-underwater-imaging-and-3D-mapping-scaled.webp 1160w, https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/structural-features-of-the-Dragon-Hole-revealed-through-underwater-imaging-and-3D-mapping-406x420.webp 406w, https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/structural-features-of-the-Dragon-Hole-revealed-through-underwater-imaging-and-3D-mapping-503x520.webp 503w" sizes="(max-width: 1160px) 100vw, 1160px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;sub&gt;Structural features of the Dragon Hole revealed through underwater imaging and 3D mapping. Credit: Nature&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A Sealed World Full Of Surprises&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In the lab, researchers managed to grow &lt;strong&gt;294 strains of bacteria&lt;/strong&gt; from samples taken inside the hole. More than &lt;strong&gt;22 percent&lt;/strong&gt; of the anaerobic bacteria they found had &lt;strong&gt;never been identified before&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Scientists also looked at the viruses living in the &lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2025/07/scientists-reveal-a-bizarre-gravity-hole-beneath-the-indian-ocean-its-origins-are-more-alarming-than-expected/"&gt;hole&lt;/a&gt;. They discovered &lt;strong&gt;1,730 distinct types&lt;/strong&gt;, mostly from phage families like &lt;em&gt;Caudoviricetes&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Megaviricetes&lt;/em&gt;. But deeper in the anoxic layers, the viral landscape changes. Many of the &lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2026/01/scientists-viruses-behave-strangely-space/" data-type="post" data-id="117781"&gt;viruses &lt;/a&gt;found there couldn’t be linked to any known group. These unknown viruses could play a big role in how microbial life functions in extreme environments.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Daily Galaxy</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQbC0zZTltVWNsQzdxYWM2LUFaUC1SbGZHb1dYSXFrV2pHNWhoVThraFNTV083Z1FiaXZ6QTBSLWlwZWhvUkRPc2VzXzhqRVVkWXpNU0dfNURJRnlNS2NHUzQ3cURPLS0tVTU5Qnh5M0R3c3NXVGJKWWFXRU1EVkVNWQ</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，对于某些美国人来说，结直肠癌现在是最致命的类型-福克斯新闻</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/health/colon-cancer-now-deadliest-type-certain-group-americans-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;&lt;div class="featured featured-video video-ct" data-v-324c3b57&gt; &lt;div class="contain" data-v-324c3b57&gt;   &lt;div class="info" data-v-324c3b57&gt;&lt;div class="caption" data-v-324c3b57&gt; &lt;p data-v-324c3b57&gt;Gastroenterologist Dr. Ali Khan on what might be behind rising colon cancer among people under 50 and screening recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div id="beyondwords-wrapper" class="beyondwords-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="info"&gt;&lt;span class="label-bg"&gt;NEW&lt;/span&gt;You can now listen to Fox News articles!
  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="speakable"&gt;Colorectal cancer is now officially the leading cause of &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/cancer" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;cancer-related death&lt;/a&gt; among men and women 50 and younger, a significant increase from the 1990s, when it was the fifth deadliest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="speakable"&gt;That’s according to research from the American Cancer Society, published on Thursday in JAMA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers analyzed national mortality data for all types of cancers over multiple decades, finding that &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/cancer/colon-cancer" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;colorectal cancer&lt;/a&gt; now kills more people under 50 than all other types — including lung, breast, brain and leukemia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/deadly-cancer-risk-could-drop-single-10-minute-workout-study-suggests" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DEADLY CANCER RISK COULD DROP WITH SINGLE 10-MINUTE WORKOUT, STUDY SUGGESTS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cancer deaths overall have been on the decline for this age group since 1990, dropping by about 44% combined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colorectal cancer is the only major cancer that has seen a spike in mortality for those under 50 during that time period, the researchers noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image-ct inline"&gt; &lt;div class="info"&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Colorectal cancer is now officially the leading cause of cancer-related death among men and women 50 and younger.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;(iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The colorectal &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/medical-research/cancer-research" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow"&gt;&lt;u&gt;cancer research&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; community has been working to determine why rates are rising among young adults, according to Dr. Aparna Parikh, medical director of the Center for Young Adult Colorectal Cancer at the Mass General Cancer Center, who is not affiliated with the ACS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLICK HERE FOR MORE HEALTH STORIES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We don't entirely understand why yet, but it seems to be an interplay of a person’s risk factors, overall makeup and early exposures," she previously told Fox News Digital. "The exposures include &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/nutrition-and-fitness/nutrition" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;dietary exposures&lt;/a&gt;, environmental exposures and possible antibiotic exposures, as well as lifestyle factors in the right host."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image-ct inline"&gt; &lt;div class="info"&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Colorectal cancer is the only major cancer that has seen a spike in mortality for those under 50 in the past three decades.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;(iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some primary risk factors include family history, obesity, smoking, &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/beer" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;heavy alcohol&lt;/a&gt;, a diet high in red and processed meats, inflammatory bowel disease, and a personal history or family history of polyps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To reduce cases in younger patients, the doctor stressed the importance of raising public awareness of the disease around recognizing symptoms early.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLICK HERE TO SIGN UP FOR OUR HEALTH NEWSLETTER&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some early warning signs of colorectal cancer include changes in bowel habits, abdominal pain, rectal bleeding, weakness and &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/nutrition-and-fitness/weight-loss" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;weight loss&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image-ct inline"&gt; &lt;div class="info"&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The U.S. Preventive Services Task Force recommends that average-risk adults begin screening for colorectal cancer at age 45.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;(iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS?pid=AppArticleLink&amp;amp;af_dp=foxnewsaf%3A%2F%2F&amp;amp;af_web_dp=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.foxnews.com%2Fapps-products" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLICK HERE TO DOWNLOAD THE FOX NEWS APP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Preventive Services Task Force (USPSTF) recommends that average-risk adults begin screening for colorectal cancer at age 45, continuing through age 75. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those with a &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/genetics" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;genetic or family history&lt;/a&gt; may be advised to screen earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between 75 and 85, the agency says screening decisions should be based on each individual’s history, preferences and overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/lifestyle/quizzes" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TEST YOURSELF WITH OUR LATEST LIFESTYLE QUIZ&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The gold standard is colonoscopy — but there are also stool-based tests that are appropriate," Parikh said. "If you are having any symptoms like weight loss, blood in stool, anemia or change in &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/digestive-health" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;bowel habits&lt;/a&gt;, you should go straight to colonoscopy."&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;div class="article-meta"&gt;&lt;div class="author-bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Melissa Rudy is senior health editor and a member of the lifestyle team at Fox News Digital. Story tips can be sent to melissa.rudy@fox.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fox News</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:00:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxPODJwanpfTHBWSUszdWkzRTVpWC13Z3BDMWFmel84YXZ0N0VVSVZzT2RwZkVhQkVROHo4UDE5Vkl5a0NGQVFqeXFhV084YlY4dGo5UFNRTjZGb2xGNkhRdkJqZl9zSzlNSkhZUGFrQkdBWUpDU0tDOWI1VUw1NU5GTU12cHUxckVCM0ZIRDNsRU1LNEdZcWhTdDhRSU1WcEnSAaQBQVVfeXFMUGZMcEgwbUpoeXVraWpRRWZyMUNzbDkwaE9uc3ZFTkxsV3dwNGFjVXlQanFaVzJ3SlJQa1RaWnloeDNLejVnM29KcEVibGs4S3dDQkd4elN1QVFVcjN3WlI2SEpheENnNXo0MXBlRWhCQTFfYkV4SmNTMnhBOUVoRDktczVocVlaTGFJWHRYTWdRTGgwTzdHM0kzWHpBcC1zU1k1M1g</guid></item><item><title>传染性信息2026年1月23日-每日科斯</title><link>https://www.dailykos.com/stories/2026/1/23/2364921/-Infectious-Information-1-23-2026</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story__text"&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Two members of the vaccine injury advisory group &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/two-members-removed-federal-vaccine-injury-advisory-group" target="_blank"&gt;Have been removed before their terms were up.&lt;/a&gt;  It is feared that RFKJr intends to alter definitions of injury and bankrupt the system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mpox can be asymptomatic and still transmitted.  &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/mpox/mpox-doesn-t-always-cause-illness-yet-many-patients-have-long-term-effects-studies-suggest" target="_blank"&gt;It also produces some long term effects.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div id="logged-in-items"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Carolina's &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/measles/south-carolina-measles-outbreak-expands-200-reaches-646-cases" target="_blank"&gt;Measles outbreak&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;  is expanding rapidly, and may soon surpass the West Texas outbreak as the country's largest.  It has spread to 2 university campuses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Utah is also &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/measles/utah-measles-total-rises-216-cdc-deputy-director-says-losing-elimination-status-cost-doing" target="_blank" title=""&gt;Seeing more cases.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; And the deputy director of the CDC thinks losing our elimination status is no big deal, and blames the outbreaks on international travel, which is untrue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div id="story-2357394"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;p class="is-empty-p"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wall Street Journal&lt;/em&gt; poll shows &lt;a href="https://www.wsj.com/politics/policy/voters-skeptical-of-rfk-jr-s-vaccine-overhaul-112f5144" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;half of US voters&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;are less confident in federal vaccine guidance due to Trump administration policies, with 50% disapproving of Trump’s handling of the changes to routine vaccine recommendations. About 36% of those polled said they approve of changes to federal vaccine guidance, while 13% said they were unsure. The poll also showed that health insurance costs, including rising premiums, are a top priority for voters in a midterm election year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p class="is-empty-p"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.newschannel5.com/news/state/tennessee/williamson-county/families-share-histoplasmosis-stories-as-tennessee-cases-climb-to-more-than-30" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Middle Tennessee&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;is seeing an emerging cluster of histoplasmosis cases, with one family going public to say their 14-year-old daughter died from the fungal infection in December. The family of that girl is urging residents and clinicians to be on the watch for histoplasmosis and increase early testing. The girl’s mother said she did not receive a positive histoplasmosis diagnosis until after her death. According to local news, histoplasmosis is commonly found throughout the soil in Tennessee. A cluster of more than 30 human cases has been identified in Williamson and Maury counties, but so far there has not been a clear source of exposure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p class="is-empty-p"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The World Health Organization’s (WHO’s) Western Pacific Region Office (WHO’s WPRO) described&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://cdn.who.int/media/docs/default-source/wpro---documents/emergency/surveillance/avian-influenza/ai_20260116.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;three new&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;human H9N2 avian flu cases in mainland China. All three cases were reported to the WHO from January 9 and 15, and all three involve children, including a 5-year-old from Hubei province, an 8-year-old from Jiangsu&lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;province, and a 1-year-old from Guangxi province. All had symptom onset in November and December of last year. Only the child from Hubei province had a known exposure to backyard poultry. All three patients have recovered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And Minnesota is being &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/avian-influenza-bird-flu/turkey-farm-minnesota-hit-hard-avian-flu" target="_blank"&gt;Hit hard with H5N1 avian flu.&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Long Covid in kids &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/covid-19/research-ties-long-covid-kids-chronic-school-absenteeism-learning-problems" target="_blank" title=""&gt;Is tied to absenteeism and learning problems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New World screwworm is now &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/new-world-screwworm/cdc-warns-about-new-world-screwworm-just-across-border-mexico" target="_blank"&gt;Just across the border in Me&lt;/a&gt;xico.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The death toll from USAID cuts under DOGE &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/chikungunya/quick-takes-death-toll-usaid-cuts-withdrawal-chikungunya-vaccine-funding-updated-ebola" target="_blank"&gt;Has reached about 3/4 of a million.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this admin doubles down by withdrawing &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/public-health/us-formally-withdrawals-world-health-organization-leaving-debt" target="_blank"&gt;From WHO, though leaving debt behind.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the Texas attorney general is now basing law enforcement decisions on &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/texas-attorney-general-takes-aim-pediatricians-who-vaccinate-claiming-they-are" target="_blank" title=""&gt;Internet conspiracy theories!&lt;/a&gt;  Because apparently insanity is contagious among Republicans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class="is-empty-p"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;..&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="table-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;table align="center" class="basic-table"&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dailykos.com/groups/Infectious%20Information" target="_blank" title=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Infectious Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;is a DK group for collecting diaries on all things infectious, both basic educational material and breaking news updates.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Given the precarious state of public health agencies under the Orange Menace, it is my hope that the information&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;itself&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;can be infectious, spread widely to all your contacts, in the hope of promoting self-defense from disease. Knowledge is the best inoculation against misinformation!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;

			&lt;div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dailykos.com/users/strawbale" target="_blank" title=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kosmail&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;for an invitation if you want to join and have info to contribute, or&lt;a href="https://www.dailykos.com/groups/Infectious%20Information" target="_blank" title=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;follow the group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;to get these posts automatically in your activity stream.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class="is-empty-p"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class="is-empty-p"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Kos</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:00:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxPdFZhTDNFcGRONTNJOUxjc2RQWk8xSU1PN0pDUmdkYjNXcE5fcl8xeXp3Z2E4T3hVNGVOWkpqcUVlcGZWSTdiMkdwYWhEMjM3UVNoWFJhamxiLW9tRHN2RGpZdkR6TWR5OGQ4Tkg1OXBwbW81Qy15MXJIYWwwRkNxRXRzSzdUcGgyYzRmdg</guid></item><item><title>老年人平衡问题的惊人原因-《每日电讯报》</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/conditions/ageing/the-surprising-cause-of-balance-issues-in-the-elderly/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;p&gt;This is all relatively straightforward, but it turns out the significance of Dr Epley and his manoeuvre is considerably greater (importantly so) than previously appreciated. Dr Hilary Cox of Newcastle University reports that those calcium crystals may also account for a much wider range of balance problems and predisposition to falls (with all their attendant hazards) in the older age group, even in the absence of those classic symptoms of acute positional change induced vertigo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is necessarily more difficult to ascertain and remedy, nonetheless “barriers to diagnosis and treatment can be overcome with simple practical measures”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;An unusual remedy for hiccups which does not require a trip to A&amp;amp;E&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2025/12/31/millions-go-to-ae-for-hiccups-and-sore-throats/"&gt;As recently reported&lt;/a&gt; in this paper, many more people nowadays are heading to A&amp;amp;E for their ‘minor’ symptoms: for coughs a tenfold increase over the past five years to 435,000, almost 300,000 for constipation, 69,000 for a blocked nose, 20,000 for nausea and so on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still the surprising revelation of 4,200 attendances for hiccups would certainly suggest the need for a greater appreciation of the diverse range of simple remedies. The most familiar – holding one’s breath and counting to 40 – is presumed to splint the diaphragm (stop it moving), countering the spontaneous muscular contractions responsible for the hiccup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If that does not work, several methods of sipping water can be tried. “My mother used to make me stand, bend over a glass of water and take regular sips from the wrong (far) side of the glass”, one reader recalls. Another advises, “Grip the nose, press the ear flaps inwards and drink from a cup of water.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The erstwhile world authority on hiccups, Dr Janet Travell, advised the rather different approach of stimulating the uvula, the fleshy protuberance at the back of the throat. This can be accomplished by, for example, pulling forcefully on the tongue or stroking with a cotton bud. Swallowing dry granulated sugar or sucking on a lemon wedge soaked in Angostura Bitters may be effective for similar impact on the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, there is the option of activating the autonomic nervous system that controls the rhythmic contractions of the muscles of the diaphragm. This is most readily accomplished by pressing on the eyeballs or massaging the carotid artery on the side of the neck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 1988, emergency physician Dr Francis Fesmire reported the impressive benefits of a more intrusive method in a 27-year-old man afflicted with hiccupping up to 30 times a minute for 72 hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When pulling on the tongue and eyeball compression proved unsuccessful, slow circumferential rectal massage was attempted. The frequency of the hiccups slowed immediately and ceased soon after.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Email queries and comments in confidence to &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a class="ck-anchor ck-custom-link" href="mailto:Drjames@telegraph.co.uk"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Drjames@telegraph.co.uk&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxNRHlSRnV2bGtZdXlGVXc4Ukd2ZWxhNUJLQUN4MDM4a3l4a3NlX2Zzd3VUNXlyWWZENTcyUE92bkxhTXR1YjgydnQ3T0FFYW1XSTdHd0l4YjN3Ty0xd3FVeW5ZUzd0NEs2aEtMZ0hXdV9Lc0ZJOExYMkNtUW9hQ3lQLXpib2w3NEdYMDZVaGR5Tmw1SHh2YVZxeDFOYjQ3LUJjWjBYZmQ2VnQxbktiRnUwZktXODJMUQ</guid></item><item><title>由于令人担忧的副作用，某些人应避免健身房补充肌酸- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/creatine-side-effects-health-risks-754673-20260123</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;One of the more popular health products out there is the gym supplement creatine, which boosts your protein and means that if you really are putting in the hard work and exercise then you should see improved results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;If you want to increase &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/health"&gt;muscle mass&lt;/a&gt;, this is one of the safer supplements &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/lifestyle"&gt;gym-goers&lt;/a&gt; can get, though it's not without side effects, and there are people who probably ought to avoid it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Nutritionist and fitness expert Alan Aragon said it was the 'king' of supplements, as it could &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/what-creatine-does-body-health-expert-810324-20250825"&gt;also help your joints&lt;/a&gt; as well as the muscles which do the pulling. There are even people who've been trying to &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/lifestyle/creatine-super-dose-what-happens-gym-798987-20251001"&gt;create a 'super dose'&lt;/a&gt; of the stuff, as they believe it boosts the positive effects, and they wanted to see what the actual impact on their body would be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Scientists reckon that as well as boosting your physical prowess, it can also improve your &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/mental-health"&gt;mental health&lt;/a&gt;, but there are limits and there are cases when it would be a bad idea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;There's a lot of benefits to creatine if you take the right amount, but there's some people who might want to avoid it (Getty Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Processor Carmine Pariante of King's College London &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15455845/Truth-wonder-supplement-creatine-boost-middle-aged-muscles-help-sleep-brain-health-ease-womens-hormone-problems-doctors-tell-you-buy-steer-clear.html"&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; the Daily Mail that creatine could help your brain with depression, indicating a study from last year which suggested adults receiving cognitive behavioural therapy (CBT) for depression did better with creatine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;That study found that someone taking 5g a day of creatine alongside CBT appeared to have more &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/science"&gt;reduced symptoms&lt;/a&gt; of depression than with just the therapy alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The professor said results were 'encouraging', but warned people not to go overboard and that people with bipolar disorder should especially be aware. In rare cases, he noted the increased energy the supplement might give the brain could run the risk of mania.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Creatine should only be used under medical supervision in depression and people with bipolar disorder must be especially careful", he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Experts have warned that people with bipolar disorder would need to be careful with creatine as in rare cases it might cause mania (Getty Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;You definitely want to be careful when trying new things, and remember you can have too much of a good thing, as one person found out when he &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/creatine-overdose-warning-hospital-060375-20251120"&gt;accidentally overdosed on creatine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Aussie bloke Chris Hogan ended up in hospital and had to have large kidney stones removed after not reading the label on his supplement properly and taking 20g a day for seven weeks. For context, the recommended dose is somewhere between 3g and 5g a day, so Chris was at least four times over that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;In doing so, he put a lot of pressure on his kidneys and landed himself in a hospital bed with a very painful experience, so please remember to always read the labels and measure your doses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:46:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxNdnh6Y05QSE9Ram02QkVkNk9ZMktNWk10YWJKOTlnYzBBZnI0U3RQZExZdHhSNnZqaFJucUJhSDVHaXlTLUZWTkxXYlhkTEhWMV9ubWxnWTlRUnF0dkl1dUJFdDktTmxvZUlhZmpTXzNDeTRxekpJamw2NEUtMHNXWGZvOVpkMUZRdWxkRmtzTnI</guid></item><item><title>17种心脏健康、高蛋白早餐食谱- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/heart-healthy-high-protein-breakfast-recipes-11891179</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-article-intro_1-0" class="comp mntl-article-intro mntl-block article-content__description"&gt;&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Start your day with one of these delicious and filling breakfast recipes. With each dish having at least 15 grams of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-is-protein-and-its-benefits-11732679" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;&lt;u&gt;protein&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; per serving from ingredients like eggs, Greek yogurt and nut butters, these breakfasts can help you feel energized and stay full for longer. Plus, these breakfasts meet our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/our-food-and-nutrition-philosophy-6746110" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;&lt;u&gt;heart-healthy nutrition parameters&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, as they focus on foods that are sodium-conscious and lower in saturated fats like &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7872995/complete-list-of-heart-healthy-foods/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;&lt;u&gt;fruits and whole grains&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Recipes like our High-Protein Peanut Butter-Banana Oatmeal Bars and our Ransperry-Banana Yogurt Parfait are satisfying and nutritious options for your morning meal.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc__content_1-0" class="comp list-sc__content mntl-sc-page mntl-block" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 3, 6, 9, 12, 15, 18]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="list-sc-item_1-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-high-protein-peanut-butterbanana-oatmeal-bars"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; High-Protein Peanut Butter–Banana Oatmeal Bars &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_1-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jen Causey, Food Stylist: Julian Hensarling, Prop Stylist: Clarie Spollen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These peanut butter–banana oatmeal bars are a perfect grab-and-go breakfast, packed with protein to keep you full and energized. The combination of oats, peanut butter and banana provides a well-balanced dose of fiber, healthy fats and natural sweetness. Plus, they’re easy to make in advance and customize with mix-ins like dark chocolate chips or chopped nuts. Whether you need a quick morning bite or a post-workout snack, these bars are the perfect choice!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_2-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-raspberry-banana-yogurt-parfait"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Raspberry-Banana Yogurt Parfait &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_2-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Morgan Hunt Ward, Prop Stylist: Abby Armstrong, Food Stylist: Ruth Skipworth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This quick and easy raspberry and yogurt parfait combines creamy Greek-style yogurt with fiber-rich fruit and crunchy toasted pecans for a gut-friendly start to your day. Layering the ingredients in a jar makes for a portable, pretty and protein-packed meal that’s ready in minutes.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_3-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-strawberry-peanut-butter-chia-pudding"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Strawberry-Peanut Butter Chia Pudding &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_3-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jen Causey, Food Stylist: Margaret Monroe Dickey, Prop Stylist: Josh Hoggle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This creamy Strawberry–Peanut Butter Chia Pudding is the ultimate make-ahead breakfast that feels like dessert. Layers of naturally sweet strawberry chia pudding and a peanut butter–yogurt topping deliver fiber, healthy fats and plenty of plant-based protein. Make a batch ahead, chill it overnight and wake up to the flavor of a PB&amp;amp;J in spoonable, pudding form.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_4-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-high-protein-orange-mango-flaxseed-shake"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; High-Protein Orange-Mango Flaxseed Shake &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_4-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;People Inc Food Studios&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Bright, creamy and packed with staying power, this protein shake blends juicy mandarin, tropical mango and tangy strained yogurt into a sunshine-hued drink. With protein from the yogurt to keep you satisfied and natural sweetness from the fruit, it’s equally at home as a quick breakfast or a post-workout refresher.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_5-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-chocolate-strawberry-baked-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Chocolate-Strawberry Baked Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_5-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jen Causey, Food Stylist: Chelsea Zimmer, Prop Stylist: Claire Spollen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These chocolate-strawberry baked oats are a delicious breakfast that uses the classic pairing of sweet, ripe strawberries with chocolate. This dish gets its protein boost from cottage cheese, which blends beautifully into the oats while adding a subtle tang. For an extra protein punch, a scoop of protein powder works seamlessly into the mixture, making the oats an even more satisfying way to start the day.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_6-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-high-protein-blueberry--peanut-butter-chia-pudding"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; High-Protein Blueberry &amp;amp; Peanut Butter Chia Pudding &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_6-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jen Causey; Food Stylist: Chelsea Zimmer; Prop Stylist: Claire Spollen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This high-protein blueberry and peanut butter chia pudding is a perfect make-ahead breakfast packed with fiber and protein to keep you energized throughout the day. Chia seeds soak up the blended almond milk and blueberries overnight, creating a creamy pudding that’s layered for a peanut butter-and-jelly effect.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_7-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-watermelon-peach-smoothie"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Watermelon-Peach Smoothie &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_7-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ali Redmond&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This watermelon-peach smoothie is a refreshing drink that’s perfect for warm days. Made with ripe watermelon and frozen peaches, this smoothie bursts with fruity flavor without the need for added sugar. Use frozen peaches from a bag or freeze your own ripe, in-season peaches for the best sweet and fruity flavor.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_8-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-no-bake-breakfast-cookies"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; No-Bake Breakfast Cookies &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_8-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Morgan Hunt Glaze, Prop Stylist: Pricilla Montiel, Food Stylist: Chelsea Zimmer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These no-bake breakfast cookies are the sweet start your morning needs! Packed with oats, almond butter, chia seeds and dried blueberries, these cookies offer a hefty dose of fiber to keep you feeling full, as well as healthy fats and plant-based protein for lasting energy. They’re easy to make and perfect for busy mornings. Just grab and go for a breakfast you can feel good about!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_9-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-chocolate-cherry-protein-shake"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Chocolate-Cherry Protein Shake &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_9-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jen Causey, Food Stylist: Emily Nabors Hall, Prop Stylist: Lindsey Lower&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This chocolate-cherry protein shake—made with Greek-style yogurt and peanut butter—is a protein powerhouse, perfect for a post-workout refuel or a satisfying snack. Cherries provide natural sweetness, and the chocolate flavor from the cocoa complements the peanut butter without any added sugar. Everything blends together in a shake that's both nutritious and delicious!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_10-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-shredded-wheat-with-raisins--walnuts"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Shredded Wheat with Raisins &amp;amp; Walnuts &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_10-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jake Sternquist, Food Stylist: Holly Dreesman, Prop Stylist: Lexi Juhl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This shredded wheat with raisins and walnuts is an easy breakfast to reach for when you want something quick with plenty of fiber and healthy fats. For a no-added-sugar breakfast, be sure to use unsweetened shredded wheat cereal. Read the label and opt for brands that contain 0 grams of added sugar.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_11-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-high-protein-cinnamon-roll-oatmeal"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; High-Protein Cinnamon-Roll Oatmeal &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_11-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Brie Goldman, Food Stylist: Annie Probst, Prop Stylist: Joseph Wanek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Flavored with cinnamon, vanilla, maple syrup and a Greek-style yogurt “frosting,” this cinnamon-roll oatmeal is a winning breakfast worth waking up for. Oats offer lots of filling fiber to help keep you full and your heart healthy. Add toasted chopped walnuts if you want a little extra crunch.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_12-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-black-forest-cakeinspired-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Black Forest Cake–Inspired Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_12-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jen Causey, Food Stylist: Chelsea Zimmer, Prop Stylist: Christina Daley&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These overnight oats are filled with classic Black Forest cake flavors. From the rich chocolaty oats to the dark-sweet-cherry yogurt base, it feels like having dessert for breakfast in the best way possible. Dark sweet cherries are traditional for the classic cake, but you can replace the cherry yogurt and chopped cherry topping with another fruit if you prefer.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_13-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-high-protein-peanut-butter-banana--blueberry-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; High-Protein Peanut Butter, Banana &amp;amp; Blueberry Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_13-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jake Sternquist, Food Stylist: Annie Probst, Prop Stylist: Joseph Wanek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These overnight oats pack 17 grams of protein per serving, thanks to Greek-style yogurt, peanut butter and soymilk. We sweeten these oats naturally with banana, and add blueberries for more fruity flavor. Divide the mixture into Mason jars for an easy grab-and-go breakfast.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_14-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-spinach-peanut-butter--banana-smoothie"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Spinach, Peanut Butter &amp;amp; Banana Smoothie &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_14-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;Ali Redmond&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Peanut butter and banana is a classic combo that's even more delicious with the addition of tangy probiotic-rich kefir. Plus, this peanut butter banana smoothie helps you up your veggie servings for the day with a bit of mild-flavored spinach mixed in.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_15-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-breakfast-beans-with-microwave-poached-egg"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Breakfast Beans with Microwave-Poached Egg &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In Costa Rica, this popular breakfast bean dish is called gallo pinto, which means spotted rooster, referring to the dark beans amid the pale rice. We call for cooked barley here, but you can use whatever leftover cooked grain you may have on hand.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_16-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-air-fryer-french-toast-sticks"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_64-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Air-Fryer French Toast Sticks &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_15-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason Donnelly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This air-fryer French toast recipe cuts the toast into strips that are crispy on the outside, tender on the inside and perfect for dipping into maple syrup or your favorite fruit compote.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_17-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3-ingredient-bell-pepper--cheese-egg-cups"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_68-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 3-Ingredient Bell Pepper &amp;amp; Cheese Egg Cups &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_69-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_16-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Morgan Hunt Glaze, Food Stylist: Jennifer Wendorf, Prop Stylist: Shell Royster&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_70-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Requiring just three main ingredients—bell peppers, eggs and shredded cheese—these portable baked eggs are simple to assemble and perfect for meal prep.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:56:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQdXNGeGlDaFdQZHB0VndfME9rRldiZ3hWdHF5Qi1TdTZIeWdSNkFrcWpKQl9rdklJaWx2T3BxdzMyMUlqaW5oU0tLRXJ6bWlwWmh5V3FkTUZBNlV2aW1pU0pVSHVCSEEtRXlndEwyTVlVczZsX1VnNVZQT1lxY2VVWVZiT0pvMVk</guid></item><item><title>生活在我们口中的微生物可能是预防肥胖的关键- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-microbes-mouths-key-obesity.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:43:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE5EU1FnVXNQcng1RWNKSFNJOWlRQ3I3azFnUWk4ZlhVUl9pWjlFc0RxcjZlaEhyeHRRaGdCamV1RDRhZEFMaTN4MzlkcXJtUlotMzRWbWNsYmM2N1otR2xnN0YxRm5samJmdEgtMEoyRnpWVG1xSzFiWWNEdw</guid></item><item><title>为缓解紧张而经常摔断脖子的女性中风（独家） - AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/woman-routinely-cracked-her-neck-093000052.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Courtesy of KayLynne Felthager&lt;/p&gt; KayLynne Felthager&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;KayLynne Felthager says she cracked her neck while driving home from Walmart and immediately felt unusual pain&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Days later, she lost vision, went numb on one side and couldn’t speak, prompting her husband to rush her to the ER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors told her she had an artery dissection and stroke, and she was flown by helicopter to a larger hospital for care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the kind of small, automatic movement most people wouldn’t think twice about: a quick stretch to pop her neck after a long day. But for KayLynne Felthager, that split-second habit would end up turning into a medical emergency she never saw coming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Okay, so it’s two different days,” Felthager says, explaining that everything started on Jan. 4, 2023, when she was driving home from Walmart and felt a headache coming on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Felthager said cracking her neck was something she used to do all the time when headaches hit. “I used to always, it was a habit,” she says. “I would get a headache and I would immediately crack my neck.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She remembered stretching her head far to the right until she felt a crack on the left side of her neck. She also noted that she didn’t use her hands to force it, something she said people online later assumed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At first, she thought nothing of it and even felt a moment of relief. But almost immediately after, she said she felt sharp, severe pain radiating down her neck in a way that didn’t feel normal for her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the next few days, the pain didn’t fade, and Felthager said she struggled to move her head without hurting. She relied on over-the-counter pain medication just to get through the discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even as the ache lingered through the weekend, she tried to keep living her life and pushed through plans with her family. She said she noticed how strange it felt, but still didn’t suspect anything serious was building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then on Jan. 9, the warning signs became impossible to ignore. Felthager said she was sitting at the kitchen island doing her makeup before a date night when a bright light suddenly took over her right eye, and her vision disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I had, like, a blinding light come through my right eye, and then lost vision,” she recalls. “It was just like I could see this bright light, but nothing else out of the right side.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Courtesy of KayLynne Felthager&lt;/p&gt; KayLynne Felthager and her husband&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;She tried blinking hard, hoping it would go away, and even attempted to research what was happening. But she said she couldn’t see clearly enough to make sense of anything, and the moment left her rattled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About 15 minutes later, her vision returned, and she assumed she was heading into yet another headache. Still, her body didn’t feel right, and she said she told her husband something felt “off” as they drove into town.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soon after, she said the entire right side of her body became tingly and then went numb. Even then, she describes the sensations as confusing more than frightening, like her body was throwing strange signals she couldn’t interpret fast enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scariest moment, she said, was when she tried to speak and realized she couldn’t form real words. “It literally just came out, like jumbled gibberish,” Felthager says, remembering how her husband immediately turned the car toward the ER.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once inside, doctors rushed her back, and from there, parts of the experience blur together. She remembers a flurry of movement, nurses working to start an IV, and being taken back for a CT scan with contrast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the middle of the chaos, Felthager said her mind latched onto one word as everything else felt unreachable. “The only word I could honestly think of was God,” she says. “And I just, like, kept repeating that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She recalls being shown picture cards as doctors tried to evaluate her, but she struggled to name what she was seeing. Slowly, she said things began to return, from recognizing loved ones to being able to speak again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eventually, Felthager said doctors told her she’d suffered an artery dissection and a clot had traveled to her brain, causing a stroke. She was told the clot dissolved before they had to intervene, something she said she still feels grateful for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because she lives in a small town in Colorado, she said doctors decided she needed to be transferred for more specialized treatment. She was flown by helicopter to a larger hospital, a detail that she said still feels surreal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the hospital, Felthager said doctors told her artery dissections can happen in situations involving chiropractic adjustments or cracking the neck. One doctor tried to calm her fears, but she remembers thinking it was easier said than done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her neurologist also offered another possible trigger: Felthager said she’d recently had the stomach flu and had been violently sick. “She was like, either from violently puking or from you cracking your neck, is what this happened from,” Felthager says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Afterward, she said she was placed on heavy blood thinners and later continued on aspirin while she healed. For months, she followed up with regular CT scans until she said doctors confirmed she was fully recovered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Obviously, they were like, ‘Maybe stop cracking your neck,’ ” she says. “And I was like, fair. I will never again.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Courtesy of KayLynne Felthager&lt;/p&gt; KayLynne Felthager and her husband&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, nearly three years later, Felthager said she feels healthy and back to normal physically. But emotionally, she said the experience changed how she thinks about her body and how quickly something can go wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I have a little more health anxiety,” she says, explaining that even small changes in her vision can still send her spiraling. She adds that anxiety sometimes extends to her kids and husband, too, because the stroke taught her how fragile “normal” can be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the time since, Felthager said life has moved forward in joyful ways, including welcoming another baby into their family. And unexpectedly, her story found a huge new audience when she posted about it on &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@kaylynnefelthager/video/7579389274747931917" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:TikTok;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;TikTok&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She said the viral video wasn’t some carefully planned warning, but a quick post she made while trying to grow her account. “Honestly, it was just like a filler post,” she says, explaining she expected her usual few hundred views.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, she watched it blow up, and with the attention came intense reactions. “Oh, my goodness, I stopped replying because I was like, I can’t handle some of these people,” she says, laughing at how overwhelming the comments became.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking back, Felthager said the biggest surprise was realizing how many people immediately saw themselves in her story. “People are, they can get really freaked out by health things,” she says, adding she understands because she lives with that anxiety now, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And while she knows her story can sound scary, she said her intention has never been to send people into panic. “I don’t want to scare people,” she says. “It’s just what happened to me.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/woman-who-routinely-cracked-her-neck-suffers-stroke-exclusive-11890602" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:40:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxOVUF6bmExT0NycURuUXo1Qng0NTRFTU8xa0VqRUp2dWhRTldFVHBTN2R3ODN2cFR5ZEdFcy15LVVVY1NadmRQXzVjRVg3ZDNoWmZ2VmRTbHN1dzlqeTh5LW9pUEU0ODI5MHFLUkJiUGdYUGhpUGRoaU5nT0E4V25ULW5n</guid></item></channel></rss>