<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>根据注册营养师的说法，您可以在超市找到的5种最健康的蛋白质棒- REAL SIMPLE</title><link>https://www.realsimple.com/healthiest-protein-bars-at-the-supermarket-11824355</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="realsimple-sc-page_1-0" class="comp realsimple-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--summary realsimple-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Not all protein bars are healthy—the best ones provide at least 12 grams of protein, minimal added sugar, and simple, whole food ingredients rather than additives or preservatives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Different types suit different needs, from nut- and seed-based bars packed with healthy fats, to whey or egg white bars that deliver complete proteins, to vegan-friendly plant protein options.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Smart shopping matters—look for short ingredient lists, at least 3 grams of fiber, and no more than 10 grams of added sugar per serving to ensure your bar supports energy, satiety, and overall health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/dietitian-favorite-sources-of-protein-11820661" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Protein&lt;/a&gt; remains incredibly popular within the health-focused community, leading to a booming protein-based product market—one of the most notable being the humble protein bar. Consumers reach for these bars as a snack, workout fuel, or even meal replacement (though that’s not recommended). “Protein bars are best used as a convenient snack, not a replacement for balanced meals. Whole foods should still be the foundation, with bars stepping in when you need something quick, portable, and reliable,” explains Stephanie Militano, MS, RD, CSSD, sports dietitian and owner of SM Nutrition.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In turn, the world of protein bars has become nothing short of overwhelming. In fact, the market is &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; saturated with options that you could try a new brand every day for an impressively long time. However, these convenience items can be incredibly deceiving when it comes to perceived health benefits. Some deliver what they advertise—clean protein with minimal unwanted ingredients—while others are no more than a glorified candy bar.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Here, we’ll explore what makes one protein bar more or less healthy than the next, and highlight five &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; nutritious options to look for on your next grocery store run.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-makes-a-protein-bar-healthy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What Makes a Protein Bar Healthy? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As with many packaged foods, the key to determining a protein bar's healthfulness (or lack thereof) lies in the &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/red-flags-on-food-labels-8781749" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nutrition facts panel and ingredients list&lt;/a&gt;. In protein bars, you primarily want to check for protein, fiber, and whole food-based ingredients—as well as fat sources, added sugar, additives, preservatives, and artificial ingredients.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; First, you (of course) want to check how much protein the bar contains. This macro helps us feel full after eating, stabilizes blood sugars, and supports the maintenance, growth, and repair of most tissues in the body&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;—most notably muscle—among many other important benefits. “Aim for at least 12 grams of protein per bar. If using it as a meal replacement or post-workout recovery, choose bars closer to 20 grams,” shares Jessica Clancy-Strawn MA, RDN, media and kidney wellness dietitian in Houston, Texas. Ideally the protein source of your protein bar will be whole food-based—like from &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/healthiest-nuts-to-eat-11686130" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nuts&lt;/a&gt;, seeds, legumes, dairy, or &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/recipe-collections-favorites/healthy-meals/healthy-egg-recipes" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;eggs&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Then, there are a few “nice to have” nutrients and ingredients in protein bars—namely &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/how-much-fiber-do-you-need-a-day-7564730" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;fiber&lt;/a&gt; and/or fruits and veggies. Fiber offers similar metabolic benefits as protein&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, boosting satiety after eating and managing the blood sugar response. However, it’s also tied to improved digestive regularity, cholesterol levels, and gut health as a prebiotic (or food for healthy bacteria) in the gut microbiome&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;—which supports several other elements of health like immune&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and brain health&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Three grams (or more) of fiber per bar is a major added bonus. Meanwhile, fruit and veggies add micronutrients like vitamins, minerals, and plant compounds to your protein bar for overall health support.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Paying attention to the type of fat found in your protein bar is also important. “Favor &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/healthy-fats-8740244" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;healthy fats&lt;/a&gt; such as polyunsaturated, monounsaturated, and &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-with-more-omega-3s-than-salmon-11784373" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;omega-3&lt;/a&gt; and -6 fatty acids from sources like &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/olive-oil-health-benefits-8754789" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;olive oil&lt;/a&gt;, nuts, and seeds. Avoid saturated&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and trans fats&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, especially those from partially hydrogenated or refined vegetable oils, which are not heart-friendly,” explains Clancy-Strawn. Zero grams of trans fat and three grams or less of saturated fat per bar is ideal.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Then, when it comes to other ingredients to be wary of, be on the look out for added sugar, additives, preservatives, or artificial ingredients. “Choose bars with short, recognizable ingredient lists. Avoid preservatives and additives—especially risky ones like erythritol, carrageenan, soy lecithin, and potassium sorbate,” shares Clancy-Strawn, as these additives have been linked with stomach upset&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, unwanted heart health events&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/signs-of-inflammation-7565179" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;inflammation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, and fatigue&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Plus, many additives and preservatives, while technically deemed safe for consumption, lack the long-term research&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; needed to truly gauge their health implications. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Meanwhile, added sugar is a major pro-inflammatory agent&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the body that can be found in high amounts in certain protein bars. “Opt for bars with 10 grams or less of added sugars. Lower sugar and higher fiber content help manage blood sugar spikes and crashes, and support sustained appetite control,” adds Clancy-Strawn. “Non-nutritive naturally-occurring sweeteners, such as stevia or monk fruit sweetener are better options to look for in a protein bar,” Maura Fowler, MPH RDN CPH, registered dietitian and founder of Healthy You by Maura notes.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Additionally, many allergens can be found in protein bars—like nuts, &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/healthiest-seeds-11688836" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;seeds&lt;/a&gt;, and dairy (or dairy-based components like whey and casein). If you or your loved ones have any food allergies or sensitivities, it’s important to carefully examine the food label and allergen statement prior to investing in a new protein bar option.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-healthiest-protein-bars"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Healthiest Protein Bars  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Thankfully, there are plenty of protein bar categories that meet these criteria. Here are five of the top better-for-you options:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Primarily Nut, Seed, or Nut-Butter Based Bars &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “I always want to encourage protein that comes from whole foods first,” says Fowler—and nut and nut butter-based protein bars definitely fit this bill. Plus, these bars often provide additional nutrients like fiber, healthy fats, and a variety of micronutrients naturally found in the nuts, seeds, and their butters. “Nuts and seeds offer numerous health benefits&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, including improved cardiovascular health and reduced risk of cancer, respiratory illness, infectious disease, and diabetes,” Clancy-Strawn adds. There are plenty of brands that offer nut, seed, or nut/seed butter-based bars. “A few of my favorite brands are Kind Bars and Larabar,” shares Militano.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Allergen-Free Bars &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For those allergic to any (or several) of the nine major allergens, there are a handful of allergen-free protein bars available. “It’s always important to be mindful of individuals who have allergies, and provide adequate options for those folks too. 88 Acres and Alio are made with simple ingredients and are free of all nine allergens,” says Fowler When searching for these bars, it’s essential to double check the food label and allergen statement before serving them to another with severe allergies or sensitivities.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Whey Protein-Based Bars &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Whey protein-based bars contain all of the essential amino acids, which make them a great choice if you are trying to support muscle health—and they are also typically &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-that-have-the-most-protein-8763731" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;higher in protein&lt;/a&gt;,” says Militano. Fowler agrees, adding, “Whey protein continues to prove it’s an ultimate source of protein that your body can better absorb&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.” Many of the protein bars that you’ll find in grocery stores fit within this category. “Rise bars are great options that feature simple ingredients including &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/health-benefits-of-cashews-7110031" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;cashews&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/almonds-health-benefits-6835790" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;almonds&lt;/a&gt;, or sunflower seeds, and natural sweeteners. They contain no hazardous additives, offer 16 grams of protein, a good amount of fruits and vegetables, and are low in sodium and saturated fat,” shares Clancy-Strawn.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Plant Protein-Based Bars &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you have dairy sensitivities or follow a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/recipe-collections-favorites/healthy-meals/easy-vegan-recipes" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;plant-based diet&lt;/a&gt;, vegan protein bars are a smart grab. “For those who prefer dairy free or a vegan/vegetarian lifestyle, these are their bars,” Fowler encourages. And there are plenty of brands offering exceptional plant-based protein bars. “Known for being gluten-free, dairy-free, seed oil-free, and free of sugar alcohols, Trubar was established in 2019 and is widely available at Target,” explains Clancy-Strawn. “Think! Plant Based Protein Bars are also low in added sugar, only 190 calories, and have minimal saturated fats,” Fowler adds.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Egg Protein-Based Bars &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Similar to whey-based protein bars, options that garner their protein power from eggs also offer all nine essential amino acids for a complete protein snack. Most of these bars use &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/egg-white-nutrition" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;egg whites&lt;/a&gt; as a protein source, which conveniently adds protein without affecting the flavor or texture. When it comes to brands to keep an eye out for within this category, Clancy-Strawn offers, “simplicity at its finest, RXBARs feature nuts, natural flavors, egg whites, and dates, with the ingredient list proudly displayed on the front.” &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-to-look-for-in-a-healthy-protein-bar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What to Look for in a Healthy Protein Bar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While these protein bar varieties and brands are a great starting point for finding healthy options, they only scratch the surface of what's available in grocery stores nationwide. To uncover other nutritious choices, keep the following guidelines in mind:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Look for protein content of at least 12 grams per bar&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fiber content of at least three grams per bar is a nice bonus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Choose options with whole food, recognizable ingredients &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Aim for bars with zero grams of trans fat and three grams or less of saturated fat per serving&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The shorter the ingredient list, the better. Select options with ingredients you recognize and can pronounce over bars with high amounts of additives and preservatives&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be sure there’s no more than 10 grams of added sugar in the protein bar you purchase&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you or your loved one has food allergies, be sure to thoroughly examine the ingredients list and allergen statement to avoid those triggering foods&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Real Simple</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxOQ1hNdU9QbEozYjBTNmx0YnZlQWR2c2JxRmlZMFpjdHNtNkpBU1NFX2FsUUhWRUREUEg3Y00wQjQydmR6TzQ5LWpSakZpd09EeGZqb3dtbWI1SG5EZmpzQ3BqT1hXYlZxNWQxczNQR0Rwb3VRTExBaHR2TWRtOENyV0V0OS0</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，与朋友一起做几乎任何事情都会更好-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/10/05/friends-activities-happiness-research/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QN3BGEEWUNHOXAMDJ3IJONFIJY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Social interactions are essential for our well-being and happiness, research has shown. And now a large study supports that finding and suggests there are many ways to squeeze in more companionship — and happiness — into our busy lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxNQnZvaGhLRG1teHQ0RkN1Y1hzSVFmSzlZd0owVS1BLU54akJ4VWkxajE3VnR6SEZEWFBlc2dqY09GdldNcGFzMlU2dGQ0N01QZ08zenUtaU5RMjVkbk9CRlhKRnFwZzNOdlhpNkFJYi1LMFBkY0MtaHUycTZWYndoaVBQa1RycGNzRU9Qc1hlTDR2RW8</guid></item><item><title>新的研究挑战治疗癌症的长期方法- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/new-research-challenges-long-standing-method-for-treating-cancer</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Removing lymph nodes during  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="175710" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; surgery has saved countless lives in many tumour types. Yet recent research is challenging parts of this long-standing practice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine your body's immune defences as a city, and lymph nodes as the hubs where police and firefighters gather fresh intel to launch their attack on criminals. What happens if you remove too many of these hubs? This is a new question at the centre of modern &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/cancer-14"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When surgeons remove lymph nodes, it's usually for two reasons: to find out whether cancer has spread, and to prevent further spread to other organs. For decades, this approach represented the best standard of care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-useless-organ-that-doctors-often-remove-could-actually-fight-cancer"&gt;A 'Useless' Organ That Doctors Often Remove Could Actually Fight Cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a tumour escapes its original site, cancer cells often travel through lymph vessels and settle in the nearest lymph nodes, which act as biological filters. Detecting cancer cells in lymph nodes signals that a patient's disease may be more likely to return after treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Removing these nodes allows doctors to &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/about-cancer/diagnosis-staging/staging"&gt;"stage"&lt;/a&gt; the disease accurately, and potentially increase the chances of eradicating all tumour cells – while also telling oncologists like me to treat the cancer more aggressively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But lymph nodes are not just passive waystations. They play an active role in the &lt;a href="https://www.aru.ac.uk/news/using-the-bodys-immune-system-to-combat-diseases"&gt;body's immune response&lt;/a&gt;, acting as meeting points for immune cells to share information about cancer. Recent scientific discoveries have led researchers to rethink how crucial these hubs are for sparking powerful, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/unlocking-the-bodys-defences-understanding-immunotherapy-226858"&gt;lasting immune reactions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41590-025-02276-7"&gt;newest studies&lt;/a&gt; shows lymph nodes help maintain a special type of immune cell called "CD8 positive T cells", which can destroy cancer cells. These immune cells are primed and kept ready to act by the environment inside the lymph nodes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without these hubs, the body's anti-cancer immune response, especially during &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-024-03083-7"&gt;immunotherapy&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39083809/"&gt;treatment&lt;/a&gt;, may be weaker than previously imagined. The &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41590-025-02276-7"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; shows how the specific cells in the lymph nodes make an initial anti-cancer burst of activity. However, this has only been demonstrated in the laboratory, not in humans as yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Removing lymph nodes is not without drawbacks. Patients can experience swelling (&lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/lymphoedema/"&gt;lymphoedema&lt;/a&gt;), increased risk of &lt;a href="https://www.jprasurg.com/article/S1748-6815(17)30492-8/pdf"&gt;infection&lt;/a&gt; in the affected limb, and sometimes chronic pain or mobility &lt;a href="https://www.cancerresearchuk.org/about-cancer/breast-cancer/treatment/surgery/remove-lymph-nodes"&gt;problems&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There's also concern that removing lymph nodes, while reducing short-term risks of cancer spread, might inadvertently weaken the body's &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10793742/"&gt;long-term immune defences&lt;/a&gt; – especially as modern treatments increasingly rely on the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/pancreatic-cancer-a-personalised-mrna-vaccine-may-boost-effects-of-treatment-205606"&gt;patient's&lt;/a&gt; natural immunity. This is in line with the new study findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;How lymph nodes work.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why do surgeons still remove lymph nodes, then?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For many types of solid tumour, the risk of metastatic spread remains high, and lymph node involvement is one of the best predictors of cancer recurrence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lymph node removal also provides vital information for choosing the most effective post-surgical treatments. In breast cancer, doctors often use a &lt;a href="https://www.macmillan.org.uk/cancer-information-and-support/treatments-and-drugs/surgery-to-the-lymph-nodes-for-breast-cancer"&gt;"sentinel node biopsy"&lt;/a&gt;. This means removing only the first lymph node that fluid from the tumour drains into. Checking just this sentinel node helps doctors see if the cancer has spread, while reducing the number of nodes removed and lowering the risk of side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical researchers are learning more about how lymph nodes work during long-term illnesses. The new study shows that lymph nodes aren't just passive filters; they're active training grounds where special immune cells grow, multiply and become powerful fighters. This is especially important during treatments that boost the immune system, such as &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41590-025-02276-7"&gt;checkpoint blockade treatments&lt;/a&gt;, which are now used for many types of &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/abs/10.1056/NEJMsb2300232"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These results suggest that taking out lymph nodes doesn't just block cancer's spread; it also removes important hubs where the immune system monitors the body and gets reactivated to fight disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the last decade, hospitals have adopted gentler, more &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7561013/"&gt;targeted&lt;/a&gt; lymph node surgeries. Instead of removing all the nodes in a region, the focus is now on minimising disruption: taking only the nodes most likely to harbour cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This approach reduces complications for patients and may help keep their immunity strong. Some patients with early-stage cancers may even avoid node removal altogether, instead relying on imaging and biopsies to monitor for spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those worried about the consequences of major lymph node removal, emerging therapies offer hope. Immunotherapy drugs, targeted treatments and even &lt;a href="https://www.aru.ac.uk/news/new-vaccines-could-transform-skin-cancer-treatment"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.aru.ac.uk/news/the-science-behind-the-new-mrna-cancer-vaccines"&gt;vaccines&lt;/a&gt; are being developed that can "re-educate" the immune system, even if some lymph nodes have been lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, there is growing evidence that patients do best when at least some hubs remain – preserving the body's ability to mount and sustain a defence against lingering cancer cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the future, cancer surgery may become even more &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38929782/"&gt;personalised&lt;/a&gt;. By mapping the activity inside lymph nodes – tracking which ones are essential for immune function and which are most likely to seed new tumours – doctors can &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/24833841/"&gt;tailor surgery&lt;/a&gt; so each patient gets maximum benefit with minimum harm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_175716" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-175716" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/personalised_cancer_treatment_642.jpg" alt="woman at a physician" class="wp-image-175716 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/personalised_cancer_treatment_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/personalised_cancer_treatment_642-600x374.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-175716" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Cancer surgery could one day be more personalised. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAGw8KXBzt4/"&gt;pixelshot/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent discoveries challenge surgeons and oncologists to weigh every decision carefully: not just for what is removed today, but for the immunity and future defences left behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is removing lymph nodes in cancer surgery a bad idea? The answer is complex. For many patients, it's still a good idea and can be lifesaving. But new science teaches us that lymph nodes are more than just staging posts; they may be indispensable for long-term immune protection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The future promises smarter, more strategic surgery, keeping more of the body's natural defence system intact while targeting cancer with precision.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/265557/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/justin-stebbing-1405462"&gt;Justin Stebbing&lt;/a&gt;, Professor of Biomedical Sciences, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/anglia-ruskin-university-1887"&gt;Anglia Ruskin University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/dont-cut-them-out-lymph-nodes-may-be-key-to-cancer-treatment-265557"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 14:01:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxQNTNTUlRZSlZvLUJzTDNKa0VjSllxdHpaU2xZYk0xTjFQZl9MOHpJRnlPYUhKZUtNNzNnVUdTWEU3eEg3TFAtSjRZUzI5NjlvZUdGQi1mSVkyQk9OcDMtQlFtd1EyNmtIM1F6VHlTTW9GTmlqLXpDQmhLS3pZRHNUUTFmOWZZYTJJNENmd3RTc05vMHRURFB5Nw</guid></item><item><title>新的研究发现，情绪健康对于长寿和身体健康同样重要- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/05/health/emotional-well-being-older-adults-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88nk3m007q26p5dfo2ai8d@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When it comes to aging and healthy living, we’re often given the same advice: Eat better, exercise every day and sleep more. But solely focusing on your physical health isn’t enough to achieve longevity, a new study has found.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000k3b6nof0249x6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Researchers looked at older adults’ optimal well-being, which they define as having social support; positive perceptions of aging, physical and mental health, happiness, and life satisfaction; and the ability to carry out daily activities without severe limitations.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000l3b6ngmo12kwt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Our study of over 8,000 older adults found that many who were not in optimal well-being at the start of the study were able to regain it within just three years,” said Dr. Mabel Ho, the study’s first author, in an email, referring to the 1 in 4 older adults whose health significantly improved. “These findings challenge the notion that well-being inevitably declines with age and highlight the potential for positive change later in life.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000m3b6nyzqknj8h@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The study, published on September 24 in the journal &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0329800" target="_blank"&gt;PLOS One&lt;/a&gt;, was a secondary analysis of data collected from the &lt;a href="https://www.clsa-elcv.ca/" target="_blank"&gt;Canadian Longitudinal Study on Aging&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000n3b6nfb2s1tc1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “These findings apply to older adults aged 60 and over who are not currently in optimal health or well-being,” said Dr. Esme Fuller-Thomson, the study’s senior author, in an email. “The study offers hope and practical insights for older adults, caregivers, and policymakers by showing that with the right supports and lifestyle choices, many older adults can regain a high level of well-being even after experiencing sub-optimal well-being.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000o3b6nuqv9zou1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            More than 1 in 5 Americans will be 65 or older by 2040, and nearly 3 in 5 of them will need long-term services and support, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/07/12/health/geriatrician-healthy-aging-wellness"&gt;previous CNN report&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000p3b6nji9la6s0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In 2023, about &lt;a href="https://www.ncoa.org/article/the-top-10-most-common-chronic-conditions-in-older-adults/" target="_blank"&gt;93% of adults&lt;/a&gt; age 65 or older in the United States reported having at least one chronic disease, such as heart disease and diabetes. While not all chronic conditions can be avoided, many can be &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/chronic-disease/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;prevented&lt;/a&gt; by altering your lifestyle.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000q3b6n9oj1tnnu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Individuals who began with strong psychological and emotional well-being were nearly five times more likely to reach optimal overall health by the end of the study,” said Ho, a recent doctoral graduate at the University of Toronto’s Factor-Inwentash Faculty of Social Work and the Institute of Life Course and Aging.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000r3b6n4ea4nlpd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The results “also underscored the critical influence of supportive relationships, socioeconomic conditions, and healthy lifestyle choices such as regular physical activity, not smoking, and good sleep,” she added.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000s3b6nyfut7jw0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But the study’s findings may not be applicable to all adults age 65 and older since the researchers focused their efforts in Canada, where patients have access to universal health care.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000t3b6nbaa7sh73@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “These findings provide valuable insight into aging and well-being in the context of a high-income country with universal healthcare,” Ho said via email. “However, it remains unclear how well these results translate to the United States, where life-long universal healthcare is not available; similarly, more research is needed to understand how older adults in diverse global settings experience and regain well-being in low- and middle-income countries, where healthcare access, social supports, and economic conditions can differ significantly from Canada.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  &lt;h2 class="subheader inline-placeholder subheader-elevate vossi-subheader vossi-subheader--size-h2" data-editable="text" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/subheader/instances/cmg88tyor00183b6nzrxb1w9l@published" data-component-name="subheader" id="taking-a-holistic-approach-to-health-and-aging" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
        Taking a holistic approach to health and aging
&lt;/h2&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000v3b6ntlwsmjie@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Physically, there are &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/05/28/health/live-long-healthy-life-eric-topol-wellness"&gt;three main lifestyle changes&lt;/a&gt; you can implement to achieve healthy aging: exercise, sleep and diet.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000w3b6nwm887ntw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            And while behaviors like &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/09/health/hobbies-social-longevity-wellness"&gt;nutritious eating and strength training&lt;/a&gt; are important, they won’t be as effective if you aren’t also addressing issues of loneliness and maintaining positive relationships.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000x3b6nf86b0dea@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “One of the things I always say to my patients is, believe it or not, there’s no disease, dis-ease or lack of ease, without your mind. The mind-body connection is unbelievably underestimated by Western medicine,” said     Dr. Andrew Freeman, director of cardiovascular prevention and wellness at National Jewish Health in Denver. He was not involved in the study.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000y3b6nbz2bkjpk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Chronically lonely adults age 50 and older have a 56% higher risk of stroke than adults lower on the loneliness scale, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/06/26/health/loneliness-stroke-wellness"&gt;previous CNN report&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000z3b6n1f09fp0v@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Stress reduction and frequent socialization were also associated with &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/28/health/cognitive-decline-pointer-study-wellness"&gt;improved cognition&lt;/a&gt; in adults experiencing early-stage Alzheimer’s disease.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700103b6n2czppi2i@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Cultivating strong social connections is an essential component of overall well-being. Lifestyle changes such as quitting smoking and addressing sleep issues like insomnia can also lead to meaningful improvements in health,” said Fuller-Thomson, professor and director of the Institute for Life Course and Aging at the University of Toronto’s Factor-Inwentash Faculty of Social Work.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg8ig0if000a3b6n6ub8ya03@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “By focusing on these key issues, older adults may be able to build resilience and enhance their quality of life, even when managing existing health challenges.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700113b6n523pfs0j@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The study highlights that it’s easier for younger adults to achieve optimal well-being, but that does not mean older adults can’t.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700123b6ns5zcwxeg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Our study shifts the narrative by showing that well-being in older adulthood isn’t static. Many older adults can recover and regain optimal health even after setbacks,” Ho said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700133b6n67dce5ck@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “While previous research has often focused on decline, this adds a new dimension by highlighting the potential for resilience, recovery, and improvement later in life. It emphasizes that aging can include periods of growth and renewed well-being, not just loss.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700143b6nksnkzakb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            And healthy living can start with increasing your steps, said Dr. Joyce Oen-Hsiao, a cardiologist at Yale Medicine, who was not part of the study.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700153b6n7nnb3vv2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “A lot of my elderly patients, their outing is going to the store. So, I’ll say, well, don’t park at the parking spot that’s close — maybe park at the parking spot that’s a little bit further. And then that way you increase your steps, you get a little bit more mobile,” said   Oen-Hsiao, who is also an associate professor of cardiovascular medicine at Yale School of Medicine.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700163b6nca5o60ml@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            No matter your age, you can start making choices to get physically and mentally healthier, experts say.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700173b6nncs8nn2o@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “If you put your mindset that you’re going to get better, that you’re going to feel better, that you’re going to do better, that you’re going to achieve whatever it is you’re trying to achieve, it makes the odds of that actually happening significantly more,” Freeman said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmg8hjtdu00073b6nw81h9gif@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    Get inspired by a weekly roundup on living well, made simple. Sign up for &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/newsletters/life-but-better?source=nl-acq_article"&gt;CNN’s Life, But Better newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for information and tools designed to improve your well-being.
&lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 13:00:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQcFpsQ1VVQkJISTRsZzNlYVRid3hhRnJDSHpxTjV5cU9RS0RPLWppMkJ6dGxsNl9mQ0ZyTzE5NlUwQmVRSVpvV0hrZWhrVGZHaEJMWTQ5U2hjUFJzQ05WQ3BSS3gzVjNtYS1hcFF1UUxYVFIyanRURTc4bHEwNkNSckZNRnZfZzg</guid></item><item><title>美国最主要的死亡原因，排名-视觉资本家</title><link>https://www.visualcapitalist.com/the-top-causes-of-death-in-the-united-states-ranked/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Visual Capitalist</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 12:12:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQTzNNd3BwRVJGNU0tWEVZekJvNmtlSnA2cnhBeTE2TXZGSGdCM3RCOXh2RkFmREtEZ255aGdkYlBzOWo3TGJ3ZHNZVlE4UlJHOF9HWkVpaWlYbHVpVDJPOThLa1loT2tKbDF2R2FQeUxZZGppb2Z4QWdheE5US0o5Ujc5SzZOd1JPUTBCRUN3</guid></item><item><title>这种“抗衰老”补充剂是新的健康热潮—但您应该服用吗？ -《旧金山纪事报》</title><link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/health/aging-longevity/article/nad-supplement-benefit-age-21055869.php</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="rel"&gt;&lt;section class="rel pb32 -mx20 sm:-mx40 lg:-mx56 x100vw sm:cw-80 lg:cw-112" aria-label="Carousel Gallery"&gt;&lt;div class="rel x100"&gt;&lt;figure role="group" aria-hidden="false" aria-label="Frame 1 of 3" class="rel m0 fdc top tdl300 td300 ttfeio rel o100 vv f x100"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel px20 sm:px0 td300 ttfeio tdl300 o100 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block oy-hidden mh46px"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Postdoctoral researcher Genesis Vega Hormazabal works Thursday in a lab at the Buck Institute for Research on Aging in Novato, which studies age-related disease. Its president and CEO, Dr. Eric Verdin, says the hype around NAD supplements has outpaced the science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 p4ywqby mnh24px"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lea Suzuki/S.F. Chronicle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure role="group" aria-hidden="true" aria-label="Frame 2 of 3" class="rel m0 fdc top tdl300 td300 ttfeio abs o0 vh f x100"&gt;&lt;p class="bgt rel vv o100 y32px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel px20 sm:px0 td300 ttfeio tdl300 o0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block oy-hidden mh46px"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientific manager Durai Sellegounder works in a lab at the Buck Institute for Research on Aging on Thursday in Novato.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 p4ywqby mnh24px"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lea Suzuki/S.F. Chronicle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure role="group" aria-hidden="true" aria-label="Frame 3 of 3" class="rel m0 fdc top tdl300 td300 ttfeio abs o0 vh f x100"&gt;&lt;p class="bgt rel vv o100 y32px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel px20 sm:px0 td300 ttfeio tdl300 o0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block oy-hidden mh46px"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0"&gt;&lt;p&gt;From left, Genesis Vega Hormazabal, postdoctoral researcher; Prasanna Vadhana Ashok Kumaar, associate director, Metalobics Core; Eric Verdin, president and chief executive officer; Durai Sellegounder, scientific manager; and Jingqi Fang, research scientist at the Buck Institute for Research on Aging in Novato on Thursday. The institute is an independent research organization that studies age-related disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 p4ywqby mnh24px"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lea Suzuki/S.F. Chronicle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may have seen wellness influencers touting the benefits of NAD on Instagram — or seen Kendall Jenner and Hailey Bieber getting IV infusions of the compound in an episode of “Keeping Up With the Kardashians.” Some swear NAD supplements give them extra energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers say NAD supplementation shows promise in animal studies, but urge caution because there have yet to be large clinical trials completed in humans that show proven benefits. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what to know about the latest longevity trend. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="A300" data-large-id="CONCERT1" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh600px ais lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh300px lg:ais"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is NAD?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAD, which stands for nicotinamide adenine dinucleotide, is a compound found in all cells of the body, particularly in the mitochondria, the energy centers of cells. NAD plays an important role in energy production, and is needed by sirtuins — proteins involved in cellular repair — to function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because NAD levels decline with age, the theory behind NAD supplementation is to restore NAD levels in the body, which then help sirtuins with cell function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="rel f m0 fdc -mx20 sm:mx0 x100vw sm:x100 mb32"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel pt8 px20 sm:px0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block ya"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buck Institute for Research on Aging research scientist Jingqi Fang, left, talks with Dr. Eric Verdin, the organization’s president and chief executive officer, on Thursday in Novato.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 mr48"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lea Suzuki/S.F. Chronicle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“NAD plays a key role in energy transfer in cells,” said Dr. Eric Verdin of the Buck Institute for Research on Aging in Novato, an independent research organization that studies age-related disease. He likens NAD’s role in the body to that of armored trucks in the economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="CONCERT1" data-large-id="CONCERT2" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh300px ais lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh300px lg:ais"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They take money from the stores and bring it to the bank,” said Verdin, who studies why NAD levels decrease with age. “If that stops, the whole economy grinds to a halt. NAD shuttles energy from one part of the cell to another.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What does research on NAD supplementation show?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAD supplementation appears to be safe, but hasn’t been studied in large controlled studies in humans, said Dr. Michael Fredericson, a sports medicine specialist and co-director of the Longevity Center at Stanford. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most studies on NAD supplementation have been conducted in animals, and have shown it can potentially help DNA repair, neurodegeneration, organ health, insulin sensitivity and metabolism, he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There’s a lot of promise here,” Fredericson said. “That’s why people are so excited about this.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="B300" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh600px ais lg:none"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings in animal studies were particularly exciting because they show that giving high levels of NAD precursors to mice appears to alleviate some diseases associated with aging, like heart attack, stroke, cancers, type 2 diabetes, macular degeneration, Parkinson’s and Alzheimer’s, Verdin said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAD precursors are the building blocks to making NAD. Because the body cannot absorb pure NAD, NAD supplements are given in the form of precursors called NR (nicotinamide riboside) and NMN (nicotinamide mononucleotide). Taking the precursors gives the body the components to make NAD. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some important limitations to these findings in animal studies. For one, animal studies used much higher doses of NAD precursors than the doses that are used for humans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;And second, animal studies don’t directly predict what will work in humans, Verdin said, pointing out that researchers have identified cures for Alzheimer’s and diabetes in mice, but those have not translated to successful therapies for humans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="CONCERT2" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh300px ais lg:none"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The field jumped ahead of itself by selling the supplements,” he said. “The evidence in humans is lacking. It’s not nonexistent, but it hasn’t been as positive as we had seen in animal studies. People have seen some promising effects, but nothing I’d take home to say, ‘Everyone has to now take NAD precursors.’”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What should you know if you’re considering it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s no specific agreed-upon dose for people, but supplement companies generally sell oral NAD supplements at doses around 125 mg to 250 mg per day, which are considered relatively low. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re shopping for a reputable supplement seller, look for companies that have an independent certification of analysis, Verdin said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some wellness centers also offer NAD IV infusions, which experts do not recommend because the body can’t absorb pure NAD, despite some celebrities like Jenner and Bieber extolling the health benefits. NAD infusions may cause more harm than benefit because they can elicit a major immune response, including chest pain, diarrhea and nausea, Fredericson said. This is because the infusion puts a huge amount of NAD straight into the blood serum, where it doesn’t belong, and the body treats it like a foreign substance, he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="S300" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh600px ais lg:none"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s not dangerous, you just feel horrible,” he said. “I’d stay away from the IV pure NAD because not only do you get that massive immune response, but you’ll pee most of it out. If you were going to try it, probably start with the oral forms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fredericson cautioned against taking NAD if you have a history of cancer because in some animal studies, very high doses of NAD may enhance tumor growth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though the doses in those animal studies were much higher than the doses you can find on the market for humans, “it’s just not worth the risk,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAD supplementation can also raise homocysteine levels in the blood, which can be a sign of dysfunctional metabolism. Verdin said this was the reason he stopped taking it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who might benefit?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fredericson has recommended NAD supplementation for some middle-aged and older patients who feel like they’re not healing as well as they used to, or who feel like their energy level is not what it used to be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’m prescribing it cautiously at this point,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main feedback he’s gotten from patients, he said, is that some feel like they have more energy — though that may be a placebo effect. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fredericson himself is taking 250 mg a day, and echoes that observation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s hard to tell. I think my energy’s been a little better than normal, but it’s just so hard to tell because there’s so many factors that go into it. Maybe I’m sleeping better. Maybe it’s in my mind. But I think there’s something to it.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;If research does in fact show that NAD is neuroprotective, “that’s going to be huge,” he said. “We have to wait and see on that. It’s one of those things where we still need more information. In five years it’ll be the biggest hit in the world, or we won’t even be talking about it anymore.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What anti-aging or longevity supplements should you consider instead?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Supplements in general are considered somewhat controversial, as studies have found that many supplements do not contain what the label on the bottle claims. Medical experts generally say supplements aren’t necessary for people who get proper nutrition from their diet.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There are dozens of supplements being touted or sold by different companies, and very few that have been shown to actually have an effect,” Verdin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among the most well-studied, he said, are &lt;a href="https://www.sfchronicle.com/health/article/vitamin-d-calcium-supplements-aging-longevity-20220319.php" data-link="native" class=""&gt;vitamin D&lt;/a&gt;, vitamin B-12 and omega-3 fatty acids. Verdin recommends getting tested to see if you’re deficient in these nutrients, and to consider taking supplements if your levels are too low. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of all, though, the most effective action you can take for aging well is to exercise, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People are looking for a magical pill that will solve their aging problem,” he said. “Physical activity is the magical pill we have today. That has an enormously protective effect. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’d urge people to look at all of this with some degree of circumspection and to not forget what does work, which is great nutrition, physical activity, stress mitigation,” he said. All the things your grandmother told you to do.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn top"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>San Francisco Chronicle</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 11:14:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxOMG9LNEtzTld4SF9IS2ViVTd3cjBGdGtQaVcwN0tQZmUtTzdXVjBsSnFSUXVaLUM4TS1taHFzY25GTnNGNUx6NmoyWWNwNzAzUjhqSllWcnQ2emh5RC1SZVF5XzBsLUYxWmxfV3lrY2VFWFNQd1o2U1YyOW1sWXpjdTdNX0hselZNT0hGTGxwMmRoV2lsWjh0WTJZdWdKaVU</guid></item><item><title>他们的父母从未给他们接种过疫苗。作为年轻人，他们面临着一个选择。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/10/05/vaccines-skepticism-childhood-family-impacts/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QC5NMJTF3BHDVAQEYE3PEOPLKE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;At 30 years old, Lacie Madison just assumed she was fully vaccinated her entire life. But when she got a job at a hospital and was required to check her immunity, the doctor called with shocking news: It appeared she was barely vaccinated as a child, if at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HR22XK2CHRB3VPIUBJT6FL2U3E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“I just said, ‘Are you kidding me?’” recalled Madison, now 39.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 10:32:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxQMlRibnl0TlpHX2FXVkExd29EVF9SdU9BbDQtMjJxWEtvcUpyMEdrVVdERlFVSjZBbF9NSF9sZENmMVBhd25MemNaN1dPMVczUUo2X0xDaWtaUWZvVlljMlM5MDBOdXpMQzVvWlJ3QXJOSkZqUDFEdzR1cml4bDJtNlNYVHJ1RjBBeWlDM2NDN1NZdTFldVk3NUtR</guid></item><item><title>117岁的玛丽亚·莫雷拉（ Maria Morera ） ： “她没有魔法基因，这可能是她每天吃3次的零食-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/maria-morera-who-lived-till-117-ate-3-snacks-regularly-she-had-no-magic-gene-the-secret-was-in-her-gut/photostory/124318974.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;For over two decades, Maria enjoyed three servings of yoghurt daily, morning, afternoon, and night. It wasn’t part of a fad or diet trend; it was simply something she liked. But this small act turned out to have an enormous impact on her health.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers discovered that Maria’s gut microbiome, her inner ecosystem of bacteria, was similar to that of someone decades younger. It was rich in Bifidobacterium, a beneficial bacterium known for reducing inflammation and promoting better metabolism. These bacteria thrive in yoghurt containing strains like Streptococcus thermophilus and Lactobacillus bulgaricus, which she consumed regularly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Cell Reports Medicine (2024), this consistent intake of probiotic-rich yoghurt possibly reshaped her gut environment, keeping it youthful and resilient, a key factor in her healthy aging.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 09:43:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAJBVV95cUxPTzUxbkJVY0RySXRCdks1Tk9UZEczTEF5QzZRQVBGczJSOHhvU09hRkNOX0lKcnV4eUVCYjRQa1lnYVhGYkFha3FBLXBoRUtOSjZxX3hlbW93RnVCTzlJZnFmNW4zRWdyWElBcTJ4amZITUZRLXZwM093dlh2ZmpQLU9YZFlNNjR2WlBKRmtYbm1VTjZ4OXpnZWs2cEJFMmhZZVU1OWNycVB1dG51STVBZFJ2LUhQdmo5RU1VQ0ZHbTBpWlBzY2lyWXF4V2FXdWpFWE9BeWxVcTl3bkJIYWxyQTA5dGQycF84V2JxVW5JbldJT0tSSU9scU1VQnNEdUNqTERsNXpPVmJVb05KX25jRlgyVGdLeHQyRWx4X3JWbWxTVzdmUDUzSdIBsAJBVV95cUxNeGVfQWhaamRXRnNpM0lmSmI5QkdmYzNPX1ZfYWlsdG9oM0wtU3ZPc2w4ZVRKa2x0OXF1cGJkM1h0N25COFplMXVIY3NJSWs1Z2JlNnIwS0J6Y1VMOGtxQ0YyclFfVE9nQ2Zka3J2ZXlyQkJhRi1vamV5UGlwUVRHREVaRlFJdnNIdy1GNUhyTUU0NkxqalJFak84YmlQM09Mc1BWLXBIZGZ2Z1NvU2FNNkp3ME1PZTZxS0tvY0FOOEc2NFcxSFFjOXdkNGpwb0ZWTnVyWC1TQ1h3Tmsya3Rua0htd2sxU3M0YlN4c055c016NHh5dUZuX2doMVZHbDNFZUZybHAzWEJ2SjBBXzZGRnNNV0lSODlBM2trZE1pbU1TUTlfaE1taEhxVFd5Sjl2</guid></item><item><title>冠状病毒病例激增： “我确信自己会死” - Ynetnews</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/health_science/article/sytkc91plg</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-contents="true"&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="1p6s2-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1p6s2-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1p6s2-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“I’m a strong woman, but it just crushed me. I had a very high fever that wouldn’t go down, muscle aches and weakness. I couldn’t get out of bed,” said Dana Gabai, 39, of Ramla, who contracted COVID-19 last month. “I had a headache like I’d never had before, as if my head was swelling to giant proportions.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="fci7d-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="fci7d-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="fci7d-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Gabai says she had previously taken only one dose of a COVID-19 vaccine. “At the time people were saying these were experimental vaccines and that the long-term effects were unknown, so I decided not to get the follow-up doses,” she said. This was the first time she had COVID-19. “This is not a mild illness at all. I was sure I was going to die. I was in bed for eight days like a corpse.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="f750r-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide firstImageInArticle firstImageInArticleBody"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.BJexd4i1Teg" id="image_ArticleImageData.BJexd4i1Teg"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;4&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.BJexd4i1Teg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/05/BkfEMYJ6el/BkfEMYJ6el_0_165_731_836_0_x-large.jpg" alt="דנה גבאי חלתה בקורונה" title="Dana Gabbai contracted COVID-19 last month (Photo: Private album) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.BJexd4i1Teg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/05/BkfEMYJ6el/BkfEMYJ6el_0_165_731_836_0_x-large.jpg" alt="דנה גבאי חלתה בקורונה" title="Dana Gabbai contracted COVID-19 last month (Photo: Private album) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Dana Gabbai contracted COVID-19 last month&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Private album&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="8o2q0-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="8o2q0-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="8o2q0-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Gil Abraham, 42, of Hod Hasharon also caught COVID-19 a few weeks ago and describes a severe, prolonged illness. “I’m vaccinated and this was the third time I got it, and this time it hit me really hard,” he said. “For two days I had a high fever that wouldn’t break, and they called an ambulance because I felt I couldn’t breathe. I had strong heart palpitations and irregular breathing, and I writhed in body pain.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="db6u5-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="db6u5-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="db6u5-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;He said he encountered indifference when he arrived at the hospital. “They closed me behind a curtain. I vomited and felt like I was choking, but the doctor looked at me for a second and just said there was nothing to be done, that it was COVID, that I’d get fluids and painkillers — and sent me home,” he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="hpb1-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.BkgkT4okpeg" id="image_ArticleImageData.BkgkT4okpeg"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;4&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.BkgkT4okpeg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/05/SJxmj5yalg/SJxmj5yalg_0_309_961_540_0_x-large.jpg" alt="גיל אברהם חלה בקורונה" title="Gil Abraham lost his sense of taste (Photo: Private album) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.BkgkT4okpeg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/05/SJxmj5yalg/SJxmj5yalg_0_309_961_540_0_x-large.jpg" alt="גיל אברהם חלה בקורונה" title="Gil Abraham lost his sense of taste (Photo: Private album) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Gil Abraham lost his sense of taste&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Private album&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="enb0t-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="enb0t-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="enb0t-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Abraham continued to feel unwell in the days that followed. “My body hurt so much, even the pads of my fingers on my hands and feet,” he said. He also reported loss of taste. “Everything I ate tasted like rust. I lost a lot of weight.” He had difficulty walking even short distances because of breathing problems. He only began to feel better after about 10 days. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="2adk5-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2adk5-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2adk5-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“This is not a mild illness, and there isn’t enough awareness that there is a wave of illness,” Abraham said. “I didn’t believe in COVID before. The other times I said, ‘OK, it’s a mild flu,’ but this time it was a level up. I never imagined I’d need an ambulance. I have no underlying conditions. I’m healthy and I exercise.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="88m01-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="88m01-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="88m01-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Health funds are reporting a rise in cases. Maccabi said its September daily average was 219 diagnosed patients, up from 162 per day in August — an increase of 35%. It said the figures are based on weekdays only and reflect only patients who reported to their family doctor; some patients use at-home tests and do not report results to a physician.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="4ulag-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4ulag-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4ulag-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Leumit said cases rose 200% from July to September, with 300 COVID diagnoses in September compared with 100 in July. Clalit said relatively few people report COVID illness to community doctors, but it noted a rise in hospitalizations. Meuhedet reported a 10% increase in patients from August to September and a nearly threefold jump from July to September.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="46klp-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.ryl3kHjy6ex" id="image_ArticleImageData.ryl3kHjy6ex"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;4&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.ryl3kHjy6ex" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2023/09/06/ByDftiSRn/ByDftiSRn_0_73_1000_563_0_x-large.jpg" alt="בדיקת קורונה" title="Coronavirus test (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.ryl3kHjy6ex" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2023/09/06/ByDftiSRn/ByDftiSRn_0_73_1000_563_0_x-large.jpg" alt="בדיקת קורונה" title="Coronavirus test (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Coronavirus test&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="7k4tl-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7k4tl-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7k4tl-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The Health Ministry said there has been a moderation in the increase in COVID hospitalizations. “According to data received from 15 general hospitals, as of mid-September there was about a 10% rise compared with mid-August, versus a 40% rise in the previous month,” the ministry said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="61oai-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="61oai-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="61oai-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“We’ve seen a slightly more significant wave of COVID-19 over the past three months, and we are now in the midst of that wave,” said Professor Tal Brosh, head of infectious diseases at the Assuta Ashdod public hospital and head of the Health Ministry’s epidemic response team. He sought to reassure the public: “These are not the huge waves we saw in 2021-22 when hundreds of thousands of Israelis were infected one after another and hospital wards filled. Since the start of COVID there has always been ongoing illness, sometimes a bit more and sometimes a bit less. It comes in waves, and most of the time it simply doesn’t interest the public.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="nti8-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="nti8-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="nti8-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;He said the current rise is seen mainly among hospitalized patients, most of them older people with underlying illnesses. “We almost never see hospitalized COVID patients who do not have underlying conditions, and certainly we do not see young people hospitalized with COVID as we did before vaccines, when people in their 40s and 50s were hospitalized with severe COVID,” he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="7l5mk-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7l5mk-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7l5mk-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Still, he said, deaths are occurring among older people and other at-risk groups. Brosh noted that in 2024 COVID caused more illness and deaths than any other respiratory virus, including influenza. “It’s important to remember that COVID is not a seasonal disease, meaning infections occur throughout the year,” he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="afn77-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta wrapped"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleWrappedImageComponenta"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleWrappedImageData.B1xcXrsk6gx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/08/07/SyLVf11GOxg/SyLVf11GOxg_225_44_544_725_0_medium.jpg" alt="פרופ' טל ברוש" title="Professor Tal Brosh&amp;amp;nbsp; (Photo: Private album) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="caption" contenteditable="false"&gt;Professor Tal Brosh &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span disabled class="credit" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Private album&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="acflt-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="acflt-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="acflt-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;According to the National Center for Disease Control report for the week ending September 27, the number and percentage of positive COVID samples among hospitalized patients remain high compared with most of the past year. That week reported 92 new cases, about 8.3% of all hospitalized patients in 11 monitored hospitals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="4482u-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4482u-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4482u-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The prominent variants in the current wave are Nimbus (NB.1.8.1) and Stratus (XFG), from the JN.1 lineage, which are also seen globally and have become dominant. Dr. Efrat Wexler, head of primary care at Meuhedet, said the variants appear more transmissible but there is no evidence they are more aggressive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="77ruc-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="77ruc-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="77ruc-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“We hear from some patients that the illness is worse compared with previous infections, with marked weakness or increased mucus production, cough and runny nose, but we have not found that the current strains produce symptoms unusual beyond what we have known so far — high fever, dry or productive cough, fatigue and weakness, muscle and throat pain, and nasal congestion,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="6lu9r-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6lu9r-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6lu9r-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Brosh said new variants continue to evolve while immunity wanes over time. He noted that most young people were vaccinated with three doses about four years ago. “In those years they may not have encountered the virus, meaning they did not develop infection-derived immunity, and therefore they experience more significant illness.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="6t6n2-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6t6n2-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6t6n2-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Against the backdrop of rising cases, Brosh also pointed to falling COVID vaccination rates in recent years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="38qlc-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="38qlc-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="38qlc-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt; “If in 2020-21 Israel was a model for the world and we carried out the fastest, most comprehensive vaccination campaign, in the past year our figures are among the worst in Western countries,” he said. “Last year fewer than 50,000 Israelis were vaccinated, compared with 60%-70% of adults vaccinated in Scandinavia, and even in the United States, despite strong vaccine hesitancy, about 40% of at-risk people were vaccinated, whereas in Israel the figure is almost zero.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="bl1m4-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="bl1m4-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="bl1m4-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;He said the main reason for low vaccination uptake is a lack of public awareness and guidance. “We did a very poor job in the past two years. The Health Ministry and the health funds failed in outreach to at-risk groups about the need to get a COVID vaccine each year, similar to influenza. So even people who see the value in vaccines are not getting vaccinated because they don’t even know they should,” according to Brosh.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="76e2q-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="d2nbd-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="d2nbd-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="d2nbd-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;He also blamed rising anti-vaccine sentiment — a growing phenomenon in Israel and worldwide, especially regarding COVID vaccines. “During the pandemic many felt the vaccine was imposed on them, and at the same time a lot of misinformation against vaccines spread. I’m convinced that even if we run a very good campaign now, many people will still be afraid to vaccinate, and we must act on this,” he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="39fd-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="39fd-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="39fd-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Under updated Health Ministry guidance, COVID vaccination is recommended for people 65 and older and for those 6 months to 64 years who belong to risk groups: people with chronic illnesses including kidney disease, chronic lung disease and heart disease; smokers; and residents of geriatric institutions, nursing homes and assisted living.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="d6tsi-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="d6tsi-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="d6tsi-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Brosh said the updated recommendations align with other countries such as Britain, the United States and the Nordic countries. For people 65 and older who live in geriatric institutions, nursing homes or assisted living, an additional vaccine dose is recommended after six months — effectively two doses a year. Two doses a year are also recommended for people 75 and older regardless of health status. People who are not in risk groups may also be vaccinated if they wish to reduce their risk of infection and illness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="5ndu9-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5ndu9-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5ndu9-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Starting next month, the vaccines available through the health funds will be Novavax — a vaccine that uses the coronavirus spike protein produced in the lab. After injection the body recognizes the protein as foreign and learns to fight it. “This vaccine also underwent scientific trials and is very safe to use,” Brosh said. “There are also financial considerations that shouldn’t be ignored regarding the cost of vaccines and the choice of these vaccines.” The Novavax vaccine is authorized for people 12 and older, which will require the Health Ministry to find solutions for children in at-risk groups.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="cg12d-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="cg12d-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="cg12d-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;As last year, the vaccines to be administered target the JN.1 strain, in line with international organizations and the Health Ministry’s advisory committee on infectious diseases and vaccines. “The understanding is that the changes the virus made over the past year are not very dramatic, so it’s likely the vaccines will be effective against the strains currently circulating,” Brosh said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="5206k-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5206k-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5206k-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Wexler summed up: “The coronavirus is not going away soon, and vaccination significantly reduces the risk of severe illness, complications and hospitalization.” She stressed: “Anyone who is sick should avoid going to crowded places and participating in gatherings. That simple step of personal responsibility can reduce many infections.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 08:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE9yZnc1Zzl2TkdmN2JqcUF1R1BTRkNFVUJBREpEbzZsQ01ScW9RQk02MkZwQ3B2Qm5HQkVEcWx2MzJUSUNuMmd6TnEzZmNEdEw1cWdTRDNEdXFXN2lFN05jb1ROODdBTkpyeXc</guid></item><item><title>哈佛大学训练有素的胃肠病学家揭示了10种最佳的气体和腹胀食物-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/diet/harvard-trained-gastroenterologist-reveals-10-best-anti-bloating-foods/articleshow/124316547.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Has this ever happened to you that the stomach feels uncomfortable and heavy right after meals? Well you’re not the only one facing it. Bloating is a problem millions of adults are facing everyday, as per Harvard. However, small changes can help relieve the discomfort. Harvard trained gastroenterologist Dr. Saurabh Sethi suggests 10 best foods that can help reduce bloating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bloating occurs when excess air or gas buildup gets trapped in the digestive tract or when gut muscles fail to move food efficiently. This can be triggered by eating too fast and swallowing air, consuming gas-producing foods like beans, onions, or carbonated drinks or food intolerances. Sometimes hormonal changes can also lead to bloating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Bloated tummy woes? Common remedies to get rid of gas and bloating&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is that certain foods can actively soothe the digestive system by providing enzymes that break down food efficiently. Here’s a detailed list of 10 foods that can beat bloating, as per gastroenterologist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="Credits: Canva" msid="124316600" width="" title="Credits: Canva " placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-124316600,resizemode-4/credits-canva.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;Credits: Canva &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;10 foods to beat bloating:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Kiwi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kiwi is rich in fiber content and contains the actinidin enzyme, which aids protein digestion. A study published in the Journal of Nutritional Science found that consuming two kiwis daily improved bowel movements in individuals with mild constipation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-type="in_view" class="  "&gt;&lt;div class="EEW3_ timeline_pollWrapper_as " data-scrollga="scroll#poll_view"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="hLnAH"&gt;Poll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="KEEGr"&gt;Which of these foods do you think helps relieve bloating the best?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Papaya&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The papain enzyme is packed with digestive support. This enzyme helps break down protein and support digestion. Clinical studies suggest that a small serving of fresh papaya is a good option to reduce bloating after a protein-heavy meal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Pineapple&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A small serving of fresh pineapple after a big meal or added to salads can help digestion for some people. Pineapple is a food source of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11243481/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;bromelain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, a group of enzymes that digest protein. According to WebMD, bromelain can aid in digestion and reduce inflammation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="Credits: Canva" msid="124316607" width="" title="Credits: Canva " placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-124316607,resizemode-4/credits-canva.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;Credits: Canva &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Cucumber&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cucumbers are high in water content and contain fiber. Their hydrating effects also help flush out excess sodium, which can contribute to water retention and bloating. Add cucumber to meals in the form of salads to get benefits. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Chia seeds&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chia seeds are packed with fiber, and when consumed with water, these seeds form &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/nutrition/chia-seed-benefits-what-you-need-to-know?" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;gel-like consistency&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; in the gut that ultimately helps soften stool and maintain regularity. However, individuals with certain health conditions, such as low blood pressure or kidney disease, should consult a healthcare provider before consuming chia seeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Quinoa&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quinoa is a whole grain that contains prebiotic fibers. These fibers can promote the growth of beneficial gut bacteria. A study published in PubMed Central found that quinoa's bioactive compounds can improve intestinal microflora. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Oats&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study published in PubMed Central found that beta-glucan-rich oats or oat-based products in a diet significantly decrease the blood lipid profile and blood pressure by regulating insulin metabolism. One can enjoy Fennel seeds that have been traditionally used to relieve bloating and gas. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Ginger&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ginger has been used as an aid to digestion for ages. A study found that ginger significantly reduced gastrointestinal pain and improved digestion. These properties can help relieve bloating. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Peppermint tea or oil&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peppermint oil relaxes smooth muscle in the gut and can reduce spasms and trapped gas. Several clinical trials show benefits for abdominal pain and bloating, particularly in IBS. To consume, one can try peppermint tea or after consultation, may consume enteric-coated peppermint oil capsules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Fennel seeds&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fennel seeds have been traditionally used to relieve bloating and gas. A study by NIH found that fennel oil was effective in reducing symptoms of irritable bowel syndrome, including bloating and gas. To consume these one can chew some fennel seeds after meals or sip fennel tea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;These dietary adjustments can help alleviate mild bloating. However, individuals who feel constant bloating, accompanied with unintentional weight loss, persistent severe pain, blood in stool, or recurrent vomiting, must consult with a healthcare professional as these can indicate conditions like celiac disease, SIBO, IBD, ovarian pathology, or obstruction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and should not replace professional medical advice. Always consult a healthcare provider for persistent digestive symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 05:32:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9gFBVV95cUxQOFBoeVlKZk01VlBuY00zeVJIRU5xRHhuOGxYdUJlTzVSXzhnWktVSFNoeFlvYlI3SlJPMjFmRDJFVXhuX0UwLTFvOHl4c2RuV2NJeWRZTGlHd3hoU0RNWHk5R2ItekotYVA0bFE5WG4xQWFWSGxsU1RVVXdjRnRqTUFFeE1ETGE5cEFLR21qNUJ4UEJSVVMxbUg0U0RESEFBaC1GdmpPQ054a29qRFNHOVJQcDNJLUw1QWxFSWRIYll5bmd1aGtfODJpM2JTQ3lpVk1UQzJ6VlhHRXNlQ1poSlRONkNWN2tsdjZuOWdhcjQzQy1MVkE</guid></item><item><title>一位长寿专家表示，营养素缺乏可能对健康和寿命产生“深远影响” -需要注意以下五点- Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://www.fitandwell.com/nutrition/a-longevity-expert-says-nutrient-deficiencies-can-have-a-profound-effect-on-health-and-lifespan-here-are-five-to-watch-out-for</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p id="7b58b023-59ed-481e-be3b-38b2fa74acc7"&gt;Nutrient and mineral deficiencies can have a big impact on your day-to-day health, often making you feel more tired, weakening your immune system and generally preventing your body from working at full capacity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And according to Dr Matt Kaeberlein, a scientist, longevity expert and founder of healthtech company &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.optispan.life/" data-url="https://www.optispan.life/" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Optispan&lt;/a&gt;, nutrient and mineral deficiencies can also impact your long-term health. “Nutrient deficiencies may sound like a minor issue, but they can have profound effects on both healthspan and lifespan,” he tells &lt;em&gt;Fit&amp;amp;Well&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="7b58b023-59ed-481e-be3b-38b2fa74acc7-2"&gt;“Think of it this way: your body is a complex machine that depends on a steady supply of essential vitamins, minerals and amino acids to keep its systems running. When those inputs are missing, the machinery starts to wear down faster.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Kaberlein, most deficiencies are “partial and chronic”. This means that although they may not have a significant impact on daily life, they may be gradually affecting your health. “[This] quietly increases vulnerability to cardiovascular disease, dementia, infections and cancers. Over decades, these small cracks in the foundation can significantly shorten both lifespan and the years of life lived in good health,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kaberlein flagged five nutrient deficiencies that are both common and have particularly negative consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-1-iron" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-1-iron"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Iron&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check id="ef0760e7-1cd7-4dac-95f7-d290c155d345"&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images / bit245)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="732cfc11-3bea-4bf9-9804-d80ae023aa70"&gt;“Chronic iron deficiency causes anemia, reducing oxygen delivery. This not only causes fatigue but also forces the heart to work harder, increasing risk of heart failure and earlier death,” says Kaeberlein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iron-rich foods include red meat, poultry, fish, beans, lentils and dark leafy greens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-WXSgj9g3nnLxJZ8fBVrfTf" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-WXSgj9g3nnLxJZ8fBVrfTf slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a id="elk-2-vitamin-d" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-2-vitamin-d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Vitamin D&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="97571ec2-601d-4065-8283-db932662ac5f"&gt;“Low vitamin D or calcium accelerates bone loss, raising fracture risk and mortality,” says Kaeberlein. “Inadequate vitamin D accelerates bone loss, leading to osteoporosis and fractures. Hip fractures in older adults carry a 20-30% one-year mortality rate, so preventing this deficiency can literally save years of life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your skin is able to make vitamin D when exposed to sunlight, but you can also get it from some foods including oily fish and egg yolks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-3-folate" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-3-folate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Folate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check id="26be9de8-6446-484d-8a0f-0c90bb14bdb5"&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images / Ekaterina Goncharova)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="0c44b72a-9af2-4555-9a75-2fb1d6a9d20e"&gt;“Folate is essential for DNA synthesis and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DNA_methylation" target="_blank" data-url="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DNA_methylation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;methylation&lt;/a&gt;,” says Kaeberlein. “Low folate levels increase DNA damage and impair repair, raising risks for cancers and cardiovascular disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Populations with chronic folate deficiency consistently show higher mortality,” he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Folate is in foods like dark leafy green vegetables, beans, lentils and citrus fruits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-4-selenium" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-4-selenium"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4. Selenium&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="6faf310b-9445-401f-a742-3a8c33832ed7"&gt;“Selenium is a trace mineral that supports antioxidant defenses and thyroid function. Low selenium intake has been associated with higher rates of certain cancers and poorer survival outcomes,” says Kaeberlein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brazil nuts contain high amounts of selenium, as do some types of seafood and lean meats, such as beef and pork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-5-omega-3" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-5-omega-3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;5. Omega-3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="d3568ec9-2027-4a22-9c1a-50544d2f7bf7"&gt;“Deficiencies in marine omega-3s (EPA and DHA) are linked to increased risk of &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/arrhythmia/about-arrhythmia" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/arrhythmia/about-arrhythmia" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;arrhythmias&lt;/a&gt;, heart attacks and sudden cardiac death,” says Kaeberlain. “Even modest supplementation lowers cardiovascular mortality in multiple studies.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll mostly find omega-3 in oily fish, but you can also find it in flaxseeds and chia seeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-should-everyone-be-taking-supplements" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-should-everyone-be-taking-supplements"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Should everyone be taking supplements?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="04223a27-37bf-453d-be15-d7eaf0e3a127"&gt;It’s best to get the vitamins, nutrients and minerals you need from a varied diet, but given the risks of nutritional deficiencies, you’d be forgiven for thinking you should turn to supplements to play it safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, it’s not that simple. “Too much of some of these nutrients can be detrimental,” says Kaeberlein. “There’s a lower bound and an upper bound, and you want to be in that range. You don't want to be above the range, or that can have negative health consequences as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kaeberlein is an advocate of blood tests to establish whether you have any nutrient, vitamin or mineral deficiencies. Generally, you can acquire a blood test from your general health practitioner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You should know what your levels are, and if you are deficient or suboptimal, supplement into the optimal range,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9gFBVV95cUxNaU5jeW44RVIzaTJiWjdJdTNTdEpoelVLMlBvdWlqaE94NTl1VjI4OHFmYnRETktrb2lzMVhKSlRMM0NuOTBBRDFpdC1DdjkzVWh1LW81emYzcHRBeHYwNE9kU0Q3ZlRGOVV6eEE4RV82Unlmb1EwWndyOEtvQjZXMWFmMjZUQzJ3Uk13OWhiWm52RkdZQWlNN0h0R2lsMXdSUVlLa3hjQmd0ZTVHd2pzRUFoMjNUUEJWRjFHNWlBVVhNaWsxTERiUHBpd1lGa05MLU5mZVZGMTJUNWZ5OGxPbF9vUFpLM3g3UDFqbXowNTBhcS1jaXc</guid></item><item><title>AIIMS整形外科医生揭示了预防颈部、背部和关节疼痛的“最佳睡眠姿势” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/aiims-orthopaedic-surgeon-reveals-best-sleeping-position-to-prevent-neck-back-and-joint-pain-101759590205030.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storyMainDiv" class="fullStory tfStory current videoStory story__detail storyAf101759590205030 " data-vars-storyid="101759590205030" data-story-section="lifestyle" data-story-subsection="health" data-vars-author="Akanksha Agnihotri" data-premium-story="false" data-performance-type="not-set" data-story-title="AIIMS orthopaedic surgeon reveals ‘best sleeping position’ to prevent neck, back and joint pain"&gt; &lt;p class="htEchoTopPageBanner dHide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="stickyCard"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;h1 class="hdg1"&gt;AIIMS orthopaedic surgeon reveals ‘best sleeping position’ to prevent neck, back and joint pain&lt;/h1&gt;  &lt;div class="actionDiv flexElm topTime"&gt; &lt;p class="dateTime secTime storyPage"&gt;Published on: Oct 05, 2025 07:13 am IST &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="googleFollow mHide"&gt; &lt;button class="htEchoShareBarDesk"&gt;&lt;/button&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;h2 class="sortDec"&gt;Many wake up with back or neck pain due to poor sleep posture. Orthopaedic surgeon Dr Dushyant shares simple positions to ease pain and protect your spine.&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;div class="storyDetails taboola-readmore"&gt; &lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/aiims-orthopaedic-surgeon-reveals-best-sleeping-position-to-prevent-neck-back-and-joint-pain-101759590205030.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;We spend nearly a third of our lives sleeping, yet many of us wake up with stiff necks, sore backs, or lingering aches. Poor sleeping &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/posture" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="posture"&gt;posture&lt;/a&gt; can silently damage your spine over time. Dr Dushyant Chouchan, Orthopaedic and Sports Injury Surgeon, AIIMS Raipur, shares in his Instagram post the best positions for neck and back pain relief. &lt;strong&gt;(Also read: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/orthopaedic-surgeon-shares-surprising-benefits-of-backward-walking-for-knee-health-on-food-pharma-podcast-101759465082024.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Orthopaedic surgeon shares surprising benefits of ‘backward walking’ for knee health on Food Pharmer podcast"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Orthopaedic surgeon shares surprising benefits of ‘backward walking’ for knee health on Food Pharmer podcast&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; )&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/10/04/550x309/13878_1759591281381_1759591287490.jpg" alt="Dr Dushyant advises incorporating specific sleeping positions to alleviate joint strain and improve comfort.(Freepik)" title="Dr Dushyant advises incorporating specific sleeping positions to alleviate joint strain and improve comfort.(Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/10/04/550x309/13878_1759591281381_1759591287490.jpg" alt="Dr Dushyant advises incorporating specific sleeping positions to alleviate joint strain and improve comfort.(Freepik)" title="Dr Dushyant advises incorporating specific sleeping positions to alleviate joint strain and improve comfort.(Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Dr Dushyant advises incorporating specific sleeping positions to alleviate joint strain and improve comfort.(Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How can your sleeping position affect joint pain&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The way you sleep can actually make your joint pain worse,” says Dr Dushyant. He explains, “If you usually sleep on your side, placing a pillow between your knees can significantly reduce discomfort in your hips and &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/what-is-reformer-pilates-know-how-it-is-a-game-changer-for-sculpting-your-lower-body-101753265468875.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="lower body"&gt;lower body&lt;/a&gt;. For those who sleep on their back, it’s best to place a pillow under their knees. This simple adjustment helps relieve pressure on your spine and joints, easing pain in your lower back and hips.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Dr Dushyant adds, “By incorporating these two easy sleeping positions into your nightly routine, you can prevent unnecessary strain and experience noticeable relief in your &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/physician-shines-light-on-a-rare-disease-that-causes-hyperflexible-joints-and-dislocations-101759218005945.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="joints"&gt;joints&lt;/a&gt;. Try it out, and you may find waking up less stiff and more comfortable a daily reality.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Tips for better spinal health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an earlier interview with HT Lifestyle, Dr Arun Bhanot, Director of Spine Services at CK Birla Hospital, Gurugram, highlighted the importance of sleep posture for spinal health. He shared, “Your sleeping position helps minimise back strain, avoid stiffness, and maintain proper spine alignment.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Bhanot recommends a firm-to-medium mattress, a pillow that keeps your neck aligned, and advises against sleeping on your stomach or using a very high pillow. Following these tips can help reduce discomfort and support long-term spine health. &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/re-you-sleeping-correctly-spine-surgeon-shares-5-best-positions-to-sleep-101755599570559.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Click here"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to read the full article.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="recommendedSliderContextual" id="recommendedSliderContextual-101759590205030" data-vars-story_id="101759590205030" data-vars-story_section="lifestyle" data-vars-author="Akanksha Agnihotri" data-vars-story_headline="AIIMS orthopaedic surgeon reveals ‘best sleeping position’ to prevent neck, back and joint pain"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" class="trendTopsSHow" id="trendTopsSHow-101759590205030"&gt; &lt;div class="trendTops"&gt;  &lt;div class="trendInlineSeo"&gt;&lt;p&gt; Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;label class="moreBtn1" for="trendTopsSHow-101759590205030"&gt;&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="followHT trendSeo__1"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="htEchoEOALite"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="bottomSeoParaEcho1"&gt; &lt;div id="bottomSeoParaEcho"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="mb5 mt5" id="bottomBreadCrumb"&gt; &lt;div class="breadcrumbs"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Home_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/" data-vars-event-cta="News"&gt;News&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Lifestyle_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle" data-vars-event-cta="Lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Health_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle/health" data-vars-event-cta="Health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; AIIMS orthopaedic surgeon reveals ‘best sleeping position’ to prevent neck, back and joint pain &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="bottomSeoParaEcho pb0"&gt; &lt;label class="moreBtn" for="trendTopsSHow-101759590205030" id="spanSeeLessEcho"&gt;See Less&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;p class="relatedStoryCricket"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="saranyuPlayer" id="saranyu-player"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="relatedStory2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="us-ad align-center mb10 mt10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="htEchoShortsEntryPoint" data-size="enlarged"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="affiliate-shop-now" id="affiliate-shop-now"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 01:43:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi8wFBVV95cUxQRVZwWVdhVEN1UmNwQ1FHWUJ0a2VUakFDS21mZktjSjMxLWt1UTJHbXVJSnc4X2d6YzF5czZXaFVob2xQMlBLM2NoX2dKM21ZS3FGMU9QVTFKTUJWUnNBZzlRZV8zcjRKQjlELW9qdVRlZ242Uk0wSFBaN3B1VlhsTVdhYjlSMTN5TTIwSE1oRm5WRTg2S3ZzVUNXaXdSb0pXcWRabXFjUlZZd0dGaWt6eG1jQVRqQnczaEJGcU5HWTlOd202T25qWmxHVExCejBDOUhRcjl1ZFFDckFEVXVjeTVGTnJkUk9jekhaR2NHT3c5OTjSAfgBQVVfeXFMT25vY3dGTEUwSmEwdzZGZlB1U0NPUktVLWQ5LUFsTWRYaWFOejIzLU42aVMxNHgtQ1hidlZYc19FR1NEZENieW0tZXkwUWFxZjNpLXlZcGJBVEtxTVJRc2Vrc0Yxcndydng1ekJBZWZTN2dRZ3gzYzE5SFhyV0Q0dEtBUFRSdWk5VlpPb2REdmFSTTdZSVdWNWs5N0tJQ1EzX1J1blc5bjc3ZV9ud1dtbndad1pBSkxMMlFqa0dORE5Jekp4T1ZwcHE1cWhXUEVNMTNLSldPbXlmQzQwbm4xRnFOZVFCSXBrMjhpakVIZFZBbDg4RHItMUc</guid></item><item><title>拯救蜜蜂，拯救世界-这种新的“超级食品”很有可能同时做到这两点- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/honeybee-superfood-sterols-test-results-are-beyond-spectacular-offering-new-hope/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Honeybees carry pollen from flower to flower, helping plants make fruits, seeds, and nuts. Most foods on our plates depend on their tireless, daily work. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet when farms plant huge blocks of a single crop and climate change throws off bloom times, bees can go hungry, and &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-are-highly-concerned-that-so-many-bee-hives-have-disappeared/"&gt;entire colonies disappear&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During these “pollen dearths,” beekeepers turn to substitutes. Those feeds keep adult bees alive, but they often fail to support brood – the next generation of bees. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent study explains why this happens and proposes a practical fix based on the right mix of nutrients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-honeybees-superfood-and-sterols"&gt;Honeybees, superfood, and sterols&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The missing piece in honeybee diets is a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/medicine-and-dentistry/sterol" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;class of fats&lt;/a&gt; called sterols. Sterols help build cell membranes and provide ingredients for hormones that guide growth and development. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humans can make cholesterol in our bodies; insects can’t. Honeybees are even more limited: unlike many other insects, honeybees can’t modify plant sterols into the forms they need. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Honeybees must eat the right sterols directly from pollen and pass them to their developing young. Without them, brood growth slows or stalls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers asked a basic question: which sterols do honey bee pupae actually use, and in what amounts? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One sterol dominated the profile – &lt;a href="https://pubchem.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/compound/24-Methylenecholesterol" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;24-methylenecholesterol&lt;/a&gt; – making up roughly two-thirds of the total. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five others consistently showed up in smaller amounts: β-sitosterol, desmosterol, isofucosterol, campesterol, and cholesterol. That six-sterol recipe became the target for a complete feed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-one-out-of-every-three-bites"&gt;One out of every three bites&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After years of poor forage and shifting climates, pollinator nutrition has become a concrete business risk. Danielle Downey is the executive director of the honey bee nonprofit &lt;a href="https://www.projectapism.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Project Apis m&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though not involved in the study, Downey noted that honeybees pollinate about one in three bites of our food, but face many stressors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good nutrition, she said, is a practical way to strengthen colony resilience – especially as natural forage dwindles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new identification of key &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/how-polyphenols-promote-heart-health-youthful-skin-and-a-healthy-waistline/"&gt;phytonutrients&lt;/a&gt; that, when added to feed, sustain brood rearing “has immense potential to improve colony survival – and the beekeeping businesses we rely on for food production.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That perspective matches what commercial &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/science-is-giving-beekeepers-a-better-way-to-fight-colony-collapse/"&gt;beekeepers&lt;/a&gt; report during long stretches between blooms: adult bees can hang on, but brood patterns break down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding the specific nutrients behind that pattern helps turn a vague problem into a solvable one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-making-sterols-for-honeybees"&gt;Making sterols for honeybees&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s a catch. The exact plant sterols honeybees need aren’t readily available in the right proportions, especially 24-methylenecholesterol. It’s rare and hard to source at scale. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get around that, the team turned to biotechnology and chose a workhorse yeast, &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/agricultural-and-biological-sciences/yarrowia-lipolytica" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Yarrowia lipolytica&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, known for producing fats efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using genetic engineering, including &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/crispr-used-to-remove-extra-chromosomes-in-down-syndrome-and-restore-cell-function/"&gt;CRISPR&lt;/a&gt;, they rewired the yeast’s sterol pathway. They shut down its default sterol, ergosterol, and redirected metabolism to produce 24-methylenecholesterol along with the other five targets. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They then blended the engineered yeast – rich in the required sterols – into a complete honeybee diet instead of purifying each sterol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;a href="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/04192448/honeybees_superfood-supplement_restores-health_boosts-numbers_Oxford_1m.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/04192454/honeybees_superfood-supplement_restores-health_boosts-numbers_Oxford_1s.webp" alt="Worker bees feeding in the lab, Oxford Bee Lab. Credit: Caroline Wood" class="wp-image-1989005" srcset="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/04192454/honeybees_superfood-supplement_restores-health_boosts-numbers_Oxford_1s.webp 300w, https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/04192454/honeybees_superfood-supplement_restores-health_boosts-numbers_Oxford_1s-150x150.webp 150w, https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/04192454/honeybees_superfood-supplement_restores-health_boosts-numbers_Oxford_1s-32x32.webp 32w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Worker bees feeding in the lab, Oxford Bee Lab. Click image to enlarge. Credit: Caroline Wood&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-testing-synthetic-sterols-on-honeybees"&gt;Testing synthetic sterols on honeybees&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The crucial test was straightforward: feed colonies different diets and watch what happens. Colonies that received &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/organic-beekeeping-is-healthier-for-bees-and-their-keepers/"&gt;complete nutrition&lt;/a&gt; without the proper sterols reared brood briefly and then declined. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Honeybee colonies that received feed containing the sterol-producing yeast continued rearing brood for significantly longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That outcome matters because maintaining brood through pollen-poor stretches helps prevent colonies from weakening or collapsing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our study demonstrates how we can harness synthetic biology to solve real-world ecological challenges,” explained senior author &lt;a href="https://www.biology.ox.ac.uk/people/geraldine-wright" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Professor Geraldine Wright&lt;/a&gt;, of the Department of Biology at the &lt;a href="https://www.ox.ac.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;University of Oxford&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Most of the pollen sterols used by bees are not available naturally in quantities that could be harvested on a commercial scale, making it otherwise impossible to create a nutritionally complete feed that is a substitute for pollen.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-honeybees-need-more-than-sterols"&gt;Honeybees need more than sterols&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Better nutrition won’t fix everything, but it’s a big step in the right direction. Pesticide exposure, parasites like &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/major-cause-of-honeybee-mortality-can-be-easily-reduced/"&gt;Varroa mites&lt;/a&gt;, and habitat loss still threaten colonies. Healthy landscapes with diverse flowers remain essential. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But nutrition is a major piece of colony health, and this work clarifies the issue: most feeds lack a realistic supply of 24-methylenecholesterol plus a small set of companion sterols, and a microbe-based approach can provide them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Safety and practicality matter, too. The study demonstrates a proof of concept: make the needed sterols in yeast, mix them into feed, and support honeybee brood rearing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before broad use, the field will need checks on cost, stability, dosing, shelf life, and performance across seasons and climates. It also makes sense to confirm that the approach does not disrupt &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/a-gentle-tap-on-the-hive-reveals-honeybee-health/"&gt;hive microbes&lt;/a&gt; or leave residues in honey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;a href="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/04192435/honeybee-colony_pollen-substitute_superfood_boosts-health-numbers_Oxford_1m.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/04192441/honeybee-colony_pollen-substitute_superfood_boosts-health-numbers_Oxford_1s.webp" alt='A pollen sterol "superfood" substitute in a honeybee colony, Oxford Bee Lab. Credit: Caroline Wood' class="wp-image-1989003" srcset="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/04192441/honeybee-colony_pollen-substitute_superfood_boosts-health-numbers_Oxford_1s.webp 300w, https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/04192441/honeybee-colony_pollen-substitute_superfood_boosts-health-numbers_Oxford_1s-150x150.webp 150w, https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/04192441/honeybee-colony_pollen-substitute_superfood_boosts-health-numbers_Oxford_1s-32x32.webp 32w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;A pollen sterol “superfood” substitute in a honeybee colony, Oxford Bee Lab. Click image to enlarge. Credit: Caroline Wood&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-wider-ecological-implications"&gt;Wider ecological implications&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Managed honeybees sometimes compete with wild bees for limited flowers during dearths. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If beekeepers can rely on high-quality substitutes that truly support brood, managed colonies may put less pressure on wild pollinators when forage is scarce. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That easing of demand during critical gaps could help local ecosystems maintain balance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also sharpens our &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/honeybee-dances-reveal-a-new-level-of-animal-communication/"&gt;understanding of bee biology&lt;/a&gt;. It confirms that honeybees need specific molecules, like sterols, found in certain pollens – generic protein or sugar won’t cut it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research also quantifies the sterol profile inside pupae and shows how that profile differs among workers, drones, and queens. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, and thankfully, it demonstrates that metabolic engineering can tailor microbes to produce those molecules at useful levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This sterol-producing yeast “superfood” will never replace wildflowers in the honeybee diet, but it offers a clear nutritional tool for beekeepers when nature’s pantry runs low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The full study was published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-025-09431-y" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Nature&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 01:42:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxQRGEzRmZRS2R2T1lId2VuRkstbVFJSk9aeU8yc0tiR0JuZk4zMmI3X2RWLXY1WXFPaXNURldKQV9GTnMzUkVGWFFuaF9vRmZHbXQxUm50ZHpMNjZvMFdMbVNDWTcybnUydGVJcjZrSmZFYWFDazBQY2F1ZTVIZzFsSFZ1RW1seGRmY2NxbF9Xb25kX25TQl8tYkZDWWN1S0x2eGxsbjNEU01uTGNy</guid></item><item><title>伯明翰妇女面临导致母亲死亡的痴呆症风险--英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/ce32kx79e7eo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Mum died from early dementia - I had to find out if I will too&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-c4820dd1-0 cYDsPh"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-c4820dd1-11 bxdaHR"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;Ed James&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;BBC Radio WM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-9 iEEPlu"&gt; and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;Shehnaz Khan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;West Midlands&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 kSquvq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/c738/live/c7e72570-a069-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/c738/live/c7e72570-a069-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c738/live/c7e72570-a069-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/c738/live/c7e72570-a069-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/c738/live/c7e72570-a069-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/c738/live/c7e72570-a069-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/c738/live/c7e72570-a069-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c738/live/c7e72570-a069-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.png.webp" loading="eager" alt="Liv Heeney A woman with long red hair, wearing a navy blue jumpsuit, stands in front of a white background. She is smiling into the camera." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Liv Heeney&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Liv Heeney discovered she had a faulty gene which puts her at risk of early onset dementia &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;When Liv Heeney was 28, she discovered she had a faulty gene that would probably cause her to develop a rare form of dementia at a young age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Early onset frontotemporal dementia (FTD) has already affected 13 members of her family, including her mum Bernie, who died from the disease aged 54.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Liv, from Birmingham, is living with the reality she will likely develop the condition in her 40s and die in her 50s - but she's using the knowledge to ensure any children she has are not born with the gene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It's also given her the chance to plan for a family, but she said: "It's a fine balance. I don't want to look so far ahead that I'm missing out on now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;FTD is a type of dementia that, according &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/frontotemporal-dementia/" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;to the NHS&lt;/a&gt;, causes problems with behaviour, language and memory, with most cases diagnosed in people aged 45 to 65.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It can also be hereditary, with about &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-humber-56843649" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;one in eight people&lt;/a&gt; with the condition having a genetic link. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/adca/live/dfe39de0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/adca/live/dfe39de0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/adca/live/dfe39de0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/adca/live/dfe39de0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/adca/live/dfe39de0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/adca/live/dfe39de0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/adca/live/dfe39de0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/adca/live/dfe39de0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Liv Heeney A woman wearing a white sun hat and T-shirt stands outside on a sunny day. A building and trees can be seen behind her. People are crossing the road." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Liv Heeney&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Bernie Heeney was 54 when she died in 2017&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Growing up, Liv knew her granddad and multiple siblings had lost their lives early to dementia before she was born, and she was a teenager when she started noticing her mum's out-of-character behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"She just didn't seem like herself, she was missing work which was very unusual [as] she loved her job. She would [also] make inappropriate comments," she told BBC Radio WM.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I think the big first telltale sign was when my granddad, my dad's dad died [in 2012] and she didn't really have much of an emotional response to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"My mum kind of confided in people that she was worried that what was happening to her dad was happening to her," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;A slow decline&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Bernie was diagnosed with dementia shortly after her 50th birthday in 2013, with her husband becoming her primary carer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Liv said her mum soon lost the ability to talk, as well as basic skills such as washing herself, walking, eating and drinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"By the time she was diagnosed, I think she didn't really know what was going on."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In 2017, Bernie died at home while Liv, who was just 21, was in a taxi rushing to catch a last-minute train home from university in London.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/a341/live/e6266660-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/a341/live/e6266660-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a341/live/e6266660-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/a341/live/e6266660-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/a341/live/e6266660-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/a341/live/e6266660-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/a341/live/e6266660-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a341/live/e6266660-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Liv Heeney A woman with blue eyes and red hair holds a young girl with blue eyes and red hair in her arms while sitting on a green sofa. The woman is wearing a blue top and the young girl is wearing a white T-shirt." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Liv Heeney&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Liv's mum Bernie started showing symptoms of FTD in her late 40s&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;After years of deliberating, Liv decided to start the process of genetic testing at Birmingham Women's Hospital in January 2024, in the hope of finding out if she had inherited the same gene that caused her mum's dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;After an eight-month process from the initial conversation, confirmation came from a simple blood test which took about five minutes, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I've always assumed that I had the gene, that it would happen to me... I don't know why, it was just a gut feeling," Liv, of Hall Green, added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;On 2 August that year, she found out she had tested positive for the faulty microtubule associated protein tau (MAPT) gene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Me and my partner Ani went in, and before I'd even sat down on the chair, she [the geneticist] just said 'I'm really sorry, it's not the result we wanted'."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Liv added the confirmation was "hard to describe" but it "wasn't really a shock".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d0fb/live/ed3642e0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d0fb/live/ed3642e0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d0fb/live/ed3642e0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d0fb/live/ed3642e0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d0fb/live/ed3642e0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d0fb/live/ed3642e0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d0fb/live/ed3642e0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d0fb/live/ed3642e0-9eb9-11f0-8e3d-5bce5d982785.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Liv Heeney A photo of a bride and groom in a car on their wedding day. The woman has wavy red hair tied up and is wearing a pearl necklace, floral headpiece and a white wedding dress and is smiling into the camera. The man has short brown hair and is wearing a dark suit and tie with a white shirt and floral pin. He is looking wistfully at the bride." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Liv Heeney&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Bernie, pictured with her husband Darryl, was diagnosed with FTD after her 50th birthday&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;For many people in their 20s, the possibility of dying at a young age is not something they have to dwell on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But for Liv, who now works as a designer in London, the disease is something she thinks about every day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The health of any future children was one of the main reasons Liv - who has a partner of seven years - wanted to find out if she carried the gene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I felt like if I wanted to have children, it was the responsible decision for me to take. That I needed to protect them from this," Liv explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;With the help of IVF and embryo screening, she hopes to be able to ensure any children she has will be born without the faulty gene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"If you find out you have the gene, there are ways to ensure that you don't pass it on now," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d8a5/live/b2d50d90-a06a-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d8a5/live/b2d50d90-a06a-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d8a5/live/b2d50d90-a06a-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d8a5/live/b2d50d90-a06a-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d8a5/live/b2d50d90-a06a-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d8a5/live/b2d50d90-a06a-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d8a5/live/b2d50d90-a06a-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d8a5/live/b2d50d90-a06a-11f0-9640-9757c7912ee3.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Liv Heeney A woman with red hair and wearing a black jacket smiles at the camera over her shoulder. She is holding a pair of brown and black sunglasses in her hand. She is walking on a rural country road." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Liv Heeney&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Liv began the process of genetic testing in January last year&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;'Not about ageing'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Liv said a common misconception was that dementia only affected older people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It's just not the case that [dementia] is a natural part of ageing, it's a disease, it's physical changes to your brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It's a disease just like cancer and Aids, even like Covid - it's a physical thing in the body," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Liv believes there should be more funding and research into FTD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Despite her diagnosis, Liv is determined to live her life the way she has planned. Next weekend, she will be holding a fundraising night in Birmingham for Alzheimer's Research UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"If I have children today, I'll get 15 years with them. If I have kids in five years time, I'll have less time with them," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I know the reality of this, I know what's coming."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;i id="if-you-have-been-affected-by-any-of-the-issues-raised-in-this-story,-help-and-support-is-available-via" class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt;If you have been affected by any of the issues raised in this story, help and support is available via &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/actionline/" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;&lt;i id="bbc-action-line." class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt;BBC Action Line.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 cnKFtO"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 01:29:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFB3OXVodURkSms4cndMNXE5Yl9HM205ay1vNl9OY3Y3U1ZwaTdyMkJIbFZUekI4dzJzTHE4QkJhbG44b1JBcFRjUWZrRGJJT3NKWlVpWTZlQjEwQdIBX0FVX3lxTE9HUndIb0dMMnZNVV9KOEtzejBneS1XaGxzWU0zbWFUTGF1NlQyVVVndGdha1lCTG9kb3RjS2ZKWnNiMnNuczNjYnc5VjJxaUdQQWNsN3RGY1I3bnBQeHU0</guid></item><item><title>癌症和深腹部脂肪：新研究将内脏脂肪活动与女性的侵袭性癌症生长联系起来-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/cancer-and-deep-belly-fat-new-study-links-visceral-fat-activity-to-aggressive-cancer-growth-in-women/articleshow/124315250.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A groundbreaking new study presented at the 38th Annual Congress of the European Association of Nuclear Medicine (&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://eanm25.eanm.org/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;EANM’25&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;) has revealed a powerful link between visceral fat, the deep belly fat stored around internal organs, and aggressive forms of endometrial cancer. Researchers found that it’s not just the amount of belly fat that matters, but how metabolically active that fat is. In other words, visceral fat that’s “burning up” more glucose (sugar) for energy may drive cancer growth and make the disease more aggressive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This discovery has major implications for women’s health across the globe as rates of obesity and endometrial cancer continue to rise. The findings could change how doctors assess cancer risk in women and open doors for new diagnostic and treatment approaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Cancer is curable if detected early: Signs to pay attention to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What the study found&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research, led by scientists from Haukeland University Hospital and the University of Bergen, analyzed PET/CT scans from 274 women diagnosed with endometrial cancer—a cancer that affects the lining of the uterus. Using advanced imaging, the team measured how much glucose each woman’s visceral fat was using, an indicator of how “metabolically active” the fat tissue was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women whose visceral fat showed higher glucose uptake tended to have:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;More advanced endometrial cancer at diagnosis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Greater likelihood of lymph node involvement, a sign of aggressive disease&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surprisingly, the total volume of visceral fat didn’t always match its metabolic activity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This means that simply having more belly fat wasn’t necessarily the problem, what really mattered was how “hot” or inflamed that fat was on a molecular level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why metabolically active visceral fat is dangerous&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visceral fat is the deeper, more harmful kind of fat that surrounds your liver, intestines, and other organs. Unlike subcutaneous fat (the softer fat under your skin), visceral fat produces inflammatory chemicals and hormones that can disrupt metabolism and fuel chronic diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how metabolically active visceral fat may worsen endometrial cancer outcomes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic Inflammation: Active visceral fat releases cytokines and fatty acids, which create an inflammatory environment that helps tumors grow and spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Insulin resistance: Inflammation promotes insulin resistance, which in turn fuels cancer cell growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adipokine signaling: Fat cells send signals called adipokines that can “talk” directly to tumor cells, helping them survive and invade nearby tissues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This “crosstalk” between fat tissue and cancer cells could explain why women with highly active visceral fat experience more aggressive and harder-to-treat cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What this means for women’s health&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For years, obesity has been a known risk factor for endometrial cancer, especially among postmenopausal women. But this new study suggests that not all fat is equal, and it’s the behavior of visceral fat that may determine cancer severity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings highlight a potential new frontier in cancer research: targeting metabolically active belly fat to reduce cancer aggressiveness. If doctors can develop imaging tools or drugs to calm down or neutralize “hot” visceral fat, it could become a breakthrough in personalized cancer treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 01:14:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwJBVV95cUxPSjJLSzZYQUI4Y2Y3NXZ4VHhOYzg4N19lemxRNlhlWXluczVGZzNGckxmVUR6YkxjMHlSNGFnaExLOGE5cFdDNmJEckpURkYxVzlKVDBfTWprbmJJTVFBektsLXVLUzBCVXRvOGlWMGtoSENJTGJGTlZFd0lVS2I4S1hJWXc5SzNQNDNqc3c4NHNPZ3hYaS1RbXhzaXFDUjVCV01oM1liOEQySHg0WC1uVHdaRzktSG1UQU1CekM0a25hRGE5WWExSXphbWVQWHZ5di1FdTVnNGk0eWYxTW1QNjVIV1J6UHhvbDVRbzEtV1pGWVM3ME52ZHRHVC1ibFRJYklHc2hJMTdnTDkxYUQ0LWVWRUxlS2labEtFa0hJajJ1SEpLM2RV0gGsAkFVX3lxTFBXZkRIcXB5N0NLNzNLYU5MbHdfMEt6R0RCLTR1blJWZ2k4RlZkZnFBNUV2dEdMTkhPWTlRT3V3YklwOU5YVkFjVUU1X0dGaTJBUzhFS01tU2FnYm1tdmpjdnhXREZHTERsTEcxNFlBTVZwNk1VcFRZX1hWbFVMYkU3TER5Mi04NGYtQURJd3BCM2cwNmtLdEMxZTRJb1ZlemI5R0JjaktvZXBEQjZnQ3I4dkJab2ltSlRLcU4wcF9oLWhOak5FeWNmRi0xMUxSTlI5Z21UcGlITWNPUjV0b1pWMDZyRXpadjNCUHVNYzVlcVdhWmRyTU1xQlRYekRlVkpUcW9iRzJoMUdPd2JzSnhSbHBzNjZYY3N5NHhLcXlIdGdicm40bkVrTzlzbA</guid></item><item><title>斐济的HIV病例因蓝斑、化疗和共用针头而激增--英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c0m42dwvlk8o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;'They're not just sharing needles, they're sharing blood': How HIV cases soared in Fiji&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 kSquvq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Three syringes, seemingly used, lying on a tattered orange blanket" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Intravenous drug use is fuelling Fiji's HIV epidemic&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ten: that's the age of the youngest person with HIV that Sesenieli Naitala has ever met.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;When she first started Fiji's Survivor Advocacy Network in 2013, that young boy was yet to be born. Now he is one of thousands of Fijians to have contracted the bloodborne virus in recent years – many of them aged 19 or younger, and many of them through intravenous drug use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"More young people are using drugs," Ms Naitala, whose organisation provides support to sex workers and drug users in the Fijian capital Suva, tells the BBC. "He (the boy) was one of those young people that were sharing needles on the street during Covid."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Over the past five years, Fiji – a tiny South Pacific nation with a population of less than a million – has become the locus of one of the world's fastest growing HIV epidemics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In 2014, the country had fewer than 500 people living with HIV. By 2024 that number had soared to approximately 5,900 – an elevenfold leap. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;That same year, Fiji recorded 1,583 new cases – a thirteenfold increase on its usual five-year average. Of those, 41 were aged 15 or younger, compared to just 11 in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A view of the Suva waterfront, with a dock in the foreground and multi-storey buildings in the background" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Fiji's assistant health minister has called the HIV epidemic a "national crisis"&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Such figures prompted the country's minister for health and medical services to declare an HIV outbreak in January. Last week, assistant health minister Penioni Ravunawa warned Fiji may record more than 3,000 new HIV cases by the end of 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"This is a national crisis," he said. "And it is not slowing down."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The BBC spoke to multiple experts, advocates and frontline workers about the reasons for such a meteoric rise in case numbers. Several pointed out that, as awareness around HIV spreads and stigma diminishes, more people have been coming forward and getting tested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;At the same time though, they also noted that countless more remain invisible to the official figures – and that the true scale of the issue is likely much bigger than even the record-breaking numbers suggest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;'Sharing the blood'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Underpinning Fiji's HIV epidemic is a spiralling trend of drug use, unsafe sex, needle sharing and "bluetoothing". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Otherwise known as "hotspotting", this latter term refers to a practice where an intravenous drug user withdraws their blood after a hit and injects it into a second person – who may then do the same for a third, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Kalesi Volatabu, executive director for the NGO Drug Free Fiji, has seen it happen firsthand. Last May, she was on one of her regular early morning walks through the Fijian capital of Suva, offering support and education to drug users on the streets, when she turned a corner and saw a group of seven or eight people huddling together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I saw the needle with the blood – it was right there in front of me," she recalls. "This young woman, she'd already had the shot and she's taking out the blood – and then you've got other girls, other adults, already lining up to be hit with this thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It's not just needles they're sharing – they're sharing the blood."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Bluetoothing has also been reported in South Africa and Lesotho, two countries with some of the world's highest rates of HIV. In Fiji, the practice became popular within the past few years, according to both Ms Volatabu and Ms Naitala.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Supplied: Kalesi Volatabu A woman in a black and turquoise dress, wearing glasses and speaking into a microphone in front of several onlookers. Behind her is a wall with several pieces of paper attached to it" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Supplied: Kalesi Volatabu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Kalesi Volatabu has spent more than a decade working at the frontline of drug awareness and advocacy in Fiji&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;One reason for its appeal, they explain, is a cheaper high: multiple people can chip in for a single hit and share it among themselves. Another is the convenience of only needing one syringe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;These can be difficult to come by in Fiji, where pharmacies, under police pressure, often demand prescriptions for syringes, and there is a lack of needle-syringe programmes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Although there is growing acceptance and approval for the rollout of such programmes – which provide clean injecting equipment to drug users in an attempt to reduce the transmission of blood-borne infections like HIV – implementation in the highly religious and conservative country has proven challenging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ms Volatabu says there is a "drastic shortage" of needle-syringe sites, which is fuelling dangerous practices like needle-sharing and bluetoothing and putting the onus on NGOs to distribute syringes as well as condoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In August 2024, Fiji's Ministry of Health and Medical Services (MOH) recognised bluetoothing as one of the drivers for the country's rise in HIV cases. Another was chemsex, where people use drugs - often methamphetamine - before and during sexual encounters. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In Fiji, unlike most other countries around the world, crystal meth is predominantly consumed via intravenous injection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;MOH also found that of the 1,093 new cases recorded in the first nine months of 2024, 223 – about 20% – were from intravenous drug use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Kids on meth&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Fiji has become a major Pacific trafficking hub for crystal meth over the past 15 years. A large part of this is due to the country's geographic location between East Asia and the Americas – some of the world's biggest manufacturers of the drug - and Australia and New Zealand – the world's highest-paying markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;During that same period, meth has spilled into and spread throughout local communities, developing into a crisis that, like HIV, was recently declared a "national emergency". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;And according to those on the frontlines, the age of users is trending downwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We see more and more of these young people," says Ms Volatabu. "They are getting younger and younger."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Fiji's most recent national HIV statistics cite injectable drug use as the most common known mode of transmission, accounting for 48% of cases. Sexual transmission accounted for 47% of cases, while mother-to-child transmission during pregnancy and childbirth was cited as the cause of most paediatric cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Everyone the BBC spoke to agreed that lack of education is a central factor in the epidemic. Ms Volatabu and Ms Naitala are both working to change that – and Ms Naitala says that as a greater awareness around the dangers of HIV spreads throughout the community, "bluetoothing" has, in her experience, fallen out of favour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;More people are getting tested and seeking treatment for HIV, leading to more robust data around the scale of the crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But there is still a worry that the official case numbers are merely the tip of the iceberg – and a fear of what may lie beneath the surface.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;The avalanche&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;José Sousa-Santos, head of the Pacific Regional Security Hub at New Zealand's University of Canterbury, says "a perfect storm is brewing".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"The concern is across all levels of society and government in regards to Fiji's HIV crisis – not just what's happening at the moment, but where it's going to be in three years' time and the lack of Fiji's resources," he tells the BBC. "The support systems - the nursing, the ability to distribute or to access the drugs for treatment of HIV - just aren't there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"That's what terrifies us, the people that work in the region: there is no way that Fiji can deal with this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Supplied: José Sousa-Santos A man with a goatee wearing a blue suit and blue shirt" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Supplied: José Sousa-Santos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;José Sousa-Santos has been ringing the alarm bell on Fiji's HIV epidemic for years&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Following its declaration of an outbreak in January, the Fijian government has sought to improve its HIV surveillance and enhance its ability to address the likely underreporting of cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The Global Alert and Response Network, which was called upon to provide that support, stated in a recent report that "addressing these pressing issues through a well-coordinated national response is crucial in reversing the trajectory of the HIV epidemic in Fiji".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;That report also noted that staffing shortages, communication issues, challenges with lab equipment and stockouts of HIV rapid tests and medicines were impacting screening, diagnosis and treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Data collection is slow, difficult and error-prone, it added – hampering efforts to understand the extent of Fiji's HIV epidemic and the efficacy of the outbreak response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;That leaves many experts, authorities and everyday Fijians in the dark.  And Mr Sousa-Santos is predicting an "avalanche" of cases still to come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"What we're seeing at the moment is the beginning of the avalanche, but you can't stop it, because the infections are already happening now, or they've already happened – we're just not going to be able to see them and people aren't going to look to get tested for another two to three years," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"There's nothing that we can do at the moment to stop the number of infections that have already happened over the past year, and that are happening now. That's what's really terrifying."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 00:58:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE40M0FvM0gtUTdVN1lyUmNCZ01fbUd0blcwQUxPSlc1QzUyekRqTmx5eG5vWndubkNZVVQ4QU1nM0NodERrcW1kN2lrR3RuR0hIU09pSGRTazdKQdIBX0FVX3lxTE01bFhzMmVvczN4VU9HUno1RThPeXhYMFBWVVBIZF9EVVgtOElhMW00S2pPY2tDVk9ZZndGOS1WdkJ6QXk4NmZ6b3VXakduTzlWYmRiVTFGSzhzTnNiT3Rn</guid></item><item><title>突破性血液检测在症状出现前10年检测头颈部癌症- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/breakthrough-blood-test-detects-head-and-neck-cancer-up-to-10-years-before-symptoms/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 23:14:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxNME9QLWx5SVlaOUt4WTcxYzd4czhJcWVpeldtWTRZbHBIcDlpNU9GUDlFWHlhd3FVRG9LYXVweldLbzRkdWxIN1BOU1gzdndhWVE0aGRJeUtaakE5VWFvajNjMDJhejVTNUNITUZ1b0ZuRmpuWUxtcUJQaUw4SVJHU0hBZDRRYVd6SkIweXhJOEczMWZPd0VOTUtSN1NLWkVzM2l2RWlXQndkd21SV1E</guid></item><item><title>新生流感：为什么学生很难躲避？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c147218x7rgo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Late nights and packed lectures - why freshers' flu is so hard to dodge&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 ERpRj"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/5c9b/live/2dd015c0-a0b2-11f0-ac11-a11de8fbd7b8.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/5c9b/live/2dd015c0-a0b2-11f0-ac11-a11de8fbd7b8.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5c9b/live/2dd015c0-a0b2-11f0-ac11-a11de8fbd7b8.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/5c9b/live/2dd015c0-a0b2-11f0-ac11-a11de8fbd7b8.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/5c9b/live/2dd015c0-a0b2-11f0-ac11-a11de8fbd7b8.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/5c9b/live/2dd015c0-a0b2-11f0-ac11-a11de8fbd7b8.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/5c9b/live/2dd015c0-a0b2-11f0-ac11-a11de8fbd7b8.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5c9b/live/2dd015c0-a0b2-11f0-ac11-a11de8fbd7b8.png.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images A person with blonde hair, dressed in a white top, stands against a blue backdrop. Surrounding them are floating, orb-like structures resembling virus particles." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It's the second week of term. You've finally figured out how to use the washing machine, your flatmates are starting to feel like friends, and the whirlwind of freshers' week is behind you. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But just as things settle down, your throat starts to scratch, your nose runs, and suddenly lectures are less about learning and more about trying not to cough louder than the person next to you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;You were warned it would happen, but didn't expect it to hit quite so fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;What's actually going on here? Why does everyone seem to get freshers' flu in the first few weeks of term? And why do so many say it feels worse than the average cold?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Freshers' flu is just an assortment of common cold viruses that come and hit us all at the same time," says Dr Zania Stamataki, associate professor of viral immunology at the University of Birmingham.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It's not the actual flu, and it's rarely serious. But when thousands of students arrive on campus they bring with them a cocktail of respiratory viruses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Add packed lecture theatres, dirty shared kitchens and late-night parties, and the result is a wave of illness that spreads quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Sheena Cruickshank, an immunologist and professor in biomedical sciences at the University of Manchester, describes it as a "mixing pot" of infections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"You're bringing people together from all over the world, putting them in close quarters, and exposing them to viruses they've never encountered before," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Respiratory viruses are constantly evolving and even small differences between variants can mean the body's immune system doesn't recognise them, forcing it to start from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;The role of drinking, diet and stress&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 geRyoc"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/232f/live/13b14560-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/232f/live/13b14560-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/232f/live/13b14560-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/232f/live/13b14560-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/232f/live/13b14560-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/232f/live/13b14560-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/232f/live/13b14560-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/232f/live/13b14560-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A young woman and a man smile as a large number of arms holding pint glasses of lager or beer are held above their heads, as if they are saying cheers" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The immune system is the body's natural defence against infections. It's made up of a network of cells, tissues, and organs that work together to detect harmful invaders like viruses and bacteria, and help the body fight them off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But during freshers' week your immune system is under-resourced and overworked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;That's because, as Prof Cruickshank explains, "your diet, your level of activity, your level of stress, and sleep are all factors that affect immune functions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Which, she recognises, are "not necessarily the first focus" for students in the early weeks of university.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Among these, stress plays a particularly disruptive role. The pressure to settle in, make friends, manage new responsibilities, and keep up with academic demands can quickly become overwhelming. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;This triggers the release of cortisol, a stress hormone that suppresses immune responses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We've all had those times when you're super stressed, you've got loads of deadlines, you work, work, work, you finish all the deadlines - and then you get ill," says Prof Cruickshank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Stress can also impact the amount of sleep you get, which also impacts the immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But for many students, the pressure to socialise and make friends during freshers' week outweighs the need to rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Imogen says freshers' flu lingers for quite a while&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I didn't want to miss out," says Imogen Farmer, 19, a second-year student at the University of Leeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She says she met up with friends every evening during freshers' week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I definitely suffered with it after the first week, like sore throat, runny nose, those typical symptoms, and it does linger for quite a while."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Imogen says it's been worth it because "so much of student culture, especially during freshers' week, revolves around nights out".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"That is how you meet a lot of people and bond with friends. So I did just say yes to everything."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 geRyoc"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/1b71/live/3e27a1e0-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/1b71/live/3e27a1e0-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/1b71/live/3e27a1e0-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/1b71/live/3e27a1e0-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/1b71/live/3e27a1e0-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/1b71/live/3e27a1e0-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/1b71/live/3e27a1e0-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/1b71/live/3e27a1e0-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Young people dance and raise their arms in the air while wearing headphones, in a dark place with a trace of some lights in the background" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But it's not just lack of sleep which makes life difficult for your immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;After&lt;b id="" class="sc-d16436d-0 kPzeuB"&gt; &lt;/b&gt;drinking a lot of alcohol - which many students will be doing to overcome nerves - your body produces fewer white blood cells, which help to fight off infections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"A lot of people have the misconception that if you're consuming alcohol, you sleep better. But you have higher stress and you sleep worse," says Dr Stamataki.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A poor diet can also weaken the immune system and, for many students, eating healthily isn't easy - especially when skipping meals is a regular occurrence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;You'll feel great... but you'll be transmitting&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;With so many viruses around, you could be stuck in a lecture between two people who are sneezing, each infected with a different one. And you'd be exposed to both.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Viruses can then be passed on very easily, without you knowing (during the incubation period), and before you notice symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Sometimes you think you've gotten away with it. And you haven't," Dr Stamataki warns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"So you'll feel great. You'll go and play rugby, you'll hug your friends and you'll have a good time but at the same time, you'll be transmitting." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She says that the immune response within young people is "quite powerful" but it's limited by the fact they haven't been exposed to many viruses yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;While everything you come across for the first time will make you sick, the next time you come across the same virus, the symptoms won't be as nasty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 geRyoc"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/6f3e/live/9232d480-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/6f3e/live/9232d480-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6f3e/live/9232d480-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/6f3e/live/9232d480-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/6f3e/live/9232d480-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/6f3e/live/9232d480-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/6f3e/live/9232d480-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6f3e/live/9232d480-a0a8-11f0-93bc-5f62999beb00.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A young man with tousled brown hair is looking glum and a bit ill, wrapped up in a grey-coloured duvet while sitting on his bed" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;You can also get two infections at once. This can help or hinder your body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Either you'll start to feel really awful - because your immune system is struggling to cope - or your body's defences will start working overtime to deal with the invaders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;When that happens, the immune system "is already super pumped up," says Prof Cruickshank, because the body is busy making chemical messengers called cytokines that help to kill viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;If you're unlucky enough to get a second infection soon after you've got rid of the first one, it's usually because you're already rundown. That's when conditions like bronchitis can occur.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"If your symptoms are persisting for a really long time or you felt like you're getting better and then you get ill again, it might be worth getting some medical help just to check that," says Prof Cruickshank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"If you see spots at the back of your throat, that's definitely a sign that you've got strep throat and you might need some antibiotics," she adds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Viruses like colds and flu don't respond to antibiotics - these drugs are only used to treat some types of bacterial infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;How do I know if it's something more serious?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;While most viruses are mild, some can be far more dangerous and &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/meningitis/" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;meningitis&lt;/a&gt; is a serious infection to watch out for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It can look a lot like freshers' flu, but if left untreated, it can lead to seizures, brain damage and sepsis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cx20nelwrnwo" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;One student, from Wolverhampton,&lt;/a&gt; had her lower legs and parts of her fingers amputated after being struck down with it a week after starting university. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Vaccines which help protect against various types of meningitis are given to children, but it's still important to be aware of the symptoms, even if you've had the jabs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;So what do you need to look out for?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;a high temperature or fever&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;being sick&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;a headache&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;a rash that does not fade when a glass is rolled over it (but a rash will not always develop)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;a stiff neck&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;a dislike of bright lights&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;drowsiness or unresponsiveness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;seizures (fits)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Meningitis spreads in a similar way to a cold - through close contact with someone carrying the infection. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It causes inflammation of the membranes surrounding the brain and spinal cord, so if you recognise these symptoms, call 999 or go to A&amp;amp;E straight away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Emily Valentine says there is pressure to keep going during an illness&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;For many students, the pressure to keep going, even when sick, is hard to ignore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"You're pushing yourself so much because that's what you're being told to do," says Emily Valentine, a 19-year-old student at the University of Leeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I tend to rest, but I know a lot of my friends try to push themselves to go to lectures, especially in the first week," she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A shift to recording lectures during the pandemic has made it easier for students to catch up with work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But experts say you should still give yourself time to recover. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It can take your body a while to get over a really big assault from a virus," says Prof Cruickshank. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 23:05:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5UQXgweWRRSFNRXzY1akJoWWRGaTBnYU5XTDJ4SkJiU2kyNkppdnlqVWg0RGsyRERPa0Fra2ZlVENJVF9KTlRjaG51R2hXWnYtS2hPazB3MDdrQdIBX0FVX3lxTE9ua0hnZEh6bG9kbUxpdkJRVEdNUmJ6R1JTazd1TW5USWxCRk9JZjRwSFZhSmppalVHX3JRQldjZ0pEZlZ5U0RIMXY3U2MwdmZFLWNtZVpHNzZpbFpRc1NV</guid></item></channel></rss>