<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Marylander has measles after international travel. Here's what to know - WBAL TV Baltimore</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxNUGNEYWl0R3JlazZJRGowYUtnSXVNOGRDT3JoRlFweXdHdEhvQjRfeVdNWVl3MldxYVVLdmZpTnk4YUdicTR4TDdxU1EwOXktbFJTNTdRYmdlYmlVaHNJa2N0MDdyZ21zaGUzcTlEZTVEcUk4RzQ4NUpnQzV3NjNFaVh4Q1I5QXM3WmRfaDJR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article-content--body-text-raw"&gt;
						A positive case of measles was confirmed in a Howard County resident who recently traveled internationally, according to health officials.The Maryland Department of health said this case is not associated with a measles outbreak in Texas and New Mexico.Out of an abundance of caution, health officials are trying to identify people who might have been exposed. State and county health officials are trying to get in touch with potentially exposed passengers on specific flights as follows.Washington Dulles International Airport: The international arrivals area on March 5 between 4-9 p.m.Johns Hopkins Howard County Medical Center Pediatric Emergency Department on March 7 between 3:30-7:30 p.m.Early symptoms of measles are a fever of more than 101 degrees Fahrenheit, runny nose, cough, and red, watery eyes. Usually, one to four days after the early symptoms, a red rash appears on the face and spreads to the rest of the body. Measles symptoms typically develop 10-14 days after exposure to the virus but can develop as soon as seven days and as long as 21 days after exposure. A person with measles is contagious, beginning four days before the rash appears until four days after the rash begins.MDH said people are generally considered immune to measles if they have had two measles vaccine shots, previously had measles or laboratory evidence of immunity or infection, or were born in the United States before 1957.Those who are most at risk of complications from measles infection are pregnant women, infants less than 1 year old, and those who are immune compromised. People in these at risk groups who may have potentially been exposed and are not immune should contact their health care provider or call Howard County Health Department's Infectious Disease Surveillance and Response Program at 410-313-6284 for additional guidance. Virginia residents with additional questions about their potential exposure can call the Virginia Department Health at 804-363-2704 or email epi_response@vdh.virginia.gov.People, especially those not vaccinated or otherwise immune to measles, who were at any of these locations during the possible exposure times should monitor themselves for any early symptoms of measles for 21 days after the potential exposure. People who develop a fever or other symptoms of measles should not go to childcare, school, work, or out in public, and should contact their health care provider. They should call their health care provider first rather than showing up in the waiting room or emergency room so that the office can take measures to prevent spread to other patients.Measles cases do occur sporadically in Maryland with one case of measles identified in Maryland in 2024, one in 2023, and no cases from 2020-2022.This report will be updated.
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;div class="article-content--body-text"&gt;
						&lt;strong class="dateline"&gt;BALTIMORE —&lt;/strong&gt; 													&lt;p&gt;A positive case of measles was confirmed in a Howard County resident who recently traveled internationally, according to health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Maryland Department of health said this case is not associated with a &lt;a href="https://www.wbaltv.com/article/measles-is-popping-up-in-the-us-how-to-avoid/64040348" target="_blank"&gt;measles outbreak in Texas and New Mexico&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Out of an abundance of caution, health officials are trying to identify people who might have been exposed. State and county health officials are trying to get in touch with potentially exposed passengers on specific flights as follows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Washington Dulles International Airport: The international arrivals area on March 5 between 4-9 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Johns Hopkins Howard County Medical Center Pediatric Emergency Department on March 7 between 3:30-7:30 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early symptoms of measles are a fever of more than 101 degrees Fahrenheit, runny nose, cough, and red, watery eyes. Usually, one to four days after the early symptoms, a red rash appears on the face and spreads to the rest of the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles symptoms typically develop 10-14 days after exposure to the virus but can develop as soon as seven days and as long as 21 days after exposure. A person with measles is contagious, beginning four days before the rash appears until four days after the rash begins.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;MDH said people are generally considered immune to measles if they have had two measles vaccine shots, previously had measles or laboratory evidence of immunity or infection, or were born in the United States before 1957.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="cream-inline-rec" class="cream-inline hidden"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who are most at risk of complications from measles infection are pregnant women, infants less than 1 year old, and those who are immune compromised. People in these at risk groups who may have potentially been exposed and are not immune should contact their health care provider or call Howard County Health Department's Infectious Disease Surveillance and Response Program at 410-313-6284 for additional guidance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Virginia residents with additional questions about their potential exposure can call the Virginia Department Health at 804-363-2704 or email &lt;a href="mailto:epi_response@vdh.virginia.gov" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;epi_response@vdh.virginia.gov&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People, especially those not vaccinated or otherwise immune to measles, who were at any of these locations during the possible exposure times should monitor themselves for any early symptoms of measles for 21 days after the potential exposure. People who develop a fever or other symptoms of measles should not go to childcare, school, work, or out in public, and should contact their health care provider. They should call their health care provider first rather than showing up in the waiting room or emergency room so that the office can take measures to prevent spread to other patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles cases do occur sporadically in Maryland with one case of measles identified in Maryland in 2024, one in 2023, and no cases from 2020-2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This report will be updated&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;


							
											&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
						
						
																			

																				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WBAL TV Baltimore</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNUGNEYWl0R3JlazZJRGowYUtnSXVNOGRDT3JoRlFweXdHdEhvQjRfeVdNWVl3MldxYVVLdmZpTnk4YUdicTR4TDdxU1EwOXktbFJTNTdRYmdlYmlVaHNJa2N0MDdyZ21zaGUzcTlEZTVEcUk4RzQ4NUpnQzV3NjNFaVh4Q1I5QXM3WmRfaDJR</guid></item><item><title>Utah colon cancer survivor shares experience with immunotherapy, encourages early detection - KSL.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixwFBVV95cUxOZFh0REMzR2NRa2N3M04tNmF1YU5BazBNZ2loS28tc29EUmRqNWNyUHFJVjVqeF9oRXFBSWhjQ3Z5bHRjd3hkeDhQX0pPbDJLWWZZQmg4WFpWcVpzTXZ5V2dxVXFkOFlEWmFpOE96ZkJLTlk2T3pCa3hiZjdhT0p6Rm9sQkJiWklJNXp0VjgwaWVFT0tFLVlWX3h1WGt0SE1FZWN5WThNRUpZeklYYm94cnJ3MUV2bWtMb29wZGRIbFhlRFBSemVR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;
                                        Estimated read time: 2-3
                                        minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;MURRAY — An avid traveler, 72-year-old Eva Brinley lives her life to the fullest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But things took a turn a few years ago after her physician encouraged her to get a colonoscopy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I went in and had it done, and they found colon cancer," she said. "It was a dark moment. I have lost many friends from different types of cancers, and so my first thought was, 'I'm done.'"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brinley had 15 inches of her colon removed. She then met with Dr. Mark Lewis, director of gastrointestinal oncology at Intermountain Health, and told him she was concerned about the side effects of chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, she was eligible for another type of treatment: immunotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A lot of patients, understandably, when you tell them they require chemotherapy, will refuse it, so it is incredibly appealing to patients that we now have another option to treat cancer, and that's immunotherapy," Lewis said. "The entire point is to turn on the immune system and allow the patient's own body to destroy the cancer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not everyone is a candidate for immunotherapy, and Lewis noted with this kind of treatment, there is a risk of developing an autoimmune disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm not going to pretend that these treatments have absolutely no side effects, but for the most part, these treatments are far more tolerable than chemotherapy," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brinley went in for an IV every three weeks for two years. She experienced nausea at first but said she had no other side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It was very successful, and I'm in remission," she said. "I feel great. I feel really good. Strong and healthy."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her cancer journey hasn't been easy, but she has remained positive, focusing on her family and her religion. She's now encouraging others to make their health a priority, especially since she didn't experience any signs or symptoms before being diagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Eva Brinley rings a bell signifying she has finished her cancer treatment. (Photo: Eva Brinley)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I just can't stress enough how important it is to do those checkups," she said. "Stay healthy. Eat right. Have your checkups, and be aware."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colorectal cancer is the second leading cause of cancer-related deaths and the third most commonly diagnosed cancer. While some people may not have any symptoms, like Eva, warning signs of colon cancer may include persistent or progressive abdominal pain, changes in bowel movements, such as constipation or diarrhea, blood in the stool and unintentional weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts recommend people at average risk of colon cancer begin screening at age 45. To schedule a colonoscopy with Intermountain Health, visit its website.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 17:18:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixwFBVV95cUxOZFh0REMzR2NRa2N3M04tNmF1YU5BazBNZ2loS28tc29EUmRqNWNyUHFJVjVqeF9oRXFBSWhjQ3Z5bHRjd3hkeDhQX0pPbDJLWWZZQmg4WFpWcVpzTXZ5V2dxVXFkOFlEWmFpOE96ZkJLTlk2T3pCa3hiZjdhT0p6Rm9sQkJiWklJNXp0VjgwaWVFT0tFLVlWX3h1WGt0SE1FZWN5WThNRUpZeklYYm94cnJ3MUV2bWtMb29wZGRIbFhlRFBSemVR</guid></item><item><title>Aspirin could actually help fight cancer, research finds - Ynetnews</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiakFVX3lxTE0yNTFDaFFkMGY0ZmQ4TGI5aXZZMWU0am1kRVp3aWtoZ1lGOWFTWmxPQmRkRjgwb3BURXR1YmJCXzFYd0ZOejNZV05pTW1sS2xIcHlPcHVfWVg1VkZwaUxzZWwyU2pzb1I5aVE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-contents="true"&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="9jrj0-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9jrj0-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9jrj0-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Scientists at the University of Cambridge believe they have discovered a way in which aspirin — a common and inexpensive pain reliever — may help inhibit the spread of cancer by enhancing the immune system's function. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="ast89-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="ast89-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="ast89-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Animal experiments have shown that the drug helps T cells, a key component of the immune system, identify and destroy cancer cells attempting to spread in the body. Researchers have described the finding as "exciting and surprising," as it could lead to the controlled use of aspirin as a complementary treatment for cancer patients in the future. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="30fou-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide firstImageInArticle firstImageInArticleBody"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.HyeKzPeoiyx" id="image_ArticleImageData.HyeKzPeoiyx"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;2&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.HyeKzPeoiyx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/03/08/ryr9jG9oke/ryr9jG9oke_0_0_1000_664_0_x-large.jpg" alt="אספירין" title="Aspirin  (Photo: shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.HyeKzPeoiyx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/03/08/ryr9jG9oke/ryr9jG9oke_0_0_1000_664_0_x-large.jpg" alt="אספירין" title="Aspirin  (Photo: shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Aspirin &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="11kjk-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="11kjk-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="11kjk-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;However, they caution against self-administering the drug, as aspirin carries significant risks. Additionally, this research is still in its early stages, and it is not yet clear which cancer patients might benefit from taking the drug. The study, recently published in the journal Nature, examined how the immune system responds to cancer metastasis. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="ec41n-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="ec41n-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="ec41n-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;It found that platelets, which are responsible for blood clotting, interfere with T cells’ ability to destroy cancer cells. Researchers discovered that aspirin, which inhibits platelet activity, helps the immune system detect and eliminate cancer cells before they form metastases. This discovery was made by chance. The Cambridge research team was not initially studying aspirin but rather how the immune system responds to cancer spread. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="9qofg-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9qofg-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9qofg-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Using genetically engineered mice, they found that animals lacking certain genetic instructions were at a lower risk of developing metastases. Further investigation into the body’s processes revealed that T-cells were affected in a manner similar to the known effects of aspirin. This unexpected finding redirected the researchers’ focus entirely.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="1t02g-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1t02g-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1t02g-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Although the findings are primarily based on animal experiments, they provide important insights that could eventually lead to human clinical trials and improvements in current treatment options. Professor Gil Bar-Sela, director of the Beit Shulamit Cancer Center at the Emek Medical Center in northern Israel, commented on the clinical implications of the new research on aspirin and cancer treatment. "It is still too early to determine the clinical significance of these findings," he said. "The big question is whether and how this will translate into a tangible impact on cancer treatment." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="6jkvl-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6jkvl-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6jkvl-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;"The immune system is complex and influenced by many factors, so additional research is needed to understand the full implications," he added.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="74uj7-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.Hkg9EPlisye" id="image_ArticleImageData.Hkg9EPlisye"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;2&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.Hkg9EPlisye" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/03/06/SJyPI7vske/SJyPI7vske_0_0_1000_660_0_x-large.jpg" alt="טסיות דם. אילוסטרציה תלת-ממדית" title="Blood platelets  (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.Hkg9EPlisye" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/03/06/SJyPI7vske/SJyPI7vske_0_0_1000_660_0_x-large.jpg" alt="טסיות דם. אילוסטרציה תלת-ממדית" title="Blood platelets  (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Blood platelets &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="bcj5l-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="bcj5l-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="bcj5l-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt; Unlike new drugs that require years of development, aspirin is an established and widely used medication. This makes it relatively easy to study its effects on cancer patients, particularly those undergoing immunotherapy — a treatment that activates the immune system against cancer cells. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="citph-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="citph-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="citph-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;"Aspirin may serve as a complementary treatment that enhances the effectiveness of immunotherapy, much like other attempts to combine drugs, viruses, or vaccines that stimulate the immune system," Bar-Sela explained. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="csdtt-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="csdtt-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="csdtt-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;He noted that a significant advantage is the ability to investigate aspirin’s potential using existing extensive data sets in Israel and globally. A comparison between cancer patients taking aspirin for unrelated reasons and those who do not could provide initial clues about its effectiveness as a complementary treatment. While this is a promising area of research, additional clinical trials are needed before definitive recommendations can be made. Over a decade ago, intriguing data suggested that people who took daily aspirin had a higher chance of survival following a cancer diagnosis. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="7bhll-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7bhll-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7bhll-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The key to this lies in the moment when a single cancer cell detaches from the primary tumor and attempts to spread through the body — a process known as metastasis, which is responsible for most cancer-related deaths. At this point, the immune system — particularly T cells, a type of white blood cell — can destroy the cancer cell before it establishes itself in a new location. However, researchers found that platelets, the blood cells responsible for clotting, interfere with T-cell activity, preventing them from destroying cancer cells. Aspirin works by inhibiting platelets, thereby removing the obstacle to T-cell function and enabling them to detect and eliminate cancer cells. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="3sqh2-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="3sqh2-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="3sqh2-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;According to the researchers, using aspirin could be most effective for patients diagnosed early, following treatments such as surgery, to help the immune system eliminate remaining cancer cells. However, they emphasize that cancer patients should not rush to purchase aspirin on their own, as much more research is needed in this area. Currently, certain patients with Lynch syndrome — a genetic mutation that increases cancer risk — already take aspirin as part of their preventive treatment. However, to determine whether more cancer patients could benefit from the drug, further clinical trials are required. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul class="public-DraftStyleDefault-ul" data-offset-key="1cum1-0-0"&gt;&lt;li class="public-DraftStyleDefault-unorderedListItem public-DraftStyleDefault-reset public-DraftStyleDefault-depth0 public-DraftStyleDefault-listLTR" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="1cum1-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1cum1-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1cum1-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Increased risk of bleeding:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1cum1-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt; Aspirin acts as an antiplatelet agent, preventing blood clotting, which can raise the risk of internal bleeding, especially in the gastrointestinal tract and brain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="public-DraftStyleDefault-unorderedListItem public-DraftStyleDefault-depth0 public-DraftStyleDefault-listLTR" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="l3nv-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="l3nv-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="l3nv-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Gastrointestinal side effects:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="l3nv-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt; Prolonged aspirin use can lead to stomach ulcers, gastritis and bleeding in the digestive tract, particularly in patients with a history of stomach issues or those taking medications that damage the stomach lining.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="public-DraftStyleDefault-unorderedListItem public-DraftStyleDefault-depth0 public-DraftStyleDefault-listLTR" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="boe1p-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="boe1p-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="boe1p-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Variable effects depending on cancer type and patient profile:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="boe1p-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt; There are differences between cancer types and patients’ genetic profiles, meaning not all patients may benefit from the treatment, and some may face higher risks of severe side effects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="public-DraftStyleDefault-unorderedListItem public-DraftStyleDefault-depth0 public-DraftStyleDefault-listLTR" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="eukuc-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="eukuc-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="eukuc-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Interactions with other treatments:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="eukuc-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt; Aspirin can affect the efficacy of other medications, including chemotherapy and anticoagulants, increasing the risk of adverse reactions or reducing the effectiveness of certain treatments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="cmc01-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta wrapped"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleWrappedImageComponenta"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleWrappedImageData.SJg0ovxsskg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/03/06/HJ11JSMDs1x/HJ11JSMDs1x_697_0_802_1068_0_medium.jpg" alt="פרופ' גיל בר סלע" title="Prof. Gil Bar-Sela  (Photo: Emek Medical Center) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="caption" contenteditable="false"&gt;Prof. Gil Bar-Sela &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span disabled class="credit" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Emek Medical Center&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="5c7ng-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5c7ng-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5c7ng-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Could aspirin have a greater impact on specific types of cancer?
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5c7ng-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;"Based on available data, aspirin’s effect was more pronounced in breast, stomach and prostate cancers,"  Bar-Sela said. "In other cancer types, its contribution was minimal or insignificant. Extensive studies, including comprehensive reviews, suggest a reduced risk of cancer recurrence and even prevention of initial cancer development among aspirin users." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8fgmp" data-offset-key="7mphh-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7mphh-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7mphh-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;In cases of active metastatic cancer, aspirin alone does not appear strong enough to serve as a primary treatment. However, as a supplement to other treatments, particularly immunotherapy, it may offer some benefits — a topic that warrants further exploration. For now, as studies remain in various stages of investigation, the use of aspirin as a complementary treatment is not recommended for all patients. Instead, it should only be considered within clinical trials or under strict medical supervision.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 12:53:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE0yNTFDaFFkMGY0ZmQ4TGI5aXZZMWU0am1kRVp3aWtoZ1lGOWFTWmxPQmRkRjgwb3BURXR1YmJCXzFYd0ZOejNZV05pTW1sS2xIcHlPcHVfWVg1VkZwaUxzZWwyU2pzb1I5aVE</guid></item><item><title>Shocking stories of people who went blind after taking Ozempic and Mounjaro - The Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgJBVV95cUxPUnduVV9UcVRvUFgydE1iYXZFN2pCQjZYdVV3N1VtR2lDeXhtZHV6bW8wVjhmWlFvaDFFMjhDV1FocWgzZGRZdHdMZ0hOeEN3Qy1zMnBBMDJXU0FaWW9rY1VIeW5oSjhRX2Y4V21iMlNIc0lzaThFQ3RsRk5ZX3cwZjdab1pxVERvQ29HRERvWTVLazJONExEcnhrU2lrWjBfOVVoWVd1bHFPN1I5VGdMY2dOZTNhSXpUTW1DUUtybFNnbHVQVnRvTDBudWVDNkhvWHc2RmRXZVNfVDRRQ0pfUVB4eHZSMUdxcG1BNVd3RmoyTkYtMmV4WHRwMnQyX0hfMmlUVEdR0gGLAkFVX3lxTFB0bEZ2RWJreUtpaGN0amlJUTJ3UEVqbTNZbDNuWEFEWlpQbU85MW8xeHpDZFl2RnZkTHdoUkpfU3VpR0o2Vm9jU29jeXFxQlYyU2M5MkhSUm5VUEh2LWVCV3FHNUEzQVNfQ09FZURPSDN0dU8tMEYxdzFGOG1HWmNuWFFaRV9nTEp3WWxrbXJSUjlQYjZvTHMzb2pzLW5KVmREcnU1VnpuY1dmdFhFSER4UHhDTmxmZjB2ZVRCQ3VhdVE5dkg4d0NNYWxWcEhyak81RHIxMzlUX3czeHF1dkFfeGluN19QSE1jNWMxNEd3eGZkRVNieXdLaW9UbDNTdHhxRi1EUVBYd1pPUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Billed by many as miracle drugs for its instant results in weight loss, the 'silver bullet' Ozempic and its cousins have now been linked to vision impairment and blindness, in a growing number of cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weight loss drugs like Ozempic, Mounjaro, and Zepbound have changed millions of lives by helping people shed extra pounds and reach a healthy weight bracket, thus reversing many chronic diseases. While this seems almost magical and holds a great promise for reducing alarming levels of obesity worldwide, some of the scary and irreversible side effects of the drugs have come under the scanner. One of them is sudden and permanent vision loss, which can have a life-altering consequence for people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/ozempic-blindness-new-study-flags-unexpected-side-effect-of-weight-loss-drugs/articleshow/118148954.cms" rel="noopener" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; two months back published in JAMA Ophthalmology talks about nine patients who developed serious optic nerve-related conditions after taking semaglutide or tirzepatide, which is the active ingredient in most weight loss drugs available today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent report in the New York Post talks about the devastating vision loss of James Norris, a 56-year-old mechanic from Roxbury, New Jersey. Always struggling with weight loss, Norris decided to try obesity drug Mounjaro in March 2023, inspired by his wife’s remarkable 60-pound transformation on the same medication. His earlier attempts at losing weight through diet and exercise didn't translate in results, and weighing 289 pounds, Norris really thought that the drug was an easy alternative to shed some quick pounds. Within a year, Norris lost 89 pounds and was able to stop taking medication for high blood pressure and cholesterol, which seemed to be an encouraging progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While initially he was on 1.5 milligrams dose - a relatively low dose - things changed rapidly for him when the dose was increased to 2.5 milligrams. To his surprise, he woke up with a clouded vision in his left eye one morning. Two weeks later, his right eye became blurry too. At first, he dismissed it as a possible sinus infection, but after a series of medical tests, a neuro-ophthalmologist diagnosed him with non-arteritic anterior ischemic optic neuropathy (NAION) — a condition in which a sudden loss of blood flow to the optic nerve causes irreversible vision damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I was devastated,” he said. “It’s extremely rare to get NAION in both eyes.” While Norris discontinued Mounjaro, he now struggles with daily tasks. Not able to do hands-on-work, he is now forced to do administrative work. He believes the risks associated with these medications, particularly at higher doses, are not worth the potential benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What studies say about Ozempic blindness&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study published in JAMA Ophthalmology on January 30, 2025, by physician-scientists from the University of Utah’s John A. Moran Eye Center reviewed nine patients who developed serious optic nerve-related conditions after taking semaglutide (the active ingredient in Ozempic and Wegovy) or tirzepatide (used in Mounjaro and Zepbound).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seven of the patients reported symptoms consistent with NAION, while others experienced optic nerve inflammation (papillitis) or a condition known as paracentral acute middle maculopathy, which can cause blind spots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research follows a July 2024 study from Harvard’s Mass Eye and Ear hospital, which found that diabetics taking these drugs had a fourfold increased risk of developing NAION, while overweight or obese individuals taking them solely for weight loss faced a sevenfold risk increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In another &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/can-ozempic-cause-sudden-vision-loss-a-study-uncovers-the-link/articleshow/116339266.cms" rel="noopener" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; diabetes patients using Ozempic were found to be over twice as likely to develop a rare eye condition known as NAION compared to those taking other diabetes medications, according to researchers who analyzed years of patient data from Denmark and Norway. If the risk remains consistent over time, a type 2 diabetes patient taking Ozempic for 20 years would face a 0.3% to 0.5% likelihood of developing NAION, according to a non-peer reviewed study published Thursday on medRxiv.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;More horror stories&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New York Post report mentions more cases of weight loss drugs causing vision loss in people. Michael Sabellico, 1 60-year-old took Ozempic in March 2024 to manage his Type 2 diabetes and lose weight. Weighing 185 pounds at the time, he initially lost weight successfully. But after eight weeks on a 1.5 mg dose, he woke up one morning unable to see clearly. He was diagnosed with NAION. At that time, there was no proper research around the link between NAION and Ozempic, so doctors actually increased his Ozempic dose to better manage his blood sugar. He finally stopped taking Ozempic in May 2024, but by then, the damage was done. He now has 20/70 vision in his left eye and 20/30 in his right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cheryl Bovee, a 56-year-old from Winston-Salem, North Carolina, has already filed a lawsuit against Novo Nordisk, the manufacturer of Ozempic, for what she calls “deceptive and misleading” marketing that downplayed the risks of the drug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bovee, who used Ozempic as prescribed for diabetes management, is now legally blind after developing NAION. “I can no longer work. I can no longer drive. I have to be careful just walking around my block. I can’t see at night,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A widow, she had envisioned a retirement spent traveling and enjoying time with her family. Now, she worries about losing her independence entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“All of my hopes and dreams have been dashed,” she said. “I no longer have the hope of seeing my grandchildren’s faces clearly.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the growing number of cases, the official websites for Ozempic and Mounjaro list “changes in vision” as a potential side effect, but none explicitly mention NAION.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Inside Ozempic: Does the drug really help in weight loss and what are its possible side effects?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 12:20:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgJBVV95cUxPUnduVV9UcVRvUFgydE1iYXZFN2pCQjZYdVV3N1VtR2lDeXhtZHV6bW8wVjhmWlFvaDFFMjhDV1FocWgzZGRZdHdMZ0hOeEN3Qy1zMnBBMDJXU0FaWW9rY1VIeW5oSjhRX2Y4V21iMlNIc0lzaThFQ3RsRk5ZX3cwZjdab1pxVERvQ29HRERvWTVLazJONExEcnhrU2lrWjBfOVVoWVd1bHFPN1I5VGdMY2dOZTNhSXpUTW1DUUtybFNnbHVQVnRvTDBudWVDNkhvWHc2RmRXZVNfVDRRQ0pfUVB4eHZSMUdxcG1BNVd3RmoyTkYtMmV4WHRwMnQyX0hfMmlUVEdR0gGLAkFVX3lxTFB0bEZ2RWJreUtpaGN0amlJUTJ3UEVqbTNZbDNuWEFEWlpQbU85MW8xeHpDZFl2RnZkTHdoUkpfU3VpR0o2Vm9jU29jeXFxQlYyU2M5MkhSUm5VUEh2LWVCV3FHNUEzQVNfQ09FZURPSDN0dU8tMEYxdzFGOG1HWmNuWFFaRV9nTEp3WWxrbXJSUjlQYjZvTHMzb2pzLW5KVmREcnU1VnpuY1dmdFhFSER4UHhDTmxmZjB2ZVRCQ3VhdVE5dkg4d0NNYWxWcEhyak81RHIxMzlUX3czeHF1dkFfeGluN19QSE1jNWMxNEd3eGZkRVNieXdLaW9UbDNTdHhxRi1EUVBYd1pPUQ</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr. could further deter childhood vaccinations as rates fall in the U.S. - CNBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipgFBVV95cUxNMllpZVJlZG5IbTFYMWtlTVlxbDRsRDczODRXYjhZa3FIQm5hU0FNdDFwOGpVT0EtVi02WUxBa3VoQnZPb0VIQ2RUN19WV09pTTJpQ3V2OEpPdTBma0hTdzlOQUFxVEJnV3N5TTZQTkM4eFp1ckk2X1VrVnBaMUhyZVVfUDhPUGVEQ3pDUmlGYWVKVXN2Q291STQ4VVFERjJYWHNoS1pB0gGrAUFVX3lxTE1DZGNweHE2WFJGdXk3ZnZBd1B1WEpURUcyTzNOWU5zWHRmMTRmUThyWmotUHgwNVhzWTJXN2pOTFRyaDdMWFNxOGxScmJkTkJkazluUTJwSlU2d3NJWmdiNXhXZ0FVM0E2RVFpaWNGbGNheTdmTGhMLWRmSloyeTJyR2syZTdJdFhoRVB5aVRMRVNjbG1wakxxeHVHbE1GZ2ppcG0tNlJtRFUydw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleBody-articleBody" id="RegularArticle-ArticleBody-5" data-module="ArticleBody" data-test="articleBody-2" data-analytics="RegularArticle-articleBody-5-2"&gt;&lt;span class="HighlightShare-hidden"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage-imageEmbed" id="ArticleBody-InlineImage-108102431" data-test="InlineImage"&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="InlineImage-imageEmbedCaption"&gt;Robert F. Kennedy Jr. speaks in the Oval Office of the White House, on the day he is sworn in as secretary of Health and Human Service in Washington, D.C., U.S., Feb. 13, 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="InlineImage-imageEmbedCredit"&gt;Nathan Howard | Reuters&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nation's &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/11/19/rfk-jr-is-trump-pick-for-hhs-secretary-heres-what-he-could-do.html"&gt;new top health official&lt;/a&gt; could further erode &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/policy-watch/childhood-vaccination-rates-continue-to-decline-as-trump-heads-for-a-second-term/" target="_blank"&gt;already falling U.S. vaccination rates&lt;/a&gt; against once-common childhood diseases, a development that comes as &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/02/26/a-child-dies-of-measles-in-west-texas-outbreak.html"&gt;a growing measles outbreak&lt;/a&gt; has led to the first U.S. death from the disease in a decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/02/25/healthy-returns-hhs-secretary-rfk-jrs-efforts-could-affect-vaccines.html"&gt;prominent vaccine skeptic&lt;/a&gt;, now leads the Department of Health and Human Services and wields enormous power over the federal agencies that regulate vaccines and set shot recommendations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy tried to distance himself from his previous views during his &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/29/watch-rfk-jr-senate-confirmation-hearing-for-hhs-secretary.html"&gt;Senate confirmation hearings&lt;/a&gt;, claiming that he isn't "anti-vaccine" and would not make it "difficult or discourage people from taking" routine shots for measles and polio. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But some health policy experts said his early moves as HHS Secretary are concerning and suggest that he could undermine immunizations in other, less direct ways, which could increase the risk of children catching preventable diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The steps that he's taken so far seem to be in line with his views of skepticism about vaccines and their safety, of wanting to allow for parents to not get their children vaccinated. It's all things he's championed," said Josh Michaud, associate director of global health policy at KFF. "There might be more dominoes to fall coming."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy has said he will review the childhood vaccination schedule, and is &lt;a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2025/02/20/kennedy-prepares-shakeup-of-vaccine-advisers-00205223" target="_blank"&gt;reportedly preparing&lt;/a&gt; to remove and replace members of external committees that advise the government on vaccine approvals and other key public health decisions, among other efforts. Some experts said he could also amplify data highlighting the risks of vaccines, promote unfounded claims about shots and undermine legal protections for vaccine makers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If rates drop even more, there could be major consequences, such as renewed outbreaks of vaccine-preventable illnesses in certain communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Within the next couple of years, we could see major drops in childhood vaccination rates," Lawrence Gostin, professor of public health law at Georgetown University, told CNBC. "He has all the powers he needs to sow public distrust in vaccines. He has a history of doing that and he has a desire to do it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This could lead to significant outbreaks of vaccine-preventable diseases throughout America, with the disproportionate impact on red states that President Trump carried in the 2024 election," Gostin added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy has a long track record of making misleading and false statements about the safety of shots. He has claimed they are linked to autism despite decades of studies that debunk that association. Kennedy is also the founder of the nonprofit Children's Health Defense, the most well-funded anti-vaccine organization in the U.S. In a &lt;a href="https://extapps2.oge.gov/201/Presiden.nsf/PAS+Index/F3C8425ED335BB5685258C1A00565D57/%24FILE/Kennedy%2C%20Jr.%2C%20Robert%20F.%20%20finalEA.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;government ethics agreement&lt;/a&gt; in January, he said he stopped serving as chairman or chief legal counsel for the organization as of December.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But vaccines have saved the lives of more than 1.1 million children in the U.S. and saved Americans &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/childhood-vaccines-have-prevented-half-billion-illnesses-saved-us-27-trillion-3#:~:text=The%20investigators%20found%20that%2C%20among,%242.7%20trillion%20in%20societal%20costs." target="_blank"&gt;$540 billion in direct health-care costs&lt;/a&gt; over the last three decades, according to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/73/wr/mm7331a2.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention research released&lt;/a&gt; in August.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;States and local jurisdictions set vaccine requirements for school children, but the federal government has a longstanding system for approving and recommending shots for the public. That includes creating the childhood vaccination schedule, which recommends when children should receive certain shots. It's used by states, pediatricians and parents. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Department of Health and Human Services did not immediately respond to CNBC's request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-subtitle"&gt;&lt;a id="headline0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Why have childhood vaccination rates fallen?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Childhood vaccinations and the state requirements in place for them have been "one of the greatest public health success stories" in the U.S., allowing the country to eliminate many diseases that people once feared, such as polio, according to William Moss, professor at the Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rates stayed relatively steady for nearly a decade before the Covid pandemic, as about 95% of kindergarten children were up to date with all state required vaccines, Moss said. That includes separate shots for polio and varicella, a vaccine for measles, mumps, and rubella – called MMR – as well as a jab that protects against diphtheria, tetanus, and pertussis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the share of kindergarten children who are up to date on their vaccinations has dipped since the pandemic, according to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/schoolvaxview/data/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;data collected and aggregated annually&lt;/a&gt; by the CDC from state and local immunization programs. Less than 93% of kindergarteners had received all state required vaccines in the 2023-2024 school year, data shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/73/wr/mm7341a3.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Exemptions&lt;/a&gt; from school vaccination requirements, particularly non-medical exemptions, have also increased, according to the CDC. The share of U.S. children claiming an exemption from one or more shots rose from 2.5% in the 2019-2020 school year to 3.3% in the 2023-2024 school year, the highest national exemption rate to date. Nearly all of that increase was driven by non-medical exemptions, such as religious or personal belief reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;That decrease appears consistent with the public's perception of childhood immunizations. A Gallup &lt;a href="https://news.gallup.com/poll/648308/far-fewer-regard-childhood-vaccinations-important.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;survey released&lt;/a&gt; in August found only 40% of Americans said they considered childhood vaccines extremely important, down from 58% in 2019 and 64% in 2001. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The overall decline is fueled in part by vaccine skepticism, a trend that "certainly existed far before the pandemic," KFF's Michaud said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vaccine hesitancy and the anti-vaccine movement have been around globally for decades. They are often intertwined with political, moral and spiritual ideas around the rights of an individual versus the community, the limits of government power over bodily autonomy, mistrust of medical institutions and misinformation about shot safety and efficacy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The politicization of the pandemic only fueled more doubts about vaccinations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It created a partisan divide on the public's acceptance of the Covid vaccine, according to Sean O'Leary, chair of the American Academy of Pediatrics committee on infectious diseases. Social media and public figures amplified misinformation about Covid jabs, and some of those "falsehoods about Covid shots spilled over to an extent to other types of vaccinations," he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There was a very precipitous drop [in vaccination rates] right when the pandemic hit, in those first few months afterwards," O'Leary said. "And we never really completely caught up." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;O'Leary noted that the vast majority of parents on both sides of the political spectrum continue to vaccinate their kids. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, surveys suggest that the partisan division on immunizations has deepened in recent years. In 2024, 63% of Democrats and Democratic-leaning voters said childhood vaccinations were "extremely important," compared to just 26% of Republicans and GOP leaners, according to the August Gallup &lt;a href="https://news.gallup.com/poll/648308/far-fewer-regard-childhood-vaccinations-important.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;survey&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five years earlier, enthusiasm was just slightly higher among the Democratic group at 67%, and double among Republican respondents at 52%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are "certainly political ideologies that are driving vaccine policy in certain areas of the country," which has a "clear downstream impact on vaccination levels," said Dr. Neil Maniar, a public health professor at Northeastern University. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over three-quarters of U.S. states, or 39, had vaccination rates for the MMR shot below the "Healthy People 2030" target rate of 95% during the 2023-2024 school year. That refers to the level needed to prevent community transmission of measles, a highly contagious and deadly virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The data means that &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/schoolvaxview/data/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;roughly 280,000 school children&lt;/a&gt; were unvaccinated and unprotected against measles during that school year, according to the CDC. MMR vaccination rates among kindergarteners vary across states, ranging from a low of around 80% in Idaho to a high of more than 98% in West Virginia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moss noted that clusters of unvaccinated people within a specific community increase the risk of disease outbreak. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's where you're going to get these larger outbreaks like we're seeing in Texas right now with measles," Moss said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A child who wasn't vaccinated died in the outbreak in rural West Texas, state officials said in late February, the first U.S. death from the disease since 2015. The childhood vaccination rate for measles in Gaines County, the epicenter of the current outbreak in Texas, is just below 82%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A second patient, an unvaccinated adult in New Mexico, &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/measles-new-mexico-resident-tests-positive-death-rcna195231" target="_blank"&gt;tested positive for measles after death&lt;/a&gt;, state officials said Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy last week said shots protect communities from measles, but emphasized that the decision to vaccinate "is a personal one." He also &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/03/06/health/kennedy-measles-texas-doctor-treatment/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;pushed unconventional treatment regimens&lt;/a&gt; for measles, including cod liver oil, which is rich in vitamin A. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-subtitle"&gt;&lt;a id="headline1"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Kennedy could target vaccine advisory panels&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy's HHS already appears to be targeting a key part of U.S. vaccine policy: external advisors to the government health agencies that approve shots and set recommendations for them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government postponed a meeting of vaccine advisors to the CDC and&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/fda-cancels-meeting-select-flu-strains-seasons-shots-rcna193931" target="_blank"&gt; a separate meeting of advisors&lt;/a&gt; to the Food and Drug Administration, the latter of which is crucial to determining the flu strains in next season's shots. It is unclear why the meetings were canceled or when they will be rescheduled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage-imageEmbed" id="ArticleBody-InlineImage-108087127" data-test="InlineImage"&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="InlineImage-imageEmbedCaption"&gt;FILE PHOTO: The headquarters of the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) is seen in Silver Spring, Maryland November 4, 2009. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="InlineImage-imageEmbedCredit"&gt;Jason Reed | Reuters&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;One "clear step" Kennedy can also take to undermine vaccinations is removing members of those advisory panels that shape the government's shot recommendations, including which jabs are covered at no cost by different types of insurance, according to Georgetown's Gostin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several reports have said Kennedy plans to replace members whom he perceives to have "conflicts of interest," though it is unclear how many people will be outed or when. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gostin called conflicts of interest one of Kennedy's "code words" for "simply purging hard working, experienced scientists from advisory committees and replacing them with those that are more skeptical of shots." All HHS agencies and their advisory panels have rigorous policies for conflicts of interest, and there have been no related issues for years, he noted. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy's shake-up of advisory committees could produce "bogus recommendations" that highlight the harms rather than the benefits of shots, according to Gostin. He said those recommendations could influence governors, legislatures and school boards in red states, which could adopt policies that reduce childhood immunizations and "create wide-open opt outs of shots." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those recommendations could also create greater distrust in the CDC and Trump administration among scientists and public health experts, including Gostin himself, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage-imageEmbed" id="ArticleBody-InlineImage-108108637" data-test="InlineImage"&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="InlineImage-imageEmbedCaption"&gt;Sherry Andrews prepares a MMR vaccine at the City of Lubbock Heath Department in Lubbock, Texas, U.S. Feb. 27, 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="InlineImage-imageEmbedCredit"&gt;Annie Rice | Reuters&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It will have a longer-term corrosive effect on the value of science in America, which is already under severe attack," he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy is also reviewing the childhood immunization schedule. Experts said that could lead to removing recommendations for certain vaccines or changing their suggested use from "routine" – when the default approach is to vaccinate – to more of an individual choice guided by discussions with a health-care provider. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hope is that officials on the state and local level influence policy or implement practices to drive higher vaccination rates, said Northeastern's Maniar. State and local governments may need to "expand the work they do" in some cases to "make up lost ground" and advocate for vaccinations, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-subtitle"&gt;&lt;a id="headline2"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Cherry-picking data&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy could also cherry-pick data, studies and any other information about vaccines that "create the misleading impression that shots aren't safe and cause severe side effects," according to Gostin. He said Kennedy could include them in official government announcements to undermine the public's faith in shots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the campaign trail, Kennedy said he wanted to "restore the transparency" around vaccine safety data and records that he accused HHS officials of hiding. Gostin called transparency another "code word" for "highlighting dubious scientific studies." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He added that Kennedy's wording suggests that the government's existing vaccine information is not transparent, when databases recording adverse events and immunization rates have long been fully open to the public. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage-imageEmbed" id="ArticleBody-InlineImage-106686395" data-test="InlineImage"&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="InlineImage-imageEmbedCaption"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="InlineImage-imageEmbedCredit"&gt;Antonio Perez | Chicago Tribune | Tribune News Service | Getty Images&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy is reportedly shelving promotions for a variety of shots, including a campaign touting seasonal flu jabs. He wanted the CDC's advertisements to promote the idea of "informed consent" in vaccine decision-making instead, STAT News &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/02/20/cdc-vaccine-promotions-rfk-jr-informed-consent/#:~:text=Kennedy%20Jr.,any%20drug%20they%20are%20prescribed." target="_blank"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; in February. That refers to giving patients important information, including possible risks or benefits of a medical treatment, such as adverse events associated with shots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts have said while informed consent is important, shifting the framing of advertisements for shots that the CDC has long recommended to focus more on the potential risks could undermine people's willingness to get vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When a parent exercises informed consent not to have their child immunized with measles, it certainly puts that child at risk, but it puts every child in that school with them at risk," Gostin said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy would need approval from Congress to change the existing legal liability protections in place for vaccine makers, but he could still undermine them in other ways, experts said. HHS' National Vaccine Injury Compensation Program currently pays patients injured by standard childhood vaccines and shields drugmakers from litigation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As HHS secretary, Kennedy can remove or add to the list of vaccines and injuries included and covered by that program, Michaud said. Any changes to the list could change some liability protections for vaccine makers, potentially spurring a wave of litigation over alleged injuries from the shots, he added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="ArticleBody-MobileAdhesion" class="MobileAdhesion-container" data-module="mps-slot"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 11:02:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxNMllpZVJlZG5IbTFYMWtlTVlxbDRsRDczODRXYjhZa3FIQm5hU0FNdDFwOGpVT0EtVi02WUxBa3VoQnZPb0VIQ2RUN19WV09pTTJpQ3V2OEpPdTBma0hTdzlOQUFxVEJnV3N5TTZQTkM4eFp1ckk2X1VrVnBaMUhyZVVfUDhPUGVEQ3pDUmlGYWVKVXN2Q291STQ4VVFERjJYWHNoS1pB0gGrAUFVX3lxTE1DZGNweHE2WFJGdXk3ZnZBd1B1WEpURUcyTzNOWU5zWHRmMTRmUThyWmotUHgwNVhzWTJXN2pOTFRyaDdMWFNxOGxScmJkTkJkazluUTJwSlU2d3NJWmdiNXhXZ0FVM0E2RVFpaWNGbGNheTdmTGhMLWRmSloyeTJyR2syZTdJdFhoRVB5aVRMRVNjbG1wakxxeHVHbE1GZ2ppcG0tNlJtRFUydw</guid></item><item><title>Expert reveals the BIGGEST mistake people on Ozempic are making - massively increasing side effect risk - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxOWlNGMzRpZHRYZ3FCLUY5d2Jhb2Z1enFGWFpnU19VLTJ1Vm1iSVM5WFVUYV9TYnVtaFdtMVpJM2Q2VzJwRFJ0SDk3WFNFUE90T0d4TE5BVHJwakdBQUxpQk5rX0VIODNJd1dnY3BUMTNncjh0cnFCTDVPcE1md2t3RklMSUNHTWM0cm5LYkFxWktaaUc1aGhQVUp1OUpKa2JTdU9ueVFwaEZCNnFlaXfSAbMBQVVfeXFMTXg2aFdIdFFMQ29NSXpHYkFBemxXS3R2TkxVRHExRVVsaTdkN2lLRlNueHR5T2JSRVVUdFVuSVhDRjFHMUFZZmpDdUpudmpFcEh2QnpIODI4RlZyMmc2ZXVaV3EzT3dweTRubkwyZGo1WnlDNXRrRjMyY3hZSnlqWFk0WlRBODdURngydmdHWWlRRHJLQm9udjExODhhT2hpTkxkYnlQOUVoYW4wWXRYcnRMd1U?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A GP has revealed the six biggest mistakes people make while taking revolutionary weight-loss jabs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sold under the brands Wegovy and Mounjaro, as well as the off-label prescriptions of &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-d6b7d080-fb79-11ef-a070-1f9934b25383"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; drug Ozempic, the injections have become an increasingly popular option for people needing, or wanting, to &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/weight_loss/index.html" id="mol-d6b8bae0-fb79-11ef-a070-1f9934b25383"&gt;lose weight&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At least half a million &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/nhs/index.html" id="mol-5e5593b0-f855-11ef-8279-ffcfdae8d660" class=""&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt; patients and some 15million in the US are now thought to be using the jabs, which can help patients shed up to 20 per cent of their body weight in just a handful of months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But family medic Dr Donald Grant, from The Independent Pharmacy, said there were a number of errors people could make when starting out on the drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He warned that not only could these mistakes derail patients' weight-loss plans, some could even land them in A&amp;amp;E.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One of the most common — and serious — mistakes slimmers make is taking too much too soon, Dr Grant said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Both Wegovy and Mounjaro patients typically start on weekly 0.25mg jabs for four weeks, before increasing the dosage in stages from there. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While Dr Grant said patients may be tempted to up the dosage under the logic of 'more is better', this was false and potentially dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Semaglutide and tirzepatide — the powerful ingredients behind Wegovy, Ozempic and Mounjaro — have long been hailed a monumental breakthrough in the war on obesity and type 2 diabetes  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Contrary to popular belief, taking a higher dosage of the medication does not necessarily mean quicker results,' he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Our bodies need time to adjust to the treatment, so beginning on a high dosage could greatly increase the intensity of symptoms such as headaches, fatigue and nausea.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It could also increase the risk of rarer but more serious side effects like pancreatitis, a serious inflammation of the pancreas, and hypoglycaemia, a medical term for potentially dangerous blood sugar levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Grant added: 'I advise anyone on the treatment to discuss their dosage with a licensed health professional, rather than increasing the strength on their own accord.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another mistake was taking a weight-loss drug without actually acquiring it legitimately. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors have long warned they are seeing increasing numbers of slim women needing emergency treatment after obtaining the drug from chemists by lying about their weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was recently revealed that a 16-year-old girl &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/news/article-14457245/high-street-Boots-selling-weight-loss-jabs-children-teens.html"&gt;was able to buy Wegovy&lt;/a&gt; at Boots as part of an undercover sting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Grant said patients obtaining the drug from unreliable sources were taking additional risks.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'A common mistake that’s unfortunately being seen more and more is the amount of Brits obtaining these treatments through illegal measures - such as fraudulent sites or social media,' he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This can be an incredibly dangerous process as these organisations aren’t regulated with the same level of health safety protocols as proper healthcare establishments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'As a result, they could have foreign ingredients that could impact well-being.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Under official guidelines, only patients who have a body mass index (BMI) of over 35, or between 30 to 34.9 and meet the criteria for referral to a specialist weight management service, should be prescribed Wegovy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mounjaro has similar restrictions under NHS guidelines, with patients needing a BMI of more than 35 and at least one obesity-related health problem. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ozempic, on the other hand, is a diabetes medication but has been prescribed for weight loss 'off label'. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Grant said another mistake patients frequently make is feeling they can 'eat whatever they like' while on the medications. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Sadly, this is simply not the case and eating too many processed or sugary foods could cause blood sugar spikes, leading to increased appetite, bloating and fatigue,' he added.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'People should prioritise a well-balanced diet of proteins, fibre and other key nutrients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Although these treatments impact appetite, it’s still important to draw up a dietary plan that includes all the key foods.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a similar vein, Dr Grant said patients should also ensure they stay hydrated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Not doing so risks increasing the intensity of side effects, which can be difficult to manage - particularly for people still adjusting to the medication,' he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Water is also a key component for weight loss, not drinking enough can slow down progress and lead to dehydration.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;On side effects in general, Dr Grant also said it was critical that patients don't ignore them and inform their medical team of any issues so they can help. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'By keeping your GP up to date with any symptoms, they can provide tailored advice and guidance to lessen side effects and restore a better quality of life,' he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Common side effects include diarrhoea, nausea and fatigue, while less common symptoms range from shortness of breath to abdominal pain.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Wegovy and Ozempic work by triggering the body to produce a hormone called GLP-1 that is released naturally from the intestines after meals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'If any side effects persist, I strongly recommend seeking medical attention for further advice.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Grant's final tip was to ensure you don't skip doses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This can halt progress, stopping people from reaching their weight loss goals, as it can increase appetite and reduce the overall effectiveness of the treatment,' he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Therefore, before beginning any weight loss medication, be sure to consider the long-term costs and reordering processes.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Weight loss jabs work by mimicking a natural hormone that makes people feel full, reducing their appetite and helping people lose weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While hailed as a breakthrough in tackling obesity, the drugs have also been shown to significantly reduce the risk of heart attacks and strokes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, side effects are wide-ranging, from nausea and abdominal pain to severe digestive issues, bone pain and a potential higher risk of &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14317293/ozempic-weight-jabs-skinny-deadly-cancer-diagnosis.html"&gt;thyroid cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A Mail on Sunday &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14300503/Hundreds-hospital-fat-jabs-numbers-surge.html"&gt;investigation &lt;/a&gt;earlier this year also revealed almost 400 patients had been hospitalised — some with life-threatening complications — since the rollout of the jabs in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 10:45:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxOWlNGMzRpZHRYZ3FCLUY5d2Jhb2Z1enFGWFpnU19VLTJ1Vm1iSVM5WFVUYV9TYnVtaFdtMVpJM2Q2VzJwRFJ0SDk3WFNFUE90T0d4TE5BVHJwakdBQUxpQk5rX0VIODNJd1dnY3BUMTNncjh0cnFCTDVPcE1md2t3RklMSUNHTWM0cm5LYkFxWktaaUc1aGhQVUp1OUpKa2JTdU9ueVFwaEZCNnFlaXfSAbMBQVVfeXFMTXg2aFdIdFFMQ29NSXpHYkFBemxXS3R2TkxVRHExRVVsaTdkN2lLRlNueHR5T2JSRVVUdFVuSVhDRjFHMUFZZmpDdUpudmpFcEh2QnpIODI4RlZyMmc2ZXVaV3EzT3dweTRubkwyZGo1WnlDNXRrRjMyY3hZSnlqWFk0WlRBODdURngydmdHWWlRRHJLQm9udjExODhhT2hpTkxkYnlQOUVoYW4wWXRYcnRMd1U</guid></item><item><title>10 foods to pair with almonds to boost brain health - The Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikgJBVV95cUxPSlRYUDhWbEpJUGJLTDNrSk85OHZ6SlZvRFh4bjduZng3Ql9hVTZGbnZBS3FKMjR3TmVmU08xaHpNQWV4R0F1SXcxU2lDblVrLWh3YVdONTFHMGZRZzY1WGdjUVlBOWlIcjEtMFVHbmZlcEpDTFdMcVZrODNPMmdoZTdIWUc2eG9oYnBtOHZnWS1LRHNVOHBPaE1lSlNaY0tHaGM4dE5ZeGtMeGJLbE1TR2VLMnAyVnRpQTBBZTkxRnBQMlNtZjM5SGR6aHpvZ3BIeFdtb0p6RDFvLXBNWDc2TDZGSlFtVW9PbHNzVVZVdC1ndGp6Yzl2WE9jS1ZKUHBUQkJXSkRxT3ViaTVlck1pdlN3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;amp-story-grid-layer class="recircular" id="rcontent" template="vertical"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt;&lt;p class="mid-heading"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;You may also like&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc3 pa"&gt;10 ayurvedic drinks to reduce belly fat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc5 pa"&gt;8 fittest Indian cricketers in ICC Champ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgJBVV95cUxPSlRYUDhWbEpJUGJLTDNrSk85OHZ6SlZvRFh4bjduZng3Ql9hVTZGbnZBS3FKMjR3TmVmU08xaHpNQWV4R0F1SXcxU2lDblVrLWh3YVdONTFHMGZRZzY1WGdjUVlBOWlIcjEtMFVHbmZlcEpDTFdMcVZrODNPMmdoZTdIWUc2eG9oYnBtOHZnWS1LRHNVOHBPaE1lSlNaY0tHaGM4dE5ZeGtMeGJLbE1TR2VLMnAyVnRpQTBBZTkxRnBQMlNtZjM5SGR6aHpvZ3BIeFdtb0p6RDFvLXBNWDc2TDZGSlFtVW9PbHNzVVZVdC1ndGp6Yzl2WE9jS1ZKUHBUQkJXSkRxT3ViaTVlck1pdlN3</guid></item><item><title>Excessive phone and screen use tied to manic symptoms for one group, study finds - AOL</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMid0FVX3lxTFBfU2ZVYWNYa2xPcXotY2c0N18xcDV4cFBTMGhad0xGSG1zbk9kQlVlQTYzWDcweU1BWTdRem90MjRsTFplOEw0aFBuUmZ0VFpYNWs2VHViTzVYb1VrVXBCeV93cHI1eVhUazlKTWhHMTJyQlI0QzhF?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent study from the University of California, San Francisco, indicates that pre-teens with greater exposure to certain types of tech use could be at a higher risk of developing &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/education/adhd" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:manic symptoms.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;manic symptoms.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Published in the journal Social Psychiatry and Psychiatric Epidemiology, the study analyzed a nationwide sample of 9,243 children in the U.S. between 10 and 11 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Young people who spent more time engaged with social media, texting, videos and video games were more likely to have "inflated self-esteem, decreased need for sleep, distractibility, rapid speech, racing thoughts and impulsivity — behaviors characteristic of manic episodes, a key feature of &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/mental-health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:bipolar-spectrum disorders;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;bipolar-spectrum disorders&lt;/a&gt;," a press release noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/limit-3-hours-weekly-screen-time-kids-positive-effect-behavior-mental-health-study" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Limit Of 3 Hours Of Weekly Screen Time For Kids Has ‘Positive Effect’ On Behavior, Mental Health: Study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Limit Of 3 Hours Of Weekly Screen Time For Kids Has ‘Positive Effect’ On Behavior, Mental Health: Study&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This study underscores the importance of cultivating healthy screen use habits early," said co-author Kyle Ganson, PhD, assistant professor at the University of Toronto’s Factor-Inwentash Faculty of Social Work, in the release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Future research can help us better understand the behaviors and brain mechanisms linking screen use with manic symptoms to help inform prevention and intervention efforts."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS/mvaj7wvj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read On The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Read On The Fox News App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Excessive use of social media, texting, videos and video games by young people of certain ages was linked to a higher risk of mental health issues in a recent study.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;To mark the Global Day of Unplugging (March 7), Verizon hosted its first-ever "digital wellness summit" in New York City to share insights with the public about the &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/tech" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:safe use of technology;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;safe use of technology&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sowmyanarayan Sampath, CEO of Verizon Consumer Group, discussed the importance of setting digital boundaries, &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/healthy-living/childrens-health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:especially for kids.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;especially for kids.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/wellness" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Digital wellness;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Digital wellness&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; should be for every age, but really we need a new blueprint as parents, because we've never been through this before," Sampath said at the event in the Big Apple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This digital age is new to us all. There's no time in history we can reclaim how we handle that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a separate interview with Fox News Digital, Sampath shared compelling statistics on phone use, including findings from Verizon’s 2024 Consumer Connections Report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kids and teenagers use social media for four to five hours a day and receive between 250 and 275 notifications daily, the report revealed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Sowmyanarayan Sampath, CEO of Verizon Consumer Group, at right, is shown at the Verizon Digital Wellness Summit on March 6, 2025, in New York City. At left, actor and talk-show host Drew Barrymore.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kids were also found to touch and pick up their phones about 150 times per day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A quarter of these events occurred during &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/education/high-school" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:school hours;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;school hours&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is what sparked us to think there is a healthier relationship people can have," Sampath said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Keneisha Sinclair-McBride, attending psychologist at Boston's Children's Hospital and an assistant professor at Harvard Medical School, also spoke at a panel at the Verizon event and in a follow-up interview with Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The expert noted that kids spending "hours and hours" of their free time on their phones can be "problematic," especially considering the possibility that they'll experience threats such as cyberbullying and hate speech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle/kids-smartphones-how-young-too-young-experts-recommendations" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Kids And Smartphones: How Young Is Too Young? Experts Reveal Important Recommendations;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Kids And Smartphones: How Young Is Too Young? Experts Reveal Important Recommendations&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We know that these are associated with depressive symptoms and other mental health concerns," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We also know that there's so much positive for social connection, learning and fun, so we have to balance those two things."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She pointed out that &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/tech/technologies/apps" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:some social media apps;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;some social media apps&lt;/a&gt; are "designed to keep you stuck" through the loop of an algorithm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Socializing with others can have a positive impact on kids’ moods, experts suggested.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This problematic use can lead to poorer functioning at work or school and can &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/sleep-disorders" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:negatively impact sleep;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;negatively impact sleep&lt;/a&gt; and relationships, Sinclair-McBride warned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Are they able to live their life and do the things they want and need to do in a positive way? If there are concerns in any of those areas, that's usually a sign of something needing to be reassessed."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sinclair-McBride encouraged parents and grandparents to learn about the apps children are using and teach them to be "critical consumers" of content by training them to detect scams, misinformation or &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/tech/artificial-intelligence" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:AI-generated content;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;AI-generated content&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Slowing down and being more thoughtful and mindful about what you're doing is, I think, the first step in modeling that &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/lifestyle/parenting" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:as a parent;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;as a parent&lt;/a&gt;," she told Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/brain-rot-science-behind-too-much-scrolling-does-brains" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:What Is ‘Brain Rot’? The Science Behind What Too Much Scrolling Does To Our Brains;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Is ‘Brain Rot’? The Science Behind What Too Much Scrolling Does To Our Brains&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Parents can also look at their own use and [ask], ‘Am I on my phone too much? Am I too addicted to social media?’"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CEO also urged adults to set boundaries involving phone use, whether it's limited to certain spaces in the home or specific times of day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;"When you do things in real life, you feel happier."&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sampath shared simple advice for families to ensure a healthy balance between tech use and unplugged activities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Go for a movie. &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/fitness-and-wellbeing" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Go for a walk.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Go for a walk.&lt;/a&gt; Go and play a game or just hang out with friends. Or just hang out with your family in your kitchen and do fun things," he suggested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think kids are going to have to be comfortable sometimes doing nothing … reading a book, just hanging out," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Sign Up For Our Health Newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Click Here To Sign Up For Our Health Newsletter&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Kids are going to have to get way more comfortable doing that – that's part of a healthy boundary, and it's part of a good relationship with technology."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sampath also encouraged Americans to take advantage of living in areas with "some of the best weather" and "the best natural sights in the world" by exploring &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/great-outdoors" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:outdoor spaces;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;outdoor spaces&lt;/a&gt; and moving more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;"The time that people spend with digital technology needs to be balanced with real-life stuff, whether it's sports, the arts, creative activities, reading or actual hands-on, tangible things."&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You want to create space to have fun. You want to create space to play. You want to create space to have physical activity, to have real relationships," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It has long-term benefits on &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/mental-health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:mental health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;mental health&lt;/a&gt; … When you do things in real life, you feel happier."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:For more Health articles, visit ;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;For more Health articles, visit &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foxnews.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:foxnews.com/health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;foxnews.com/health&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sinclair-McBride echoed the advice to get outside and "touch grass."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The time that people spend with digital technology needs to be balanced with real-life stuff, whether it's sports, the arts, creative activities, reading or actual hands-on, tangible things," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Experts advocated for kids to be given more time to explore tangible activities and hobbies instead of defaulting to digital.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think people are in this mindset that this generation only wants to do digital, digital, digital," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They still like other stuff, too. We have to give them options, space and freedom to have that time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Original article source:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/excessive-phone-screen-use-tied-manic-symptoms-group-study" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Excessive phone and screen use tied to manic symptoms for one group, study finds;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Excessive phone and screen use tied to manic symptoms for one group, study finds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 21:44:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTFBfU2ZVYWNYa2xPcXotY2c0N18xcDV4cFBTMGhad0xGSG1zbk9kQlVlQTYzWDcweU1BWTdRem90MjRsTFplOEw0aFBuUmZ0VFpYNWs2VHViTzVYb1VrVXBCeV93cHI1eVhUazlKTWhHMTJyQlI0QzhF</guid></item></channel></rss>