<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>患有狂犬病的器官捐赠者移植后肾脏受者死亡-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/06/health/rabies-death-skunk-kidney-transplant.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 14:37:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNQzZrR3dBTGhlRzdHTlhETUxUYnlCNjlHY1RtSlZTcnJ1OFlXaVdKQTVjVk9oVld3TXRIUlhsMFBPMVBJSldxTHcwc2VmcC0wbFh3Z0JwY3VSVXd1bXY0ZTdKc2R3N2J3OGdBNU85N1pIM1FwT0VabndORjJDcHBuUnB1X0lyam82YUtB</guid></item><item><title>我已经在后脑勺里藏了一个石灰大小的洞30年了- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/cancer-hole-head-neck-pain_n_68fd1945e4b011e80886928d</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Isn’t it amazing how old trauma like this can still present itself all these years later?” Jade said as she tapped hair-thin needles into pressure points along my shoulder blades. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;What does she mean, old trauma? I didn’t ask about that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;At 38, a neurologist told me I have degenerative disc disease in my cervical spine that is so bad it looked like I spent years wrangling a jackhammer on a construction site. As a suburban mom and college professor, what could I have possibly done in life to contribute to this condition? Carry a growing baby in the björn and a toddler on my hip as I ran in and out of Target? Lug my entire office in a tote bag from class to class across campus? It has never been clear. So it made sense that the acupuncturist assumed all of my neck pain radiated from the bulging discs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;What I brought up with Jade, though, was my tumor site. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When I was in college,” I told her, “I had a malignant tumor removed from the base of my skull.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I had no idea,” Jade said with surprise. “Did you have physical therapy?” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“No, I didn’t. It was so long ago, and I was so young,” I explained. “The surgeon removed a chunk of my scalp and it wasn’t until 10 years later that I realized he had actually removed part of my occipital bone, too.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;She stood close behind me, giving me time and space to put two and two together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Is it possible that I have simultaneous issues causing my pain and discomfort?” I asked. “Could my decades-old surgery have anything to do with the chronic throbs I always feel on both sides of my neck?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jade sat me at the edge of the table and turned my head right, then down, then left as she ran the tip of her pointer finger along each side of my hanging head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood rushed into my cheeks. I fumbled for an answer to her unexpected question. Hearing no audible objection from me, Jade tenderly parted my hair. Her thumbs pushed inside the lime-sized hole in my head, precisely tracing the suboccipital muscles to see where they had reattached themselves after my surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;This is the photo that the author submitted to accompany her melanoma community profile. It was the first time she ever photographed her scar.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Courtesy of Jennifer Young"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Courtesy of Jennifer Young&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who was the last person to ask to see my flawed scalp? I shifted on the table. It was probably my surgical oncologist. Who even knows that skin graft is there? My family, of course, but who else? My hairdresser? She is probably the only one. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Engrossed by the sea foam color sunlit on the wavy glass of the window, I sat transfixed. The soft spa sounds of lapping waves and sea birds chirping circulated in the room as I half listened to Jade speak about the physical trauma to my head and neck and the surgical scar that has now been part of my body for more than half my life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It isn’t until we uncover old trauma like this and begin to treat it that we can truly heal,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Jade was clearly referring to my physical body, her words synonymously triggered thoughts about something else too — the scars she can’t see on the inside. It has finally dawned on me that, even after continuously interacting with the world and understanding how it has shaped me, I never truly realized that surviving cancer as a young adult could still have an enormous impact on my life decades later. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is it possible for people to not realize how much previous traumas affect them? &lt;a href="https://www.thenationalcouncil.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Trauma-infographic.pdf" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="According to the National Council for Mental Wellbeing" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68fd1945e4b011e80886928d" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.thenationalcouncil.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Trauma-infographic.pdf" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;According to the National Council for Mental Wellbeing&lt;/a&gt;, 70% of adults in the U.S. have experienced some type of traumatic event at least once in their lives. That’s 235.1 million people. Trauma, then, is more universal than we probably realize. And while some people do not remember traumatic or painful experiences from the past at all, many others work to understand the potential effects on their lives. But do these attempts to understand what they’ve been through automatically translate into true healing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In spite of these efforts, emotions and thoughts we ignore or push down can still manifest physically, sometimes as tension, fatigue, or even illness. In other words, “your body expresses what your mind suppresses,” says &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/loroxburgh/reel/C7znvUzSqP7/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Lauren Roxburgh" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68fd1945e4b011e80886928d" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.instagram.com/loroxburgh/reel/C7znvUzSqP7/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;Lauren Roxburgh&lt;/a&gt;, international body alignment expert and wellness educator dubbed The Body Whisperer. And while repressed memories may not be readily accessible, they can sometimes resurface later in life, often triggered by specific cues or situations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sitting in my acupuncturist’s office, I was suddenly aware that I had been holding that broken girl deep inside of me for too long. I felt ready to reconnect with her, to write her back into my story. As the mother of four children around the same age as when I was diagnosed with cancer, I see pieces of her in them. Each of them are navigating all the challenges that come with new adulthood — finding your own identity, learning to navigate new and old relationships, and developing emotional and financial independence. All of that was happening for me back then, too. How did I manage a cancer diagnosis on top of everything else? How could the 19-year-old me have juggled those balls and not have expected one to drop? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;The author and her husband, age 19, just a few weeks before her biopsy.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Courtesy of Jennifer Young"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Courtesy of Jennifer Young&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A rush of memories released as Jade carefully pushed the slender points of filiform into the narrows of my neck. I thought back to my 19-year-old self and realized she and I still have a lot in common. She had to borrow wisps of hair from behind her ears to bobby pin over the bald spot on the back of her head every time she twisted up her hair. I still do that. She had to carefully cover the pockmarks on her shoulders from the vaccine shots with just-long-enough capped sleeves. I do that, too. She always yanked at her swimsuit to cover the square skin graft scar on her left butt cheek. Guess what? It still shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;But how did it never occur to me until this moment that the emotional trauma I endured as a young adult was even bigger and brighter than every blemish on my body? And while I am grateful to now have nurturing practitioners to help ease my physical pain, I realized that every time I worked to cover up these imperfections so that no one can see them, I stashed those old painful feelings beneath metal hairpins and bathing suit bottoms at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Desperate to put as much space as possible between my trauma and the rest of my life, I thought I had to erase that chapter entirely. How would it feel if instead I paid closer attention to the cues my body has been giving me and worked to acknowledge that heartbreak from long ago?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although today many people are better at recognizing the emotional and psychological impacts of trauma like cancer has, I believe there are many others like me who never gave themselves that grace. Psychiatrist and author &lt;a href="https://www.besselvanderkolk.com/resources/the-body-keeps-the-score" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Bessel Van Der Kolk, M.D." data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68fd1945e4b011e80886928d" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.besselvanderkolk.com/resources/the-body-keeps-the-score" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;Bessel Van Der Kolk, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, underscores this notion in his bestselling book “The Body Keeps the Score”: “... trauma almost invariably involves not being seen, not being mirrored, and not being taken into account.” Is releasing these trapped emotions the key to restoring balance and well-being? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, it seems like a no-brainer that missing bone from the back of my head was one likely cause of upper body pain for all of these years. But having my very own ah-ha moment in the least expected time and place is not lost on me, and what Jade has been saying gets through: A textbook understanding of trauma is not enough. True healing will only come if I accept every scar and allow each version of myself to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;My physical wounds healed long ago, of course, but I now understand that scars — both physical and emotional — are stories our bodies carry, even when we’d prefer them to stay untold. Old traumas heal, it seems, not when we hide our scars, but when we finally let them speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since that moment at my acupuncturist’s office, I’ve started unpacking this chapter more intentionally — reflecting on it, writing about it, and having honest conversations I used to avoid. It’s helped. I even worked up the courage to submit a survivor profile to a melanoma community on Instagram — including a photo that showed the scar on the back of my head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;I almost hit delete a dozen times! But I didn’t, and the multitude of likes and messages I received connected me to others whose lives had been touched by cancer — and, unexpectedly, it felt like that 19-year-old version of me was connected to them too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Healing isn’t about going back; it’s about bringing every part of myself forward. And for the first time in a long time, that feels possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;The author and her husband married after she reached five years in remission. They have four children.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Courtesy of Jennifer Young"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Courtesy of Jennifer Young&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jennifer Young, a long-term melanoma survivor, is currently working on a coming-of-age memoir about love, illness, and the decades-long journey to reclaim who she was. She’s written for Coping Magazine, Business Insider, and Elephants and Tea, among others. A writing professor, she teaches students how to find their voice on the page and serves as faculty adviser for the Oncology Society. She lives in New York with her husband, their four children, and a 100-pound Golden Retriever who thinks he still fits in their laps. Visit&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://jenniferyoung.net/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="jenniferyoung.net" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68fd1945e4b011e80886928d" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="http://jenniferyoung.net/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;jenniferyoung.net&lt;/a&gt; or follow her on Instagram &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/jennifer_young_writer/?hl=en" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="@jennifer_young_writer" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68fd1945e4b011e80886928d" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.instagram.com/jennifer_young_writer/?hl=en" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;@jennifer_young_writer&lt;/a&gt; for more.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Do you have a compelling personal story you’d like to see published on HuffPost? Find out what we’re looking for &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/static/how-to-pitch-huffpost" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="here" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68fd1945e4b011e80886928d" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/static/how-to-pitch-huffpost" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="mailto:pitch@huffpost.com" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="send us a pitch at pitch@huffpost.com." data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68fd1945e4b011e80886928d" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="mailto:pitch@huffpost.com" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;send us a pitch at pitch@huffpost.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 13:58:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxNRHFuMEU1dy1HUmhUQkU3c1JQTDhrUzhTS2FXTHl1LUJINmkxTTlUSzVxdUZrTEtwYmJIc0VMZWJwNm4wWlVSWUJXRGotVExQb2JPUXZXaWJ5QVhWUExxX1haYl8xY0E0OG0yWXJoZm1tVi10UnFtNGgyc0U5YnluVjlWcDdLZXREVXZCedIBkgFBVV95cUxORHNaMjZydVY5RDQ3MnZOd3c5czU4bi1uZUhZNE03dDZkWlZLR2lIYlJlZGxYOVBOTzdKeU4wLWJSakVDTFFZSHFOeW9reEs3NzFLLXJFeDNZZ0FmWEVtOUl0TEU4TWxlNWNydC1UNzBBTGhBbzNNUUpaQ1B3NEFMdk1GRnZkS0pmOXl5RVNlV0FHQQ</guid></item><item><title>在RFK Jr.的领导下，疾病预防控制中心为反疫苗运动提供了扩音器-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/06/cdc-acip-anti-vaccine-rhetoric/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DZ4Y2POOUFDI5NZLOBMPXWXP4I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;ATLANTA — For decades, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has fought attempts by the anti-vaccine movement to sow doubts in the safety and efficacy of the shots that marked a triumph of public health. This week, the agency instead provided a powerful platform for the cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:32:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxOS28teDI1TzlTbW1UNG1RenBJQUoxT21naExIcnRyTFQxeDVEaHJCcExTd1l4Y21lam14Sm9VRFhnc0duOUJxUDk3ampyaGk3eFpoQWpjUDY4Y0hPekV5WlNia3BOM2xmRkRpMUlpcW1ENVlzQ2lPQUlmV09fWXJTMlQyem9GVnc</guid></item><item><title>医学谜团：下巴剧烈疼痛。然后她的脸在眼前开始“变形”。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/06/medical-mysteries-jaw-popping/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="IYMR4BTAK5BEFNVXUYQH3RLYQQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In the spring of her senior year at college, Annie Sedoric woke up with jaw pain. It was March 2020, and there was a lot to worry about at the start of the covid pandemic, so she tried to ignore the pain, even as it grew worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:32:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxPWnJKUTBGdDB2TXdDa3hWZDBSdGt1aGZQU1N6UlhiU1BjZFdOZ1B4T3pTRTVsSkFidGU0VzBoZ3ZiS2ZIcGo4V0d2QWp0SjhjOS1BRGFmOTNVcGJPUnA0NEp5Q2dDcEFGVWNURFlCRHgzZm9TWjgwVlhMeEhXd0pDQm5HRjYydw</guid></item><item><title>忘记褪黑激素：从NASA启发的研究中诞生的时差疗法，更快地重置您的身体-印度国防评论</title><link>https://indiandefencereview.com/forget-melatonin-the-jet-lag-cure-born-from-nasa-inspired-research-that-resets-your-body-faster/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-entry-content"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an era of hypermobility, where business meetings in Berlin follow red-eyes from Boston and leisure travelers chase sunsets across hemispheres, &lt;strong&gt;jet lag remains a stubborn adversary&lt;/strong&gt;. Despite decades of research and a booming wellness industry promising quick fixes, the human body continues to resist the tyranny of time zone shifts.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Jet lag isn’t just a minor inconvenience—it’s a physiological &lt;strong&gt;tug-of-war&lt;/strong&gt; between your internal clock and the external world. The result? Days of &lt;strong&gt;fatigue&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;insomnia&lt;/strong&gt;,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/this-popular-yogurt-should-be-avoided-according-to-this-expert/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="70829" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;digestive issues&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;cognitive fog&lt;/strong&gt; that can derail even the most meticulously planned itinerary. And as global travel rebounds post-pandemic, the urgency to understand and mitigate jet lag has never been greater.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;What makes jet lag so insidious is its unpredictability. Two travelers on the same flight can experience vastly different symptoms. Age, chronotype, direction of travel, and even genetics play a role. Yet, the core conflict remains universal: our circadian rhythms, finely tuned to the &lt;strong&gt;24-hour cycle of light&lt;/strong&gt; and dark, don’t take kindly to abrupt changes.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Now, a growing body of research is shedding new light on how to outsmart this biological inertia. From strategic light exposure to pre-flight sleep adjustments, scientists are uncovering practical, evidence-based strategies that could finally offer weary travelers a fighting chance.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Resetting the Clock: Light as the Master Regulator&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The single most powerful tool in the jet lag arsenal? Light. Exposure to natural light is the primary cue that synchronizes our internal clocks with the external environment. Morning sunlight can help advance the circadian rhythm, making it easier to adjust to eastward travel, while evening light can delay it for westward shifts. The &lt;a href="https://www.sleepfoundation.org/jet-lag" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Sleep Foundation&lt;/a&gt; highlights light exposure as one of the most effective ways to reset your body clock.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Apps like Timeshifter, developed with input from NASA scientists, use this principle to create personalized jet lag plans. They recommend when to seek or avoid light, &lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/losing-attention-span-4-science-backed-habits-help-get-back/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="92798" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;caffeine&lt;/a&gt;, and sleep based on your itinerary and sleep patterns. While not a cure-all, these tools represent a leap forward from the days of blindly popping melatonin and hoping for the best.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For travelers without access to such apps, the rule of thumb is simple: get outside. Even 20–30 minutes of natural light exposure in the morning can accelerate adaptation, especially when paired with light exercise like walking.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Sleep Strategically, Not Spontaneously&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;One of the most common mistakes travelers make is trying to “power through” jet lag by staying awake until local bedtime. The intention is right, but the execution often backfires. Sleep deprivation can intensify symptoms and make it harder to adjust.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Experts recommend gradually shifting your &lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/to-sleep-better-science-recommends-doing-this-1-2-hours-before-bed-and-its-surprisingly-simple/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="87863" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;sleep schedule &lt;/a&gt;before departure. If you’re flying east, try going to bed and waking up an hour earlier each day for a few days before your flight. For westward travel, do the opposite. The &lt;a href="https://wwwnc.cdc.gov/travel/page/jet-lag" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC)&lt;/a&gt; supports this approach as a proactive way to reduce jet lag.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt="Tourist With A Suitcase Sleeping At Boarding Gate Waiting For His Delayed Flight" class="wp-image-98134" data-lazy-srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight.jpg 1000w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight-380x253.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight-520x346.jpg 520w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-lazy-src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight.jpg"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight.jpg" alt="Tourist With A Suitcase Sleeping At Boarding Gate Waiting For His Delayed Flight" class="wp-image-98134" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight.jpg 1000w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight-380x253.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight-520x346.jpg 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tourist With A Suitcase Sleeping At Boarding Gate Waiting For His Delayed Flight. Credit: Shutterstock&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Avoiding naps during the first day at your destination can also help, though short, strategic naps (20–30 minutes) may be beneficial if timed correctly. The key is consistency—your body needs clear signals to recalibrate.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Hydration, Caffeine, and the Myth of the Midnight Meal&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Air travel is notoriously dehydrating, and dehydration can intensify jet lag symptoms. The Aerospace Medical Association recommends drinking at least eight ounces of water for every hour in the air. Alcohol and caffeine, while tempting, should be used sparingly. Caffeine can help with alertness but should be avoided within six hours of your intended bedtime.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Emerging research suggests that meal timing may influence circadian rhythms. A study in Cell Reports found that mice who ate during their active phase adjusted more quickly to time zone changes. While human studies are ongoing, some experts suggest aligning meals with local time upon arrival to help reset the body’s internal clock.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;From Wearables to Chronomedicine&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As interest in circadian health grows, so too does the technology designed to support it. Wearables like the &lt;strong&gt;Oura Ring &lt;/strong&gt;and &lt;strong&gt;WHOOP strap&lt;/strong&gt; now track sleep stages and recovery metrics, offering insights into how travel affects the body. Meanwhile, pharmaceutical companies are exploring chronobiotic drugs—compounds that can shift circadian rhythms more precisely than melatonin.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The most promising frontier may lie in personalized medicine. Researchers are beginning to understand that circadian rhythms vary widely between individuals. Tailoring interventions to each person’s biological profile could redefine how we approach jet lag in the years ahead.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That future may still be on the horizon. For now, the best defense against jet lag remains a blend of science and strategy: plan ahead, seek the sun, hydrate well, and respect your body’s need for rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Indian Defence Review</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixwFBVV95cUxOcldwcjJwSEFxMklWRHpRemJfZkE1Um9aX3pEMDdrenA5Z0VJbkEtRlExZUt6ZXAtaV9qdHFCRmRzU29rZFhhSWIyYTVVT2lacmw1UTZUZ0swOFRnMUc2dFlQcXhMSEU3ZHpXaTBERnR3RXhyM0J4Z2VLN2k4Q1ZFU0R3ei1CZTR5bzhqS242eXlQT1JJNmxEMUFnZW0ta1RZQnh2ajdtZ3p6T0J0dkZNMGI1RmI1X0Z1X2g0Y25fRlYxRGJkQ3RJ</guid></item><item><title>营养学家分享了11种有害新陈代谢的日常食物和饮料：精制谷物、植物油等|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/nutritionist-shares-11-everyday-foods-and-drinks-that-harm-your-metabolism-refined-grains-vegetable-oils-and-more-101764929472518.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/nutritionist-shares-11-everyday-foods-and-drinks-that-harm-your-metabolism-refined-grains-vegetable-oils-and-more-101764929472518.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Have you ever wondered why your energy drops in the afternoon or why you can’t lose those extra pounds? People don’t realise that their food choices can harm their metabolism. Think of your metabolism as an engine; it powers your body and controls how well you burn calories. When your metabolism works well, you feel energetic and strong. But some common foods can slow down metabolism quietly.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/05/550x309/_3eee26e2-6336-11e8-a998-12ee0acfa260_1764930241698.jpg" alt="When a person includes at least 4 to 5 servings of fruits and vegetables, it helps enhance digestion and increase metabolism, which leads to weight loss. (Adobe Stock)" title="When a person includes at least 4 to 5 servings of fruits and vegetables, it helps enhance digestion and increase metabolism, which leads to weight loss. (Adobe Stock)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/05/550x309/_3eee26e2-6336-11e8-a998-12ee0acfa260_1764930241698.jpg" alt="When a person includes at least 4 to 5 servings of fruits and vegetables, it helps enhance digestion and increase metabolism, which leads to weight loss. (Adobe Stock)" title="When a person includes at least 4 to 5 servings of fruits and vegetables, it helps enhance digestion and increase metabolism, which leads to weight loss. (Adobe Stock)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;When a person includes at least 4 to 5 servings of fruits and vegetables, it helps enhance digestion and increase metabolism, which leads to weight loss. (Adobe Stock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;What foods slow down your metabolism?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Siddhi Kripal, Consultant Nutritionist at Nutriiya, shares 11 common &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/hepatologist-shares-which-foods-drinks-you-should-restrict-completely-avoid-consume-to-reduce-fatty-liver-risk-indians-101762917862419.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="foods and drinks"&gt;foods and drinks&lt;/a&gt; that might be slowing you down, along with tips to boost your metabolism.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;1. Sugary beverages&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sugary drinks like soft drinks, packaged juices, and energy drinks may seem refreshing. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Still, they contain a lot of refined sugars that can spike your blood sugar levels, often leading to energy crashes and making you feel tired and sleepy.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;"Drinking these high-sugar beverages regularly can also make it harder for your body to use insulin, slowing your metabolism", nutritionist Siddhi Kripal tells &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.healthshots.com/healthy-eating/nutrition/artificial-sweeteners-and-their-effect-on-blood-sugar/" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Health Shots"&gt;Health Shots&lt;/a&gt;. Additionally, liquid calories don't fill you up, so you might end up eating more later. Instead of reaching for a sugary drink, try water, herbal tea, or flavoured water to keep your energy steady without a sugar rush.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;2. Refined grains&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do you enjoy the soft texture of white bread and the smooth feel of refined pasta? However, these refined grains do not provide the nutrients and fiber that your body needs. They digest too quickly, which can cause spikes in blood sugar and lead to tiredness and increased fat storage. Choosing whole grains can help keep your energy stable throughout the day and support a healthy metabolism.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;3. Instant or ready-to-eat foods&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is easy to grab instant noodles, chips, or frozen meals. However, these processed foods often have high levels of sodium, unhealthy fats, and preservatives. “These ingredients can cause inflammation and make it harder for your body to burn fat,” says the expert. Cooking simple meals from scratch, even when you’re busy, can make a big difference. The nutritionist cited how a client, a dad with three kids, started preparing healthy meals on weekends. He found that he felt more energetic, and his whole family enjoyed the benefits of fresh, home-cooked food.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;4. Low-protein breakfasts&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breakfast is a necessary time to start your &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/10-yoga-asanas-to-boost-metabolism-and-burn-belly-fat-yoga-expert-shares-a-20-minute-morning-routine-for-beginners-101764777445993.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="metabolism"&gt;metabolism&lt;/a&gt;. One common mistake people make is skipping protein in the morning. Without enough protein, your breakfast won't give you the energy you need for the day. "A sugary cereal or plain toast alone isn't enough. Instead, add eggs, Greek yoghurt, or a scoop of plant-based protein powder to your breakfast," says the nutrition expert. Eating protein regularly can help boost your metabolism by repairing muscles and increasing calorie burn throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;5. Refined vegetable oils&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have you checked your pantry lately? Oils are important for cooking, but many common oils, such as palm, sunflower, and corn oil, contain high levels of omega-6 fatty acids. "Overeating of these can lead to inflammation, which can hurt your metabolism", says the expert. Instead, use heart-healthy oils like olive or &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/gallbladder-removal-diet-nutritionist-6-simple-food-swaps-diarrhea-bloating-fatty-liver-coconut-oil-instead-of-canola-101755143338007.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="coconut oil"&gt;coconut oil&lt;/a&gt;, which are better for you and can help your metabolism work well.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;6. Caffeine overload&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coffee lovers enjoy caffeine for its ability to get them started in the morning; however, drinking too much caffeine can be harmful. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;"At the same time, a moderate amount can give your metabolism a short-term boost, too much caffeine increases cortisol levels, the stress hormone", says the nutritionist.&lt;/span&gt; This can lead to fat storage, especially around the belly. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;It is important to keep your caffeine intake moderate and avoid drinking coffee late in the day, as it can disrupt sleep and affect a healthy metabolism.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;7. Gluten from modern wheat&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Modern wheat has changed and now contains 3 to 4 times more gluten than older varieties. This excess gluten can cause digestive problems, such as bloating, which may slow your metabolism. “If you often have stomach issues, consider replacing modern wheat with gluten-free options like quinoa, millets, or brown rice,” says Kripal. You may notice more energy after making this dietary change.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;8. Low water intake&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hydration is often overlooked in nutrition. Even mild dehydration can lower your metabolism by 2-3%. Water is essential for quenching thirst and for almost every metabolic process in the body. “Aim to drink 8-10 glasses of water each day,” shares Kripal. You can also include hydrating foods and drinks, such as coconut water, herbal teas, and homemade soups, to stay hydrated.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;9. Alcohol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social drinks can make gatherings more enjoyable, but drinking alcohol, especially beer and sugary cocktails, can slow down your metabolism. When alcohol enters your body, your liver focuses on breaking it down, which temporarily stops fat from burning. "Alcohol also dehydrates you and affects the hormones that help regulate your metabolism", said the expert. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;It is important to drink in moderation, try to have drinks less often, and look for non-alcoholic options to stay upbeat without hurting your metabolic health.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;10. Low-fiber diet&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fiber is important for your digestive health and helps your metabolism. Eating a low-fiber diet can make you feel tired and affect how well you digest food. “Try to include fiber-rich foods such as fruits, &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe/everyday-mix-vegetable-recipe-for-a-nutritious-plate-helping-you-increase-daily-veggie-intake-without-any-extra-effort-101764746253895.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="vegetables"&gt;vegetables&lt;/a&gt;, beans, and whole grains in your meals,” says the nutritionist. Feel lighter and more energetic after eating more fiber, which helps keep blood sugar levels steady and supports effective fat breakdown.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;11. Excess non-vegetarian consumption&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eating protein is important for your metabolism, but eating too much non-vegetarian food, especially red or processed meats, can cause issues. “These foods often contain a lot of saturated fat and not enough fiber, which can slow digestion,” shares the expert. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;To support better digestive health and a more efficient metabolism, try balancing your meals with plant-based foods, salads, and lean proteins like steamed fish or chicken.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;(&lt;strong&gt;Note to readers:&lt;/strong&gt; This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:00:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwJBVV95cUxOa0VrM2ZaZkkydFdIancySW9YV2VCNG9sNjVyTzhPOHJFRVZLWkxqQXNfcnUxNlRvbGlZX3h6STg5c0lFSnZYd1lJYkJOSXJlZEpYSXNxdWN0bkFfcjRCUFVTNmFoMHRrWExjYTRTSVVWQzJzbms5WFFtRDlxMkFJTHRmY1RPbHVVUTBBdkhpWjQ5RnY1dXJnMXRUbVlGbWppT3k1NGVxR0wxbzhFUkNsS1JnOVZYSzlYN1hHWWNDUGNFdTZzaTFnY21yaHdWQWVzLVZZay1YU0tqVnNCRVRZdEx6UXBtWGstM1Bua0pDNWFxMjJUdmhQWHBNMlhkd2tVZkZhaUgxcG04RUtyS25B0gGUAkFVX3lxTFB6N3pIMEF0SWh0YXYwLWJiNXlpV0JJRWVkb19LQ21WMkJaM0NfZFRKODB3QlZESUhfdWlleVVWTm9ObzJpWVdEVEZLc2o4QVlHR0tSQnU0WXl6Ylo2cm91SzAtSENNb3A5MDBvZVB4MzJhNktRR0VsRWJROG5tSVJfSWR4ZHBWeklPR0g5MzY4d3dHb3hWWnRvTzlXU1p4M0lSQkdTY004YllNSTYyelpNc0Z0QVcwZ0NzWnJOUS1TUWJYb245a0wwZjdkeG02UG5UbDA1ZnhJdmdzR2xxQmhQQ3B5akVrcWxId3hYVHY0QjIwWXFLWGNhNXhBUzFMVUI4d1BNSG9aY2dkLU05b292aGRVMg</guid></item><item><title>我扮演了爱妻的角色。在紧闭的门背后，我丈夫的秘密正在摧毁我。- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/danakillion/husband-wife-alcoholism-sober-therapy?origin=web-hf</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-1
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="fast fashion" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139715228" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The deeper my husband got into boozing, the deeper I got into my own self-imposed bubble of silence. A loyal, loving wife doesn’t talk about her husband peeing in an alley or passing out in the middle of sex while still inside her. She doesn’t tell stories of turning away in bed, tears streaming because the sour stench of his drunken body is revolting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Or was that just part of &lt;em&gt;my&lt;/em&gt; loyalty pledge?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don’t remember a specific moment in my childhood that taught me to follow a code of silence. As the oldest of five, my responsibilities started young, and I thoroughly understood the expectation that I was to be the kid that gave no one any trouble.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We Midwesterners are not thought of as hotheaded, heart-on-our-sleeve types. Silence is simply understood as standard operating procedure. We aren’t brought up to expose ourselves or make ourselves vulnerable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We do. We are. We exist. We move on. We don’t talk about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To place yourself in the middle of any story is to be vain. To call attention to something that should be kept private is simply not done. Unmet needs? Everybody has them. Talking about it won’t change anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prevailing understanding around tough issues in polite society is to be quiet, at least where I was raised. But silence is also the expectation forced on all women. Be pretty and quiet and compliant and thoughtful. With an emphasis on quiet, please.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And I have been as guilty of silence as every other woman before me. In what I assumed was marital loyalty, I kept quiet about my husband’s alcoholism, rarely even questioning why I did so. I didn’t cover for him or make excuses. I didn’t have to lie because life — the part visible to the world outside our home — looked fine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A high-functioning drunk gets through life hiding it all. He’d tough it out through the hangover and go to work anyway. He’d compartmentalize his drinking into time slots so that outward appearances remain untouched. He’d rationalize that because he was still kicking ass on the job, he had it all under control. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I alone held the truth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I played the role a loving wife is supposed to play. She protects her family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking publicly about my husband’s flaws would be a betrayal, wouldn’t it? I thought so. But was my silence about him or me? I didn’t know then, and I don’t know now. But the silence, the silence I chose, languished inside me like something rotting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holding in. Holding back. Holding on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I paused on the sidewalk outside a Michigan Avenue high-rise and stared up at the carved stone arch that crested the double doors. Buses and taxis buzzed behind me, and pedestrians sidestepped me as I struggled with my &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/evelinamedina/which-human-emotion-are-you"&gt;emotions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had no reason to be nervous, yet my heart thumped in my chest as I gathered myself for the appointment I’d made. With a therapist. A therapist to help me navigate addiction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pulse racing, palms sweating, I looked up at the building and took several deep breaths. Why was &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; standing here on the concrete feeling like a shaky schoolgirl? I suppose I irrationally thought of his continued drinking as &lt;em&gt;my&lt;/em&gt; failure. I hadn’t found the exact right formula of love and concern that would get through to him. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although there had been stretches of time where I believed he’d turned a corner, it never lasted more than a few months. And now, many years in, after so many empty promises and broken dreams and returns to booze, it was abundantly clear his problem was too big for me to handle alone, so I’d opened a browser and scrolled Psychology Today looking for practitioners with a specialization in alcoholism. It was one step up from the Yellow Pages, but I wasn’t going to ask friends for a referral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So here I was staring up at a building in downtown Chicago, steeling myself to say aloud for the first time, “My husband is an alcoholic.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The therapist sat in her chair, notepad in hand, and asked, “What can I help you with?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“My husband is an alcoholic, and I don’t know how to get him to stop,” I choked out, tears already filling my eyes and constricting my throat. My body trembled as I sat, hands gripping my thighs. I had said it. For the first time, I had said it. Out loud. Now it was real. There could be no more rationalizing. No more minimizing or softening the label by thinking of him as a “heavy drinker” or “having a drinking problem.” He was a full-on alcoholic. A drunk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Have you suggested a support group? AA?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I laughed. Her question wasn’t intended as sarcasm, but all I could think was, “Honey, if a suggestion was all it took, I could add a Dr. prefix to my name and set out my own shingle.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We spent 45 minutes discussing the ways in which I had attempted to get him to his come-to-Jesus moment. Then as the session wrapped up, she told me she “normally worked with the alcoholic, not the family” and repeated her suggestion of a support group. Then she asked whether I thought he would do better with a male or female therapist if she were to provide a referral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But I didn’t want a referral for him. Who he saw was his damn business! I needed help navigating and understanding his problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was only years later that I realized she had never asked a single question about me. How &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; was doing. How &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; was coping. What support &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; might need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And in the ways of a woman only seeing part of her problem, my thoughts too were laser-focused on my husband’s issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was a lifetime away from realizing that a crisis was in my future too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Excerpted with permission from &lt;a href="https://u7061146.ct.sendgrid.net/ls/click?upn=4tNED-2FM8iDZJQyQ53jATUd1gOWGyyREHiaxJ1NU0Q9tjkxy0CFcmCH3nleILYEpNxjITXRmwJ-2BWLzgpCpuif2LgIOwt7x0HKb6h-2BI2eSnl6twK0kebeyNL4ccc5NkWtRhROoDa2HVbnAxgBKUtcO-2Fm80VnqTGr38yUrsd3s3WCgrWErymMzCtmV9lfOgezXfqN-2Fe7cfjTN3sjlepCm12OZ2nFzumlBEVhZrzaFOCVmdCDeSmdYL5zxx2v1zTL-2FgIb2K5g6AMaIjlcP270Yj5G2npY7gioXXmQHF-2BA6435vicwELjN-2BCFw3022h83el70gnti8O8IUMudmdrsm2TandHuPAzfEQoO1aQopHX69ELiyW7tirs32WZhy4C16fsLJD3idt51CDgCZ1j6LFI4k8g8SSBdtKyytei3EINNCZOYza9HCUDUbRW1px5dTOX8sFuvOjf7V4K5hMTOkR4R7Plxmz8U3CRQmb2o-2FW95TnwDPMehwt0fxywmoq2Pyc1AVV0F8ADc5WmifHhiG9qyBFbpUBnKS2XTgttdXX-2F2WgQFGmAAnv4-2BXGnXeTeEGgzAvWR66RI4w-2BxbTp-2BVVHfOrH13b1GzTosdsNf4CLZpdY5wdIIcgKFNuNdaeQbGQjA7y8gLXwBH9vx7C1zzjvZ-2FhLGAjZzVg-2BGCVc5eLIhghDBl0ibr6LtqxDdL-2BTO4WMGDEbwiAXRs8L3c1rXwFjMjmQ2akli99ROfsftAraVXvDo-3DOtlK_Ps5uOjyCpFslDeso1wdwvvUwnAohiFunuIxA7lzd9uSfz-2BDPamfPG9hlmc9Y0GgV3tEeJ9fFWPEYmnno7uhvujziORgEF3ErUy4fxfnhPtV-2BfSCeOsmK4Y35mqUxtZzK-2B4QIUKU-2Bl58LikAAvRdQDTzOxqgU4bGHNQfCtDXBqhG6XMF70jG2SLJ5BecYaEO9PnVOlCd-2FaTVRDywjta-2Foz-2F0LBAVEP87HhFrNNibB533LPWMwxwJ0TULJu2ic-2FJFHJZzWLJxuu-2BDOJ1zeHBgjXFnQpGhu434zo-2BGf3gEW24yJmGJsPzHALg-2Fqt1OXdN96skLUNzusDnr2KZkG84zN17ReZloN-2FXJVTYXV5yu2Y-2Bs-3D" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7981341" data-affiliate="true"&gt;“Where the Shadows Dance: He Got Sober. I Got Broken,”&lt;/a&gt; by author &lt;a href="https://u7061146.ct.sendgrid.net/ls/click?upn=4tNED-2FM8iDZJQyQ53jATUd1gOWGyyREHiaxJ1NU0Q9tjkxy0CFcmCH3nleILYEpNxjITXRmwJ-2BWLzgpCpuif2Hz6ETqvYy5yiq9z7e52RSFeElcFm1VlMI0otVL8dN2AAcKyPwXmsfgqlEQJG6Mwz1p9-2F1jBO0gD78Ud6cY78QzS1IgcvDYL9PeCwfdlylYt2x1WeazjgX-2BfHPRhodSLFAp-2B7oQYQ-2BEHSJhnKnnXxjyVH8bli1fllICcptbODcTGXzpokLBqASOus7W8WrqSOc5Cr-2FuTJGqCdHIud5Jx4ykLj7sv9cVPFbQpz19yvVbpuM217KulNXWzgvy5eCUJXUH-2FJXwXo5hvtyeSQqewiS-2FvXSj0Gtr0s3sUJGM1QldF8rjPL7AEtIl6g6p72tR1vmDLrH17eqwDc9TxT06fCKHXe2Wnh7bZrAG2uJe8PB1bvvDcONXxXsc5x405en5gx9KSC2UCnTyV6XNwbmRGmFMMuftSq63Iqw9cJCSclLRKsKAMf-2FwmLa7VnowRAOugD6wfUY6eeiNAsfOFRzDE1vf2UNfZ-2FXBKWTqDd-2FjkMrMklOosNB7hQNjgBIbLTIG1dxLMGoQwE7OIzFlHa8RF2l5ENUrl6Z7lN99L1B-2Bs6P1fPu2zqLpSMeNJJLNMBTg8kRsjnchUaQYk4fYfsbkGTBo488xeodhCZq7-2FXJCc4Dcv_mTr_Ps5uOjyCpFslDeso1wdwvvUwnAohiFunuIxA7lzd9uSfz-2BDPamfPG9hlmc9Y0GgV3tEeJ9fFWPEYmnno7uhvujziORgEF3ErUy4fxfnhPtV-2BfSCeOsmK4Y35mqUxtZzK-2B4QIUKU-2Bl58LikAAvRdQDTzOxqgU4bGHNQfCtDXBqhG6XMF70jG2SLJ5BecYaEO9PnVOlCd-2FaTVRDywjta-2Fozx2FzmEDR60WYkclprTp3MKbfwW-2BAMLs1vVqIjzgl2GhOlfB7Y6zwkG6Ob0Yaqx5pmg-2BbTKEpn1baZcB1xHDHJNermTd5jTX1r2fqufsPFOpDu9pCz2IEALcb6hBQEIICm1sy63nO3LVfYQOqzYoP3Y-3D" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7981341" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Dana Killion&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Need help with substance use disorder or mental health issues? In the U.S., call 800-662-HELP (4357) for the &lt;a href="http://www.samhsa.gov/find-help/national-helpline" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7981341" data-affiliate="true"&gt;SAMHSA National Helpline&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/husband-wife-alcoholism-sober-therapy_n_6466866ee4b035573934e1ac" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7981341"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/a&gt; in May 2023.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 03:31:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPQWxGSnFJeFJudXBIaUVzRWFVdlFJc01scFg0Vll3bUFMeUxmd0p6azJsQXpIN3NDcmF6UFJpeTA2Y1JhRzBYOXU0bEV1MEV1YUlZVkxTOVR5c0U2TVdsVmVvTXpDR2lTREtfS2ZZQU5VSERaZjMzdmR6d3hzTElYYUpZN01aSEtIUWgzNnNpUmJzZw</guid></item><item><title>我扮演了爱妻的角色。在紧闭的门背后，我丈夫的秘密正在摧毁我。- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/danakillion/husband-wife-alcoholism-sober-therapy</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-1
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="fast fashion" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139715228" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The deeper my husband got into boozing, the deeper I got into my own self-imposed bubble of silence. A loyal, loving wife doesn’t talk about her husband peeing in an alley or passing out in the middle of sex while still inside her. She doesn’t tell stories of turning away in bed, tears streaming because the sour stench of his drunken body is revolting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Or was that just part of &lt;em&gt;my&lt;/em&gt; loyalty pledge?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don’t remember a specific moment in my childhood that taught me to follow a code of silence. As the oldest of five, my responsibilities started young, and I thoroughly understood the expectation that I was to be the kid that gave no one any trouble.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We Midwesterners are not thought of as hotheaded, heart-on-our-sleeve types. Silence is simply understood as standard operating procedure. We aren’t brought up to expose ourselves or make ourselves vulnerable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We do. We are. We exist. We move on. We don’t talk about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To place yourself in the middle of any story is to be vain. To call attention to something that should be kept private is simply not done. Unmet needs? Everybody has them. Talking about it won’t change anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prevailing understanding around tough issues in polite society is to be quiet, at least where I was raised. But silence is also the expectation forced on all women. Be pretty and quiet and compliant and thoughtful. With an emphasis on quiet, please.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And I have been as guilty of silence as every other woman before me. In what I assumed was marital loyalty, I kept quiet about my husband’s alcoholism, rarely even questioning why I did so. I didn’t cover for him or make excuses. I didn’t have to lie because life — the part visible to the world outside our home — looked fine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A high-functioning drunk gets through life hiding it all. He’d tough it out through the hangover and go to work anyway. He’d compartmentalize his drinking into time slots so that outward appearances remain untouched. He’d rationalize that because he was still kicking ass on the job, he had it all under control. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I alone held the truth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I played the role a loving wife is supposed to play. She protects her family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking publicly about my husband’s flaws would be a betrayal, wouldn’t it? I thought so. But was my silence about him or me? I didn’t know then, and I don’t know now. But the silence, the silence I chose, languished inside me like something rotting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holding in. Holding back. Holding on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I paused on the sidewalk outside a Michigan Avenue high-rise and stared up at the carved stone arch that crested the double doors. Buses and taxis buzzed behind me, and pedestrians sidestepped me as I struggled with my &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/evelinamedina/which-human-emotion-are-you"&gt;emotions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had no reason to be nervous, yet my heart thumped in my chest as I gathered myself for the appointment I’d made. With a therapist. A therapist to help me navigate addiction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pulse racing, palms sweating, I looked up at the building and took several deep breaths. Why was &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; standing here on the concrete feeling like a shaky schoolgirl? I suppose I irrationally thought of his continued drinking as &lt;em&gt;my&lt;/em&gt; failure. I hadn’t found the exact right formula of love and concern that would get through to him. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although there had been stretches of time where I believed he’d turned a corner, it never lasted more than a few months. And now, many years in, after so many empty promises and broken dreams and returns to booze, it was abundantly clear his problem was too big for me to handle alone, so I’d opened a browser and scrolled Psychology Today looking for practitioners with a specialization in alcoholism. It was one step up from the Yellow Pages, but I wasn’t going to ask friends for a referral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So here I was staring up at a building in downtown Chicago, steeling myself to say aloud for the first time, “My husband is an alcoholic.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The therapist sat in her chair, notepad in hand, and asked, “What can I help you with?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“My husband is an alcoholic, and I don’t know how to get him to stop,” I choked out, tears already filling my eyes and constricting my throat. My body trembled as I sat, hands gripping my thighs. I had said it. For the first time, I had said it. Out loud. Now it was real. There could be no more rationalizing. No more minimizing or softening the label by thinking of him as a “heavy drinker” or “having a drinking problem.” He was a full-on alcoholic. A drunk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Have you suggested a support group? AA?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I laughed. Her question wasn’t intended as sarcasm, but all I could think was, “Honey, if a suggestion was all it took, I could add a Dr. prefix to my name and set out my own shingle.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We spent 45 minutes discussing the ways in which I had attempted to get him to his come-to-Jesus moment. Then as the session wrapped up, she told me she “normally worked with the alcoholic, not the family” and repeated her suggestion of a support group. Then she asked whether I thought he would do better with a male or female therapist if she were to provide a referral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But I didn’t want a referral for him. Who he saw was his damn business! I needed help navigating and understanding his problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was only years later that I realized she had never asked a single question about me. How &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; was doing. How &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; was coping. What support &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; might need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And in the ways of a woman only seeing part of her problem, my thoughts too were laser-focused on my husband’s issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was a lifetime away from realizing that a crisis was in my future too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Excerpted with permission from &lt;a href="https://u7061146.ct.sendgrid.net/ls/click?upn=4tNED-2FM8iDZJQyQ53jATUd1gOWGyyREHiaxJ1NU0Q9tjkxy0CFcmCH3nleILYEpNxjITXRmwJ-2BWLzgpCpuif2LgIOwt7x0HKb6h-2BI2eSnl6twK0kebeyNL4ccc5NkWtRhROoDa2HVbnAxgBKUtcO-2Fm80VnqTGr38yUrsd3s3WCgrWErymMzCtmV9lfOgezXfqN-2Fe7cfjTN3sjlepCm12OZ2nFzumlBEVhZrzaFOCVmdCDeSmdYL5zxx2v1zTL-2FgIb2K5g6AMaIjlcP270Yj5G2npY7gioXXmQHF-2BA6435vicwELjN-2BCFw3022h83el70gnti8O8IUMudmdrsm2TandHuPAzfEQoO1aQopHX69ELiyW7tirs32WZhy4C16fsLJD3idt51CDgCZ1j6LFI4k8g8SSBdtKyytei3EINNCZOYza9HCUDUbRW1px5dTOX8sFuvOjf7V4K5hMTOkR4R7Plxmz8U3CRQmb2o-2FW95TnwDPMehwt0fxywmoq2Pyc1AVV0F8ADc5WmifHhiG9qyBFbpUBnKS2XTgttdXX-2F2WgQFGmAAnv4-2BXGnXeTeEGgzAvWR66RI4w-2BxbTp-2BVVHfOrH13b1GzTosdsNf4CLZpdY5wdIIcgKFNuNdaeQbGQjA7y8gLXwBH9vx7C1zzjvZ-2FhLGAjZzVg-2BGCVc5eLIhghDBl0ibr6LtqxDdL-2BTO4WMGDEbwiAXRs8L3c1rXwFjMjmQ2akli99ROfsftAraVXvDo-3DOtlK_Ps5uOjyCpFslDeso1wdwvvUwnAohiFunuIxA7lzd9uSfz-2BDPamfPG9hlmc9Y0GgV3tEeJ9fFWPEYmnno7uhvujziORgEF3ErUy4fxfnhPtV-2BfSCeOsmK4Y35mqUxtZzK-2B4QIUKU-2Bl58LikAAvRdQDTzOxqgU4bGHNQfCtDXBqhG6XMF70jG2SLJ5BecYaEO9PnVOlCd-2FaTVRDywjta-2Foz-2F0LBAVEP87HhFrNNibB533LPWMwxwJ0TULJu2ic-2FJFHJZzWLJxuu-2BDOJ1zeHBgjXFnQpGhu434zo-2BGf3gEW24yJmGJsPzHALg-2Fqt1OXdN96skLUNzusDnr2KZkG84zN17ReZloN-2FXJVTYXV5yu2Y-2Bs-3D" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7981341" data-affiliate="true"&gt;“Where the Shadows Dance: He Got Sober. I Got Broken,”&lt;/a&gt; by author &lt;a href="https://u7061146.ct.sendgrid.net/ls/click?upn=4tNED-2FM8iDZJQyQ53jATUd1gOWGyyREHiaxJ1NU0Q9tjkxy0CFcmCH3nleILYEpNxjITXRmwJ-2BWLzgpCpuif2Hz6ETqvYy5yiq9z7e52RSFeElcFm1VlMI0otVL8dN2AAcKyPwXmsfgqlEQJG6Mwz1p9-2F1jBO0gD78Ud6cY78QzS1IgcvDYL9PeCwfdlylYt2x1WeazjgX-2BfHPRhodSLFAp-2B7oQYQ-2BEHSJhnKnnXxjyVH8bli1fllICcptbODcTGXzpokLBqASOus7W8WrqSOc5Cr-2FuTJGqCdHIud5Jx4ykLj7sv9cVPFbQpz19yvVbpuM217KulNXWzgvy5eCUJXUH-2FJXwXo5hvtyeSQqewiS-2FvXSj0Gtr0s3sUJGM1QldF8rjPL7AEtIl6g6p72tR1vmDLrH17eqwDc9TxT06fCKHXe2Wnh7bZrAG2uJe8PB1bvvDcONXxXsc5x405en5gx9KSC2UCnTyV6XNwbmRGmFMMuftSq63Iqw9cJCSclLRKsKAMf-2FwmLa7VnowRAOugD6wfUY6eeiNAsfOFRzDE1vf2UNfZ-2FXBKWTqDd-2FjkMrMklOosNB7hQNjgBIbLTIG1dxLMGoQwE7OIzFlHa8RF2l5ENUrl6Z7lN99L1B-2Bs6P1fPu2zqLpSMeNJJLNMBTg8kRsjnchUaQYk4fYfsbkGTBo488xeodhCZq7-2FXJCc4Dcv_mTr_Ps5uOjyCpFslDeso1wdwvvUwnAohiFunuIxA7lzd9uSfz-2BDPamfPG9hlmc9Y0GgV3tEeJ9fFWPEYmnno7uhvujziORgEF3ErUy4fxfnhPtV-2BfSCeOsmK4Y35mqUxtZzK-2B4QIUKU-2Bl58LikAAvRdQDTzOxqgU4bGHNQfCtDXBqhG6XMF70jG2SLJ5BecYaEO9PnVOlCd-2FaTVRDywjta-2Fozx2FzmEDR60WYkclprTp3MKbfwW-2BAMLs1vVqIjzgl2GhOlfB7Y6zwkG6Ob0Yaqx5pmg-2BbTKEpn1baZcB1xHDHJNermTd5jTX1r2fqufsPFOpDu9pCz2IEALcb6hBQEIICm1sy63nO3LVfYQOqzYoP3Y-3D" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7981341" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Dana Killion&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Need help with substance use disorder or mental health issues? In the U.S., call 800-662-HELP (4357) for the &lt;a href="http://www.samhsa.gov/find-help/national-helpline" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7981341" data-affiliate="true"&gt;SAMHSA National Helpline&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/husband-wife-alcoholism-sober-therapy_n_6466866ee4b035573934e1ac" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7981341"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/a&gt; in May 2023.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 03:31:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE8xTFJTUmJEem05Nm45QlptT2p1TzF0cmFLUW5kT0dIamJoZk5qNzJlYzJZT3Q0MGxCUnp6NGxmdTQ2bUhxMHVpbDVzNEhhd01tdGhtZVVsLU12cmxzSTI4REpaUFNQdFRQYUd1ZS13WjNXMnE5TFZWQko1VUZPVXM</guid></item><item><title>高血压药物自愿召回： FDA - NewsNation</title><link>https://www.newsnationnow.com/us-news/recalls/high-blood-pressure-med-recall/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>NewsNation</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 02:08:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNVnl6UjlFYXhWcE03UHFnN1hZdmZyOEJKRG9ZQTNxM1BHejNJa3RPVTBuX2g2YldMMDBONTF5LW1GZDctd2Vzc2lPYXRST29wZ0xNZ2I0WUxlWk51emNWV0ExQ1dlVGlfeUZQZmszWWJoQWhfSmd1SmJ2Z085MlhJSDFUNNIBiAFBVV95cUxNb3JYWldMWi1DR3dib0QwS1pscTJLSkdHQnQ3RFdveW1pNVNqUWptRVBOZXY0djJvc2tycmZmNE94VmpqOEdmWTNiZTBfZDdLcWZxTVQ4Vy05d1Z6UGVPOWNyTGQ2aUdkcFVSdE9fbG9mZ0pHbDNjRGZYWXhreTkzdi1CamFXYVZH</guid></item><item><title>一项新研究表明，常见的营养素缺乏可能会增加阿尔茨海默氏症的风险- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/choline-alzheimers-study-11862978</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Choline is an essential micronutrient for a healthy brain and nervous system. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Low blood choline levels are linked with a higher risk of Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Choline is found in seafood, meat, dairy, nuts, potatoes, legumes and whole grains.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Choline is one of those underrated micronutrients we don’t hear much about—in fact, most Americans aren't eating enough of it.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; But every nutrient, no matter how micro, is essential—and choline is no exception. It’s necessary for a healthy brain and nervous system and helps regulate mood, memory and muscle control, plus it’s essential for forming the membranes surrounding your cells.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; It’s also vital for the proper brain development of babies in utero and after birth.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Besides being underrated, choline is also a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/diabetes-vitamin-deficiency-study-8784014" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;commonly deficient nutrient&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; And deficiency of this micronutrient comes with some potential harm. For example, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/choline-dementia-study-8779484" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;one recent study linked low choline intake&lt;/a&gt; with a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/dementia-risk-doubling-study-8776659" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;higher risk of dementia&lt;/a&gt;, including the most common type of dementia, Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Researchers from Arizona, including Arizona State University and Mayo Clinic Arizona, set out to shed more light on the &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7893378/these-13-things-could-make-you-more-likely-to-get-alzheimers-according-to-a-new-study/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;connection between choline and Alzheimer’s disease&lt;/a&gt;. They published their findings in &lt;em&gt;Aging and Disease&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Let’s break down what they found.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-was-this-study-conducted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Was This Study Conducted? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Researchers wanted to compare choline levels in people with obesity to those with a healthy BMI. They state that previous studies suggest that people with obesity tend to have lower blood choline levels. They also state that obesity is linked with insulin resistance, a condition that predisposes people to type 2 diabetes. &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-happens-to-your-body-when-you-have-insulin-resistance-8400321" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Insulin resistance&lt;/a&gt; is also a major &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7909431/have-a-family-history-of-dementia-or-alzheimers-heres-how-to-protect-your-brain-as-you-age/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;risk factor for Alzheimer’s disease&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For this study, a total of 30 participants, ages 29 to 36, were recruited: 15 (7 males, 8 females) with what is considered a healthy BMI (18.5 to 24.9 kg/m2) and 15 (8 males, 7 females) with a BMI that is considered obese (&amp;gt;30 kg/m2). All participants were deemed healthy based on their medical history, routine physical examination, electrocardiogram, standard blood tests, and urinalysis. Participants were all nonsmokers, free of diabetes and had no history of liver, kidney or heart disease. They also took no prescription or over-the-counter medications or nutritional supplements, and were not engaging in a weight loss regimen. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Body composition was measured and fasting blood samples were collected. Researchers measured choline levels and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8001377/having-diabetes-can-speed-up-cognitive-decline-here-are-5-things-you-can-do-to-help/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;factors related to diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, including glucose, HbA1c and insulin, as well as blood components associated with inflammation and cognitive decline. In addition, liver enzymes were measured, as certain ones can indicate dysfunctional sugar metabolism and brain nerve damage.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In addition, researchers also drew blood postmortem from people with known mild cognitive decline and Alzheimer’s disease. With this, they could compare blood levels of the same components in the 30 healthy individuals with those of individuals with known Alzheimer’s disease and cognitive decline.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-did-this-study-find"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What Did This Study Find? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; After running statistical analyses, researchers found:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Individuals with obesity had lower levels of blood choline, which, in turn, were associated with poor metabolic markers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Markers of inflammation and liver enzymes were elevated in people with obesity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;As choline levels in the blood decreased, neurofilament light (NfL), a marker of Alzheimer’s disease, increased. Higher levels of NfL suggest that damage to brain cells has occurred, and increases the risk of dementia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Overall, researchers found that obesity was associated with lower blood levels of choline, dysregulated inflammatory markers and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/sneaky-signs-you-have-metabolic-syndrome-8694742" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;elevated markers of metabolic dysfunction&lt;/a&gt;. And all of these factors are related to Alzheimer’s disease risk.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One major limitation of this study is that the dietary intake of choline was not assessed, so researchers cannot conclude whether people with obesity eat fewer choline-rich foods or if there’s some other factor involved concerning the lower levels. The number of participants for this study is considered moderate. Since more participants tend to increase the accuracy of the results, researchers note that larger sample sizes in the future will be helpful. This study also did not include cognitive assessments, so comparing blood work between the living participants and those who were post-mortem with cognitive decline should be interpreted with caution.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-does-this-apply-to-real-life"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Does This Apply to Real Life? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While you could supplement with choline, we believe it’s best to try to get your nutrients through food. Like most nutrients, choline is found in many foods, which is why we recommend eating a wide variety of foods to ensure you get all the nutrients you need. You’ll find choline in eggs, beef, poultry, pork, fish and dairy products. Cruciferous vegetables, soybeans (including tofu), shiitake mushrooms, peanuts, wheat germ, almonds, kidney beans, lima beans, red potatoes and quinoa are plant-based sources of choline.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These researchers note that following a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/2058981/ultimate-mediterranean-diet-shopping-list/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Mediterranean diet eating pattern&lt;/a&gt; will help ensure you get enough choline. The &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/290813/mind-diet-best-foods-to-eat-to-keep-your-brain-young/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;MIND diet&lt;/a&gt; is a fusion of the Mediterranean and DASH diets, and is chock-full of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-to-eat-every-week-for-better-brain-health-11784254" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;brain-healthy foods&lt;/a&gt; that contain choline, powerful antioxidants and healthy fats, including seafood, chicken, berries, whole grains and leafy greens (to name a few). To get acquainted, try our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/30-day-mind-diet-meal-plan-for-cognitive-health-11700108" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;30-Day MIND Diet Meal Plan for Cognitive Health&lt;/a&gt;. Follow it as-is or choose recipes that look appealing. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Other lifestyle factors also play a role in brain health, including regular &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/habits-to-avoid-cognitive-decline-study-11782889" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;physical activity&lt;/a&gt;, plenty of quality sleep and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8024858/walking-plan-to-reduce-stress/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;reducing stress levels&lt;/a&gt;. Your &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/things-doctors-do-every-day-for-better-brain-health-11678638" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;brain also requires hydration&lt;/a&gt; for optimum cognitive function. Even &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/loneliness-dementia-risk-study-8733921" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;socializing&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/volunteering-for-cognitive-decline-study-11845338" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="5"&gt;volunteering&lt;/a&gt; can help keep your brain healthy.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This study adds to the growing body of evidence that suggests a connection between low choline blood levels and Alzheimer’s disease. It also indicates a link between obesity and low choline, though researchers admit that they can’t yet say with confidence why this link exists. Many people are deficient in choline, despite it being found in a variety of foods. Evaluate your diet and start swapping ultra-processed foods with whole foods, like seafood, meats, dairy, nuts, eggs, legumes, cruciferous vegetables, potatoes and whole grains. Following a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/simple-7-day-cognitive-health-meal-plan-11685540" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;meal plan designed for cognitive health&lt;/a&gt; can help you take the guesswork out of it.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 23:04:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibEFVX3lxTE5iSXdoYVZmUGpob3IyLUtoYjJfaHNzcmdnS3MtUFhudFV6MHQxd1JjMzE0Vy1Na3k3d3FSMTNaM2tuUlR0NWdwQUoyLV96ZzU0Q1RGTlBPRHE4c3VwaXFNZHhhNTYtdFlCMlotbw</guid></item><item><title>在纽约废水中检测到高传染性病毒- NewsNation</title><link>https://www.newsnationnow.com/health/norovirus-detected-in-new-york-wastewater/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>NewsNation</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:53:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxQY1IwMkpXVmlvVVdfRktPYjlHY3dwaWlLWWtfbkY1UGo4R1VuX2hqbXNtN0lDVjk1c0NxenBCTURyMllJOWdxT3JzQzFtSnYwMWpGdFVoV3poanpnZmtEYnVRMjB0Rk9GWWFpWlltb25sQzJPdElkdS1vdDJ0S2VkazdYTjdtUdIBiwFBVV95cUxNYlVXZUVWWlZXZXR1LTdhaEFkV2xmSEJabjcwNS1nZUFQMDBSckhUa0hyUnRVaWEtZ1QxcHRhaUV1dWh1bW5YZWdTbHB1eXVaYWRJcHZkelcya2tHQjlReWZRTFJtZ2pMOEFkNGdOMUZqbEtiSUFoTmtmd0FzeFBrMXNxbGR0VHRsVHZZ</guid></item><item><title>佛罗里达州报告的14例军团病可能与健身房有关- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/14-cases-legionnaires-disease-reported-florida-linked-gym/story?id=128156214</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;At least 14 cases of Legionnaires' disease have been reported in central Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In an email to state Sen. Carlos Guillermo Smith, the Florida Department of Health revealed the outbreak is linked to a gym, reported ABC News affiliate &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.wftv.com/news/local/14-confirmed-cases-legionnaires-disease-central-florida-gym-exposure/LSPPM3P535DLLA3SBYZZFBAO24/" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;WFTV&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The letter from the department did not list the name of the gym, but WFTV reported that a Crunch Fitness in Ocoee -- 12 miles west of Orlando -- had members reporting cases of Legionnaires' disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Crunch Fitness told the station it is working with the health department, has closed off parts of the gym and is testing its pool and spa systems "out of an abundance of caution."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Neither the Florida Department of Health nor Crunch Fitness immediately returned ABC News' request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Stock photo of the Legionnaire's Disease bacterium.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Bsip/uig/Getty Images/Universal Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Legionnaires' disease is a severe form of pneumonia &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/about/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;caused&lt;/a&gt; by inhaling the Legionella bacteria in small droplets of water mixed in the air or contaminated water accidentally going into your lungs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Legionella bacteria are found naturally in freshwater but typically grow best in warm water and in warm to hot temperatures, according to the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/causes/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; (CDC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The disease does not spread from person to person, but outbreaks can grow if the bacteria get into a building's water supply, including in shower heads, sink faucets, hot water tanks, heaters and other plumbing systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Legionnaires has increased in prevalence over the last decade, reaching a peak of 2.71 cases per 100,000 in 2018, the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/php/surveillance/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;CDC said&lt;/a&gt;. Cases dropped during the first year of the COVID-19 pandemic and then rebounded in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Although most people recover from Legionnaires' disease with antibiotics, certain patients -- including those who are immunocompromised or who suffer from chronic lung diseases -- &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/about/index.html#cdc_disease_basics_outlook-complications" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;can develop complications&lt;/a&gt; that can be fatal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;About one out of every 10 people who develops Legionnaires' disease will die due to complications, according to the CDC. Among those who develop Legionnaires' disease during a stay in a health care facility, about one out of every four people will die, the federal health agency added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:47:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxObnQxdktIekxfeGM0RjJ6LTJiel9LSTJXVWZGWnhfOFJXamRuMENZRUF4Rkc5LUU5NmpNRU5od0hTNUdYekg1NFZKQTRvQ3pmc2VsWDBXeUhTLS1qMldQYXNPdnB1VUtRWm1IZzhqeW95d3FBM1N6LXFDWnR2QTI5aHgzeDNNaC1mMzEzbG5XRjgwQlpOZWRBR2VQM3h2cW9mekRnNjJhR0xXZ9IBrwFBVV95cUxNMmVDTVVCN3piTFZVRWh0Tk5PYnBwWG9DQThpeTMzOHVPV0ZZQlJMdmc1XzRVUHZlT0tURDlZX3NJWjYyZnhHcnpvbXU4dlJZZEZwaUNMRUhmQi1LMXNXaUtqcGFlX2JYdjhlRUlHWmxiTDQ3MjdtdjUya2NMX3lZbEZuMkJEc2llSFdwWGpHaFJqT2dEaXE5dmpPX3hRdzlPa25vSjdGVVZzZlhGcjFr</guid></item><item><title>为什么记忆会改变：大脑如何重写过去-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://neurosciencenews.com/episodic-memory-change-30022/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;A new review explores how episodic memories are formed, stored, and reshaped over time, revealing why our recollections of past events often change. Rather than functioning like fixed files, memories consist of multiple components that can lie dormant until triggered by environmental cues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When retrieved, these components blend with general knowledge, past experiences, and current context, creating updated versions of the original event. The findings help explain memory distortion and offer insights for mental health, learning, and legal settings where accuracy matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dynamic Memories:&lt;/strong&gt; Episodic memories are continually updated, not stored as perfect copies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trigger-Based Recall:&lt;/strong&gt; Hidden memory traces become conscious only when activated by cues.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-World Impact:&lt;/strong&gt; Memory reshaping affects mental health, education, and legal decision-making.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;University of East Anglia&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A study from the University of East Anglia is helping scientists better understand how our brains remember past events – and how those memories can change over time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new paper published today explores episodic memory – the kind of memory we use to recall personal experiences like a birthday party or a holiday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team say their work has important implications for mental health, education, and legal settings where memory plays a key role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working collaboratively with the University of Texas in Dallas, the team show that memories aren’t just stored like files in a computer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, they’re made up of different parts. And while some are active and easy to recall, others stay hidden until something triggers them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, the review shows that for something to count as a real memory, it must be linked to a real event from the past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But even then, the memory we recall might not be a perfect copy,” said lead researcher Prof Louis Renoult, from UEA’s School of Psychology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It can include extra details from our general knowledge, past experiences, or even the situation we’re in when we remember it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Memories of older events often go through a process called re-encoding, which means the brain updates or reshapes the memory over time. This creates a chain of connections from the original experience to the version of the memory we can access now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This work helps us understand why our memories aren’t always reliable and how they can be influenced by time, context, and even our own imaginations.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How the research happened&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team looked at almost 200 psychology and neuroscience studies about memory representations, as well philosophical papers and recent studies using animal models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prof Renoult said: “We wanted to suggest a new way of looking at things by combining ideas from different fields. The goal was to make sense of problems that haven’t been solved yet and spark fresh research.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key part of the study focused on how the brain physically stores memories, highlighting the role of the hippocampus – a part of the brain that helps form and organise memories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research explains how memory traces in the brain can lie dormant and only become conscious representations when something – typically a cue from the environment – activates that memory trace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These conscious representations of our past are typically a combination of retrieved information of the original experience, generic knowledge about the world and information relevant for the current situation,” explained Prof Renoult.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“While memories need to have a causal link to past events to count as memories, they may differ each time they are retrieved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This means that memories can and do change. They might become less accurate or include new information, making them feel different from the original event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A crucial part of our daily lives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Understanding how memories are formed, stored, and reshaped over time is crucial because memory underpins so much of our daily lives – from learning and mental health to decisions made in courtrooms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“By revealing that memories are dynamic rather than fixed, this research helps us better understand why they can change and how that impacts the way we think, feel, and act,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Key Questions Answered:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq wp-block-yoast-faq-block"&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1764972817388"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Why do memories change over time?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; Each retrieval blends original memory traces with generic knowledge and present context, reshaping the memory into a revised version of the past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1764972819163"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: What determines whether something is a “real” memory?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; It must be causally linked to an actual past event, even though the recalled version may include altered or added details.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1764972818675"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Why is this research important for everyday life?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; Understanding how memories evolve informs mental health treatment, supports better learning strategies, and highlights the limitations of eyewitness testimony.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Editorial Notes:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list has-background"&gt;&lt;li&gt;This article was edited by a Neuroscience News editor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Journal paper reviewed in full.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Additional context added by our staff.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this memory and neuroscience research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#64084a0c0b16100b0a241101054a05074a110f" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Lisa Horton&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://uea.ac.uk" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;University of East Anglia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Lisa Horton – University of East Anglia&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image:&lt;/strong&gt; The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.neubiorev.2025.106417" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;The cognitive neuroscience of memory representations&lt;/a&gt;” by Louis Renoult et al. &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Neuroscience &amp;amp; Biobehavioral Reviews&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The cognitive neuroscience of memory representations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The present paper considers the cognitive neuroscience of memory from a representational perspective with the aim of shedding light on current empirical and theoretical issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We focus on episodic memory, differentiating active versus latent, and cognitive versus neural memory representations. We adopt a causal perspective, according to which a memory representation must have a causal connection to a past event to count as a memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We note that retrieved episodic information may nonetheless only partially determine the content of an active memory representation, which can comprise a combination of the retrieved information with semantic, schematic and situational information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We further note that, especially in the case of memories for temporally remote events, re-encoding operations likely lead to a causal chain that extends from the original experience of the event to its currently accessible memory trace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We discuss how the reinstatement framework provides a mechanistic basis for the causal linkage between an experience, the memory trace encoding it, and the episodic memory of the experience, highlighting the crucial role of hippocampal engrams in encoding patterns of neocortical activity that, when active, constitute the neural representation of an episodic memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, we discuss some of the ways in which a memory can become modified and hence distanced from the episode that precipitated it.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:21:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE9KV2lVbjlyV2cwcFBUOUpMc1BFaHZBRjJmQ1RUQlZGdi1PTGJkQ2w5LVAxcG41MzlOajZueTZLR2hydDI2al9DeDJodmwtMnN5XzA0SFoyeDNyV3F4MDhzcVJ5OXVndVhFOUE</guid></item><item><title>超级计算机创造了有史以来最逼真的虚拟大脑之一- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/supercomputer-creates-one-of-the-most-realistic-virtual-brains-ever-seen</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Getting a better understanding of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-brain-goes-through-5-distinct-epochs-massive-study-finds"&gt;how the brain works&lt;/a&gt; is tricky, as living brains aren't easily prodded and analyzed. Scientists now have a new simulation of a mouse's brain to refer to – one of the most comprehensive that's ever been put together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The creation was led by a team from the Allen Institute in the US and the University of Electro-Communications in Japan, and it may allow diseases &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimer-s-disease"&gt;such as Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; to be modeled and studied in greater detail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The simulation models an &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cerebral_cortex"&gt;entire mouse cortex&lt;/a&gt;. While this isn't nearly as large or as intricate as a human brain, which contains &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/brain/awae390"&gt;billions of neurons&lt;/a&gt;, there are &lt;a href="https://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2023/09/human-brain-too-big-to-map-so-theyre-starting-with-mice/"&gt;similarities&lt;/a&gt; between human and rodent brains – so this could be a useful study tool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/boosting-one-protein-reawakens-aging-brain-cells-in-mice-study-shows"&gt;Boosting One Protein Reawakens Aging Brain Cells in Mice, Study Shows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The numbers are impressive: the virtual brain contains 9 million neurons, as well as 26 billion synapses (&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/millions-of-silent-synapses-could-be-the-key-to-lifelong-learning"&gt;neuron connectors&lt;/a&gt;). There are 86 interconnected regions in the brain simulation, and it can process quadrillions of calculations every second.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To put that in perspective, the real and full mouse brain &lt;a href="https://www.hhmi.org/news/mouselight-project-maps-1000-neurons-and-counting-mouse-brain"&gt;contains&lt;/a&gt; roughly 70 million neurons in a space about the size of an almond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This shows the door is open," &lt;a href="https://alleninstitute.org/news/one-of-worlds-most-detailed-virtual-brain-simulations-is-changing-how-we-study-the-brain/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; computational neuroscientist Anton Arkhipov, from the Allen Institute. "We can run these kinds of brain simulations effectively with enough computing power."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's a technical milestone giving us confidence that much larger models are not only possible, but achievable with precision and scale."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_183655" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-183655" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/BrainModel.jpg" alt="Brain model detail" class="wp-image-183655 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/BrainModel.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/BrainModel-600x149.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-183655" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The simulation enables researchers to track the activity of individual neurons. (Kuriyama et al., 2025).&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The complexity of the simulation means that researchers can watch as models of cognition,  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/consciousness" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73104" data-postid="183652" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;consciousness&lt;/a&gt;, and disease &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-severe-brain-disorder-is-common-but-often-goes-undiagnosed"&gt;spread through the brain&lt;/a&gt;. It's a three-dimensional, moving map that shows individual neurons firing and connecting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the ways this could be used, according to the researchers, are to test hypotheses on how seizures spread in the brain, or how brain waves &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-brain-has-a-hidden-rhythm-and-it-may-reveal-how-smart-you-are"&gt;contribute to focus&lt;/a&gt; – without any need for repeated, invasive, physical brain scans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The necessary computing power was provided by &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/breakthrough-simulation-maps-every-star-in-the-milky-way-in-scientific-first"&gt;the Fugaku supercomputer&lt;/a&gt; in Japan, which built upon existing cell databases and charts to form the model. The team also developed new software to more efficiently process brain activity and keep unnecessary calculations down to a minimum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fugaku is used for research in a wide range of computational science fields, such as astronomy, meteorology, and drug discovery, contributing to the resolution of many societal problems," &lt;a href="https://alleninstitute.org/news/one-of-worlds-most-detailed-virtual-brain-simulations-is-changing-how-we-study-the-brain/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; computer scientist Tadashi Yamazaki, from the University of Electro-Communications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"On this occasion, we utilized Fugaku for a neural circuit simulation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our brains are, of course, essential to good physical and mental health, and healthy old age – and studies of virtual &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-tiny-piece-of-mouse-brain-has-finally-been-mapped-in-mindblowing-detail"&gt;brain maps&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/breakthrough-helps-scientists-grow-more-realistic-human-brain-models"&gt;mini-brain structures&lt;/a&gt; are going to be crucial in learning more about how this organ works, and how it can break down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team has already been busy putting their new model to use, making discoveries about &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/brain-waves-move-in-opposite-directions-for-memorizing-and-recalling"&gt;brain wave synchronization&lt;/a&gt; and the way the two hemispheres of the mouse brain interact with each other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's a massively impressive feat of computing and biological modeling, but the researchers have even grander plans, and one day want to build a full-sized model of a human brain inside a virtual computing space.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our long-term goal is to build whole-brain models, eventually even human models, using all the biological details our Institute is uncovering," &lt;a href="https://alleninstitute.org/news/one-of-worlds-most-detailed-virtual-brain-simulations-is-changing-how-we-study-the-brain/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Arkhipov. "We're now moving from modeling single brain areas to simulating the entire brain of the mouse."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been presented at the &lt;a href="https://sc25.supercomputing.org/"&gt;SC25 supercomputing conference&lt;/a&gt;, and is &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1145/3712285.3759819"&gt;available online&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:01:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxOUlVoNmpRT0lHNWxhd05fbjI2bXI5TWZPMWI0N2VtTjl6Mnk5dDAwNXBQUGxJWDE0Y1NnaWUtUV9Rb0Q2Y2dLLUZ0WmxiQWNoSkU4RElibE5JdjBTU0xwWHRFWXhIUXI3aHpJREZ6clpXMnB0UVdrc1dVNENDdURnb3hKRnVJc2hQaXdHRjRoZExIU0RhUFA5SUJ2MkExZWx5TE4w</guid></item><item><title>“弦上傀儡” ： ACIP主席播放独立担忧- Politico</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2025/12/05/puppets-on-a-string-acip-chair-airs-independence-concerns-00678876</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Politico</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:49:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxQNk5GaU9tQjJyUTdKRTJXV3NFcXVoWFI2NlV4S1FCLVhkTXhxMUJrMWNPcVFCX2lDOV9wNkVZLXo1dHZ6N2hWN1dURzJVZEQwcno0T09EVjZybDdaY2lqN2xwQ3ZydExpaUFjWE5GQWpmZk9oZ0VYTXFUV1ZROEJzak1SSnRKbGZiUW9veGplcEcxUjFaWDFWTDhsLVJzSUtGU2JSYXZZdG1RVnM</guid></item><item><title>罕见的癌症正在年轻人中激增，专家们感到困惑- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/a-rare-cancer-is-surging-in-young-people-and-experts-are-puzzled</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A very rare type of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="180700" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; is on a sharp upward trajectory in younger generations, and no one knows why.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent research in the US reveals that Gen X-ers and Millennials are three to four times more likely than older generations to be diagnosed with cancer of the appendix, the finger-sized organ hanging off our digestive tract that few think about unless something goes awry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Historically, cancers of the appendix almost always impacted older people, but today, 1 in every 3 appendiceal cancer patients is diagnosed under the age of 50.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/most-people-develop-diverticulosis-in-their-gut-by-age-80-so-what-is-it"&gt;Most People Develop Diverticulosis in Their Gut by Age 80 … So What Is It?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lead author of two recent analyses, epidemiologist and molecular biologist Andreana Holowatyj from Vanderbilt University, wants to know why. For years now, she has studied a sharp uptick in appendix cancers across generations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When we think about the significant progress we've made in other cancers, there's a big gap," she &lt;a href="https://discoveries.vanderbilthealth.com/2024/06/defining-the-unknowns-in-appendix-cancer/"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few years before, in 2020, Holowatyj led a national &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.7326/ANNALS-24-02479"&gt;analysis&lt;/a&gt; that found the incidence of malignant appendix cancer in the US increased by 232 percent between 2000 and 2016. Every generation saw an uptick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a long time, the appendix was dismissed as vestigial, a leftover organ with no real function. But &lt;a href="https://www.mcgill.ca/oss/article/medical/your-appendix-may-not-be-useless-after-all"&gt;recent evidence&lt;/a&gt; suggests it may &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-appendix-might-serve-an-important-biological-function-after-all-2"&gt;not be so useless after all&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_180735" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-180735" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/GettyImages-1682974946-642x361.jpg" alt="Female Appendix" class="size-medium wp-image-180735" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/GettyImages-1682974946-642x361.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/GettyImages-1682974946-1200x675.jpg 1200w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/GettyImages-1682974946-768x432.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/GettyImages-1682974946-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/GettyImages-1682974946-2048x1152.jpg 2048w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/GettyImages-1682974946-600x338.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-180735" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Illustration of the female appendix. (Sebastian Kaulitzki/Science Photo Library/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inflammation of the appendix, or &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Appendicitis"&gt;appendicitis&lt;/a&gt;, is the most common complication associated with the organ, and, on very rare occasions, cancer is found when the appendix is removed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The progression of appendix cancer can be insidious. The &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1200/JCO.2025.43.4_suppl.824"&gt;warning signs&lt;/a&gt;, such as abdominal pain, bloating, and pelvic pain, can be easily confused with other conditions that are far more common, like digestive issues or colorectal cancers, the latter of which impact &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/colon-rectal-cancer/about/key-statistics.html"&gt;roughly 150,000&lt;/a&gt; people in the US yearly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By comparison, there are only about &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41568-024-00788-2"&gt;3,000 cases&lt;/a&gt; a year of appendix cancer. As a result, the disease lacks research and awareness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Albeit cancer of the appendix is rare, it is important for individuals who have these symptoms to see a health care professional," &lt;a href="https://news.vumc.org/2025/06/10/study-shows-sharp-increase-in-appendix-cancer-for-generation-x-and-millennials/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Holowatyj.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Ruling out the possibility of an appendix cancer diagnosis, or diagnosing it early, is important for this cancer as we continue to learn what factors may be contributing to this worrisome trend."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently, there are no standardized screening guidelines for appendix cancer, and available treatments are limited. Appendiceal cancers can easily be missed, according to Holowatyj, especially as managing appendicitis without surgery is becoming more common.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes it can present like hernias, fibroids, or cysts. In women, the cancer can be mistaken for endometrial lesions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Appendiceal tumors harbor different molecular features from colorectal cancers," &lt;a href="https://www.vumc.org/holowatyj-lab/news-media/rare-appendiceal-cancer-affecting-younger-adults-0"&gt;explained&lt;/a&gt; Holowatyj in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They present and spread differently, don't respond to the chemotherapy most colorectal tumors do, and they disproportionately affect younger adults."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Holowatyj and her team's &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.7326/ANNALS-24-02479"&gt;most recent research&lt;/a&gt;, cases of appendix cancer tripled for Americans born between 1976 and 1984, compared to those born between 1941 and 1949. Meanwhile, for those born between 1981 and 1989, they quadrupled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists are not yet sure why that is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holowatyj and her colleagues &lt;a href="https://www.vumc.org/holowatyj-lab/news-media/rare-appendiceal-cancer-affecting-younger-adults-0"&gt;suspect that changes&lt;/a&gt; in health behaviors, like diet and physical activity, inherited gene variants, and possible environmental exposures, such as plastic or chemical pollution, may contribute to the development of the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_180739" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-180739" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/glass-of-water.jpg" alt="Glass of Water" class="size-full wp-image-180739" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/glass-of-water.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/glass-of-water-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-180739" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Changes in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1021/acsestwater.4c00210"&gt;water quality&lt;/a&gt; might play a role in appendix cancer cases increasing. (pixelshot/Canva)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/vomiting-syndrome-linked-to-cannabis-is-on-the-rise-in-the-us"&gt;Vomiting Syndrome Linked to Cannabis Is on The Rise in The US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;University of Colorado surgical oncologist Steven Ahrendt, who was not involved in the research, is &lt;a href="https://news.cuanschutz.edu/cancer-center/appendix-cancer-people-younger-than-50"&gt;not surprised&lt;/a&gt; by the recent increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I certainly see patients in their 20s and 30s who have advanced appendix tumors that we take care of," he &lt;a href="https://news.cuanschutz.edu/cancer-center/appendix-cancer-people-younger-than-50"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; in June, commenting on Holowatyj and her team's most recent study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We know that colon cancer has been increasing in incidence in young adults, so it stands to reason that the same factors are operating in patients with appendix cancer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other recent studies have found a surge in cancer in young people in recent years, with the rate of diagnosis in under-50s jumping to nearly 80 percent in three decades, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer-in-under-50s-has-jumped-80-in-30-years-according-to-a-new-global-study"&gt;according to a 2023 study&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/more-young-people-are-getting-cancer-and-we-dont-know-why"&gt;2022 international review&lt;/a&gt; found that gastrointestinal cancers were the forerunners, with the most significant increases seen in cancers of the bowel, appendix, bile duct, and pancreas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the reasons for this are &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/bowel-cancer-in-young-people-is-rising-heres-how-to-reduce-your-risk"&gt;yet to be established&lt;/a&gt;, experts believe that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/why-millennials-face-higher-cancer-risk-than-their-parents-and-how-to-reduce-it"&gt;diet and poor sleep may play a role&lt;/a&gt;, with &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-reveals-how-ultra-processed-foods-may-fuel-bowel-cancer"&gt;ultra-processed foods&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/there-is-no-safe-level-of-alcohol-consumption-us-surgeon-general-warns"&gt;alcohol&lt;/a&gt; looking particularly suspicious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So-called forever chemicals &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/forever-chemicals-in-us-drinking-water-linked-to-cancer-scientists-find"&gt;contaminating drinking water&lt;/a&gt; and microplastics &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-suspected-to-cause-fertility-gut-and-lung-issues-warns-new-review"&gt;have also been implicated&lt;/a&gt; in cancers more generally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holowatyj and her colleagues plan to continue studying who is most at risk of appendix cancer, and why.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As a rare cancer, appendix cancer garners limited attention. Our team is passionately committed to driving marked advances in our understanding of this disease for our patients," she &lt;a href="https://www.vumc.org/holowatyj-lab/news-media/rare-appendiceal-cancer-affecting-younger-adults-0"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; on her Vanderbilt lab website.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The studies were published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1053/j.gastro.2020.06.011"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gastroenterology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.7326/ANNALS-24-02479"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Annals of Internal Medicine&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:47:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPUU9IMXp2dUh4MWp5RU5jZ1J2NzR3ZXl4M1BNQnloT2lsUW0wMnJfblUwZTl2WC1GSWFacGh5S1RTR25BSXdCVG95Ri1sZVNGVmQ1dmRsQkZTZWtVY0d5aG80d2dvVVdja1pYSl93WE1JT0pFLWxOd1FwTTVCckRkUHZGWi1lTm1LMEdvZmc4U2pJS0JPQjdITQ</guid></item><item><title>美国疫苗顾问表示，并非所有婴儿在出生时都需要注射乙型肝炎疫苗-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/vaccines-babies-hepatitis-b-10f8db54beb38c5cd39a94f8a3657752</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A federal vaccine advisory committee voted on Friday to end the longstanding recommendation that all U.S. babies get the hepatitis B vaccine on the day they’re born.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A loud chorus of medical and public health leaders decried the actions of the panel, whose current members were all appointed by U.S. Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. — a leading anti-vaccine activist before this year becoming the nation’s top health official.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is the group that can’t shoot straight,” said Dr. William Schaffner, a Vanderbilt University vaccine expert who for decades has been involved with ACIP and its workgroups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several medical societies and state health departments said they would continue to recommend them. While people may have to check their policies, the trade group AHIP, formerly known as America’s Health Insurance Plans, said its members still will cover the birth dose of the hepatitis B vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="AudioEnhancement" data-separate-event="audioModule" data-separate-value="AP AUDIO: US vaccine advisers say not all babies need a hepatitis B shot at birth" data-module data-gtm-region="AP AUDIO: US vaccine advisers say not all babies need a hepatitis B shot at birth" data-align-center&gt;
    
    &lt;a class="AnchorLink" id="ap-audio-us-vaccine-advisers-say-not-all-babies-need-a-hepatitis-b-shot-at-birth"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;


    
    
    
    
        
            &lt;bsp-custom-headline custom-headline="div"&gt;
                &lt;p class="AudioEnhancement-title" data-mb-5&gt;
                    AP AUDIO: US vaccine advisers say not all babies need a hepatitis B shot at birth
                &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/bsp-custom-headline&gt;
        
    
    
    &lt;p class="AudioEnhancement-description"&gt;AP correspondent Ed Donahue reports on a new vaccine advisory for babies.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;For decades, the government has advised that all babies be vaccinated against the liver infection right after birth. The shots are widely considered to be a public health success for preventing thousands of illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But Kennedy’s Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices decided to recommend the birth dose only for babies whose mothers test positive, and in cases where the mom wasn’t tested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For other babies, it will be up to the parents and their doctors &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/meetings/upcoming.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;to decide&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; if a birth dose is appropriate. The committee voted 8-3 to suggest that when a family elects to wait, then the vaccination series should begin when the child is 2 months old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The acting director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Jim O’Neill, is expected to decide later whether to accept the committee’s recommendation.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;The decision marks a return to a health strategy abandoned more than three decades ago&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asked why the newly-appointed committee moved quickly to reexamine the recommendation, committee member Vicky Pebsworth on Thursday cited “pressure from stakeholder groups,” without naming them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Committee members said the risk of infection for most babies is very low and that earlier research that found the shots were safe for infants was inadequate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They also worried that in many cases, doctors and nurses don’t have full conversations with parents about the pros and cons of the birth-dose vaccination. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The committee members voiced interest in hearing the input from public health and medical professionals, but chose to ignore the experts’ repeated pleas to leave the recommendations alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The committee gives advice to the director of the &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/cdc-director-susan-monarez-50dfbec849b53b4593755d2e6e616687"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; on how approved vaccines should be used. CDC directors almost always adopted the committee’s recommendations, which were widely heeded by doctors and guide vaccination programs. But the agency currently has no director, leaving acting director O’Neill to decide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In June, Kennedy &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/kennedy-cdc-acip-vaccines-3790c89f45b6314c5c7b686db0e3a8f9"&gt;fired the entire 17-member&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; panel earlier this year and replaced it with a group that includes &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/cdc-acip-vaccine-committee-9f58e1f004075b081718ff078de88d76"&gt;several anti-vaccine voices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Hepatitis B and delaying birth doses&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hepatitis B is a serious liver infection that, for most people, lasts less than six months. But for some, especially infants and children, it can become a long-lasting problem that can lead to liver failure, liver cancer and scarring called cirrhosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In adults, the virus is spread through sex or through sharing needles during injection drug use. But it can also be passed from an infected mother to a baby. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 1991, the committee recommended an initial dose of hepatitis B vaccine at birth. Experts say quick immunization is crucial to prevent infection from taking root. And, indeed, cases in children have plummeted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, several members of Kennedy’s committee voiced discomfort with vaccinating all newborns. They argued that past safety studies of the vaccine in newborns were limited and it’s possible that larger, long-term studies could uncover a problem with the birth dose. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But two members said they saw no documented evidence of harm from the birth doses and suggested concern was based on speculation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three panel members asked about the scientific basis for saying that the first dose could be delayed for two months for many babies.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;“This is unconscionable,” said committee member Dr. Joseph Hibbeln, who repeatedly voiced opposition to the proposal during the sometimes-heated two-day meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The committee’s chair, Dr. Kirk Milhoan, said two months was chosen as a point where infants had matured beyond the neonatal stage. Hibbeln countered that there was no data presented that two months is an appropriate cut-off. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Cody Meissner also questioned a second proposal — which passed 6-4 — that said parents consider talking to pediatricians about blood tests meant to measure whether hep B shots have created protective antibodies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such testing is not standard pediatric practice after vaccination. Proponents said it could be a new way to see if fewer shots are adequate.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;A CDC hepatitis expert, Adam Langer, said results could vary from child to child and would be an erratic way to assess if fewer doses work. He also noted there’s no good evidence that three shots pose harm to kids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meissner attacked the proposal, saying the language “is kind of making things up.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Health experts say this could ‘make America sicker’&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health experts have noted Kennedy’s hand-picked committee is focused on the pros and cons of shots for the individual getting vaccinated, and has turned away from seeing vaccinations as a way to stop the spread of preventable diseases among the public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second proposal “is right at the center of this paradox,” said committee member Dr. Robert Malone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some observers criticized the meeting, noting recent changes in how they are conducted. CDC scientists no longer present vaccine safety and effectiveness data to the committee. Instead, people who have been prominent voices in anti-vaccine circles were &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/cdc-vaccine-committee-hepatitis-b-f5e0cd8dad2c3d07c0ab0beb96b481ff"&gt;given those slots&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The committee “is no longer a legitimate scientific body,” said Elizabeth Jacobs, a member of Defend Public Health, an advocacy group of researchers and others that has opposed Trump administration health policies. She described the meeting this week as “an epidemiological crime scene.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican Sen. Bill Cassidy, a liver doctor who chairs the Senate health committee, called the committee’s vote on the hepatitis B vaccine “a mistake.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This makes America sicker,” he said, in &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://x.com/SenBillCassidy/status/1996974038413971766?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;a post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; on social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The committee heard a 90-minute presentation from Aaron Siri, a lawyer who has worked with Kennedy on vaccine litigation. He ended by saying that he believes there should no ACIP vaccine recommendations at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a lengthy response, Meissner said, “What you have said is a terrible, terrible distortion of all the facts.” He ended by saying Siri should not have been invited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The meeting’s organizers said they invited Siri as well a few vaccine researchers — who have been vocal defenders of immunizations — to discuss the vaccine schedule. They named two: Dr. Peter Hotez, who said he declined, and Dr. Paul Offit, who said he didn’t remember being asked but would have declined anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hotez, of the Texas Children’s Hospital in Houston, declined to present before the group “because ACIP appears to have shifted its mission away from science and evidence-based medicine,” he said in an email to The Associated Press.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AP writers Ali Swenson in New York, Laura Ungar in Louisville, Kentucky, and Lauran Neergaard in Washington, D.C., contributed to this report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:32:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxQTnJjQUhxaWxUVzNJLWNhUEpIbEhRWWdjeVlHLXBKak5KbkgxUDhPZ1EyOUVENDkxTnRpVkE2TDV4cjVOdjJvdEJwMzBTXzNxb1luVF9hemg3aFpyQ2xwSmNhWFlEOWlaQllCYmRzV2ZZQmEyd1VfcnQ5RmZmMlZVa3IxN0xwTjZYcmtPbDVlRnY</guid></item><item><title>像Ozempic这样的GLP-1药物可能会产生没有人预料到的副作用- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/glp-1-drugs-like-ozempic-might-have-a-side-effect-nobody-expected-2000696194</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl prose-science dark:prose-science"&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Every drug has its risks, no matter how tremendous its benefits may be, and sometimes it can take a while to uncover less obvious side effects. New research suggests that GLP-1 medications like semaglutide—the active ingredient in popular drugs Ozempic and Wegovy—might leave some users feeling a little wheezy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Researchers at the University of Southern California and others examined the medical records of people taking GLP-1s for their type 2 diabetes. Compared to people on other diabetes treatments, GLP-1 users were more likely to develop a chronic cough, they found. The findings warrant more study into this potential side effect and why it may be happening, the researchers say.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;A potential risk of chronic cough?&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The most common side effects of GLP-1s are gastrointestinal, such as nausea, vomiting, and constipation. Research has also &lt;a href="https://www.drugs.com/news/glp-1-increase-risk-acid-reflux-gerd-125796.html"&gt;indicated&lt;/a&gt; that they can raise the risk of gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD) and acid reflux, likely because they slow the emptying of food from the stomach.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;GERD/acid reflux can also be a common cause of chronic cough. According to the researchers, though, there hasn’t been any study specifically looking into a potential association between GLP-1s and chronic cough.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The researchers analyzed electronic health care records collected from 70 health care organizations. They looked at nearly a half million people taking a GLP-1 for their diabetes and compared them to a similar group of 1.6 million people taking other medications.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;All in all, GLP-1 use was associated with a 12% higher risk of a new case of chronic cough compared to all other diabetes medications. When looking at specific drug classes, they failed to find any increased risk compared to SGLT2 inhibitors. Interestingly enough, a higher overall risk of chronic cough was still seen even when the researchers excluded people who had a past diagnosis of GERD.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;What does this mean?&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;These findings are observational, meaning they can’t concretely prove a cause-and-effect link between chronic cough and GLP-1 use. So for now, this study should only encourage scientists to look deeper into this possible connection, the researchers say.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Further research is needed to confirm the existence, strength, and mechanisms of this association,” they wrote in their paper, &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaotolaryngology/article-abstract/2842204"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; late last month in the journal JAMA Otolaryngology–Head &amp;amp; Neck Surgery.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;GLP-1 drugs like semaglutide have greatly improved &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/ozempic-is-an-essential-drug-who-says-as-agency-calls-for-cheaper-generics-2000654348"&gt;obesity treatment&lt;/a&gt; in recent years. But it’s always important to keep tracking the safety of every drug once it reaches the public. While the discovery of a new side effect might not change the overall value of a medication, it can help doctors and patients better manage or prevent it from happening.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:20:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxQZTJ4MlEydDBTYkpGUUhNLVYwLXZWREVvdDctSTJucE5lTXoyVUpNWW1xM0RyVVBzX0NicFZuLS04SGs5azBpNUxsV0I1Zkk3SDl2MEJGeWtoSFphYUl1Sm5xSENMOGFVR3R5Q0V4WVYxa3lqaTR1c21VQV9NcHV2ZnpXR09yRXZNOW40LWVYWE1sZkFwTkhQeVMxZ1A</guid></item><item><title>这种病毒在NC中迅速传播，没有真正的治疗方法。须知事项-夏洛特观察家报</title><link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article313281240.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="" class="paper story-body"&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="trinityAudioPlaceholder trinity-player-iframe-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A fast-moving virus is spreading across North Carolina, slipping from person to person — and there’s no treatment to stop it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From Aug. 1-Nov. 13, there were 153 &lt;b&gt;norovirus&lt;/b&gt; outbreaks reported in 14 states, including North Carolina, according to data from the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.cdc.gov/norovirus/php/reporting/norostat-data.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We have seen increased cases in North Carolina,” &lt;b&gt;Dr. David Weber&lt;/b&gt;, an infectious disease specialist at the UNC School of Medicine, told The Charlotte Observer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-101" class="zone zone-el" index="2" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This virus spreads easily and can be &lt;b&gt;transmitted through close contact with someone who’s infected,&lt;/b&gt; contaminated food or water, or by touching surfaces that carry the virus, according to the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://epi.dph.ncdhhs.gov/cd/diseases/norovirus.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;N.C. Department of Health and Human Services&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (NCDHHS). Outbreaks are especially common in close-quarter settings like &lt;b&gt;schools, workplaces and health care facilities&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what you need to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="h2"&gt;Norovirus vs. stomach bugs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Stomach bugs” share similarities with norovirus, but the two aren’t identical, according to the &lt;u&gt;American Medical Association&lt;/u&gt; (AMA).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Onset:&lt;/b&gt; Norovirus symptoms usually begin 12 to 48 hours after someone is exposed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Duration:&lt;/b&gt; The illness typically runs its course within one to three days, often making it shorter-lived than many other stomach bugs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Symptoms:&lt;/b&gt; Norovirus most often triggers nausea, vomiting, diarrhea and stomach pain, and can also bring on fever, headaches and body aches.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="h2"&gt;Who is most at risk of contracting norovirus?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Anyone who eats raw shellfish&lt;/b&gt; can be exposed to norovirus, according to the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.cdc.gov/norovirus/about/index.html#:~:text=Anyone%20who%20consumes%20raw%20shellfish,eat%20raw%20or%20undercooked%20shellfish."&gt;&lt;u&gt;CDC&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The agency warns that “if eaten raw, oysters and other filter-feeding shellfish can contain viruses and bacteria that can cause illness or death.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Young children, older adults and people with weakened immune systems&lt;/b&gt; are also at higher risk for developing severe symptoms, the CDC says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="photo-inline-"&gt;                      &lt;div class="img-container picture "&gt;                        &lt;picture&gt;                                                &lt;source srcset="https://www.sunherald.com/public/latest-news/g3hprm/picture239997023/alternates/FREE_1140/21347_lore_fitted.jpeg" media="(min-width: 992px)"&gt;                &lt;source srcset="https://www.sunherald.com/public/latest-news/g3hprm/picture239997023/alternates/FREE_960/21347_lore_fitted.jpeg" media="(min-width: 768px)"&gt;                &lt;source srcset="https://www.sunherald.com/public/latest-news/g3hprm/picture239997023/alternates/FREE_768/21347_lore_fitted.jpeg" media="(min-width: 601px)"&gt;                &lt;source srcset="https://www.sunherald.com/public/latest-news/g3hprm/picture239997023/alternates/FREE_640/21347_lore_fitted.jpeg" media="(min-width: 441px)"&gt;                &lt;source srcset="https://www.sunherald.com/public/latest-news/g3hprm/picture239997023/alternates/FREE_480/21347_lore_fitted.jpeg" media="(min-width: 320px)"&gt;                                                &lt;img class="responsive-image" srcset="https://www.sunherald.com/public/latest-news/g3hprm/picture239997023/alternates/FREE_1140/21347_lore_fitted.jpeg" alt="Based on electron microscopic (EM) imagery, this illustration provides a three-dimensional (3D), graphical representation of a number of norovirus virions, set against a black background." title="21347_lore_fitted.jpeg" loading="lazy"&gt;                            &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;                                        &lt;figcaption&gt;                                            Based on electron microscopic (EM) imagery, this illustration provides a three-dimensional (3D), graphical representation of a number of norovirus virions, set against a black background.                                                                                                                                                                        &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Centers for Disease Control&lt;/span&gt;                                                            &lt;/figcaption&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 class="h2"&gt;How can you treat the symptoms of norovirus?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s &lt;b&gt;no targeted treatment once symptoms&lt;/b&gt; begin, so recovery mostly means waiting it out while managing how you feel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-106" class="zone zone-el" index="14" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To reduce the risk of complications, try the following:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stay hydrated.&lt;/b&gt; Replace fluids lost through vomiting and diarrhea with water, clear broths, fruit juices or sports drinks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Consider oral rehydration solutions&lt;/b&gt; if other liquids are hard to keep down, as they help your body absorb fluids more efficiently.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rest as much as possible&lt;/b&gt; to support your body’s recovery.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stick to bland foods&lt;/b&gt; once you’re able to eat again, choosing soft, gentle options as you ease back into normal meals.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Steer clear of caffeine, alcohol and very sugary drinks.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Use over-the-counter medications cautiously,&lt;/b&gt; as they may help with some symptoms but aren’t always appropriate.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="h2"&gt;When should you see a doctor?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You should seek medical attention if you develop &lt;b&gt;diarrhea that doesn’t go away within several days&lt;/b&gt;, according to &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/norovirus/symptoms-causes/syc-20355296#when-to-see-a-doctor"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-107" class="zone zone-el" index="18" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You should also contact your doctor if you experience &lt;b&gt;severe vomiting, bloody stools, stomach pain or dehydration&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="h2"&gt;How to prevent norovirus&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can use these tips to help prevent norovirus infections in your household, according to &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://epi.dph.ncdhhs.gov/cd/norovirus/NorovirusFoodborneFactsheets.pdf"&gt;&lt;u&gt;NCDHHS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wash your hands thoroughly with soap and water often.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Handle and prepare food safely.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;When you are sick, do not prepare food or care for others who are sick.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wash laundry thoroughly.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean and disinfect surfaces.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-108" class="zone zone-el" index="22" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to choosing a disinfectant for surfaces, Weber recommended checking the Environmental Protection Agency’s &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.epa.gov/pesticide-registration/epas-registered-antimicrobial-products-effective-against-norovirus-feline#use"&gt;&lt;u&gt;list of disinfectants that are effective against norovirus&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. He also advised people to focus on “ready-to-use” products under “formulation type” on the list, instead of dilutable products more suitable for hospital or nursing home settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="embed-infographic"&gt;  &lt;gray-box&gt;  &lt;h3&gt;Ask the North Carolina Service Journalism Team &lt;/h3&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Questions about life in North Carolina? Or have a tip or story idea you’d like to share? The service journalism teams at The News &amp;amp; Observer and The Charlotte Observer want to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can submit your question by &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSccVKD-gL7FQf5pkdkbdjLw965_FcrhM0VNSNc3CpkcOakHFg/viewform?usp=dialog" target="_blank" rel="Follow"&gt;filling out this form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/gray-box&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="zone grid"&gt;&lt;div class="related-stories story-module"&gt;
        &lt;h5&gt;Related Stories from  Charlotte Observer&lt;/h5&gt;
        
        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="story-module"&gt;&lt;div class="author-card "&gt;
        
        &lt;div class="article-details"&gt;
            
                
                &lt;a class="author-name" href="/profile/256802412/"&gt;Evan Moore&lt;/a&gt;
                
                &lt;p&gt; 
                
                
                    
                    
                    &lt;span class="credit"&gt;The Charlotte Observer&lt;/span&gt;
                    
                
            &lt;/p&gt; 
            
            
                
                
                     
                
            
            
            

            

        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;p class="author-description"&gt;

            &lt;span&gt;Evan Moore is a service journalism reporter for the Charlotte Observer. He grew up in Denver, North Carolina, where he previously worked as a reporter for the Denver Citizen, and is a UNC Charlotte graduate.&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-16" class="zone-el"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Charlotte Observer</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:11:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxPTVZ4VnFObEZzczZNQ0RsOGFYbWU1SHNkc1BIdVBkVGFVLUNRSEVkSVN0dW5pRUQ2Z3dSMTJzQkt3R1hrbklkakZ2eW14TVpkTnVZUVhNLVYzX1NsbVJlZXlLVjFZNFJjMkJfb1hiTXE5NHp1ZVBqU3lTSllZRVBtWndOY3lXdWJJ</guid></item><item><title>逆转肾损伤：可能改变肾脏治疗的突破性治疗-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/reverse-kidney-damage-a-breakthrough-treatment-that-may-transform-kidney-treatment/articleshow/125792760.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kidney disease has long been considered a progressive and irreversible condition, where treatment focuses only on slowing decline rather than restoring lost function. However, a promising scientific discovery challenges that belief. Researchers have identified a potential way to reverse kidney damage by blocking the activity of ceramides, a type of fat molecule linked to cellular injury inside the kidney. In animal trials, targeting ceramides protected kidney cells from damage entirely and allowed renal function to return to normal. If future studies confirm similar results in humans, this breakthrough could transform how kidney disease is treated and provide new hope for millions of patients worldwide. Take a look&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9907354" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;peer-reviewed study published in JCI Insight&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; investigated the role of ceramides in acute kidney injury. The researchers demonstrated that suppressing ceramide production in mice preserved mitochondrial function in kidney cells and prevented injury. They reported significantly improved kidney structure and function in treated animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How the potential to reverse kidney damage could change future treatment&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The role of ceramides in kidney injury&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ceramides are lipid molecules that rise sharply in kidney tissue when the organs are under stress. High ceramide levels interfere with mitochondrial function inside kidney cells. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mitochondria provide the energy cells need to survive and recover, so once they fail, cells begin to die. This leads to inflammation, scarring and long-term loss of kidney function. Researchers believe that stopping ceramide accumulation may prevent early injury from becoming permanent damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Protecting kidney cells by reducing ceramides&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the recent animal study, scientists treated mice with a compound that reduced ceramide production before inducing acute kidney injury. The treated mice maintained healthy mitochondrial function and experienced no significant loss of kidney performance. In contrast, untreated mice developed severe damage typical of acute kidney injury. This suggests that kidney cells may be able to recover if they are protected at the cellular level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Why this matters for patient care&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If treatments based on ceramide control can be proven safe and effective in humans, the implications are significant. Instead of waiting for damage to accumulate and eventually relying on dialysis or transplantation, patients may one day receive targeted therapy to restore healthy kidney function shortly after injury. This could dramatically change clinical outcomes for individuals affected by sudden kidney failure caused by infection, surgery complications or medication side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What &lt;keyword id="31340037" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="reversing-kidney-damage" source="keywords"&gt;reversing kidney damage&lt;/keyword&gt; could mean for patients&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hope for recovery after acute kidney injury rather than long-term decline&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Less progression to &lt;keyword id="20063661" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="chronic-kidney-disease" source="keywords"&gt;chronic kidney disease&lt;/keyword&gt; and fewer cases of end-stage kidney failure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reduced need for dialysis or kidney transplantation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improved quality of life and reduced healthcare burden&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Earlier intervention guided by future biomarkers, like urinary ceramide levels&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why caution and further research are essential&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although results are promising, research is still in early stages. The treatment has only been tested in mice, and human kidneys may respond differently. The studies also examined injury prevention rather than full reversal of long-standing kidney damage. Clinical trials will need to confirm safety, dosage, and effectiveness in humans, and it remains unclear how well this method might work for chronic kidney disease with established scarring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What scientists plan to explore next&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research groups are now preparing to test ceramide-targeting drugs in human cell models and, later, early-stage clinical trials. Scientists are also exploring whether combining metabolic therapies, cell regeneration strategies, and anti-fibrosis treatments could enhance kidney repair even further. Another focus is the development of early detection tools, so patients receive support before irreversible scarring forms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The discovery that kidney function can be restored in animal studies challenges one of the longest-held assumptions in nephrology. If researchers succeed in translating these findings to human treatment, the future of kidney care may shift from slowing damage to restoring health. Though there is a long road ahead, the progress already achieved marks an important step toward a future where kidney damage does not have to be permanent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This content is intended purely for informational use and is not a substitute for professional medical, nutritional or scientific advice. Always seek support from certified professionals for personalised recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also read| &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/your-poop-is-more-valuable-than-you-think-why-stool-donors-are-in-demand-and-how-it-can-save-lives/articleshow/125792574.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Your poop is more valuable than you think: Why stool donors are in demand and how it can save lives&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 19:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwJBVV95cUxOZWo0UnN0RFZSV2Q2RWR0WDJGNkVMZUtiakk0cmlncllhUTBtY1puVFF3VEloZkdvTXI2UU5GMmNwSzVmUXhjTENRT252TmsyWmpvMmpBZEJ0Y1YwUm93cWg2MFQ5RjdhTVVHOFQxV3Y4WEtBV3V5SXhaVGY4UmNIWTJGMnhMWG9fTjVLV0dMUUtwQnVwamVMZXUtR0xkS29EX01MYTR6aWFza2wxVXlnb1RmM2xFQjNmSE9qNUZfejZpNlhiMmtiQmhRU2wzWFdIT3pHaGdNcjFaaUpyWkRVVnd5VGg0b09rd3haX3p5dEk1RS1PSzFqRFpUQ3RuZEY3YWsxb3BMV3RtelU1Y0s40gGUAkFVX3lxTE9uaUphSm8wQVVwelBwWFktRFhkeUdfcGw3dlYxSnBDN3Q5Z1FsdlVSdEwwX1RIaklKeGRIcm9oaGhWQkR1RmtBM0swT1VkS2t0eE9TTFQzVFIwMThGUTJhdzBVSWtHeE9XNUFpb2EyaEEyUW5hSkhqNFdrQ191Vk94RXdvanJSYW1yMXhxZjdnaG1GYXdocU4xbTZoNlpNRkdxRmFoeUZlTmFaRDhMeXRrc0xWSGZFOTJkdHh6YXpJZG5CVWFYeHNuLWZCNV9teVNqdlcwWTB1b01qVGNiSnZUWVNkQWxOUl9jSEw3NDJjTlA5UkRxREVlQ2oza2Z0N2N6SnBJNkxFRUpmeDBrX0dETFpuSw</guid></item><item><title>黑死病的全球蔓延与地球另一侧的火山爆发有关-印度国防评论</title><link>https://indiandefencereview.com/black-deaths-spread-volcanic-eruption/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-entry-content"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Black Death&lt;/strong&gt; remains one of the most tragic and far-reaching pandemics in history, killing millions in Europe during the 14th century. New research published in &lt;em&gt;Communications Earth &amp;amp; Environment&lt;/em&gt; reveals a fascinating connection between the plague’s devastating spread and a volcanic eruption. This groundbreaking study suggests that volcanic activity may have triggered a series of environmental and economic disruptions that made the spread of the plague almost inevitable.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Unseen Forces Behind the Plague’s Spread&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Historically, the origins and rapid spread of the Black Death have been shrouded in mystery. While it’s well-known that the disease was caused by the bacterium &lt;em&gt;Yersinia pestis&lt;/em&gt;, what’s less understood is how the plague reached Europe and became so deadly. The recent study &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s43247-025-02964-0" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;published in &lt;em&gt;Communications Earth &amp;amp; Environment&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; , led by historians and paleontologists, takes a novel approach to this question by suggesting that a volcanic eruption around 1345 CE may have played a pivotal role.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The researchers argue that &lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/campi-flegrei-volcanic-activity-and-risks/" data-type="post" data-id="82071"&gt;volcanic activity&lt;/a&gt;, which likely occurred in the tropics, caused severe climatic disruptions. Using a combination of ice core data, tree rings, and historical records, they found evidence of unusually cold and wet summers&lt;strong&gt; between 1345 and 1347&lt;/strong&gt; across southern Europe. The spike in sulfur levels found in the ice cores from Antarctica and Greenland suggests that a major eruption released vast amounts of sulfur into the atmosphere, leading to a short-term cooling of the planet. This cooling, in turn, severely disrupted agricultural systems across Europe.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As crops failed and food shortages became widespread, famine ensued. This created a perfect storm for the plague, which had already been spreading in Central Asia. The researchers explain, “We used climate proxy and written documentary archives to argue that a yet unidentified volcanic eruption, or a cluster of eruptions around 1345 CE, contributed to cold and wet climate conditions between 1345 and 1347 CE across much of southern Europe.”&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt="A map of the grain shipment plague vectors of the late 1340s. (Bauch &amp;amp; Büntgen, Commun. Earth Environ., 2025)
" class="wp-image-98196" data-lazy-srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/image-20.png 642w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/image-20-380x269.png 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/image-20-520x368.png 520w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" data-lazy-src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/image-20.png"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/image-20.png" alt="A map of the grain shipment plague vectors of the late 1340s. (Bauch &amp;amp; Büntgen, Commun. Earth Environ., 2025)
" class="wp-image-98196" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/image-20.png 642w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/image-20-380x269.png 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/image-20-520x368.png 520w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;A map of the grain shipment plague vectors of the late 1340s. (Bauch &amp;amp; Büntgen, &lt;em&gt;Commun. Earth Environ.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Role of Trade Routes in Plague Transmission&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study also highlights how the economic and trade routes of the time facilitated the spread of the disease. In 1347, the Italian maritime republics of Venice, Genoa, and Pisa were in dire need of grain to feed their populations. As a result of the famine caused by the cooling climate, these city-states were forced to reconfigure their supply chains. They turned to the Mongol empire, particularly the Golden Horde, for grain shipments from the Sea of Azov.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This shift in trade networks, however, unwittingly introduced a new risk. The grain shipments carried fleas infected with &lt;em&gt;Yersinia pestis&lt;/em&gt;, which were thriving in the fur of rats aboard the ships. These fleas spread the disease to humans, particularly in port cities like Messina, Genoa, and Venice, where the first European outbreaks of the plague were recorded.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study asserts, “This climatic anomaly and subsequent transregional famine forced the Italian maritime republics of Venice, Genoa, and Pisa to reconfigure their supply network and import grain from the Mongols of the Golden Horde around the Sea of Azov in 1347 CE.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A Perfect Storm: Climate, Trade, and the Plague’s Arrival&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The chain of events triggered by the volcanic eruption created an environmental crisis that fed directly into the social and economic vulnerabilities of 14th-century Europe. While the grain shipments from the Golden Horde were necessary for survival, they inadvertently became vectors for one of history’s deadliest pandemics. By the time the grain reached European ports, it was too late to prevent the disease from spreading.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The researchers explain that the dramatic changes in trade routes, along with the weakened state of European populations due to famine, contributed significantly to the rapid spread of the plague. The disease moved through the Mediterranean basin, reaching Italy in 1347 and continuing northward into France, Spain, and beyond. “The unusual change in long-distance maritime grain trade prevented large parts of Italy from starvation and distributed the plague bacterium &lt;em&gt;Yersinia pestis&lt;/em&gt; via infected fleas in grain cargo across much of the Mediterranean basin, from where the second plague pandemic emerged into the largest mortality crisis in pre-modern times.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Aftermath: A Pandemic That Shaped History&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Black Death’s impact was not only medical but also social, economic, and cultural. The death toll was staggering, with estimates suggesting that anywhere from one-third to half of Europe’s population perished. Entire communities were wiped out, and the economic structure of Europe was forever changed. The epidemic also had profound effects on the course of human history, influencing everything from labor markets to social structures.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In hindsight, the confluence of volcanic eruption, climate change, famine, and the reconfiguration of trade routes seems like an improbable series of events. Yet, this study shows how environmental factors beyond human control, combined with economic needs, set the stage for one of history’s most catastrophic pandemics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Indian Defence Review</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 19:35:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE9MMm5fbGhLQXlJZXlGNTdHSDl4TEJlQUoxUHplVFZVc3pEMjIxMnhDVWd2My1UQlRZT3FLTG9YUHh5VHFkbC1LTjBMc3RfU212R282MDd4b3N3OTVRaUpBX2lIbl9oc3g5cFd4YVp4NEN0Z2ZPZVU3MHNn</guid></item><item><title>温暖和拥抱增强了做自己的感觉-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://neurosciencenews.com/temperature-hugging-body-awareness-30020/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;Changes in skin temperature play a key role in how strongly we experience our bodies as our own. Thermoception influences emotion, identity, and mental health by acting as a direct “skin-to-brain” pathway supporting bodily self-awareness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disruptions in thermal perception are linked to altered body ownership in conditions such as stroke, anorexia, depression, and trauma-related disorders. These insights open avenues for sensory-based therapies, more natural-feeling prosthetics, and new ways to understand climate-related effects on cognition and mood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skin-to-Brain Pathway:&lt;/strong&gt; Temperature signals directly shape bodily self-awareness and emotional grounding.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clinical Relevance:&lt;/strong&gt; Disturbed thermal perception is tied to altered body ownership in several mental health and neurological conditions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Therapeutic Potential:&lt;/strong&gt; Findings may guide sensory-based interventions, prosthetic design, and rehabilitation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Queen Mary University London&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As winter closes in, you might start to notice your fingers and toes freezing when you go outside, or your face flushing hot when you go into a heated building. In these moments of changing temperature, we become more aware of our bodies.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until now, bodily temperature has been seen as a purely physiological signal. But a new review published in Trends in Cognitive Sciences looks at how ‘thermoception’ – our perception of changes in skin temperature, such as a warm hug or a chill in the air – influences how strongly we experience our bodies as “our own.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The article, by Dr Laura Crucianelli, Lecturer in Psychology at Queen Mary University of London and Professor Gerardo Salvato of the University of Pavia, reviews decades of research in neuroscience, psychology and clinical science. The findings expand the neuroscience of bodily self-awareness to include temperature, revealing a previously overlooked pathway through which the body communicates with the brain.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers propose that the link between thermoception and body temperature regulation contributes not only to survival and comfort, but also touches on emotion, identity, and mental health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Temperature is one of our most ancient senses,” says Dr Crucianelli. “Warmth is one of the earliest signals of protection – we feel it in the womb, in early caregiving, and whenever someone holds us close. It keeps us alive, but it also helps us feel like ourselves. By studying how the brain interprets warmth and cold, we can begin to understand how the body shapes the mind.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Altered body awareness is a feature of several mental health conditions, including eating disorders, depression, anxiety, and trauma-related disorders. Sufferers can feel a sense of detachment or disconnection from themselves.  Clinical evidence from stroke, anorexia nervosa and body integrity dysphoria shows that disruptions in thermal perception may accompany disturbances in body ownership.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Salvato says: “For example, we now know from experimental studies that thermal signals play a fundamental role in clinical conditions. People with altered temperature regulation and temperature perception, due to a brain stroke, may develop pathological conditions according to which they do not recognize part of their bodies as belonging to themselves”.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond the lab, these findings carry wide implications.  Understanding the contribution of thermal signals and the “skin-to-brain” dialogue opens up possible new avenues for identifying mechanisms of vulnerability and developing sensory-based interventions for mental health. For example, it may improve rehabilitation for neurological patients, inform the design of prosthetics that feel more natural, and guide mental health interventions.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The review also highlights the potential impact of climate change and extreme temperature exposure on body awareness and cognition.  Drs Crucianelli and Salvato adds, “As global temperatures rise, understanding how warmth and cold shape the relationship with ourselves may help explain shifts in mood, stress, and bodily awareness in everyday life”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So why DO warm hugs make us feel good about ourselves? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When we hug, the combination of tactile and thermal signals increases our sense of body ownership, so we are more connected to our embodied sense of self,” says Dr Crucianelli. “Feeling warm touch on the skin enhances our ability to sense ourselves from the inside and recognise our own existence. We feel, ‘this is my body, and I am grounded in it.’” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientifically put, warm interpersonal contact engages specialised C-tactile afferents and thermosensitive pathways that project to the insular cortex, facilitating interoceptive signalling associated with safety and affective regulation. This sensory input is accompanied by oxytocin release and reductions in physiological stress, supporting social bonding and enhancing bodily self-awareness, and ultimately, wellbeing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, “Warm touch reminds us that we are connected, valued, and part of a social world,” says Dr Crucianelli. “Humans are wired for social closeness, and hugs briefly dissolve the boundary between ‘self’ and ‘other’.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Key Questions Answered:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq wp-block-yoast-faq-block"&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1764960558119"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: How does temperature influence the sense of self?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; Thermal signals shape bodily self-awareness by reinforcing the feeling that the body belongs to us, influencing identity, grounding, and emotional regulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1764960559928"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Which conditions show altered thermal perception and body awareness?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; Disruptions appear in stroke, anorexia, depression, anxiety, and trauma-related disorders, where individuals may experience detachment or reduced body ownership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1764960559336"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: How might this research guide new therapies?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; Understanding thermal pathways could improve sensory-based mental health interventions, enhance prosthetic design, and support rehabilitation strategies for neurological patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Editorial Notes:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list has-background"&gt;&lt;li&gt;This article was edited by a Neuroscience News editor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Journal paper reviewed in full.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Additional context added by our staff.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this emotion and temperature research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#117a3f6570687d7e633c767e7e736851607c647d3f70723f647a" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Katy Taylor-Gooby&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://qmul.ac.uk" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Queen Mary University London&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Katy Taylor-Gooby – Queen Mary University London&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.tics.2025.11.008" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Shaping bodily self-awareness through thermosensory signals&lt;/a&gt;” by Laura Crucianelli et al. &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Trends in Cognitive Sciences&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shaping bodily self-awareness through thermosensory signals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cutaneous thermosensory signals are a fundamental component of human evolution and individual development, supporting physiological regulation and survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent behavioral and clinical evidence suggests that thermal signals from the skin contribute to the construction of body ownership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The insular and parietal cortices may underlie the relationship between cutaneous thermosensory signals and body ownership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding how thermosensory signals shape body ownership offers translational insights with implications for neurorehabilitation, prosthetic embodiment, and human adaptation to environmental change.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 19:04:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTFBncFVkSG5lSlhnakhuQklNUTRHaGdfQlpGbG16VFR2cDNUVGNaQ1FKQjRRNHlKNmVnTWZPajBjYk85OU53NU9XNjl0cFBtMmVEMjdBdVFkaTZVSjhIaWlYaVdmckxXdURMRG1nUkV2UTFLUzhTREYxZnRR</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心专家组建议推迟乙型肝炎疫苗的出生剂量- statnews.com</title><link>https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/05/cdc-hepatitis-b-vaccination-acip-panel-overturns-30-year-policy/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A panel that advises on U.S. vaccine policy voted on Friday to recommend a delay in when most babies begin to be vaccinated against hepatitis B, overturning a 30-year-old policy that has contributed to a &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/09/11/newborn-hep-b-vaccine-debate-how-it-started/"&gt;massive decline in cases of the virus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices voted 8-3 to recommend the change, following &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/04/cdc-acip-meeting-hepatitis-b-birth-dose/"&gt;more than a day of contentious discussion&lt;/a&gt;. The new recommendation is that parents should discuss with their doctors whether to give the hepatitis B vaccine at birth, or at all, and that those who choose to do so should wait to begin the vaccine series until their baby is at least 2 months old.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That recommendation applies to mothers who test negative for hepatitis B during their pregnancy. The previous recommendation, in place since 1991, was that all babies receive a dose of hepatitis B vaccine at birth.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The change has to be endorsed by Jim O’Neill, the acting director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, or by health secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. before it becomes part of the CDC vaccination schedule.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The vote was quickly denounced by Sen. Bill Cassidy, (R-La.), a physician whose support was critical to Kennedy securing Senate confirmation. Cassidy urged federal health officials to reject it.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;“As a liver doctor who has treated patients with hepatitis B for decades, this change to the vaccine schedule is a mistake,” Cassidy wrote &lt;a href="https://x.com/SenBillCassidy/status/1996974038413971766" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;on the social media site X&lt;/a&gt;. “This makes America sicker.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The recommendation, if adopted, seems likely to deepen the fracturing in U.S. vaccine recommendations. The American Academy of Pediatrics said it would continue to advise that infants receive a birth dose of hepatitis B vaccine. And New York State’s Department of Health said in a statement that it would continue to tell medical practitioners to offer the birth dose.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The vote does not change the policy for babies born to mothers who tested positive for hepatitis B during pregnancy or whose hepatitis B status is unknown. They should continue to receive a dose of vaccine within 12 hours of birth as well as a dose of hepatitis B immune globulin.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Ending the recommendation for a universal dose of hepatitis B vaccine at birth would be Kennedy’s &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/09/19/what-acip-meeting-says-about-vaccine-schedule-rfk-restoring-trust-vaccines/"&gt;latest move against vaccines&lt;/a&gt;, and arguably the most significant to date. Before becoming health secretary, Kennedy was the founder of the anti-vaccine group Children’s Health Defense. He has been using his platform as health secretary to rapidly change vaccination policy and undermine confidence in vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The votes will not affect insurance coverage for hepatitis B shots, including under Medicaid and the Children’s Health Insurance Program. Likewise, the CDC said it would not affect coverage through the Vaccines for Children program.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;No fresh safety concerns or effectiveness issues prompted ACIP to reconsider the hepatitis B vaccine birth dose. Instead, panelists said the review was prompted by parents concerned about the shot, the fact that most European countries give the immunization a few months after birth, and the length of time since ACIP last reviewed the topic. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Some ACIP members — including Retsef Levi, an operations management professor at MIT’s Sloan School of Management, and Evelyn Griffin, an OB-GYN from Baton Rouge General Hospital — argued that vaccinating infants against the virus was in effect requiring babies to face a risk because society hadn’t managed to come up with programs that drive the virus out of the adult population in the United States. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Throughout the discussion there were repeated claims from ACIP members who voted against the birth dose that the risk to most babies was very low and that hepatitis B is largely a disease of sex workers, drug users, and immigrants from countries with high rates of infection.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;All pregnant people are supposed to be tested for hepatitis B during pregnancy. But testing doesn’t always occur, some test results are faulty, and some pregnant people become infected later in pregnancy, after being tested, resulting in babies slipping through the safety net meant to protect them against infection at birth.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;After the birth dose policy was adopted in 1991, the number of infants and babies who tested positive for hepatitis B &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/09/11/newborn-hep-b-vaccine-debate-how-it-started/"&gt;plummeted&lt;/a&gt; into single or low-double digits, from the thousands.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;James Campbell, vice chair of the American Academy of Pediatrics’ committee on infectious diseases, said the new policy, if added to the CDC’s childhood vaccine schedule, will put children in harm’s way. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;He noted that before the birth dose policy was adopted, he cared for a 15-year-old girl in Baltimore who had become chronically infected with hepatitis B. The girl, who hadn’t been vaccinated in infancy because it was not believed she was at risk of contracting the virus, died after having two failed liver transplants. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“This is a very dangerous decision. It will certainly cause harm,” Campbell said. The AAP, which has nonvoting liaison membership on the ACIP, has been boycotting meetings of the group since Kennedy &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/06/09/rfk-jr-fires-every-member-of-cdc-vaccine-expert-panel-acip/"&gt;fired the previous panel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Cody Meissner, an ACIP member who is a pediatrician, said there are abundant data to suggest the vaccine is safe and that the risk to babies from the virus is real. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Meissner was joined in his opposition to the change by Joseph Hibbeln, a psychiatrist and neuroscientist, and by Raymond Pollak, a surgeon and transplant specialist, who did not detail his opposition to the change. &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2025.11.24.25340907v1" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;modeling study&lt;/a&gt; posted online late last month estimates that delaying the start of hepatitis B vaccination by two months could lead to &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/02/cdc-acip-meeting-hepatitis-b-shots-vaccine-integrity-project/"&gt;more than 1,400 babies becoming chronically infected&lt;/a&gt; with hepatitis B in the first year of the change, which could result in 304 cases of liver cancer and 482 hepatitis B-related deaths among those children as they age. The study is a preprint; it has not yet been published in a peer-reviewed journal.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;An estimated 90% of babies infected in infancy become chronically infected with the virus, which can lead to liver disease and premature death from liver cancer or cirrhosis. About a quarter of children chronically infected in early life will die prematurely from liver disease.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Many liaison members — representatives of the professional organizations that have direct interest in vaccination policy — also argued against the change.&lt;br&gt;The ACIP meeting bore little resemblance to those of the past, with CDC subject matter experts effectively sidelined or silenced, and data presentations being made by people with ties to the anti-vaccine community but little expertise in the assessment of vaccine data. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of Friday’s session, acting chair Robert Malone noted that two prominent proponents of vaccines — and critics of Kennedy and the new ACIP — had been invited to make presentations to the committee. But both Paul Offit, director of the Children’s Hospital of Philadelphia’s Vaccine Education Center, and Peter Hotez, director of the Texas Children’s Hospital Center for Vaccine Development, declined the invitation, he said. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Offit told STAT the request was made via his hospital’s speaker’s bureau in October, and did not indicate when he would be asked to address ACIP or on what topic. But even if he’d known he was being asked to speak to this meeting, he would not have agreed, he said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I don’t want to legitimize what I think is an illegitimate process. I don’t want to be part of a process that gives bad advice, that’s putting children in harm’s way,” Offit said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Hotez &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/05/health/kennedy-vaccine-committee-vote-hepatitisb.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;told the New York Times&lt;/a&gt; he declined the invitation for similar reasons.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;At times during the hepatitis B discussion, the committee acknowledged they didn’t have data to support some of the things they were recommending — the suggestion, for instance, that the first dose of hepatitis B not be given before a baby is 2 months old. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A similar situation arose with the second vote put to the committee, a recommendation that parents who choose to vaccinate their babies against hepatitis B should ask for a serology test of the baby after the first dose, to see if additional doses are actually needed. The hepatitis B vaccine for young children is given in a three- or four-dose regimen.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Several ACIP members — including new chair Kirk Milhoan — conceded there are no data to suggest that a single dose of the vaccine would provide long-lasting protection. The recommendation appeared to be crafted on the understanding that some babies achieve an antibody titer after one dose that is believed to be protective after three doses. But Meissner noted that all the studies looking at the effectiveness of the vaccine were done on the three-dose series.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;“We have no idea if less than three doses of the vaccine will be protective,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Adam Langer, a CDC subject matter expert who was asked to comment on the proposal, agreed, saying the committee “would be making a real huge assumption” to conclude that data generated after three doses of vaccine would apply to a single dose, and create durable protection.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Milhoan said he would have been comfortable voting instead to recommend that the issue of whether three doses are needed should be studied. But he didn’t propose an amendment to the voting language, and voted with the majority of the committee to make the recommendation. It passed by a vote of 6-4, with one abstention. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Later on Friday, Aaron Siri, an attorney with ties to Kennedy, led the committee through a &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/05/aaron-siri-vaccine-critic-presents-acip-meeting/"&gt;sweeping, 76-slide presentation&lt;/a&gt; that broadly addresses the childhood vaccine schedule. In the slides, Siri invited the committee to consider revisiting “prior recommendations made without robust data” and requiring “robust trial and, when possible, post-licensure safety data.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;An ACIP working group, which includes people with ties to vaccine-skeptical groups, is currently reviewing the entire schedule. It’s not yet known what changes to the childhood vaccine schedule the committee may decide to consider.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Daniel Payne and Chelsea Cirruzzo contributed reporting.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:37:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxPM3FEQjZuZTlOdG5LUTRDc0NXMU5iSnY0dGdvWjVreDhOdEFPTDZsdkh1bGcwX1IxRktPMWN6dkI0bW1YWkcyZW41VGctckNQRllJOFZpa2tjbnJSTFJtVHNpdFVxc3NKSzcwd3diN1ROVS1oa25hQTg3VUhsQy1wYTZfa0U0MTk1Y0RKZUxoLXBYdkRZb0RKTnFfUk9pS09xLVE</guid></item><item><title>专栏|我怀疑我体内潜伏着一个隐藏的杀手。这是我的发现。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/05/full-body-mri-scan-experience/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BD2TJB52EZAVZLHOJ7RBVXX6MM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Nine out of 10 doctors agree: I am a highly creative hypochondriac.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YLX2RVY55RDNLEOOSB2SYKO6LE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Using medical expertise I obtained from the internet, I have successfully misdiagnosed myself with, among other things: heart disease, pancreatitis, liver and kidney disorders, a blood platelet deficiency, malignancies of the colon and prostate, Lyme disease and memory loss (although I don’t recall exactly when that was). The pain I sometimes get when I sleep on my side? Must be cancer. Headache after a hard workout? Brain aneurysm. My tombstone will say, “I told you so.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxQaWVYU2VWOENJRmFscFJSSnoyUHpCS1JyNG9OSUNTVlpuS0ZyWldzbHY3SE9aZFIyOER0UVBFaGhhQW9HblJWeWI3S2l6WDFSaDhpaFdMbGJyS1JyNjJ1bXFPcEY5a19XV1g3QW1kb2lZUENfX2ltcUtIOURYRzNBaTBaMFBLdw</guid></item><item><title>根据RFK Jr. ， CDC专家组对儿童疫苗接种时间表进行了最彻底的修订。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/05/acip-childhood-immunization-schedule-hepatitis-b/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FGUDHUWB5VEJHFHTKF42E55C7U" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;ATLANTA — An influential vaccine advisory panel on Friday voted to lift a long-standing recommendation that all newborns receive a vaccine for hepatitis B, marking the most significant change to the childhood immunization schedule under Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:57:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxObDdmdnRMSlBhcGhuZFkzRF9JbHdxSXdGSk04Uml4S2JJYXlXUkFqSVVvVkwtN2ZTTmRLRGJQRTl5Q1F5bkpLYnlOYnlEMVdtaEZreTk0YUVVRDZ5aW9UTUNaS3Vla2labHRTZHU2QmUydEF3U2VxaGtQbzRqbUlZV2NralhSYzBJWVZOUkZuaHZGRUdEN1VfSVFTRlFXVXM</guid></item><item><title>肝炎：有关症状、诊断和治疗的知识-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/05/well/hepatitis-symptoms-treatment.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:46:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE11TEhLZERtaTBncHU1VkI0OHltbmk2QUlhMFlOZFN2eGxBVXR6cnFQWU5GRkdDMWkyMDNnVkhDcWRkcjVwcjhyU1dNNnpac3RmWjl6RG9rQXo3bVMxeFd5cjVhcjRhMTNPSnRBTk5XRFI1YXA4Z0hIUkFkSVFRQQ</guid></item><item><title>罕见的各种因素触发黑死病- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/science/2025/12/how-volcanoes-helped-spark-the-black-death/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
          
          
&lt;figure class="ars-wp-img-shortcode id-2130579 align-none"&gt;
    
          &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption font-impact dusk:text-gray-300 mb-4 mt-2 inline-flex flex-row items-stretch gap-1 text-base leading-tight text-gray-400 dark:text-gray-300"&gt;
    &lt;p class="caption-icon bg-[left_top_5px] w-[10px] shrink-0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class="caption-content"&gt;
      Close-up of tree ring samples taken from the Pyrenees, showing the telltale “blue rings.”

              &lt;span class="caption-credit mt-2 text-xs"&gt;
          Credit:

          
          Ulf Büntgen

                  &lt;/span&gt;
          &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tree ring data enabled Büntgen et al. to determine that there had been a volcanic eruption (or a cluster of eruptions) around 1345, specifically so-called “blue rings” that indicate unusually cold or wet summers—in this case, for three consecutive years (1345, 1346, and 1347). The textual sources also referenced details like an unusually high degree of cloudiness and darkened lunar eclipses, indications of the after-effects of volcanic activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That colder climate in turn led to widespread crop failures and associated famine, particularly in parts of Spain, southern France, Egypt, and northern and central Italy. While Milan and Rome were largely self-sufficient, per the authors, smaller urban centers like Bologna, Florence, Genoa, Siena, and Venice relied on a complex grain supply system to import grain from the Mongols of the Golden Horde via established trade routes along the Black Sea coast. Textual evidence supports this, showing substantial price hikes for cereals and the imposition of grain trade regulations in 1346. This saved people from starvation but also brought Y. pestis along for the ride, with devastating consequences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Per the authors, while the factors that triggered the spread of the Black Death to Europe are unique, the study illustrates the risks of a globalized world and calls for a similar interdisciplinary approach to future threats. “Although the coincidence of factors that contributed to the Black Death seems rare, the probability of zoonotic diseases emerging under climate change and translating into pandemics is likely to increase in a globalized world,” &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107493?"&gt;said Büntgen&lt;/a&gt;. “This is especially relevant given our recent experiences with COVID-19.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Communications Earth &amp;amp; Environment, 2025. DOI: &lt;a href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1038/s43247-025-02964-0"&gt;10.1038/s43247-025-02964-0&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="http://arstechnica.com/science/news/2010/03/dois-and-their-discontents-1.ars"&gt;About DOIs&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;


          
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                  
          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:44:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNWllENzA1R3FIeHdRUDU5X1c0ekVpNWdYNmp5d2trRXJsVlNoNXBRT3Rmd2JTemVCY2doUmpWX00zWE9IXy13TWotdkhrQVJaRnZWNVJicWRaMFBHT0JNaGsyYlpzdlR1ZkpHRHlIOHlNaElkM3dmUnlONUN1Z2lJUWx1OGpHYmFjVzlv</guid></item><item><title>关于“scromiting”的知识， “scromiting”是潜在致命大麻病症的不寻常症状- Axios</title><link>https://www.axios.com/2025/12/05/scromiting-symptom-cannabis-hyperemesis-syndrome</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:31:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxPa1ZmOGJmY3FxMnNqbWJuUlp0MzJGZFBMTHhuTjNuVUN4TUdHTWFPNHl3SEZ6U3RfX0xCcmdFekNaaGpfbVI1RktuTDc5d3lGOFN3QngyUS1QVG9nVWtRXzRxOFJxRkhCejNrUXk1MFhqeUZOQlpXcEtUM1dCcWdQODlYTlVnUTNx</guid></item></channel></rss>