<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>疾控中心员工因被解雇、重新雇用和再次解雇而陷入混乱： “陷入困境” -《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/oct/31/cdc-employees-hiring-firing-limbo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;As layoff notices swept through the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) on 10 October, Aryn Melton Backus thought she would be safe this time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Then she received the email: she was part of a major reduction in force (RIF) during the US government shutdown. It wasn’t the first time she’d been fired from the CDC by email, nor the second.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Backus has been terminated and then reinstated three times &lt;em&gt;this year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Her experience demonstrates the inefficiencies and tumult at US health agencies as leaders continue cutting into the workforce and ending programs vital for Americans’ health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The latest round of shutdown RIFs is illegal, &lt;a href="https://www.afge.org/publication/federal-employee-unions-file-expanded-lawsuit-challenging-trump-administrations-illegal-shutdown-firings/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;according&lt;/a&gt; to the American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE), which is among the unions representing federal workers that are suing the government to stop the layoffs. A quarter of the CDC has now been cut by multiple rounds of layoffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="1a988aa5-7f8a-4ea5-8130-5c256b108904" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":5,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"New York declares state of emergency to issue food banks $65m amid shutdown","elementId":"1a988aa5-7f8a-4ea5-8130-5c256b108904","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/oct/30/new-york-food-banks-emergency-shutdown"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":10,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some employees who had to work without pay through the shutdown received RIF notices; others who were furloughed learned they would never return to their jobs. Employees who were supposed to be protected from RIFs by an ongoing lawsuit received them anyway. The human resources department at CDC was brought back from unpaid furlough in order to process about 1,300 layoffs – and then their own, as the entire HR department was eliminated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some of the gutted departments are required by law to continue their work, despite having no employees. The ethics office and the institutional review board (IRB) were also ended, which means the CDC will no longer have oversight on ethical violations and research protocols.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The entire library staff at the CDC, an integral part of research and recommendations, was terminated. The Washington office, which developed policy briefings and provided information to Congress members, was eliminated as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The National Center for Chronic Disease Prevention and &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/health" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; Promotion, the national health and nutrition examination survey, and the staff focused on suicide prevention also suffered layoffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The multiple cuts across the agency mean the CDC is not able to carry out much of its work, even as some employees remain, said Karen Remley, who previously ran the National Center on Birth Defects and Developmental Disabilities and was a state health official in Virginia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In April, for instance, the entire team behind the Pregnancy Risk Assessment Monitoring System (Prams) was cut, which means a critical tool for understanding maternal and child health is now missing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“You can’t take out Prams and keep the registry and have all that work happen,” Remley said. “This artificial separating and splitting really means the work on the local level stops.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Meanwhile, CDC employees have endured attacks and harassment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;On 8 August, a gunman fired 500 rounds of ammunition at the CDC headquarters, killing David Rose, an officer, and traumatizing agency employees and their families.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Health agency employees have been doxed, with their identities and personal information revealed. Matthew Buckham, Kennedy’s acting chief of staff, was co-founder of the group that maintains a “DEI Watch List” targeting HHS employees. The agency has also been roiled by high-profile &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/sep/17/rfk-jr-senate-hearing-cdc-susan-monarez" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;departures&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“At the highest level of leadership in the CDC, there are no public health or medical professionals left to help guide CDC recommendations,” said Abigail Tighe, a former CDC employee and founding member of the National Public Health Coalition, which held a recent press conference where Backus and other former CDC employees spoke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Billions in contracts and direct funding to state and local public health agencies has been canceled or clawed back, and the American people are cued up to suffer. It is hard to succinctly put into words what the decimation of the CDC means for everyday Americans.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The first round of layoffs at CDC came on Valentine’s day. Probationary employees – who were in the first year or two of their jobs, either because they had been recently hired or had moved to new positions – along with &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/feb/20/trump-fired-health-employees" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;established senior employees&lt;/a&gt; received notices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A judge &lt;a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.cand.444883/gov.uscourts.cand.444883.261.0.pdf" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;ruled&lt;/a&gt; in September that the probationary terminations went too far and some of the employees were reinstated and placed on administrative leave.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the meantime, RIF notices went out on 1 April, eliminating entire offices such as the office on smoking and health, where Backus worked. She didn’t even receive the notice at first because her access to the CDC network, including email, had been cut off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The lawsuit specifically prevents employees like Backus from being reorganized into new offices or terminated from the agency, she said. That’s why she thought she would be safe this time – but she still received a third layoff notice. That notice was rescinded after less than 24 hours. About 700 employees were reinstated, while 600 &lt;a href="http://theguardian.com/us-news/2025/oct/14/cdc-job-cuts-partial-reversal" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;remain terminated&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“I still remain on administrative leave, unable to do my job,” Backus said. “My situation just highlights the chaos and confusion that federal employees have experienced over the past year. I’m stuck in limbo, following court cases, gathering information, and trying to figure out what my next steps should be.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Charlotte Kent, former editor-in-chief of the Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report (MMWR), said: “We have so many people who, if they’ve been [un-RIFed], have been on administrative leave. We have the inefficiency of so many government resources, our taxpayer dollars, going to fight the illegal activities that have been done by the administration.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The MMWR was among the departments completely gutted and then reinstated – which was particularly surprising, because the highly regarded scientific journal was specifically included in the president’s budget request for the first time this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“To have it cut at this point is just shocking,” Kent said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s like being in a strange game where there’s no rules,” said one former CDC employee who was RIFed on 10 October and spoke anonymously to avoid reprisal from the &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/trump-administration" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Trump administration&lt;/a&gt;. “It’s honestly like Squid Games – we don’t know what’s going to happen next.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;John Brooks, who retired last year from the CDC after 26 years and served as the chief medical officer for several emergency responses, said the RIFs demonstrated a “stunning level of incompetency”. Firing the CDC Washington staff means “Congress no longer has a means of direct access to the agency it funds when it needs information or briefings”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Trump administration &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/government-shutdown-live-updates-as-military-poised-to-miss-first-paychecks-next-week/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;reportedly&lt;/a&gt; says about 700 of the terminations were a coding error.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It is clear to us that this was not a coding error,” said Tighe. “This RIF was carried out just as all the other ones have been, where they fire as many people as they think they can get away with, there’s public outcry, there’s outcry from congressional members and then they bring back the things that they think people cannot get over.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;She called the firings “an intentional attack on the American people and the public’s health”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Our country is on an uncertain and frankly frightening path,” Tighe said. “We would love to see Congress step in.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNejJUUTZISC1UOUtOdlVMOU5jczR0eHloTXZ6RFlpdjFnWVJMUjZ6aExyQURPNXNFeHFlVXVTaHFldGY2UkxHc0FBNnk4S1BIQUFDc2diSmJMMGd1c3YzaGpPd1EzREVEZmRxQmN4RjU3d3RmTXpaVzdJVVpZWVMzQi1BZ2taSE83</guid></item><item><title>我可能仍然患有前列腺癌，但我已经是幸存者- AL.com</title><link>https://www.al.com/news/2025/10/i-may-still-have-prostate-cancer-but-im-already-a-survivor.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MMBCSYCYONDKXDE4UWJO5PLRXA"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;This is an opinion column.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MNZRLCJGQFFSXH254C5HOCLW5Y"&gt;Sometimes I get mixed up. That’s not unusual. Not at this age. You’d think, though, that I’d be crystal clear about my prostate cancer treatment. About the active surveillance treatment path that I chose to pursue &lt;a href="https://www.al.com/news/2025/07/johnson-i-have-prostate-cancer-and-the-faith-to-beat-it.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.al.com/news/2025/07/johnson-i-have-prostate-cancer-and-the-faith-to-beat-it.html"&gt;after being diagnosed with the disease&lt;/a&gt; this summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="E45CPNPCKRGARI3FSGPW7IKZ7M"&gt;Except sometimes I call it active &lt;i&gt;waiting&lt;/i&gt;, and it’s not the medically correct term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WN7MXZIBEBDVDLSLZDNBF5SJXU"&gt;Active &lt;i&gt;surveillance &lt;/i&gt;is getting a PSA test every six months or so to measure the level of prostate-specific antigen in my blood. If it rises significantly, surgery and/or radiation are more aggressive treatment options. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UU5SG7KGFZAR5CFJ4ADJJU5LMU"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Read more of Roy’s ‘&lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.al.com/topic/cancer%20chronicles/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.al.com/topic/cancer%20chronicles/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cancer Chronicles&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;.’&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3N3FPPSUJFE2NK6NHAH2VACUEQ"&gt;My PSA score in July was 4-almost-5, a spike from prior annual tests, which prompted my primary care physician to send me to a urologist. Weeks later, a biopsy confirmed prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RRP4FZ357ZGZZPDJSK2VIDASAI"&gt;Damn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TCAH4ZB43BCYHJH42OHOKHDNVQ"&gt;Yet I was not wholly surprised. One in eight men in America will be diagnosed with the disease this year, and one in six Black men. If a direct relative — a father or brother, for instance — had or has prostate cancer, you’re a near-lock to get it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="L2SF3U7R4JA7ZAILMEQ5GDEH5M"&gt;My father died of prostate cancer when I was 11 years old. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="C5WALNRQ75CTPNF6UVXVWEISDE"&gt;Again, not wholly surprised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ICYMK2SLX5DUJAJTYDXQXXSAZU"&gt;That doesn’t mean I wasn’t scared more than at any time in my life (and I love roller-coasters). Scared to death when I heard the C-word referring to me. Scared &lt;i&gt;of&lt;/i&gt; death. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="T4ANH6TRVJDVJBSRBAO2P3QAZ4"&gt;Weeks later, back in September &lt;a href="https://www.al.com/news/2025/07/johnson-i-have-prostate-cancer-and-the-faith-to-beat-it.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;when I first told you that I’ve been diagnosed with prostate cancer,&lt;/a&gt; I shared, too, that my faith gives me confidence that I’ll beat it. I’ve long held onto Isaiah 40:31 as one of my go-to scriptures, knowing that &lt;i&gt;those who wait upon the Lord shall renew their strength&lt;/i&gt;. It became my mantra as my wife and I navigated the waves of treatment options, including surgery and/or radiation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="K6AN4O7TEJHFBHW7TGIPRM445Y"&gt;My cancer was deemed stage 2, a slow-moving cancer confirmed by a genetic test. And because I caught it early, thanks to regular PSA testing at annual checkups, active surveillance was a viable option.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ROPDRLCLXRH4VG4VRFRF2DQAXY"&gt;And it’s the one we chose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XV4J4QFJVZG2FJBEHUTFIWW4FU"&gt;I am not alone, surprisingly. In September, &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/24/well/live/prostate-cancer-treatment-explainer.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;The New York Times published an overview of prostate cancer treatments&lt;/a&gt; and I learned that “today &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/22335873/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;nearly 60 percent of patients&lt;/a&gt; with low-risk cancers choose active monitoring instead of treatment — up from 26 percent in 2014. Some experts believe that number should be higher.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ALJHAIVNFVEL5PJOISPJNYAK5A"&gt;I am &lt;i&gt;far &lt;/i&gt;from alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4WBFLBILFVBUPNX7OKTXMSQHFY"&gt;So, yes, I am waiting because I know &lt;a href="https://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=2%20Corinthians%2012%3A9&amp;amp;version=NIV" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;His power is made perfect in our weakness&lt;/a&gt;. And cancer is a profound weakness that, even as treatments of almost all forms of the disease have drastically improved in my near-70 years of life, kills far too many. Far too many.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ABKLHLKDEFCQBMSFCJ5DEYJEIQ"&gt;My treatment, however, isn’t called waiting. It’s &lt;i&gt;surveillance&lt;/i&gt; — and my cancer was caught soon enough for me to pursue this path. Thank God.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LUHGWAQRLRCPTO7N6YEZPMFFEA"&gt;It’s been almost two months now since I revealed my diagnosis. Sixty days or thereabouts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4DKU3L5WHJAMBAUDUJKRKI44BE"&gt;I don’t recall how long I endured the expected waves of emotions — fear, sadness, grief and some feelings I don’t even remember — before peace won. Peace in the waiting. In the stillness of waiting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="F3DLNEW24FFORHKNAFFRR2S3JI"&gt;Surviving in the waiting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JVNLSAESDJGYDCELHXXZDOV3XQ"&gt;Which is why I sometimes get mixed up and describe my treatment as ... &lt;i&gt;waiting&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-22" data-gaid="inarticle-22"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6FJPXVXMANHT5HY4UFZ57K3KJ4"&gt;I endured the emotional gauntlet, in part, thanks to the unmitigated support of my wife, children, family, my faith fam at Rock City Church, co-workers, and many, many people whom I did not know before sharing my diagnosis. People who are sharing their own personal cancer journeys with me. I find myself praying for as many as are praying for me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-23" data-gaid="inarticle-23"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="E7DWV47KV5DVRADRHD4USODYTY"&gt;That’s why I consider myself a cancer survivor. I know the term. It’s generally meant for those who’ve rung the bell. For those who’ve undergone a bombardment of treatments — surgery and/or chemo or radiation or some treatment I never heard about before — and ultimately became cancer-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-24" data-gaid="inarticle-24"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HMRFMDKYNJC5TN3BUMDGT6IDOE"&gt;Many such survivors reached out to me in the days following my initial Cancer Chronicle. I told each of them: I pray that I’ll be able to join you there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-25" data-gaid="inarticle-25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AVPIIG4ZLZBOXP37JX4FC6TGTM"&gt;I already have. To be clear: I may still have cancer in my body. My next PSA test isn’t scheduled for a long while, but I am fully confident in this — I am a survivor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-26" data-gaid="inarticle-26"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OGY5VQB5XVBTLFHBYHQXFVKTSE"&gt;I survived anxiety. I survived fear. I survived grief. I survived the sadness. I now wake up each day with peace, joy, confidence, and expectation. And I live every moment with urgency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-27" data-gaid="inarticle-27"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ODT33MX4XBHYBBGQGZQUWHCYVM"&gt;I’ve got stuff to do. For me. For the people I love. For others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-28" data-gaid="inarticle-28"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:C2FOL3YYBFB7PEO7BGTDXWOEFA" data-fusion-component="C2FOL3YYBFB7PEO7BGTDXWOEFA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:C2FOL3YYBFB7PEO7BGTDXWOEFA" data-fusion-component="C2FOL3YYBFB7PEO7BGTDXWOEFA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-29" data-gaid="inarticle-29"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4ZFTSODVSFASRJ2IO5ZZHEN2AM"&gt;I recently joined a couple of organizations that are committed to elevating awareness about the need for prostate cancer testing, particularly among Black men. I joined the board of directors of the&lt;a href="https://mikeslivefoundation.org/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt; Mike Slive Foundation for Cancer Research&lt;/a&gt;, which provides early-stage grants for potentially groundbreaking efforts to cure for prostate cancer, and host free PSA testing at various events across Alabama and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-30" data-gaid="inarticle-30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5BY2KYGKONDF5IZVAXQNTOCOAY"&gt;I am also an ambassador for&lt;a href="https://nowincluded.com/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt; NowIncluded&lt;/a&gt;, an online community where people in underrepresented communities are heard and supported throughout their health journey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-31" data-gaid="inarticle-31"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GCDVMF2JDJD5TMI62V6QIOWB3A"&gt;Both entities are committed to saving lives. Our lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-32" data-gaid="inarticle-32"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NSHM4PSXIZHKDKY4FQUIZBDN34"&gt;Because our families need us. Our community needs us. We are needed, gentlemen, to stand up to the challenges of today and tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-33" data-gaid="inarticle-33"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RFES6WJUHJDXHLIMRXU3LXFS74"&gt;To stand up for those who still look to us for guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-34" data-gaid="inarticle-34"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="L7PR7PHJMRFJ7CAP4CUJLQZCEA"&gt;Recently, I shared with one of the NowIncluded leaders that I’m already a prostate survivor. She smiled. “We call that thriving,” she said, “thriving with cancer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-35" data-gaid="inarticle-35"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6ZG2K5T4ANA73GJ3N6CGOJDXNY"&gt;It’s been long proven that a positive attitude can impact health outcomes. So, I’m going to be the healthiest person in every room I walk into. At least I’ll make you think so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-36" data-gaid="inarticle-36"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="447CHTU22ZHOJBUZ4SFXUWK3X4"&gt;My pastor often says we can’t always control our circumstances, but we can always control how we view our circumstances. So each day while I actively survey &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; wait, I count it all joy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-37" data-gaid="inarticle-37"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2BS5QCDNYRGTJKAXNNYASM53ZU"&gt;In truth, I rarely think about my diagnosis. I almost forget I have (or may not) cancer – until someone asks, “How are you?!” Ask with that puppy-dog expression of someone who actually wants to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-38" data-gaid="inarticle-38"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IXVFX2STAJDJHHQZ5DUUWX2LPM"&gt;“Great,” is my response. And my truth. Save for stiff knees and a back that’s been annoyingly aggravating lately, I really feel great. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-39" data-gaid="inarticle-39"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WZPVEYONANGRRBYSOB6FA7VBVA"&gt;I step aside and let His power be made perfect in me, whether I still have cancer or not. Whether or not my PSA rises or falls. Whether I live all of my days with prostate cancer or ring the bell someday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-40" data-gaid="inarticle-40"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SNIED2J67RCUHHAOXJQPIV35CQ"&gt;In all ways, I am a survivor, thriving amid the battle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-41" data-gaid="inarticle-41"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AL.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxNXzhjUFNjYWlOT1A4d0JvU25WV1pqbDcwOF9KRzh5dTBKTW5fd2hFLUlTWGxoangtN21uRnVDdGN0aTJvUzVucG0tazVRSXh2U3F1ckhDX0RzcllKT1RMVWpVdGlPaTNBdVhndGIzVlByenduemRlMzNwSzJDTXB4ZzBiRVZRaHctQTcyMGRpQVRaWHFyUXpwd3JYUdIBrwFBVV95cUxObWh0UmRYMFZ5T01LdVc2Q3R5dy1udUd2YjVqcmoyQXIzWXZ2eGMwNXFBelFYcm9PUmJEOVlhMnpoamptdW0xTHNjQ2ZkNkNWY3ZCeHVqaDVScnVEeHh3Z1g2T2pGU1lVN3hFLUl6dEJGQkR2ZEJmbmpKaUk2eDlqc3I5SWVCenlRa1pfenFLTl95V0RNei1vVFVoZzNyd29HTm1oWURCWjFWVVoyaWxZ</guid></item><item><title>这些是成年人自闭症的9个主要指标，往往被完全忽视- Yahoo Lifestyle Canada</title><link>https://ca.style.yahoo.com/9-major-indicators-autism-adults-103104223.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;You may have seen &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@sunnygiovanni/video/7205024706439728426" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:videos;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;videos&lt;/a&gt; on social media where people detail the signs that made them realize they’re autistic. Viewers are finding them enlightening and comforting as many people  — mainly women — are undiagnosed as they reach adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://neurodivergentinsights.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Megan Anna Neff;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Megan Anna Neff&lt;/a&gt;, a clinical psychologist based in Oregon, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35204992/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:a recent study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;a recent study&lt;/a&gt; found that 80% of women with autism are still undiagnosed at age 18.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There are many reasons for this: For starters, people learn to adjust their behavior to fit in with society. Additionally,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;the autism diagnostic tools used today were developed exclusively on white boys from high socioeconomic status, said &lt;a href="https://www.stephaniegardnerwright.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Stephanie Gardner-Wright;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Stephanie Gardner-Wright&lt;/a&gt;, a licensed master social worker and certified autism clinical specialist in Michigan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There is also a huge focus on the external signs and not so much the internal symptoms of autism, Gardner-Wright said. And those internal symptoms are very different from person to person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“There are so many ways that autism can show up and present,” Neff added. “I think there’s more diversity within autism than there is between autism and allistic.” (Allistic people are folks who aren’t on the autism spectrum.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;That said, there are a number of signs or thought patterns that undiagnosed autistic people may be able to relate to. HuffPost spoke with mental health professionals, including some people who are neurodivergent themselves, about the signs of autism in adulthood:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Feeling Of Being ‘Different’ From Others&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Pixelcatchers / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/laurengarafano/doctors-share-little-things-people-ignore?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Doctors Are Sharing The 16 &amp;quot;Tiny&amp;quot; Health Things That Most People Ignore But 100% Shouldn't;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Doctors Are Sharing The 16 "Tiny" Health Things That Most People Ignore But 100% Shouldn't&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;All four experts shared that it’s common for autistic people to feel different. &lt;a href="https://effectiveartistry.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Brandon Tessers;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Brandon Tessers&lt;/a&gt;, the director of Effective Artistry, a therapy group that supports neurodivergent people, said some folks will describe it as “feeling like an alien sometimes,” while &lt;a href="https://gsapp.rutgers.edu/faculty/vanessa-bal" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Vanessa Bal;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Vanessa Bal&lt;/a&gt;, the director of the Center for Adult Autism Services Psychological Services Clinic at Rutgers University in &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeednews.com/carolinekee/what-is-adenovirus" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:New Jersey;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;New Jersey&lt;/a&gt; said folks describe it as “a lifetime experience of feeling different.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The difference between this feeling and the occasional outsider feeling everyone deals with from time to time is that for autistic folks, this feeling does not come and go and is not only during one specific period, like middle school, Bal told HuffPost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Gardner-Wright added that this is a big indicator and an internal experience at that — you cannot look at a person and know if they feel like an outsider. The feeling could be overpowering or could be more subtle, it depends on the person, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But, it’s important to know that autistic people don’t necessarily feel like outsiders all the time, Bal noted. They may find settings that are more inclusive for neurodivergent people. Additionally, some adults also say they feel more comfortable with who they are and worry less about differences, sometimes seeing them as strengths, as they get older, Bal said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty With Social Cues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Oliver Rossi / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Social cues are also another sign. Someone with undiagnosed autism may find they have trouble deciphering how much eye contact is appropriate or when they should stop smiling during a conversation, Gardner-Wright said. They may be able to mask these uncertainties by learning how much is appropriate, but it’s not an innate sense as it is with someone who is allistic, she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Confusing Relationship History — Both Romantically Or Platonically&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Peopleimages / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According to Neff, many undiagnosed autistic adults have a confusing and complicated social relationship history. Additionally, romantic relationships may feel tough to navigate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“There might be relationships that have that kind of suddenly burst apart but the autistic person doesn’t understand why,” she said. When it comes to the reason behind this complicated relationship history, it’s likely that the person with autism doesn’t know why their relationships fail when other people’s don’t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sensory Differences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/scarymouse/doctors-sharing-mild-symptoms-actually-serious-medical-3?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:"Get To The Doctor Right Now" — People Are Revealing 24 "Mild" Medical Symptoms That Can Actually Be A Sign Of A Major, Major Issue;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;"Get To The Doctor Right Now" — People Are Revealing 24 "Mild" Medical Symptoms That Can Actually Be A Sign Of A Major, Major Issue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Simpleimages / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Sensitivity to sensory input — like noise and sight — is another potential sign of autism, said Gardner-Wright, who added that this can mean being hyper-aware of a sound or totally unaware.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;People who are not autistic tend to be more or less responsive to sensory stimuli, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;For example, an autistic person may find that they’re constantly aware of a ticking clock at a friend’s house or really sensitive to the sound of a loud siren, Gardner-Wright noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Desire For Routine&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Tatiana Maksimova / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Many people with autism thrive on consistency. “The world we occupy is much more uncertain and unpredictable. So we go to routine as a way of self-soothing,” Neff said. When a routine is disrupted, strong &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/evelinamedina/which-human-emotion-are-you" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:emotions;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;emotions&lt;/a&gt; may present, including intense irritability or anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Gardner-Wright added that the routine doesn’t need to be super strict, either; it’s a common misconception when people think about people with autism’s day-to-day schedule. Instead, it could be a strong preference for a certain mug every morning. Routine looks different for different people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Additionally, big changes can be hard, too. “If they move [homes] or they move careers, this could create a season of insomnia or anxiety,” Neff said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Routine can extend to certain behaviors as well. It also includes repetitive body movements, which is known as stimming, Neff added. &lt;a href="https://www.research.chop.edu/car-autism-roadmap/stimming-what-is-it-and-does-it-matter#:~:text=%22%20Stimming%20%2C%22%20also%20known%20as,spectrum%20engage%20in%20routine%20stimming%20." rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:According to the Children’s Hospital of Pennsylvania’s Research Institute;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;According to the Children’s Hospital of Pennsylvania’s Research Institute&lt;/a&gt;, stimming behaviors can include body rocking, hand flapping, spinning, rubbing a specific surface, and squealing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Need For Solitude &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-health-lies-medical-myths?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:&amp;quot;There Is No Cure&amp;quot;: Doctors And Nurses Are Calling Out The Health &amp;quot;Lies&amp;quot; People Still Believe (But Really Shouldn't);elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;"There Is No Cure": Doctors And Nurses Are Calling Out The Health "Lies" People Still Believe (But Really Shouldn't)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Jordan Siemens / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Another common sign? “Needing solitude to recharge after social situations or really overstimulating situations — and overstimulating could be different for everyone — but that is a very typical hallmark of [autism],” Gardner-Wright said. This could mean feeling totally exhausted after a work presentation or a family party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Bal said this exhaustion comes from a term known as “camouflaging” or “masking.” “This is the idea that you have to really hide different facets of yourself or different behaviors in order to fit in what you think the expectations around you are.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;And while we all do this at times, the degree that autistic people have to camouflage aspects of themselves may result in a feeling of total drainage where afterward they report spending long periods of time alone or in dark and quiet places to recover, Bal said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Tessers added that, from the outside, people have no idea when someone is camouflaging. “They’re doing what everybody wants or expects of them to some successful degree.” This could look like behaving as you “should” at work but going home and crashing and dreading the idea of having to do this camouflaging all over again tomorrow, Tessers noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More Intense Interests&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Natalia Lebedinskaia / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A deep curiosity and passion for one particular activity or subject can also develop. “Our brains tend to gravitate with a lot of passion towards our area of interest and we become very invested in them and it’s also a way we self-soothe,” Neff said. This could mean building a career around a specific interest or knowing everything about a specific hobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;And while everyone has interests — and many people have strong interests — Neff said autistic folks likely find a way to relate everything to their specific interest. For example, this could look like finding a way to talk about a favorite TV show even when the conversation revolves around current events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Allistic people can have a special interest but then it doesn’t become their lens for their whole world,” Neff said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Dislike Of Small Talk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Tom Werner / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-health-warning-signs-symptoms-shouldnt-ignore?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Doctors And Nurses Are Revealing The &amp;quot;Small&amp;quot; Health Signs You Should Never Ignore, And It's Shocking;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Doctors And Nurses Are Revealing The "Small" Health Signs You Should Never Ignore, And It's Shocking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Most people don’t love small talk, but for people with autism, small talk can feel totally exhausting or something that shouldn’t have to happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“They typically don’t enjoy small talk and perhaps found ways to avoid it,” Neff said. “Maybe they structured their life or their career in a way that they don’t have to do a lot of that allistic communication.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Gardner-Wright added that people who are on the spectrum tend to prefer deep, meaningful conversations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Desire For Direct Communication&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Manu Vega / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;People with autism thrive on straightforwardness, with “really honest, clear communication being a strong preference,” Gardner-Wright said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Neff said autistic people tend to be pretty literal. For example, when you say the phrase “it’s raining cats and &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/chelseamarshall/what-kind-of-dog-are-you" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dogs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;dogs&lt;/a&gt;,” she said autistic people may picture literal cats and dogs falling from the sky in their mind, but then realize the person speaking is referring to rain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“So, actually, I think it’s perhaps more precise to say we’re visual in our communication style versus literal, but it often shows up as being literal,” Neff said. Additionally, the communication style can be described as direct and honest. “What we say, we tend to say at face value,” Neff added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you think you have these signs, look to autistic voices for guidance.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Both Gardner-Wright and Neff recommend exploring the hashtag &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/explore/tags/actuallyautistic/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:#actuallyautistic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;#actuallyautistic&lt;/a&gt; on social media to listen to lived experiences and hear from people in your specific community about how this exists for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Discovering that you’re autistic as an adult can be really validating,” Gardner-Wright said. It can help you more fully understand yourself and your life. “But there can also be a grieving process for that,” she said, where you may wish you had this information when you were a kid so certain situations could have been different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Feeling a mix of grief and also excitement is very, very normal,” Gardner-Wright said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Additionally, &lt;a href="https://embrace-autism.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:embrace-autism.com;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;embrace-autism.com&lt;/a&gt; is a helpful resource for free screening tools and tests to help you understand if you are autistic — though it is not diagnostic, they’re simply online guides to help arm you with information, Gardner-Wright noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can reach out to mental health professionals, too.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Olga Pankova / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Neff said it can be helpful to connect with a therapist to talk about this new discovery, but she stressed that it’s important to find one who is neurodivergent-affirming or -informed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Bal agreed and said “we have a long way to go with respect to training medical professionals and mental health professionals about autism. I worry there’s a lot of misinformation and misconceptions out there.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Bal added that you can also look up autism centers near you for diagnosis or treatment, but noted that many have a yearslong waitlist and may focus only on children. If they can’t fit you in, Bal said, you can ask if they have resources they recommend, or look for community autism organizations to see if they have any resources.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Additionally, a community of supportive people can be helpful as well, which is where the #actuallyaustic hashtag — or other online communities — can be helpful.&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/the-9-biggest-signs-of-autism-in-adulthood-goog_l_68013c24e4b0b87197a6e18d" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:HuffPost.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;HuffPost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/alanavalko/unhinged-microfeminisms?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:&amp;quot;He Thinks This Is Hostile And He Is Correct&amp;quot; — Women Are Sharing The &amp;quot;Unhinged&amp;quot; Ways They Practice Microfeminism That Reaally Grind A Small Man's Gears;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;"He Thinks This Is Hostile And He Is Correct" — Women Are Sharing The "Unhinged" Ways They Practice Microfeminism That Reaally Grind A Small Man's Gears&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-bad-health-habits?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:"They Had No Idea How Dangerous It Was." Doctors Are Calling Out The "Bad" Habits That Are Actually Ruining Your Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;"They Had No Idea How Dangerous It Was." Doctors Are Calling Out The "Bad" Habits That Are Actually Ruining Your Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/dannicaramirez/older-adults-are-sharing-the-difficult-truths-about-aging-fs?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:"Young People Would Be Surprised By This": 21 "Hard To Swallow" Truths About Getting Older That No One Talks About;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;"Young People Would Be Surprised By This": 21 "Hard To Swallow" Truths About Getting Older That No One Talks About&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/jillianwilson/biggest-signs-of-autism-in-adulthood-sc?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read it on BuzzFeed.com;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Read it on BuzzFeed.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Lifestyle Canada</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:31:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE94WHhZazRhMHlvbjhSMTVuSmM1MkU3SUNLZXduc3ExTnJxTHpRN1ZqVlNlOWw1QzBOQWFJaHU4alB6RWtBdDVGdDQyaWI1REJtaXJZN3N5N2o5MnRLQ2hZV0EyWFlkZmw5SFBMN1lUVkplNlNZeVFoTkI4RDhXTDA</guid></item><item><title>以下是成年人自闭症的9个主要指标，这些指标往往被完全忽视- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/jillianwilson/biggest-signs-of-autism-in-adulthood-sc</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-19
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="fast fashion" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139570589" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;People with autism thrive on straightforwardness, with “really honest, clear communication being a strong preference,” Gardner-Wright said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neff said autistic people tend to be pretty literal. For example, when you say the phrase “it’s raining cats and &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/chelseamarshall/what-kind-of-dog-are-you"&gt;dogs&lt;/a&gt;,” she said autistic people may picture literal cats and dogs falling from the sky in their mind, but then realize the person speaking is referring to rain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“So, actually, I think it’s perhaps more precise to say we’re visual in our communication style versus literal, but it often shows up as being literal,” Neff said. Additionally, the communication style can be described as direct and honest. “What we say, we tend to say at face value,” Neff added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you think you have these signs, look to autistic voices for guidance.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both Gardner-Wright and Neff recommend exploring the hashtag &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/explore/tags/actuallyautistic/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7965909"&gt;#actuallyautistic&lt;/a&gt; on social media to listen to lived experiences and hear from people in your specific community about how this exists for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Discovering that you’re autistic as an adult can be really validating,” Gardner-Wright said. It can help you more fully understand yourself and your life. “But there can also be a grieving process for that,” she said, where you may wish you had this information when you were a kid so certain situations could have been different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Feeling a mix of grief and also excitement is very, very normal,” Gardner-Wright said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, &lt;a href="https://embrace-autism.com/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7965909" data-affiliate="true"&gt;embrace-autism.com&lt;/a&gt; is a helpful resource for free screening tools and tests to help you understand if you are autistic — though it is not diagnostic, they’re simply online guides to help arm you with information, Gardner-Wright noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can reach out to mental health professionals, too.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:31:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxOVWRjZjJVZkRJSV9JRkc0ZVNRZ0ZnT3JwbDFHUV9oN3dLbktjTFVFWlRkUGRTVVBuczRXTlkxbHgzX2laeDZ6V0N2TnFPaDZJNXdtSEJvdXdRdWI2YWtuaEQ1ZWFIUmZpbTNMX0tBeUhkS19xdUxpM185V0x3bDJiMUI0Tm4</guid></item><item><title>隐藏在大脑深处的信号可以跟踪帕金森症状- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/a-signal-hidden-deep-in-your-brain-could-track-parkinsons-symptoms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A search for  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IYl" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73029" data-postid="179672" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Parkinson's&lt;/a&gt; in the hiss of our brain's static has revealed measures of motor control that could one day &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/smart-brain-implants-can-now-adapt-to-optimize-parkinsons-treatment"&gt;fine-tune precise forms of stimulation therapy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Led by the Max Planck Institute for Human Cognitive and Brain Sciences in Germany, an international team of scientists combined five sets of electrophysiological data taken from deep within the brains of 119 people with Parkinson's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By comparing specific brain-wave activity to the severity of individual patients' symptoms, the researchers were able to sift out patterns that could be confidently matched to the condition's impact on movement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/restless-legs-treatment-slashes-increased-risk-of-parkinsons-disease"&gt;Restless Legs Treatment Slashes Increased Risk of Parkinson's Disease&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parkinson's disease is fundamentally a &lt;a href="https://www.neurolab360.com/blog/basalgangliaandpd"&gt;breakdown in the functioning&lt;/a&gt; of a part of the brain called the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/body/23962-basal-ganglia"&gt;basal ganglia&lt;/a&gt;, robbing people of the ability to filter information required to keep their body movements precise and steady. The result is slow, stiff, shaky motion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_179673" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-179673" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/basal_ganglia_PD_642.jpg" alt="basal ganglia" class="wp-image-179673 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/basal_ganglia_PD_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/basal_ganglia_PD_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-179673" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Location of the basal ganglia in the brain. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAC_WeBNVN4/"&gt;decade3d/Getty Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In theory, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/dopamine-doesnt-work-in-our-brains-quite-the-way-we-thought"&gt;changes in the basal ganglia's operation&lt;/a&gt; should be noticeable in their electrical activity, appearing as a general excess of &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/alpha-beta-theta-what-are-brain-states-and-brain-waves-and-can-we-control-them-219236"&gt;mid-to-high-range oscillations&lt;/a&gt; known as &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Beta_wave"&gt;beta waves&lt;/a&gt;, as well as an increase in spiking signals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41531-022-00443-3"&gt;Studies&lt;/a&gt; have captured &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1113/JP284768"&gt;plenty of beta-wave activity&lt;/a&gt; in the past through electrodes implanted deep in the brain as a means of treatment. Although it was evident that these waves varied with symptom severity, the methods used to interpret the buzz left a lot to be desired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A mix of patient diversity, combinations of symptoms, and a lack of unaffected controls made it difficult to compare the brain-wave activity of diseased states with a 'healthy' standard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By pooling multiple datasets and comparing differences in similar activity between more-or-less affected basal ganglia in each brain hemisphere, the researchers behind this latest study could 'listen in' on harmonies hidden within the brain's roar.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You can imagine the brain as a concert hall full of musicians before a rehearsal," &lt;a href="https://www.mpg.de/25632689/1030-nepf-noise-as-a-signal-a-new-electrical-signature-of-parkinson-s-disease-149575-x"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; lead author and neurologist Moritz Gerster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Some groups play together, creating a distinct rhythm. Others practice on their own, merging into a non-rhythmic 'noise'. If you only measure the overall volume, you miss this distinction."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identifying precise rhythms in the basal ganglia could eventually play a valuable role in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-ultrasound-helmet-reaches-deep-inside-the-brain-without-surgery"&gt;treatments that use deep brain stimulation&lt;/a&gt;. This could help return a degree of motor control to those with Parkinson's by dynamically responding to changing rhythms – like a conductor who now knows what to listen out for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ebiom.2025.105988"&gt;eBiomedicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 03:41:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxNaTJBNTFRSGR2S2ZrblBoa0wzdGc0RXZQRktZdzJlT1FWYlEwZGU3STNtRTlUQTEyTi1QYU1JTG1mU3BGRFkyTS0yNVFaYXl1eFNjczBscElZWkJIRklCUURra0JjX0pEYXFDcmlOektWSEpIMW4yRFlUalpnNVpCMGdTVDJUMUMzZUFWcUp0WXNYRmo2SUNNZXIwRQ</guid></item><item><title>大脑训练应用程序“扭转了关键大脑系统10年的衰退” - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/brain-training-app-reverses-10-years-of-decline-in-a-key-brain-system</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;It's not just your body that needs to be 'worked out'. Your brain also needs &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-made-a-video-game-that-boosts-short-term-memory-in-older-adults"&gt;training&lt;/a&gt; to stay young and fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A digital brain exercise, developed by the American biotech company &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Posit_Science_Corporation"&gt;Posit Science Corporation&lt;/a&gt;, has been put to the test by neurologists at McGill University in Canada, with some promising results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a rigorous, double-blinded controlled trial, 82 healthy adults over the age of 65 were randomly assigned to play either Posit's 'BrainHQ' app or a recreational computer game for thirty minutes a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After 10 weeks, brain scans revealed that those who played BrainHQ, which focused on speed-based challenges, showed measurable increases in &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cholinergic"&gt;cholinergic&lt;/a&gt; activity, a type of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/part-of-your-brain-acts-like-a-pause-button-that-freezes-your-whole-body"&gt;brain signalling&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was seen in a part of their brain known as the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anterior_cingulate_cortex"&gt;anterior cingulate cortex&lt;/a&gt; (ACC) – which supports selective attention, inhibitory control, and memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-type-of-activity-is-particularly-effective-at-keeping-your-brain-young"&gt;&lt;b&gt;One Type of Activity Is Particularly Effective at Keeping Your Brain Young&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The increase in cholinergic signaling was comparable in magnitude to how much the ACC usually shrinks over 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The training restored cholinergic health to levels typically seen in someone 10 years younger," &lt;a href="https://www.mcgill.ca/newsroom/channels/news/researchers-neuro-show-brain-exercise-yields-benefits-368265"&gt;claims&lt;/a&gt; neurologist Etienne de Villers-Sidani from McGill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is the first time any intervention, drug or non-drug, has been shown to do that in humans."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_179584" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-179584" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/double-decisioneasy-_easy_level_0-642x402.png" alt="Brain-Training App " class="wp-image-179584 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/double-decisioneasy-_easy_level_0-642x402.png 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/double-decisioneasy-_easy_level_0-1077x675.png 1077w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/double-decisioneasy-_easy_level_0-768x481.png 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/double-decisioneasy-_easy_level_0-600x376.png 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/double-decisioneasy-_easy_level_0.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-179584" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;In the Double Decision exercise in the BrainHQ app, participants identified images on a screen at increasing speed. (&lt;a href="https://www.mcgill.ca/newsroom/channels/news/researchers-neuro-show-brain-exercise-yields-benefits-368265"&gt;BrainHQ, Posit Science&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The BrainHQ app is currently available for purchase via monthly and yearly subscriptions, and the company &lt;a href="https://www.brainhq.com/world-class-science/"&gt;claims&lt;/a&gt; it has developed the technology &lt;a href="https://www.brainhq.com/news/press-releases/hundreds-of-studies-show-efficacy-of-one-particular-brain-fitness-program/"&gt;based on scientific evidence&lt;/a&gt;, testing it in hundreds of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2196/53623"&gt;peer-reviewed&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/cam4.5904"&gt;papers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preliminary evidence does suggest that the app can impact the brain, and these changes might be beneficial, but it's unknown if those changes are lasting or if they translate to real differences in memory, attention, and learning in the everyday function of older individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent trial is only small, and it is incentivized by company profit, so there is reason to remain cautious. That said, it is rigorously designed and uses advanced brain scanning techniques in collaboration with McGill neurologists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We used a rare technology," &lt;a href="https://www.mcgill.ca/newsroom/channels/news/researchers-neuro-show-brain-exercise-yields-benefits-368265"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; de Villers-Sidani. "The [Montreal Neurological Institute-Hospital] is one of the few centers worldwide that can produce the tracer and run the scan."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_179706" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-179706" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Intervention-and-active-control-programs.jpg" alt="Schematic depicting the two tasks in the intervention" class="size-full wp-image-179706" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Intervention-and-active-control-programs.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Intervention-and-active-control-programs-600x458.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-179706" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The intervention and active control tasks.  (Attarha et al., &lt;em&gt;JMIR Serious Games&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cholinergic system connects many parts of the brain, including the hippocampus – which is heavily involved in learning and memory. Theoretically, if this system is strengthened, it could improve common symptoms of aging, like memory loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeing changes to the cholinergic system following brain training is intriguing, but further trials among larger and more diverse cohorts are needed to understand more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Identifying and implementing effective strategies to support brain health has the potential to reduce health care costs, increase workforce participation and community engagement, and improve quality of life," the authors of the trial &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2196/75161"&gt;conclude&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These findings support the use of this promising, low-risk intervention and contribute to a mechanistic understanding of cognitive training that establishes a foundation for future trials."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2196/75161"&gt;&lt;i&gt;JMIR Serious Games&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 02:03:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxNbU5DSm9FU1lJTTZMbTRmaHlSc2U1cTk5d3JCLUtFYjVXZWZFM0RHckpIeHllU0pPN0VScGtqMVpvM0ZnTDRZd21peUdHbmFDWXhXVFJUQVZUMnhqRWRkdEtJc3lINGdTTzZpZk9ENFVFdzFMOExJTG5ieWxQdVY1V3VHTFVMYktaLWYwTGRBR0tybWpYQ2FvM0hNVWZxdnc</guid></item><item><title>眼睛对健康的看法：营养师解码9个警告标志以及如何自然修复它们-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/what-the-eyes-say-about-health-dietitian-decodes-9-warning-signs-and-how-to-fix-them-naturally/photostory/124970884.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;While sleepless nights often get the blame, persistent dark circles can also signal low iron. Iron supports oxygen flow to tissues, and when it drops, the skin under the eyes darkens due to poor circulation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What helps: Dates, moringa powder, and soaked raisins are powerful iron-rich foods that help brighten under-eye areas from within.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingJBVV95cUxOUWJwcFhZb3BWREhDQlgyMG80VF84b3VUdzY4ZV90ZllxWmpiellISUFEdEhzb2lFcHJLdE1nUU1FcEFxYXQwa3V5RXhTUmlYdGxZUklOeGlhdHdHMHljWGljUUgwclp5Vi0xR2pHWi1EVmxpZWtCVTVNSG1ETHpERHRyMVczRElCbk16N1VoVXpKTnVuV2l6OThtLXRTNnJDYklVSFpSS1g4YmNhNENJT0JVbXkzSVlhN2hoMXJ0Q2FnNDNRRWpES0owMTR5Q2xyMGJnT193Ujc5Rnp6cmY1bWNxRk1HRGNLWnlidFdpeXZjazhyelBZSXNvQVp2TmxxME1PdFNhRXNxTEV4YnFFNjM1S3VmcGZOVWZma09R0gGmAkFVX3lxTE9mbUFVdHhfNVRwelJJb0ktUnlId2picGlkN1JvdUNRYTBnSmZuMVBDa0RnVW1VWWdDN0tmX3NpTnppeV83eFhOckVPeW1IeFVVNk9Hb292TzFEdGxxVVFLSWlFdGhUWFJLWG1jZkNod3RDMXVHcTlvc0QwckR5Rk10LXpRVFphRklHUTQwTkkwTmttNnhBYlk5NGdHOVV4eVJOQmhGRTVCaFllamdLS2J4aXB3UC1IZmY2bnhTUFRRamJUaDhpV3VSa29pamc2ZTNjMHU3Q1AtVjI5ZmlTRXFZMFhmRGJ4TWtXM1BIOEx2c2kxMjNaazJSZHFTcUhoTFotWk1hanhlVmZCMjZzZzMxZ0FITURaMGxVelJwSk9kZlRlOENJQQ</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，怀孕期间感染新冠肺炎的母亲所生儿童的自闭症诊断率较高- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/30/health/autism-covid-pregnancy</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe174qo000x26oyhb4y4qof@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Children may be more likely to be diagnosed with autism and other neurodevelopment disorders if their mother had a Covid-19 infection while pregnant, according to a new &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/greenjournal/abstract/9900/neurodevelopmental_outcomes_of_3_year_old_children.1392.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi300043b6nzxm4apar@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Researchers from Massachusetts General Hospital analyzed more than 18,000 births that occurred in the Mass General Brigham health system between March 2020 and May 2021, assessing records for laboratory-confirmed Covid-19 tests among the mothers and for neurodevelopment diagnoses among their children through age 3.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi300053b6nl7sqz3df@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            They found that children born to mothers who had Covid-19 during pregnancy were significantly more likely to be diagnosed with a neurodevelopment disorder than those born to mothers who did not have an infection while pregnant: more than 16% versus less than 10%, or a 1.3 times higher risk after adjusting for other risk factors.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi300073b6n1rgwvjnp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Overall, differences in risks were more pronounced among boys and in cases where the mother had a Covid-19 infection during the third trimester. Previous studies have suggested that male fetal brains are more susceptible to maternal immune responses, according to the authors of the new study, and the third trimester is a “critical window for brain development.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi300063b6na3bx6p6z@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The most common diagnoses included disorders in speech and motor function development and autism. About 2.7% of children born to mothers who had Covid-19 while pregnant were diagnosed with autism, compared with about 1.1% of others, according to the study, published Thursday in the journal Obstetrics and Gynecology.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi300083b6nn0v0elm4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The new findings are “particularly notable in light of their biological plausibility,” the researchers wrote. They build on previous research that identified potential pathways for a maternal Covid-19 infection to affect the developing fetal brain even without direct transmission.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1l1ce00023b6n7tk5ji48@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Parental awareness of the potential for adverse child neurodevelopmental outcomes after COVID-19 in pregnancy is key. By understanding the risks, parents can appropriately advocate for their children to have proper evaluation and support,” Dr. Lydia Shook, maternal-fetal medicine specialist at Massachusetts General Hospital and lead author of the study, said in &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/about/newsroom/press-releases/covid-19-during-pregnancy-linked-to-neurodevelopmental-disorders" target="_blank"&gt;a news release&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi300093b6nvczsesgz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            About 1 in 31 children in the US was diagnosed with autism by age 8 in 2022, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/04/15/health/autism-rate-cdc-report-2022"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; published by the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention that was published in April. The increase — up from 1 in 36 children in 2020 — continues a long-term trend that experts have largely attributed to better understanding of and screening for the condition.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi3000a3b6npcnyzrw4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Earlier this year, the US Department of Health and Human Services launched a “massive testing and research effort” to determine “what has &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/04/10/health/kennedy-autism-causes"&gt;caused the autism epidemic&lt;/a&gt;.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1llo7000e3b6qgrzfaaue@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In a news conference in September on the “&lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/videos/finding-the-cause-of-autism/" target="_blank"&gt;cause of autism&lt;/a&gt;,” President Donald Trump — flanked by HHS Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. and other federal health leaders – said that use of &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/22/health/trump-autism-announcement-cause-tylenol"&gt;Tylenol during pregnancy&lt;/a&gt; can be associated with a “very increased risk of autism,” despite decades of evidence that it is safe.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi3000b3b6nzh9oih78@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Kennedy also has a history of comments linking autism and vaccines, despite strong evidence that the two are not connected.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi4000c3b6n4nxeot91@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The timeframe of the new study – early in the pandemic, before vaccines were widely available – meant that ​the researchers were able to “isolate the association between SARS-CoV-2 infection and offspring neurodevelopment in an unvaccinated population.” About 93% of the mothers included in the assessment had not received any doses of Covid-19 vaccine. Strong infection-control policies at that time also helped reduce the potential for unreported or undetected Covid-19 cases, the researchers said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1pk6x00053b6n5tc239vt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “These findings highlight that COVID-19, like many other infections in pregnancy, may pose risks not only to the mother, but to fetal brain development,” Dr. Andrea Edlow, a maternal-fetal medicine specialist at Mass General Brigham and senior author of the new study, said in a news release. “They also support the importance of trying to prevent COVID-19 infection in pregnancy and are particularly relevant when public trust in vaccines – including the COVID-19 vaccine – is being eroded.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 01:06:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibEFVX3lxTE5hT3E1anItcU82YzhNYnlHZXZES3RyNWlZcm01X2pIOV81QTIxVm9nTnNRMTdSdVBjdXJQVzFFMWh2RmpORXBlUVcxYVhGVGFma2NIV21BSUVoeEtPZU1OdEFPbnc5Ynd5OGVTNQ</guid></item><item><title>卫生官员在致命疾病到达热门旅游热点时发出警告： “非常令人担忧” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/health-officials-issue-warning-deadly-001000971.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A popular Spanish resort town has been placed on alert after officials found mosquitoes carrying West Nile virus there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The mosquitoes in question, the &lt;a href="https://www.express.co.uk/travel/articles/2120538/horror-spain-deadly-virus-tourist-hotspot" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Daily Express reported;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Daily Express reported&lt;/a&gt;, were discovered only a few feet from homes in Malaga, a popular tourist town in southern Spain's Andalusia region that is known for its breathtaking beaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The Andalusia Health and Consumer Department verified that the mosquitoes carried West Nile virus, which can, in rare cases, be fatal to humans. With that announcement came a four-week alert period, stretching through early November, that included higher levels of monitoring by local health teams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Similar findings and warnings have also occurred in the Spanish towns of Tahivilla and La Luisiana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why is West Nile virus concerning?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In most cases, West Nile virus doesn't show any symptoms in humans. But in rare cases, people can develop symptoms that last for months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"The symptoms presented like a stroke. It was really worrying," Jim Skinner, who decided to retire after contracting West Nile virus, &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c1w850qlx94o" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:told the BBC;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;told the BBC&lt;/a&gt;. "I had weakness down the left-hand side, palsy on the left-hand side, and I got tremors. … The weakness and tremors are still there a year on."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Even more concerning, however, is that West Nile virus cases appear to be increasing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Health officials say 13 European countries saw a total of &lt;a href="https://www.express.co.uk/travel/articles/2120538/horror-spain-deadly-virus-tourist-hotspot" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:989 cases;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;989 cases&lt;/a&gt; of West Nile — including 63 deaths — between June and September, higher than the 10-year average of 687. And in the United States, reported cases were about 40% higher than normal through early September.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/actions/explore-critical-climate-issues/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Human-caused pollution;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Human-caused pollution&lt;/a&gt; likely plays a role in that increase. That heat-trapping pollution has caused global temperatures to rise, which has led to more of the warm, wet conditions in which mosquitoes thrive. Mosquito season is now longer in many parts of the world, and the insects have reached places that were once too cold for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What can I do to avoid West Nile virus?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/west-nile-virus/prevention/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; note, there is no vaccine or medicine available to prevent West Nile. Instead, the only way to prevent getting the virus is to avoid getting bitten by mosquitoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Officials offer several tips on how to avoid those potentially dangerous bites. They advise people to wear long, loose-fitting shirts and pants when outside, to use screens on windows and doors, to avoid outdoor exposure between dusk and dawn, and to use approved insect repellent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/future-newsletter/?reczp5UAUgwtvYBcd" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;good news&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;useful tips&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxQM0xWRjhPZUhHcHF1dDd3bVpUeGIxcXJyNXFRdUNOajdKamZuYXQ1d0pYQ3ZpOG5LWWxqaGZEdm45Z2RHSnBrLWZNOUZQekdwbjM1OGo2N2tFcF9kOVZqN0VKbFIxVFhVUHZJZmVyZ1pGeEhXVFNXTWNKVmctWE9LV002X2ZkeC01NjBpYklLNHlNdw</guid></item><item><title>前疾病预防控制中心官员，负责新的mpox病例和当前的联邦资源- The Hill</title><link>https://thehill.com/newsletters/health-care/5582409-former-cdc-official-on-new-mpox-cases-and-current-federal-resources/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>The Hill</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:54:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxQaTRQQ0hhaGdhLW9YLUs3cHlNbV9rV094V1hQbDBXUkREcVBSaThLVmt2RUloaFAwUXlncG5DSGlqYkhzZFJSV3pCUGMycW95bzBiYkhaVzBjRlpQSUxIZjFoT3QwbXlwLU5JdXdCeWZYMU1MS2xCT0R3NTNUVTNIcFVUbmgwdnJsVWlvTURIUmt0QkE2OC1oVm9MMDhTNzJJWHpiQTllSmxScWEzX1FrWUdKOENERDRnWnpiR9IBwgFBVV95cUxQS0lSNEY0b092aVJVY084aGRxak9Yb2w4eWNCbkhVQWVUZl80WnBoN0dlVFlMa1dqTGxacGg1R3d3OFB1N0M2anJ0d3c4azRObTBCS24tQWxlckNEeVZ5U0Q2OGR1Y2FCQm15NUdBZ0xqN25PbkxuY3doTnlmbzFoOUhKRnNndDFUc2U4X21aTzJFVWp6TzBOUDBuQkQ2a2lnSmVScFAzM2cxUjBacWNmRlBvcmR6Vjd5c1d0YjltSDE3UQ</guid></item><item><title>索诺玛县鸭子和蛋农场受到2025-26冬季首次禽流感爆发的打击-新闻民主党人</title><link>https://www.pressdemocrat.com/2025/10/30/large-sonoma-county-duck-farm-hit-with-first-avian-flu-outbreak-of-2025-26-winter/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-copy"&gt;&lt;p&gt;California’s first bird flu outbreaks of the 2025-26 winter season have hit close to home. The owner of Reichardt Duck Farm, which sits in the rolling hills between Petaluma and the Two Rock area, confirmed that his facility recently recorded positive cases of the dreaded virus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And Thursday, the U.S. Department of Agriculture &lt;a href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/livestock-poultry-disease/avian/avian-influenza/hpai-detections/commercial-backyard-flocks"&gt;added to its public database&lt;/a&gt; a second incidence of the highly virulent avian flu in Sonoma County, this one at an egg farm. The Press Democrat was unable to immediately confirm the location of that outbreak, which resulted in the deaths of 231,000 birds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The timing is a wake-up call. Two winters ago, when Sonoma County poultry farms were &lt;a href="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/2024/01/12/sonoma-county-poultry-farmers-euthanize-thousands-more-birds-as-avian-flu-losses-devastate-local-industry/"&gt;ravaged by the spread of avian influenza&lt;/a&gt;, the first case didn’t hit until around Thanksgiving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The latest outbreak is another blow to the Reichardt family. Their Middle Two Rock Road farm was also heavily affected in 2023-24, when it was &lt;a href="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/2023/12/01/250000-birds-to-be-killed-at-2-petaluma-poultry-farms-after-avian-flu-detected-2/"&gt;the first of multiple local facilities &lt;/a&gt;infected by the deadly and highly virulent avian flu virus, which typically requires producers to destroy all of their birds on site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="s2nPlayer k-8p60lgsb" data-type="float" data-s2n-api="dfm_stn_player_script_id_8p60lgsb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bird flu outbreaks hit flocks at nine other chicken, duck and egg-laying facilities in the county that season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phil Reichardt paused to talk to a reporter &lt;span&gt;Tuesday &lt;/span&gt;as his farm staff went about euthanizing 57,000 birds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Look at the last six years now, with &lt;a href="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/2023/12/03/activism-prospective-ballot-fight-heighten-drama-of-sonoma-county-bird-flu-outbreak/"&gt;the DxE (animal liberation) raid&lt;/a&gt;, COVID, bird flu in ’23, now bird flu again in ’25. My older sister passed in 2020,” he said. “It’s been hit after hit. We’re looking for our fate to change at some point.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reichardt Duck Farm is not to be confused with Liberty Ducks, a smaller Sonoma County&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;producer, owned by members of the same family but operating at a separate location.&lt;/p&gt;				
&lt;p&gt;The latest outbreak was detected after Reichardt Duck Farm staff noticed “a modest increase in mortality” — eight dead birds — in one of the barns last week, Phil Reichardt said. The next morning, there were a few more than that. They took a sample of birds to UC Davis for analysis, and received confirmation of Highly Pathogenic Avian Flu, or HPAI, on Oct. 24.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The duck farm began “depopulating” its flock Sunday, borrowing some machinery from Weber Family Farms, an egg facility that also was forced to put birds to death in 2023-24. Phil Reichardt expected to finish the grim task Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s a departure from two years ago, when local ranchers knew much less about the spread of the pathogen and how best to block it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In that previous round, Reichardt said, the farm received instructions from the U.S. Department of Agriculture the day before Thanksgiving. Because of the holiday, and a lower sense of urgency, they didn’t begin depopulating for six days. This time, Reichardt expected to be done five days after confirmation, which he hoped would reduce the chances of the flu hopping to another facility.&lt;/p&gt;				
&lt;p&gt;“The industry, unfortunately, is getting very good at this,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The report Thursday of another outbreak in one of the region’s bird farms demonstrates the limitations of that quick action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rodrigo Gallardo, professor of poultry medicine at the UC Davis School of Veterinary Medicine and an expert in poultry RNA viruses, agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s definitely a concerted effort,” Gallardo said. “The California Department of Food and Agriculture usually helps with this, the USDA usually helps. We’re all at high alert. We’re approaching winter. And we have learned a lot of things about biosecurity and prevention. The hope is that we will reduce dissemination after one detection.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The recommendations on biosecurity measures haven’t changed based on the new appearance of HPAI, said Sue Ostrom, Sonoma County’s assistant agricultural commissioner, because — as Reichardt alluded — producers have gotten the work pretty buttoned down since their unprecedented local losses in the winter season two years ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One thing that led to,” Ostrom said, “is that producers understand what needs to happen. How we dispose of carcasses, bedding and so forth. They can get to that faster now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="article-slideshow" id="mng-gallery-acbb91da5dd2a61221fbbbb4f9e7b501"&gt;&lt;button class="icon-close mng-gallery-fullscreen-close" aria-label="Close fullscreen slideshow"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;ul class="mng-gallery-initialized mng-gallery-slider"&gt;&lt;button id="mng-gallery-prev" class="mng-gallery-prev mng-gallery-arrow" aria-label="Previous" type="button"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;div class="mng-gallery-list draggable"&gt;&lt;div class="mng-gallery-track"&gt;&lt;li data-index="1" class="mng-ge mng-gallery-active" id="mng-ge-0" aria-hidden="false" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;div class="image-wrapper"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" alt="Workers remove dirt from a cage-free chicken house at a..." class="size-article_inline" sizes="(max-width: 40em) 620px,(min-width: 40em) and (max-width: 50em) 780px,(min-width: 50em) and (max-width: 65em) 810px,(min-width: 65em) and (max-width: 80em) 1280px,(min-width: 80em) 1860px,1860px" srcset="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2025/01/594dafea-c977-5b2b-a7f1-b3f60982c38b.jpg?w=620 620w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2025/01/594dafea-c977-5b2b-a7f1-b3f60982c38b.jpg?w=780 780w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2025/01/594dafea-c977-5b2b-a7f1-b3f60982c38b.jpg?w=810 810w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2025/01/594dafea-c977-5b2b-a7f1-b3f60982c38b.jpg?w=1200 1280w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2025/01/594dafea-c977-5b2b-a7f1-b3f60982c38b.jpg?w=1200 1860w"&gt;&lt;p class="slide-credit"&gt;Christopher Chung / The Press Democrat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="slide-caption"&gt;Workers remove dirt from a cage-free chicken house at a Weber Family Farms facility in Petaluma, in January 2024. The farm had to destroy 550,000 chickens and 3.2 million eggs after an avian flu outbreak. (Christopher Chung / The Press Democrat)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-index="2" class="mng-ge" id="mng-ge-1" aria-hidden="true" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;div class="image-wrapper"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" alt="Reichardt Duck Farm in the rolling hills of Two Rock,..." class="lazyload size-article_inline" data-sizes="auto" data-src="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/12/ea7ae9c7-5470-5d06-8545-36e710f075b7.jpg?w=620" data-srcset="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/12/ea7ae9c7-5470-5d06-8545-36e710f075b7.jpg?w=620 620w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/12/ea7ae9c7-5470-5d06-8545-36e710f075b7.jpg?w=780 780w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/12/ea7ae9c7-5470-5d06-8545-36e710f075b7.jpg?w=810 810w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/12/ea7ae9c7-5470-5d06-8545-36e710f075b7.jpg?w=1200 1280w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/12/ea7ae9c7-5470-5d06-8545-36e710f075b7.jpg?w=1200 1860w"&gt;&lt;p class="slide-credit"&gt;Kent Porter / The Press Democrat file&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="slide-caption"&gt;Reichardt Duck Farm in the rolling hills of Two Rock, west of Petaluma, Friday, December 2023. (Kent Porter / The Press Democrat file)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-index="3" class="mng-ge" id="mng-ge-2" aria-hidden="true" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;div class="image-wrapper"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" alt="Law enforcement officers in riot gear wait to arrest animal..." class="lazyload size-article_inline" data-sizes="auto" data-src="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/10/63373263-3937-466c-b073-2d3331343031.jpg?w=620" data-srcset="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/10/63373263-3937-466c-b073-2d3331343031.jpg?w=620 620w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/10/63373263-3937-466c-b073-2d3331343031.jpg?w=780 780w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/10/63373263-3937-466c-b073-2d3331343031.jpg?w=810 810w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/10/63373263-3937-466c-b073-2d3331343031.jpg?w=1200 1280w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/10/63373263-3937-466c-b073-2d3331343031.jpg?w=1200 1860w"&gt;&lt;p class="slide-credit"&gt;photo by John Burgess/The Press Democrat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="slide-caption"&gt;Law enforcement officers in riot gear wait to arrest animal welfare activists holding dead ducks they claim to have found inside the Reichardt Duck Farm on Middle Two Rock Road. (photo by John Burgess/The Press Democrat)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button id="mng-gallery-next" class="mng-gallery-next mng-gallery-arrow" aria-label="Next" type="button"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class="caption mng-gallery-information-container"&gt;&lt;button class="caption-expand mng-gallery-caption-expand" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Show caption"&gt;Show Caption&lt;/button&gt;&lt;p class="slideshow-credit mng-gallery-image-credit"&gt;Christopher Chung / The Press Democrat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="slide-count"&gt;&lt;span class="current mng-gallery-current-image-number-display"&gt;1&lt;/span&gt; of &lt;span class="total"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="slideshow-caption mng-gallery-image-caption"&gt;Workers remove dirt from a cage-free chicken house at a Weber Family Farms facility in Petaluma, in January 2024. The farm had to destroy 550,000 chickens and 3.2 million eggs after an avian flu outbreak. (Christopher Chung / The Press Democrat)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="#" class="icon-enlarge mng-gallery-fullscreen-expand" aria-label="Expand fullscreen slideshow"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Expand&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The strain of bird flu detected in recent tests at Reichardt Duck Farm is the same as the one that swept Sonoma County two years ago, resulting in the &lt;span&gt;destruction of 1.2 million birds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We don’t have any real smoking gun,” Reichardt said. “We can only expect it was migratory birds flying overhead. We step into their droppings and enter the barns. We have foot pans in place, and we are careful to use them. But I guess we can’t hit everywhere.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like viruses transmitted among humans, HPAI tends to peak during the cold winter months. It generally spreads from migrating waterfowl to domesticated flocks along the major north-south flyways, including the Pacific Flyway that travels above Sonoma County. Researchers estimate 1 billion birds fly south along the Pacific Flyway each fall, and north again in the spring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s normal, in a certain sense, to think cases will go up in the winter,” Gallardo said. “Usually, respiratory infections in chickens are related to changes in temperature and humidity. With birds migrating south, we’re right at a time when this might happen.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While Reichardt Duck Farm was obligated to put down all of its birds, the business is not without prospects. Phil Reichardt estimated they have about 15,000 eggs currently incubating, and another 20,000-30,000 that are eligible to take that step soon. Those eggs must be moved off the property to raise elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s an expensive process when no revenue is coming in,” Reichardt said. “But it’s all we know how to do. So we keep going even when it feels like we’re battering our heads against a brick wall.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Department of Agriculture &lt;a href="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/2025/01/21/why-local-poultry-farmers-say-10-million-bird-flu-reimbursement-falls-short-2/"&gt;has an indemnity program&lt;/a&gt; that compensates poultry farmers for income lost to avian flu. In the 2023-24 outbreaks, affected Sonoma County farms received a total of $10.6 million.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reichardt said he’s appreciative of “anything that helps keep us afloat,” but noted that he and the department are far apart in their estimation of fair market value for the ducks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He also is hoping to open a discussion on USDA depopulation requirements. Because the flu is so highly transmissible, the federal agency insists on complete depopulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Could we have euthanized the affected birds and monitored the others? And continue testing birds?” Reichardt wondered, noting that only a couple dozen were confirmed sick in the recent outbreak. “I think I understand USDA’s stance. This thing is terrible. When it takes hold, it’s like a wildfire. But I think there are other methods to put out the wildfire. It’s a depressing process to put down healthy, happy birds.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The duck farm must now wait four months before reintroducing birds, and it will takes months beyond that for young ducks to mature and become egg layers. Reichardt Duck Farm had yet to fully bounce back from late 2023, when the company was forced to euthanize more than 200,000 birds. The owner estimates that before getting the bad news last week, they were at about 40% of their pre-2023 levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most depressing for Phil Reichardt is knowing there’s a good chance the staff members who have been handling the depopulation may soon find their hours slashed, or could even be laid off as some were two winters ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It really gets me emotional. Some of them are family to us,” Reichardt said. “These people are working their butts off to put themselves out of work.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first big California outbreak of 2023-24 was also in late October, at a turkey meat facility in Merced County. By the end of that winter, at least 6.3 million commercial birds had been killed in the state. In Sonoma County alone, officials estimated the financial loss to producers at around $22 million. The effects were felt well beyond farm properties, with &lt;a href="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/2025/01/15/aftermath-of-bird-flu-lowers-supply-and-ups-cost-of-eggs-2/"&gt;egg prices skyrocketing in stores&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last winter was far more devastating statewide, with more than 16.5 million dead birds. But that pandemic left Sonoma County unscathed. This winter already threatens to be different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;You can reach Phil Barber at 707-521-5263 or phil.barber@pressdemocrat.com. On X (Twitter) @Skinny_Post.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Press Democrat</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:24:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxNRVp6MUc1S01NTG4wNHJpSXFVcVNJaDZMdm9GamEwdndKM2thbW4tR093NktsTkRoQXlpdWVwYWdmcWhveDJwaDhDckM2c2JhVHdPT0htYXRLNUs5SlhEa19LdVhPVnp5RDRlNWQtazJjdTY2ZjFpRUNYbGk5eGR4anpCMzBUSlg4TG4yZ2E0UzUyYlY2ZlJsYjRZczNQVXFXSWtLWW85eWJYakdTaG9LcWF6MnFnUExPdjdDOHphSzk</guid></item><item><title>狗妈妈在篱笆下爬行以逃避被忽视—然后为她的小狗找到帮助-渡渡鸟</title><link>https://www.thedodo.com/daily-dodo/mama-dog-crawls-under-fence-to-escape-neglect-then-finds-help-for-her-puppies</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="NodeArticlestyles__ObscuredContentWrapper-sc-1rwhog1-6 eCcsQv"&gt;&lt;div class="ParagraphBodyTextstyles__BodyText-sc-zv221u-0 eJmGWQ page-element paragraph undefined " data-element-type="ParagraphBodyText" data-element-index="0"&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="0"&gt;Last month, Don Boston, founder of &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/asap.325/"&gt;Abilene Stray Animal Program&lt;/a&gt;, was out looking for an abandoned husky when he stumbled upon someone unexpected. He saw a dog wandering around all by herself on the side of a dirt road, looking hungry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="1"&gt;Boston gave the dog some food while he tried to figure out who she was and where she’d come from. Once she’d eaten her fill and started walking away, Boston followed her around the corner — and saw her puppies behind a fence in someone’s yard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-element-type="ParagraphImage" data-element-index="1" class="ParagraphImagestyles__ImageContainer-sc-puj0e1-0 hHKvH page-element paragraph-image "&gt;&lt;picture class="picture-tag picture-tag--lazy" data-testid="picture-tag"&gt;&lt;img class="" src="https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200629/714x1012/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg" srcset="https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200629/714x1012/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg 1000w, https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200629/1428x2024/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg 2000w" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200629/714x1012/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="Caption-sc-1do4sd3-0 kEEwas caption__paragraph-image"&gt;&lt;span class="Credit-sc-ke5nu1-0 jmSitH"&gt;Abilene Stray Animal Program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="ParagraphBodyTextstyles__BodyText-sc-zv221u-0 eJmGWQ page-element paragraph undefined " data-element-type="ParagraphBodyText" data-element-index="2"&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="0"&gt;Boston could immediately tell that the yard was no place for dogs. There were sharp pieces of metal everywhere and no food anywhere in sight. Upon closer inspection, he saw that several of the dogs had flystrike on their ears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="1"&gt;“They are hungry,” Boston said in a Facebook video. “Hungry, hungry, hungry.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="2"&gt;The mama dog and two of her puppies had escaped through a hole in the fence. Seeing how neglected they all were, all Boston wanted to do was take the whole family home with him. But he knew he had to talk to the property owner first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="ConnatixVideostyles__ConnatixVideoWrap-sc-woid5f-0 ktIfME connatix-article-mobile"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="ParagraphBodyTextstyles__BodyText-sc-zv221u-0 eJmGWQ page-element paragraph undefined " data-element-type="ParagraphBodyText" data-element-index="5"&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="0"&gt;“[I]t broke my heart, honestly,” Boston told The Dodo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="1"&gt;Boston learned from the owner that the dogs had originally belonged to his brother, who’d passed away. Since taking in the mama dog, she’d had multiple litters of puppies. Boston knew he couldn’t let that cycle continue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="2"&gt;“I was like, ‘I have to help these guys,’” Boston said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="3"&gt;Boston was able to convince the property owner to rehome the puppies. Now that they’re with their new families, the puppies have a safe home environment, where they have access to the fresh water and food they need to grow big and strong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="ParagraphBodyTextstyles__BodyText-sc-zv221u-0 eJmGWQ page-element paragraph undefined " data-element-type="ParagraphBodyText" data-element-index="7"&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="0"&gt;As for the mama dog, Boston talked her owner into letting him get her spayed. At the very least, he wanted to put a stop to her having any more puppies in that environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="1"&gt;While Boston was preparing to take the mama to get spayed, he got a call from animal control that she’d been picked up by one of their officers after escaping through the fence again. They’d contacted her owner and never heard back, which meant Boston was allowed to foster her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-element-type="ParagraphImage" data-element-index="8" class="ParagraphImagestyles__ImageContainer-sc-puj0e1-0 hHKvH page-element paragraph-image "&gt;&lt;picture class="picture-tag picture-tag--lazy" data-testid="picture-tag"&gt;&lt;img class="" src="https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200635/792x1213/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg" srcset="https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200635/792x1213/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg 1000w, https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200635/1584x2426/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg 2000w" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200635/792x1213/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="Caption-sc-1do4sd3-0 kEEwas caption__paragraph-image"&gt;&lt;span class="Credit-sc-ke5nu1-0 jmSitH"&gt;Abilene Stray Animal Program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="ParagraphBodyTextstyles__BodyText-sc-zv221u-0 eJmGWQ page-element paragraph undefined " data-element-type="ParagraphBodyText" data-element-index="9"&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="0"&gt;As soon as the mama dog is cleared, Boston will be taking her home with him and helping her find a forever family. After everything she’s been through, Boston is looking forward to making her as comfortable and happy as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="1"&gt;“We’re [going to] try to give her a happy life,” Boston said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="ParagraphEditorsNotestyles__EditorsNoteDiv-sc-tvi916-0 bBnoeL page-element paragraph undefined" data-element-type="ParagraphEditorsNote" data-element-index="10"&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you'd like to donate to Abilene Stray Animal Program, you can do so &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://venmo.com/u/asap325"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Dodo</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 22:52:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxOZXVRcUp6UVY1WjBOWjVxdTlMblVBa3I3cXQ4bjZORkZBR3RXWDJIV1BlckhPMm5UQi05RUU0VnNTbUw3UF9RRGdxblFZM1Y3STU5aFRiSldUemVUY0d6YnU0RWlQUmVKN1dxUEV5dDdhNzYyYUd5RmRJUTFLczJja2w0b3pTVENETFpMbHNUalRpb0lNOVZpN1hfclAzYUl3a2RjNGFiTmJVY0JNNUY1UjZB</guid></item><item><title>研究人员在不安全的自恋者中发现了一种特殊的倾向- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/researchers-identify-a-peculiar-tendency-among-insecure-narcissists/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2020-11895-001" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Psychology of Aesthetics, Creativity, and the Arts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; suggests that individuals with a combination of high narcissism and psychological insecurity are more likely to be “cultural omnivores,” consuming both highbrow and lowbrow art forms. This behavior appears to be a strategy to satisfy two distinct psychological needs: signaling social status and projecting a sense of personal integrity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Narcissism is often understood as a personality trait characterized by a grandiose sense of self, a persistent need for admiration, and a focus on one’s own importance. While this may project an image of supreme confidence, psychological research has shown that narcissism can exist alongside deep-seated feelings of insecurity, such as low self-esteem or a sense that one is not living as their “true self.” It is this particular combination of traits that interested the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, cultural taste was seen through the lens of social class. Sociologists argued that elites used their preference for “highbrow” culture, like classical music and fine art, to distinguish themselves from other social classes. In recent decades, however, this pattern has shifted. Observers have noted the rise of the “cultural omnivore,” an individual who appreciates both high-status cultural products and more popular, “lowbrow” forms like pop music or street art.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study’s authors proposed that this modern trend might be explained not just by social class, but by specific personality dynamics. They hypothesized that people high in narcissism but low in self-security might use cultural consumption as a tool. Liking highbrow culture could serve their need to signal superior status, while an appreciation for lowbrow culture, often seen as more authentic, could help soothe their inner feelings of inauthenticity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To investigate this idea, the researchers conducted two separate studies. In the first experiment, they surveyed 178 university students. Participants completed questionnaires designed to measure their levels of narcissism and self-esteem. They were then asked to rate how likely they would be to participate in a variety of cultural activities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of these activities were classified as highbrow, including attending a classical symphony or visiting art galleries. Others were categorized as lowbrow, such as going to pop concerts or viewing graffiti and street art. The researchers analyzed the data to see if there was a connection between the participants’ personality scores and their cultural intentions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings revealed a distinct pattern. For individuals who scored high on the narcissism scale, having lower self-esteem was associated with a stronger intention to participate in highbrow cultural activities. A similar relationship appeared for lowbrow culture. The participants with high narcissism and low self-esteem also expressed a greater interest in lowbrow activities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This confirmed that the insecure narcissist profile was linked to being a cultural omnivore, showing an appetite for both ends of the cultural spectrum. The analysis also suggested that this behavior was connected to a general motivation for “distinction seeking,” or a desire to establish a unique and notable identity through their choices. This relationship held even when the researchers accounted for other factors, like a person’s openness to new experiences or their own perception of their social status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second study was designed to explore the specific motivations behind these dual preferences. The researchers wanted to confirm if status seeking was driving the interest in highbrow culture, while a need for integrity was behind the preference for lowbrow culture. This experiment involved 144 university students and used a slightly different approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of measuring general self-esteem, the researchers measured a more specific form of insecurity known as self-alienation, which is the feeling of being out of touch with one’s true self. They also focused on a particular aspect of narcissism related to superiority and arrogance. Participants were then randomly assigned to read a biography of a fictional artist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One version of the biography presented the artist as highbrow, noting that her paintings were exhibited in major museums around the world. The other version framed her as lowbrow, explaining that her work was given to family and friends before being discovered by an art dealer in her hometown. After reading one of the biographies, participants rated their interest in seeing the artist’s work. They also answered questions about their current motivations, including their desire to signal status and their need to project self-integrity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results of this experiment provided clearer support for the researchers’ hypothesis. Among participants who read about the highbrow artist, those with the insecure narcissist profile showed greater interest in her work. This increased interest was statistically linked to a heightened desire for status at that moment. Consuming high-status art appeared to satisfy their need to be seen as having high status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the participants who read about the lowbrow artist, a different motivation was at play. In this case, the insecure narcissist group’s interest in the art was connected to their desire to signal self-integrity. The perceived authenticity of the lowbrow artist seemed to offer a way for these individuals to bolster their own shaky sense of self. The two studies together paint a nuanced picture of how personality can shape cultural tastes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research provides a new psychological perspective on a phenomenon that has largely been studied through a sociological framework. It suggests that for some people, the choice of what art to consume is not merely a matter of taste but a complex strategy for managing their identity and internal insecurities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors note that their findings are based on statistical associations, and future research could explore these mechanisms further. For instance, an experiment could temporarily change a person’s feelings of security to see if it directly affects their cultural preferences. Researchers could also examine whether this pattern of behavior extends to other domains, such as luxury consumption, social media use, or even charitable giving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/doi/10.1037/aca0000303" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;How Insecure Narcissists Become Cultural Omnivores: Consuming Highbrow Culture for Status Seeking and Lowbrow Culture for Integrity Signaling&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Hanna Shin and Nara Youn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 22:03:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxON2c5TFNxeEx6Z2M3d0xpekt3RUozU1l1X05xQmdvaE9GRXNOMERPZXVmVUFjUjJfYVBLd0Y1a3JNVlg1bzBCTHAwbHpxeVhXcURDbU0xSU0zS3NpS1VYbmZkTHp0VjRnSEJnYmtnb29zeEU1bHZXTlAxOFpSQ0ttOXdWc095S1lzWk1SV0V6R0hhUU1CNzI0</guid></item><item><title>专家揭示了超加工食品对身体的100种影响...以及如何扭转它们-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15243725/effects-ultra-processed-foods-junk-exercise-gut-hormones.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is no secret that high-fat, high-sugar ultra-processed foods make a person sluggish and depressed. It is also not a surprise that a sedentary lifestyle compounds those effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a recent study, University College Cork researchers discovered that a two-month &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-13135781/processed-foods-cigarettes-expert-cancer-heart-lung-disease.html"&gt;junk food diet&lt;/a&gt;, one &lt;span&gt;that mirrored &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-13399283/graphic-exactly-ultra-processed-foods-doing-body-including-ruining-skin-hair-depression.html"&gt;an ultra-processed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; food (UPF) diet typical in the US, &lt;/span&gt;drastically altered the gut environment of rats, changing 100 out of 175 measured bacterial compounds and depleting specific metabolites that affect brain function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The brain and gut are closely connected via what scientists call the gut-brain axis, a complex and constant 'conversation' between the digestive system and brain, where gut bacteria produce compounds that directly influence mood, stress levels and cognition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In the latest study, exercise combatted &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="/news/depression/index.html" id="mol-bdb7db90-b5d5-11f0-be90-313e077171fe"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; caused by a diet mirroring the one that Americans often adhere to, by rebalancing crucial metabolic hormones and restoring beneficial gut compounds.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Physical activity also reduced anxiety- and depression-like behavior and enhanced learning and memory in the rats who ate the junk food diet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Until now, it has been unclear whether exercise can reverse the unhealthy diet’s effects on mood, as well as cognitive behaviors, but this latest study suggests that it can.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers concluded that a primary way exercise combats depression is by repairing the gut microbiome, which is damaged by a poor diet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The restored gut bacteria then release beneficial substances that travel from the gut to the brain, acting as crucial chemical signals to improve mood. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;While exercise is known to improve mood and cognition, it has been unclear whether it can counteract the negative effects of an unhealthy diet on these same behaviors (stock)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ultra-processed foods (UPFs) dominate the American diet, accounting for roughly 70 percent of grocery items. The industrially engineered products contain artificial flavors and additives rarely found in home kitchens. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Their hyper-palatable, salty, and sweet design makes them hard to resist, with emerging research suggesting they may be addictive. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Americans get about 55 percent of their daily calories from cheap, tasty and unhealthy manufactured foods. Diets made up mainly of these offenders are strongly linked to an increased risk of heart disease, heart attacks, stroke and cardiovascular-related deaths. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There is a consistent and growing body of evidence linking a diet high in UPFs to an increased risk of overall cancer and specific cancer types such as colorectal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2023 analysis found that &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10285062/"&gt;every 10 percent increase&lt;/a&gt; in the proportion of UPFs in the diet was associated with a four percent higher risk of colorectal cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Diets heavy in UPFs have also been associated with markedly higher rates of depression. In August, Turkish researchers reported that &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12393073/"&gt;a 10 percent increase&lt;/a&gt; in UPF consumption per daily calorie intake increased the depression risk by 11 percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To measure depression in rats, the Irish team conducted a swim test in which they measured the amount of time a rat spent immobile, floating passively and making only the minimal movements necessary to keep its head above water, an indication of despair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers divided the rats into four distinct groups: one ate a healthy diet without access to a running wheel for exercise, a second ate an unhealthy 'cafeteria diet' without exercise, a third ate a healthy diet with voluntary running wheel access, and the fourth ate the unhealthy diet with exercise access. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rats on the unhealthy diet spent significantly more time floating passively compared to the healthy diet group. However, when the rats with unhealthy diets had access to a running wheel between meals and then were put in the pool, this inactivity was reversed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" aria-label="To enrich screen reader interactions, please activate Accessibility in Grammarly extension settings"&gt;Sedentary rats on a junk food diet ((CAF-SED) gave up swimming faster, a sign of depression. But when they exercised (CAF-EX), they kept swimming, showing that exercise reversed the diet's adverse effect on mood&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They spent less time floating and more time actively swimming, just like the healthy rats. Rats were less likely to give up, which researchers interpret as indicating they were less depressed in the context of the model.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While exercise had a minimal effect on the gut microbiomes of rats eating healthy food, it had a powerful restorative effect on the rats eating junk food, reversing dozens of the harmful changes caused by the poor diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The unhealthy diet depleted three key gut compounds: anserine, a brain-protecting antioxidant; deoxyinosine, a building block for stable mood; and indole-3-carboxylate, which aids in the production of serotonin. The loss of these beneficial molecules disrupted crucial communication between the gut and the brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Exercise restored these compounds. Since these molecules are known to influence mood and brain function, this appears to be a primary way exercise combats diet-induced depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The unhealthy diet spiked insulin and leptin levels, hormones that, when chronically elevated, are linked to depression. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When the rats on the unhealthy diet exercised, researchers observed that insulin did not spike after eating, leptin levels were reduced and the body increased production of beneficial hormones that were reduced by the poor diet, such as GLP-1, which helps regulate blood sugar and promotes feelings of fullness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Exercise effectively normalized these hormones, improving metabolic health and directly contributing to a better mood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In addition to performing a forced swim test after eight weeks, they also performed tests for anxiety and spatial memory. Rats were placed in a large pool of opaque water. &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A hidden platform was submerged just below the surface, invisible to the rats. The rats had to learn and remember the location of the platform based on visual cues placed around the room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Over the four training days, all groups of rats learned to find the hidden platform at a similar rate. The unhealthy diet did not severely impair their ability to learn the task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The most telling result came from analyzing how the rats searched. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers found that sedentary rats on an unhealthy diet tended to use less efficient, more random swimming patterns, such as circling, while exercised rats on the same diet used more direct and purposeful search paths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, the study’s results must be interpreted cautiously, as human studies are still needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The study’s lead author, Yvonne Nolan, professor in anatomy and neuroscience at University College Cork, said: ‘We studied young adult male rats only. While animal models provide valuable mechanistic insights, we cannot assume identical effects in humans, females, or different age groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Our rats exercised voluntarily with continuous wheel access, which differs from structured human exercise programs.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Their research was published in the journal &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://genomicpress.kglmeridian.com/view/journals/brainmed/aop/article-10.61373-bm025a.0116/article-10.61373-bm025a.0116.xml#d96192e456"&gt;Brain Medicine&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 21:18:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQZVlvckEtV0I0cndVVTY3Y2g1VGV4MDg4UXk4cDBEcTBKTE1mcUtfUWxTeHNnSVJ3N2FyOHExa25ubUVqclQ4MVFfcEJwZ3o3YTB3cnhaVGNKcXlYZFlubVg3SmZKcEVhRHJiaUNOYmp4dUQtN3FucFJZNVFTR1h5ZTl5SEZNUUNTYl9UdGNJOUJRdHFPT1plRkN3Mmo2VGJfM1RlMkNIcnFOZWMzckRxR2dRUQ</guid></item><item><title>湾区发现蝙蝠确诊狂犬病-补丁</title><link>https://patch.com/california/pacifica/rabies-confirmed-bat-found-bay-area</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN MATEO COUNTY, CA — County health officials confirmed Thursday that a bat found in a San Mateo County park has tested positive for rabies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Oct. 24, a bat was found near the Little People’s Park playground at Portola Valley Town Center, officials said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Encounters with rabid animals in San Mateo County are very rare, but we take every case seriously,” said Dr. Kismet Baldwin-Santana, San Mateo County health officer. “Never touch a bat or other wild animal, even if it looks sick or injured, and keep your pets’ rabies vaccinations up to date.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;SMC Health officials urges anyone with bat contact to see a doctor immediately due to rabies risk. No treatment exists once symptoms appear. Currently, no exposures are identified.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rabies is a deadly, preventable viral disease spread through infected animal saliva. Humans and pets can contract it via bites or, rarely, through contact with saliva or brain tissue on broken skin or eyes, nose or mouth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;San Mateo County Health investigates positive animal rabies tests, contacting exposed individuals for medical attention. If exposures are unknown, public notices are posted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;San Mateo County averages two rabid bats yearly. In 2025, two bats have tested positive, including one found in Half Moon Bay on October 24, with no remaining risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;If anyone had contact with a bat at Little People’s Park at Portola Valley Town Center on Oct. 24, health officials advise they contact their medical provider.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bats that appear sick, injured or dead should be reported to the Peninsula Humane Society at 650-340-7022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Patch</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 21:05:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE5ERHBxU1dXaDk4dnJBeTNKdk9BNWtXMHFpRzRoNHkwZnZBaHZ2enllZUJuVnQwRDAwVXgzVHdEWjJMcUlHLUk0WEljN3V1c3dTWU9YVWVHRE1BeUVIMnlZQ0NsYjJTT2NnWmhncTdETlhidzc4U01WeVdlNWRtZ9IBlwFBVV95cUxNV05iZmctUGVRZjBJLURKbFJRLXNELURZdnBFYmJhblVoM3ZQUlJ3R0Fyb3ppVlR0NVN0X1p3RDRSdTFjTTEzcmJlRjQzZ0VMLWpBU0o2dDRJR0FoaHZqUm9INjhzVHBGR1B0OEZfTVB2X3lxVG5VUnJXa3QzQV8tU1pobDhTSmM2UTdmbDQ3eEVUemhSMUh3</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，怀孕期间的新冠肺炎与自闭症、发育问题有关-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/10/30/covid-19-pregnancy-autism-risk/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XSL5J7NUMRCJLNYOC34OKCRIT4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Children born to mothers infected with covid-19 during pregnancy faced a higher risk of autism, along with other neurological differences such as delays in speech and motor development, according to a study published Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 21:03:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQZ1VrX21ndXUtRUlfVEJJckxFcXU4Z0lacGdvSEwxMmd1ck03LWJkTHRRZkFKb0hyaWpxdS1xN1h3ME00azBNTjZiVEpfYy1xT2NUZ3N2QVUzWlk0alR4UFpjcE11TU5SMS1laUtMSHUtdUpZWjZaUW5teEVJTzJVWlZsaHhIVjA</guid></item><item><title>这些是痴呆症医生说您不应忽视的症状- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/symptoms-dementia-doctors-never-ignore-194200870.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;The Symptoms Dementia Doctors Wouldn’t Ignore&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;getty images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;It happens. You’re mid-sentence when you realize you totally forgot what you’re saying, or you’re driving to work—on a route you’ve traveled 100 times—but you take a wrong turn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The truth is that occasional forgetfulness, wrong turns, mind farts—whatever you want to call them—are a part of life, but that doesn’t make them any less unsettling, especially as you, or someone you love, gets older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a65667352/dementia-misdiagnosed-normal-aging-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dementia;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dementia&lt;/a&gt; affects more than &lt;a href="https://www.nih.gov/news-events/nih-research-matters/risk-future-burden-dementia-united-states" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:6 million Americans;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;6 million Americans&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and U.S. cases are expected to &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/news/united-states-dementia-cases-estimated-double-2060" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:double by 2060;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;double by 2060&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, so it’s worth knowing when to take a &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a67950962/excessive-sleepiness-dementia-symptom-new/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:symptom;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;symptom&lt;/a&gt; seriously. When it comes to &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a68148089/how-to-improve-brain-health-doctor-tips/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:brain health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;brain health&lt;/a&gt;, knowing and understanding the signs of a potential problem can be a huge asset because acting at the earliest signs of cognitive changes can make a big difference. And, even if you’re not experiencing any decline, you can act now to reduce your risk. Up to 45 percent of dementia risk is modifiable, according to research in &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/infographics-do/dementia-risk" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The Lancet;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Lancet&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. “Anyone with a brain should be looking out for their brain health, from kids to elders,” says Georgina Aldridge, MD, a neurologist at University of Iowa Health Care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part of being proactive involves knowing which signs and symptoms to take seriously. The main symptom people associate with declining brain health is forgetfulness, especially during older age, but it’s far from the only indication that something could be off. Many common symptoms fall into one of the following categories, per Dr. Aldridge: short-term memory, language, visual-spatial, executive (thinking, planning, solving problems), and behavioral. That said, everyone is different, and a person may experience any combination of symptoms depending on their condition and stage of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ahead, doctors share the specific symptoms they wouldn’t ignore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet the experts:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://uihc.org/providers/georgina-m-aldridge" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Georgina Aldridge;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Georgina Aldridge&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MD, is a neurologist at University of Iowa Health Care. &lt;a href="https://www.sutterhealth.org/research/investigators/armen-moughamian-1049681097" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Armen Moughamian;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Armen Moughamian&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MD, is the medical director of the Ray Dolby Brain Health Center at Sutter’s California Pacific Medical Center (CPMC). &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1720493141/shae-datta" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Shae Datta;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Shae Datta&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MD, is a neurologist at NYU Langone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6 Symptoms Brain Doctors Wouldn’t Ignore&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Forgetfulness and short-term memory problems.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most widely-known signs of declining &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a64853713/sleep-cognitive-performance-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:brain health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;brain health&lt;/a&gt; are forgetfulness and/or having issues with short-term memory (your brain’s ability to hold limited information for a few seconds to hours). But it’s important to state upfront that memory issues in middle-aged adults could be due to any number of causes unrelated to dementia, Dr. Aldridge says, which is all the more reason to start a conversation with your doctor. “The person may have undiagnosed &lt;a href="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/sleep-apnea" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sleep apnea;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;sleep apnea&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which means they aren’t getting the good sleep that is necessary to form memories,” she says. “The person could also have a deficiency in a vitamin, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7077099/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:such as B12;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;such as B12&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, that is necessary for the cells and nerves to function correctly.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;General forgetfulness can start in a person’s mid-50s or 60s, but it’s particularly important to look out for progressive changes in adults over 65 since the risk of a neurodegenerative brain disease like Alzheimer’s rises significantly with age, says Armen Moughamian, MD, the medical director of the Ray Dolby Brain Health Center at Sutter’s California Pacific Medical Center (CPMC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forgetting recent conversations or events can be a warning sign of mild cognitive impairment that may progress to dementia and/or Alzheimer’s disease, says Dr. Moughamian. Sometimes this symptom is subtle: “Families might think their loved one just ‘wasn’t listening’ or ‘isn’t paying attention,’” Dr. Moughamian says. One way to tell if there may be something more serious going on is to take note of the consistency and frequency of these episodes. If it’s happening repeatedly, it’s worth having a conversation with a doctor, Dr. Moughamian says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. &lt;strong&gt;Irregular sleep patterns or poor sleep quality.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it wasn’t clear already, practicing good &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a68129140/how-to-get-good-deep-restorative-sleep/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sleep hygiene;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;sleep hygiene&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is the key to better health all-around, and that includes your brain. (In fact, lack of sleep in middle age may increase dementia risk, per the &lt;a href="https://www.nih.gov/news-events/nih-research-matters/lack-sleep-middle-age-may-increase-dementia-risk" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:National Institutes of Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;National Institutes of Health&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you notice that you haven’t been resting well lately, it doesn’t necessarily mean it’s due to a brain disorder, but it’s worth getting to the bottom of. Feeling sleepy and excessive napping during the day &lt;em&gt;could&lt;/em&gt; serve as an early marker of dementia, particularly for women in their 80s, per a 2025 study in the journal &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40106755/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Neurology;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Neurology&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if you’re not concerned about dementia or Alzheimer’s, sleep influences brain health and vice versa, so to help your body function optimally, try to get your Zzzs in. “I often remind patients that sleep is one of the most effective ways to protect the brain,” says Shae Datta, MD, is a neurologist at NYU Langone. “Sleep is when the brain &lt;a href="https://medicine.washu.edu/news/neurons-help-flush-waste-out-of-brain-during-sleep/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:clears waste products;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;clears waste products&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and consolidates memories. When sleep quality declines, it can affect cognitive performance and &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a68915281/sleep-brain-aging-link/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:long-term brain health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;long-term brain health&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just remember: Everyone’s sleep needs are different, but the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/sleep/about/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Centers for Disease Control and Prevention;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (CDC) recommends that most adults get between seven to nine hours per night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Mood, personality, or behavior changes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changes in mood, personality, and behavior can all be signs of dementia or Alzheimer’s. Behavior change is broad, but it can often look like someone feeling suspicious of or threatened by others for little or no reason, showing unusual sexual behavior, becoming physically violent (like hitting someone else), and more, per the &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/alzheimers-changes-behavior-and-communication/alzheimers-caregiving-managing-personality-and" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:National Institute on Aging;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;National Institute on Aging&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. It can also look like a social faux pas like talking excessively to strangers, Dr. Aldridge says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“New-onset anxiety, depression, or irritability in your 60s can be an early and often overlooked sign of Alzheimer’s disease,” Dr. Moughamian says. “These mood changes frequently appear before any memory problems, signaling that something deeper may be happening in the brain.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, personality changes can suggest a specific condition called &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a65090545/mom-dementia-diagnosis-marathons/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:frontotemporal dementia;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;frontotemporal dementia&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (FTD), Dr. Aldridge adds. FTD is one of the most common types of dementia that affect younger and middle-aged adults. Symptoms usually start between the ages of 40 and 65, but it can strike younger and older adults as well, and it affects women and men equally, per &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/dementia/frontotemporal-dementia" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Johns Hopkins Medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Johns Hopkins Medicine&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4. &lt;strong&gt;Struggling with language or trouble finding the right words.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have you ever had the feeling that a word is “right on the tip of your tongue?” We’ve all been there, but experiencing new or worsening issues with language (past the occasional slip-up) can signal potential problems in the brain, Dr. Datta says. In cases of Alzheimer’s and dementia, this can look like having difficulty understanding complex sentences, dropping connecting words, struggling to name a familiar object, and more, experts say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trouble finding everyday words mid-sentence or frequently “hitting a wall” in conversation is also potentially concerning and may point to early Alzheimer’s or another neurological condition, Dr. Moughamian says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;5. &lt;strong&gt;Difficulty with everyday household skills and tasks.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the most common symptoms of dementia and Alzheimer’s that people experience have to do with the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/executive-function" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:executive function;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;executive function&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; side of brain health, Dr. Aldridge says—basically, how you manage everyday tasks like making plans, solving problems, and making decisions. If you consistently have trouble with any of those things and didn’t necessarily struggle with them before, it could be a sign of dementia, Dr. Moughamian says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If someone stops cooking, stops managing medications, or misses paying bills, this is concerning,” he says. “People typically don’t just stop doing things, and often these changes are changes that are associated with dementia.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Changes in visual-spatial awareness.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with emerging brain health issues might encounter trouble with visual-spatial awareness, which is your brain’s ability to understand what you see and interpret the relationship between objects in space. Conditions like dementia can &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.3233/JAD-215435" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:affect your vision;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;affect your vision&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, so if you have trouble with something like depth perception—signing too high up on a check or not being able to find objects among clutter— it could be an &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2227-9032/9/2/157" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:early sign of Alzheimer’s;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;early sign of Alzheimer’s&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or certain types of dementia, Dr. Aldridge says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a person starts experiencing visual hallucinations (seeing or hearing things that aren’t there), it could be a sign of Lewy Body Dementia (LBD), a complex disorder involving abnormal deposits of a protein called alpha-synuclein in the brain, per the &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/lewy-body-dementia/lewy-body-dementia-causes-symptoms-and-diagnosis" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:National Institute on Aging;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;National Institute on Aging&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. These deposits, called “Lewy bodies,” affect chemicals in the brain, which can lead to changes in thinking and behavior. As a result, a person might experience visual hallucinations that are vivid and even scary in nature. (If the hallucinations are severe, doctors can prescribe medication, per the &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/lewy-body-dementia/lewy-body-dementia-causes-symptoms-and-diagnosis" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:National Institute on Aging;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;National Institute on Aging&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;). If you’re experiencing hallucinations, you should definitely see a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you or someone you love are experiencing any of the above symptoms, it may be a good time to see a doctor. Although some cognitive changes come naturally with age, things could progress from mild cognitive impairment to something more serious—so, better to be proactive and see a neurologist who can help you navigate what comes next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:55:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQZ0hHMDhXTXMxMHk0b0R0dmlfQ0FGbHFQRUhMcXYzaVcwXzRqeHBiTkdTZlFtNTN3b2ZmTjAxbmlGWjR3NTFaSlhnN1RSaVVHd3RES1NFQW42OTZMTFdsWXB2bVIxZHhZYmxYQjFITVZQcFd1ZVllYTdQMng3Rnp4SWh2eEpMdDAydkE</guid></item><item><title>金毛小狗采摘苹果是总可爱超负荷-PetHelpful</title><link>https://pethelpful.com/pet-news/golden-retriever-puppies-picking-apples-is-cuteness-overload</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PetHelpful</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxPUVVTQ2gxTTV1cnpJUi1RVy0tdEpSQkUtZVFyUkdpQ1dzT21zclFsOWNmdFBrc1BQalhwYUZ1MFUwVE50aGpadkpObE9nYXR6eFlFRFg4ZjBKMk95UlBuMWl6MHY5WEhXWjM3YVh3UHFpckl0QllzZmNtdVVlTXY3ZjBUSmd0UjhfRzUydExtdDNWMWFPT21B</guid></item><item><title>由皮特研究员共同创造的眼睛植入物帮助近视盲人再次看到- TribLIVE.com</title><link>https://triblive.com/news/health-now/eye-implant-designed-by-pitt-researcher-helps-the-near-blind-see-again/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storyContent"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A retinal implant the size of a strawberry seed co-created by a University of Pittsburgh researcher has helped partially restore vision for older people suffering from macular degeneration.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was conducted in Europe and co-led by Dr. José-Alain Sahel, chair of Pitt’s ophthalmology department and director of the UPMC Vision Institute.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results, &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2501396?logout=true" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;published last week&lt;/a&gt; in the New England Journal of Medicine, showed significant vision improvement after a year for 26 of 32 people who had the tiny device surgically implanted.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All participants were older than 60 and considered legally blind because of the disease, which affects part of the retina and erodes central vision, or people’s ability to clearly see things in front of them.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The implant mimics the light-sensitive cells destroyed by macular degeneration. 

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sahel described the device, which measures just 2 millimeters each way, as a “miniaturized solar panel.”

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It must be paired with specialized glasses. A small camera mounted on the frame captures images and sends them to a cell phone-sized processor in the user’s pocket. The information goes back up to the camera and is projected onto the implant.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From here, the brain’s normal vision processes take over and, in many cases, patients who are nearly blind regain some of their vision.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before the implant, participants couldn’t see the first or second line of a vision chart. A year in, patients saw an average improvement of five lines, with one being able to see 12 more lines than before.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They can read letters, they can read words and some of them can read a book, which is something we didn’t even really think could happen,” Sahel said.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one patient reported being able to navigate the subway again.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="neFMT neFMT_body-subhead"&gt;Disease afflicts millions&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The system is called PRIMA, and has been in development for 20 years. Along with Sahel, Stanford University professor and study co-author Daniel Palanker has been a driving force behind this research.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two past pilot studies showed promise, but “this is the first study of this size and this level of improvement that has ever been achieved in this field,” Sahel said.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advanced macular degeneration affects more than 5 million people worldwide, according to the researchers. For those older than 80, it’s the leading cause of irreversible blindness.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disease progressively blurs, darkens and distorts the center of the field of vision, while leaving peripheral vision intact.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the late stages of macular degeneration, central vision goes completely dark. Existing treatments can only slow the disease’s advance.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients tend to just see zaps of light after surgery, Sahel explained, but through a training program, the brain learns to better process the implant’s signals. This usually takes a few weeks.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even at its best, the bionic vision is limited. It appears in black and white and can be somewhat blurry.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sahel and other researchers are working on a next-generation device with higher resolution.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRIMA has the potential to restore vision in patients with other diseases, as long as they have a functional optical nerve. It cannot compensate for eye trauma, for instance.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="neFMT neFMT_body-subhead"&gt;Working with regulators&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The device manufacturer, Science Corp., is working to obtain regulatory approval in the U.S. and Europe for use beyond clinical trials.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Science hopes to make PRIMA available in Europe by the end of 2026, according to spokeswoman Elizabeth McKenzie.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She did not give a target date in the U.S., but said the company is engaged in an approval process with the federal Food and Drug Administration.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regulators will likely look at some of the negative effects reported in the study, mostly related to the surgery, rather than the device itself.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The procedure is done in most cases under general anesthesia, as opposed to just numbing the eye. To insert the chip, surgeons make a small incision into the retina — the back part of the eye used to detect light — and place the chip underneath it.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most frequent side effects were pressure in the eyes, bleeding and small rips at the edges of the retina.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None were life-threatening, and nearly all resolved quickly.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Past studies already proved to Sahel the device was safe and effective. After these latest results, widespread use of PRIMA appears closer than ever.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The goal was to show this is scalable,” he said.

&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="s2nPlayer k-7fvO6bjp" data-type="float"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="credits"&gt;Jack Troy is a TribLive reporter covering business and health care. A Pittsburgh native, he joined the Trib in January 2024 after graduating from the University of Pittsburgh. He can be reached at &lt;ahref&gt;jtroy@triblive.com.&lt;/ahref&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TribLIVE.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 19:47:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxONXBiU2V2cHM0VmtoUEwtVDhxWXR3V1FCVjZ4azR4QVRDei1hRWZMbHhONlgzZDRUa1ZWRVJ4Rk5yMjM2aW1wVzdqcjZkMVNfeG92S2h5a2pHcjhoeXRvd3JObGJzRmp0MnFmWGhFdV9PeUNFWHNDZzhNRVV2eWF4Zi05NHJGVmd4SWVBX1A3VGFiZ0tEUUFma0NuU1BjMTJQUkFlMUdiNU12OWhV</guid></item><item><title>这些是痴呆症医生说你永远不应该忽视的症状-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/symptoms-dementia-doctors-never-ignore-194200128.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It happens. You’re mid-sentence when you realize you totally forgot what you’re saying, or you’re driving to work—on a route you’ve traveled 100 times—but you take a wrong turn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The truth is that occasional forgetfulness, wrong turns, mind farts—whatever you want to call them—are a part of life, but that doesn’t make them any less unsettling, especially as you, or someone you love, gets older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a65667352/dementia-misdiagnosed-normal-aging-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dementia;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dementia&lt;/a&gt; affects more than &lt;a href="https://www.nih.gov/news-events/nih-research-matters/risk-future-burden-dementia-united-states" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:6 million Americans;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;6 million Americans&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and U.S. cases are expected to &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/news/united-states-dementia-cases-estimated-double-2060" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:double by 2060;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;double by 2060&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, so it’s worth knowing when to take a &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a67950962/excessive-sleepiness-dementia-symptom-new/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:symptom;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;symptom&lt;/a&gt; seriously. When it comes to &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a68148089/how-to-improve-brain-health-doctor-tips/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:brain health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;brain health&lt;/a&gt;, knowing and understanding the signs of a potential problem can be a huge asset because acting at the earliest signs of cognitive changes can make a big difference. And, even if you’re not experiencing any decline, you can act now to reduce your risk. Up to 45 percent of dementia risk is modifiable, according to research in &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/infographics-do/dementia-risk" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The Lancet;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Lancet&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. “Anyone with a brain should be looking out for their brain health, from kids to elders,” says Georgina Aldridge, MD, a neurologist at University of Iowa Health Care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Part of being proactive involves knowing which signs and symptoms to take seriously. The main symptom people associate with declining brain health is forgetfulness, especially during older age, but it’s far from the only indication that something could be off. Many common symptoms fall into one of the following categories, per Dr. Aldridge: short-term memory, language, visual-spatial, executive (thinking, planning, solving problems), and behavioral. That said, everyone is different, and a person may experience any combination of symptoms depending on their condition and stage of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ahead, doctors share the specific symptoms they wouldn’t ignore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet the experts:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://uihc.org/providers/georgina-m-aldridge" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Georgina Aldridge;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;Georgina Aldridge&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MD, is a neurologist at University of Iowa Health Care. &lt;a href="https://www.sutterhealth.org/research/investigators/armen-moughamian-1049681097" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Armen Moughamian;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;Armen Moughamian&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MD, is the medical director of the Ray Dolby Brain Health Center at Sutter’s California Pacific Medical Center (CPMC). &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1720493141/shae-datta" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Shae Datta;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;Shae Datta&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MD, is a neurologist at NYU Langone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6 Symptoms Brain Doctors Wouldn’t Ignore&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Forgetfulness and short-term memory problems.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The most widely-known signs of declining &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a64853713/sleep-cognitive-performance-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:brain health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;brain health&lt;/a&gt; are forgetfulness and/or having issues with short-term memory (your brain’s ability to hold limited information for a few seconds to hours). But it’s important to state upfront that memory issues in middle-aged adults could be due to any number of causes unrelated to dementia, Dr. Aldridge says, which is all the more reason to start a conversation with your doctor. “The person may have undiagnosed &lt;a href="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/sleep-apnea" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sleep apnea;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;sleep apnea&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which means they aren’t getting the good sleep that is necessary to form memories,” she says. “The person could also have a deficiency in a vitamin, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7077099/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:such as B12;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;such as B12&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, that is necessary for the cells and nerves to function correctly.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;General forgetfulness can start in a person’s mid-50s or 60s, but it’s particularly important to look out for progressive changes in adults over 65 since the risk of a neurodegenerative brain disease like Alzheimer’s rises significantly with age, says Armen Moughamian, MD, the medical director of the Ray Dolby Brain Health Center at Sutter’s California Pacific Medical Center (CPMC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Forgetting recent conversations or events can be a warning sign of mild cognitive impairment that may progress to dementia and/or Alzheimer’s disease, says Dr. Moughamian. Sometimes this symptom is subtle: “Families might think their loved one just ‘wasn’t listening’ or ‘isn’t paying attention,’” Dr. Moughamian says. One way to tell if there may be something more serious going on is to take note of the consistency and frequency of these episodes. If it’s happening repeatedly, it’s worth having a conversation with a doctor, Dr. Moughamian says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;2. &lt;strong&gt;Irregular sleep patterns or poor sleep quality.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If it wasn’t clear already, practicing good &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a68129140/how-to-get-good-deep-restorative-sleep/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sleep hygiene;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;sleep hygiene&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is the key to better health all-around, and that includes your brain. (In fact, lack of sleep in middle age may increase dementia risk, per the &lt;a href="https://www.nih.gov/news-events/nih-research-matters/lack-sleep-middle-age-may-increase-dementia-risk" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:National Institutes of Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;National Institutes of Health&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you notice that you haven’t been resting well lately, it doesn’t necessarily mean it’s due to a brain disorder, but it’s worth getting to the bottom of. Feeling sleepy and excessive napping during the day &lt;em&gt;could&lt;/em&gt; serve as an early marker of dementia, particularly for women in their 80s, per a 2025 study in the journal &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40106755/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Neurology;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Neurology&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Even if you’re not concerned about dementia or Alzheimer’s, sleep influences brain health and vice versa, so to help your body function optimally, try to get your Zzzs in. “I often remind patients that sleep is one of the most effective ways to protect the brain,” says Shae Datta, MD, is a neurologist at NYU Langone. “Sleep is when the brain &lt;a href="https://medicine.washu.edu/news/neurons-help-flush-waste-out-of-brain-during-sleep/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:clears waste products;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;clears waste products&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and consolidates memories. When sleep quality declines, it can affect cognitive performance and &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a68915281/sleep-brain-aging-link/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:long-term brain health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;long-term brain health&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Just remember: Everyone’s sleep needs are different, but the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/sleep/about/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Centers for Disease Control and Prevention;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (CDC) recommends that most adults get between seven to nine hours per night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Mood, personality, or behavior changes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Changes in mood, personality, and behavior can all be signs of dementia or Alzheimer’s. Behavior change is broad, but it can often look like someone feeling suspicious of or threatened by others for little or no reason, showing unusual sexual behavior, becoming physically violent (like hitting someone else), and more, per the &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/alzheimers-changes-behavior-and-communication/alzheimers-caregiving-managing-personality-and" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:National Institute on Aging;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;National Institute on Aging&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. It can also look like a social faux pas like talking excessively to strangers, Dr. Aldridge says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“New-onset anxiety, depression, or irritability in your 60s can be an early and often overlooked sign of Alzheimer’s disease,” Dr. Moughamian says. “These mood changes frequently appear before any memory problems, signaling that something deeper may be happening in the brain.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Sometimes, personality changes can suggest a specific condition called &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a65090545/mom-dementia-diagnosis-marathons/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:frontotemporal dementia;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;frontotemporal dementia&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (FTD), Dr. Aldridge adds. FTD is one of the most common types of dementia that affect younger and middle-aged adults. Symptoms usually start between the ages of 40 and 65, but it can strike younger and older adults as well, and it affects women and men equally, per &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/dementia/frontotemporal-dementia" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Johns Hopkins Medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;Johns Hopkins Medicine&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;4. &lt;strong&gt;Struggling with language or trouble finding the right words.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Have you ever had the feeling that a word is “right on the tip of your tongue?” We’ve all been there, but experiencing new or worsening issues with language (past the occasional slip-up) can signal potential problems in the brain, Dr. Datta says. In cases of Alzheimer’s and dementia, this can look like having difficulty understanding complex sentences, dropping connecting words, struggling to name a familiar object, and more, experts say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Trouble finding everyday words mid-sentence or frequently “hitting a wall” in conversation is also potentially concerning and may point to early Alzheimer’s or another neurological condition, Dr. Moughamian says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;5. &lt;strong&gt;Difficulty with everyday household skills and tasks.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Some of the most common symptoms of dementia and Alzheimer’s that people experience have to do with the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/executive-function" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:executive function;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;executive function&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; side of brain health, Dr. Aldridge says—basically, how you manage everyday tasks like making plans, solving problems, and making decisions. If you consistently have trouble with any of those things and didn’t necessarily struggle with them before, it could be a sign of dementia, Dr. Moughamian says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“If someone stops cooking, stops managing medications, or misses paying bills, this is concerning,” he says. “People typically don’t just stop doing things, and often these changes are changes that are associated with dementia.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Changes in visual-spatial awareness.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;People with emerging brain health issues might encounter trouble with visual-spatial awareness, which is your brain’s ability to understand what you see and interpret the relationship between objects in space. Conditions like dementia can &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.3233/JAD-215435" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:affect your vision;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;affect your vision&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, so if you have trouble with something like depth perception—signing too high up on a check or not being able to find objects among clutter— it could be an &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2227-9032/9/2/157" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:early sign of Alzheimer’s;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;early sign of Alzheimer’s&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or certain types of dementia, Dr. Aldridge says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If a person starts experiencing visual hallucinations (seeing or hearing things that aren’t there), it could be a sign of Lewy Body Dementia (LBD), a complex disorder involving abnormal deposits of a protein called alpha-synuclein in the brain, per the &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/lewy-body-dementia/lewy-body-dementia-causes-symptoms-and-diagnosis" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:National Institute on Aging;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;National Institute on Aging&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. These deposits, called “Lewy bodies,” affect chemicals in the brain, which can lead to changes in thinking and behavior. As a result, a person might experience visual hallucinations that are vivid and even scary in nature. (If the hallucinations are severe, doctors can prescribe medication, per the &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/lewy-body-dementia/lewy-body-dementia-causes-symptoms-and-diagnosis" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:National Institute on Aging;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;u&gt;National Institute on Aging&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;). If you’re experiencing hallucinations, you should definitely see a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you or someone you love are experiencing any of the above symptoms, it may be a good time to see a doctor. Although some cognitive changes come naturally with age, things could progress from mild cognitive impairment to something more serious—so, better to be proactive and see a neurologist who can help you navigate what comes next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 19:42:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxQdzg1OGp1ZHdvVzM5VDJHLVhfTEJVOTF6VkNwQ1FhR3JBUXNSUVdYLUFIekM0b29maVlMbks2Y2lDczFDNi1qanc4c2Z0Qm9UZ0tUVThXM1JSUzNaZ2d6c3FSTWgwQm02WDZ6endGaGdPWnVBd1lyWUl2ekZLMENiemVlS0xfT2tnVHRJcVdBOW9BbXM</guid></item><item><title>综述：人类H5N1禽流感病例可能无症状，病毒可能在人群中传播- CIDRAP</title><link>https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/avian-influenza-bird-flu/review-human-h5n1-avian-flu-cases-can-be-asymptomatic-and-virus-likely</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-field-body field--type-text-long field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Asymptomatic human avian influenza A(H5N1) infections occur, and person-to-person transmission is likely in some settings, reveals a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2840680"&gt;&lt;span&gt;scoping review&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; by US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) researchers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The study, published yesterday in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;JAMA Network Open&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;, involved a search for studies on confirmed highly pathogenic H5N1 infection published through August 25, 2025.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Since 1997, more than 1,000 infections with highly pathogenic avian influenza A(H5N1) virus among humans have been reported globally," the researchers wrote. "Given ongoing A(H5N1) outbreaks in animals, understanding the frequency of A(H5N1) virus infections among asymptomatic persons can inform public health risk assessments and infection prevention guidance."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;18 symptom-less human infections&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The team identified 10 reports of 18 asymptomatic human H5N1 infection, including 2 with molecular and serologic confirmation (MSC) and 16 with molecular confirmation alone (MC).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Robust data collection is needed from persons with possible asymptomatic A(H5N1) virus infection to inform future public health responses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The two MSC cases occurred in adults in Pakistan and Vietnam who were identified through investigations of household contacts of index H5N1 patients; one patient was also exposed to infected chickens, and the other is believed to have been infected through human-to-human spread, because they had no contact with sick or dead poultry.  Neither MSC patient had used personal protective equipment when in close contact with an infected household member or chickens. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Of the 16 MC patients (14 adults and 2 children), 11 were identified through enhanced surveillance of people exposed to poultry infected with H5N1 (8 in Bangladesh, 2 in Spain, and 1 in the United Kingdom), and the remaining 5 patients (3 in Vietnam and 2 in Cambodia) were identified through contact tracing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Asymptomatic human infections with A(H5N1) virus have been infrequently reported, with most cases identified through enhanced surveillance or household contact investigations of persons with known exposure," the authors noted. "Robust data collection is needed from persons with possible asymptomatic A(H5N1) virus infection to inform future public health responses."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gaps in surveillance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2840687"&gt;&lt;span&gt;commentary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in the same journal, Rick Bright, PhD, of Bright Global Health, and Nicole Lurie, MD, MSPH, of the Coalition for Epidemic Preparedness Innovations (CEPI) and Harvard Medical School, noted that since March 2024, H5N1 clade 2.3.4.4b has spread among dairy cattle, with confirmed infections in more than 800 herds in at least 16 states. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Human cases have been confirmed in multiple states, and as of mid-2025, approximately 70 cases have been officially reported, most with mild illness but including at least 1 death.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;High viral levels have been found in raw milk, and live virus has been detected in mammary tissue and milking equipment. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Spillover into, and transmission among, other mammals has been documented, including cats, dogs, mice, wild carnivores, marine mammals, and swine," they wrote. "Human cases have been confirmed in multiple states, and as of mid-2025, approximately 70 cases have been officially reported, most with mild illness but including at least 1 death." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bright and Lurie said the findings challenge the traditional perception that human H5N1 infections are almost always symptomatic and severe and that no human-to-human H5N1 spread has occurred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"It also highlights a critical gap in many national and global surveillance systems, which tend to focus on the detection of symptomatic illness rather than infection, and underscores the importance of carefully examining clusters where limited transmission may occur," they concluded.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CIDRAP</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 19:16:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxOY3I1SjkzS2xvMEdLeS1hd1ZLdEtjOFBMY2Zob0FjMHNfRFFKOWpxb01rZlNFT04wcDhLRFQwbkFvM2NLVG85cE5fOUpzWWw4RzNxazZxa25UR1ZjcTJPdW84VjBOcFRaVWNYUjVsNkEwV25WRVNXT3FfWWdrVzVIUk5sTmo1c1RyUS1mdm9sdVBwUlh1NlpLM045anZxbC03bG13SFFEZzZjajJWY3JzeG5Ua1JuMFJBN3ROVmpYYw</guid></item><item><title>哈佛大学教授称每晚需要8小时睡眠的“谎言” ，称这是工业时代的“胡说八道” -财富</title><link>https://fortune.com/2025/10/30/harvard-professor-how-much-sleep-do-you-really-need-8-hours/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-cy="article-content" class="rawHtml-content-no-nativo content-sentinel"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most adults do not need a hard eight hours of sleep; a growing body of evidence and evolutionary research suggest the optimal nightly sleep for many healthy adults is closer to seven hours, with health risks rising on either side of that range in a U‑shaped pattern. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall-selector"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="paywall"&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Harvard evolutionary biologist Daniel E. Lieberman calls the rigid “8 hours” rule Industrial Era “nonsense,” noting that people without modern electricity typically sleep six to seven hours without napping, and large cohorts show the lowest mortality risk around seven hours, not eight. Lieberman expanded on the research for his book, &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Exercised/dp/0141986360/ref=sr_1_2?crid=1N2T1NB5HRXT0&amp;amp;dib=eyJ2IjoiMSJ9.r2yZNIS8wod-0Kgg7gocBjwtCkGSc66oJbZSOygtbxxo4Fr4vBxrpZYlMIlz-d52RBSGySlsN38HyEJYeg1ebrp9D7viSXFM8UARQvVytXT24YdaJXaRSQDxFukCn4meo0KfgmLVju1xphiMdrqpRgF3eBqGlcesq9XPm4EWxf0aaAtAPd8kndKpim7HDSbDFpE4hZLyTG4MZCbMkkXkPBLK2xrIDw2utEcTWUGTwb0.Q0aT327twNqjo6QylD9UhZeXHpXcZZgBSB6PLHVhYRw&amp;amp;dib_tag=se&amp;amp;keywords=exercised+book&amp;amp;qid=1761848364&amp;amp;sprefix=exercised+book%2Caps%2C194&amp;amp;sr=8-2" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://www.amazon.com/Exercised/dp/0141986360/ref=sr_1_2?crid=1N2T1NB5HRXT0&amp;amp;dib=eyJ2IjoiMSJ9.r2yZNIS8wod-0Kgg7gocBjwtCkGSc66oJbZSOygtbxxo4Fr4vBxrpZYlMIlz-d52RBSGySlsN38HyEJYeg1ebrp9D7viSXFM8UARQvVytXT24YdaJXaRSQDxFukCn4meo0KfgmLVju1xphiMdrqpRgF3eBqGlcesq9XPm4EWxf0aaAtAPd8kndKpim7HDSbDFpE4hZLyTG4MZCbMkkXkPBLK2xrIDw2utEcTWUGTwb0.Q0aT327twNqjo6QylD9UhZeXHpXcZZgBSB6PLHVhYRw&amp;amp;dib_tag=se&amp;amp;keywords=exercised+book&amp;amp;qid=1761848364&amp;amp;sprefix=exercised+book%2Caps%2C194&amp;amp;sr=8-2" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;Exercised: The Science of Physical Activity, Rest and Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, in a &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ujRwf1HdNjk" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ujRwf1HdNjk" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;2023 interview&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;em&gt;The Diary of a CEO&lt;/em&gt;. 



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What Lieberman argues&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lieberman says the idea “natural” humans sleep eight hours is unfounded; field data from communities without electric light show typical nightly sleep of about six to seven hours, contradicting the cultural prescription of eight hours as a target.&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/01/21/959140732/just-move-scientist-author-debunks-myths-about-exercise-and-sleep" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Go to https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/01/21/959140732/just-move-scientist-author-debunks-myths-about-exercise-and-sleep" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;​&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;He frames modern eight‑hour dogma as a legacy of the Industrial Revolution rather than a biological necessity, and points to epidemiologic curves where risk bottoms out around seven hours, producing a U‑shape with higher risk from both short and long sleep.&lt;a href="https://sleepopolis.com/news/harvard-professor-argues-against-8-hours-of-sleep/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Go to https://sleepopolis.com/news/harvard-professor-argues-against-8-hours-of-sleep/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;​&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Popular summaries of his stance emphasize seven hours often outperforms eight for health outcomes, while stressing variability by age and condition, and that sleep need is not one-size-fits-all.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;How much sleep do you really need?&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://fortune.com/videos/watch/fact-or-fiction:-do-you-really-need-eight-hours-of-sleep-a-night%3F/91338a5f-7719-4d1c-b12c-ac6615421d88" target="_self" aria-label="Go to https://fortune.com/videos/watch/fact-or-fiction:-do-you-really-need-eight-hours-of-sleep-a-night%3F/91338a5f-7719-4d1c-b12c-ac6615421d88" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fortune&lt;/em&gt; explainer&lt;/a&gt;, sleep scientist Rebecca Robbins addresses the eight-hour belief, explaining how the benchmark emerged and offering practical tactics to improve sleep quality rather than fixating on a single number.&lt;a href="https://fortune.com/videos/watch/fact-or-fiction:-do-you-really-need-eight-hours-of-sleep-a-night%3F/91338a5f-7719-4d1c-b12c-ac6615421d88" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Go to https://fortune.com/videos/watch/fact-or-fiction:-do-you-really-need-eight-hours-of-sleep-a-night%3F/91338a5f-7719-4d1c-b12c-ac6615421d88" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;​&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;More than one-third of Americans &lt;a href="https://fortune.com/well/2023/06/28/guide-to-better-sleep/" target="_self" aria-label="Go to https://fortune.com/well/2023/06/28/guide-to-better-sleep/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;miss the seven-hour minimum&lt;/a&gt;, underscoring the importance of consistency and sleep hygiene as much as chasing a magic number.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://fortune.com/well/article/sleep-habits-tips-guide/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Go to https://fortune.com/well/article/sleep-habits-tips-guide/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;​The American Academy of Sleep Medicine and Sleep Research Society recommend “seven or more hours per night” for adults—explicitly a range beginning at seven rather than an eight-hour mandate.&lt;a href="https://aasm.org/seven-or-more-hours-of-sleep-per-night-a-health-necessity-for-adults/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Go to https://aasm.org/seven-or-more-hours-of-sleep-per-night-a-health-necessity-for-adults/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;​&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://fortune.com/company/mayo-clinic/" target="_blank" aria-label="Go to https://fortune.com/company/mayo-clinic/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt; guidance aligns: Adults generally need seven or more hours, with individual variation based on age, sleep quality, prior sleep debt, pregnancy, and aging patterns that fragment sleep but do not increase total need.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The U‑shaped risk curve&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Multiple large contemporary &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/public-health/articles/10.3389/fpubh.2022.880276/full" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/public-health/articles/10.3389/fpubh.2022.880276/full" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;datasets show&lt;/a&gt; a U‑shaped association between sleep duration and adverse outcomes, with the nadir around seven hours for all‑cause and cardiovascular mortality risk.&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/public-health/articles/10.3389/fpubh.2022.880276/full" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Go to https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/public-health/articles/10.3389/fpubh.2022.880276/full" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;​&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;U.K. Biobank analyses also report U‑shaped relationships, with elevated risks for both short sleep (less than seven hours) and long sleep (often defined as more than nine hours for adults), after adjusting for health and lifestyle factors.&lt;a href="https://jcsm.aasm.org/doi/10.5664/jcsm.10732" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Go to https://jcsm.aasm.org/doi/10.5664/jcsm.10732" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;​&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Mechanistic and biomarker work echoes the U‑shape, with deviations below seven or above eight to nine hours linked to markers of biological aging, though causality can be confounded by illness extending time in bed.&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10178027/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Go to https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10178027/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;​&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Practical guidance for sleep&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Aim for seven to nine hours, using seven as a realistic minimum if you wake refreshed and function well; extend toward nine during illness, heavy training, or pregnancy as needed.&lt;a href="https://aasm.org/seven-or-more-hours-of-sleep-per-night-a-health-necessity-for-adults/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Go to https://aasm.org/seven-or-more-hours-of-sleep-per-night-a-health-necessity-for-adults/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;​&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Watch for the U‑shape: chronic short sleep (less than seven hours) and habitual long sleep (more than 9 hours) are both linked to higher risks; if you routinely need more than nine hours, consult a clinician to evaluate for underlying conditions like depression, sleep apnea, or chronic disease.&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/public-health/articles/10.3389/fpubh.2022.880276/full" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Go to https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/public-health/articles/10.3389/fpubh.2022.880276/full" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;​&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Prioritize consistency and quality—regular bed/wake times, morning light, reduced evening blue light, cool dark bedrooms, and limiting caffeine/alcohol—rather than obsessing over an eight‑hour target.&lt;a href="https://fortune.com/well/article/sleep-habits-tips-guide/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Go to https://fortune.com/well/article/sleep-habits-tips-guide/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;​&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The ‘sweet spot’ for sleep&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;The eight‑hour rule is a cultural simplification, not a universal biological requirement; seven hours often sits at the health “sweet spot” for many adults, with flexibility around that based on life stage and health.&lt;a href="https://sleepopolis.com/news/harvard-professor-argues-against-8-hours-of-sleep/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Go to https://sleepopolis.com/news/harvard-professor-argues-against-8-hours-of-sleep/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;​&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Business leaders and individuals should reframe sleep goals toward the evidence-based range and measurable daytime function, investing in &lt;a href="https://fortune.com/well/article/sleep-habits-tips-guide/" target="_self" aria-label="Go to https://fortune.com/well/article/sleep-habits-tips-guide/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;sleep quality practices &lt;/a&gt;that improve performance and long‑term health without enforcing a rigid eight‑hour quota.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;​​&lt;em&gt;For this story, &lt;/em&gt;Fortune&lt;em&gt; used generative AI to help with an initial draft. An editor verified the accuracy of the information before publishing. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content-sentinel" data-index="1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fortune</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:46:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxOU1ZtOTYyRllFemFfcS1fRDg5TWJJUU11MFZPZFlvSUVkWGRXTWh2N3FoQ3N3cGRhSkpDTUNkRERDYmVKemxYQ05FWThjcjdyR2dGNjRDTWZXMWpzdGV2OWdtZFZnUFExaThYYTlhdjZJblp3eURJY25DTG9zaURCM2R2Q3NFYm4xYmtmRjBtNGVzaVd4WWc</guid></item><item><title>专家们担心新冠肺炎疫情后疾病反弹。这并没有发生。- UGA Today</title><link>https://news.uga.edu/flu-sti-cases-low-post-covid/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content wp-block-post-content has-global-padding is-layout-constrained wp-block-post-content-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the COVID-19 lockdown in 2020 stretched on, scientists watched for all sorts of unintended effects, from social to economic to environmental.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But the experts who predict disease transmission wondered specifically whether infectious diseases other than COVID-19 would surge after the prolonged isolation of the population. Would social distancing cause us to have less immunity to common diseases? Would those diseases rebound with deadly consequences?&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/science.adw4964"&gt;paper published in Science&lt;/a&gt;, the University of Georgia’s &lt;a href="https://ecology.uga.edu/directory/toby-brett/"&gt;Tobias Brett&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://ecology.uga.edu/directory/pejman-rohani/"&gt;Pejman Rohani&lt;/a&gt; explored which infectious diseases were impacted by COVID-19 control measures and, of those, which rebounded. They found airborne diseases were most likely to rebound — but not as much as some feared. Surprisingly, the incidence of sexually transmitted diseases remained low, even long after pandemic-era behaviors changed.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image alignleft size-medium"&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.uga.edu/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/brett_toby-1-e1537387754252.jpeg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://news.uga.edu/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/brett_toby-1-e1537387754252-300x300.jpeg" alt="Environmental portrait of a man in front of greenery outside" class="wp-image-83406" srcset="https://news.uga.edu/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/brett_toby-1-e1537387754252-300x300.jpeg 300w, https://news.uga.edu/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/brett_toby-1-e1537387754252-150x150.jpeg 150w, https://news.uga.edu/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/brett_toby-1-e1537387754252.jpeg 500w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Tobias Brett&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Early in the pandemic, there was some concern raised in the scientific community that lockdowns would disrupt the circulation of other diseases, such as influenza, and this would lead to what are called ‘gaps in immunity.’ So basically, because people aren’t getting infected, they aren’t developing immunity to the disease, and so then you’ve got this big buildup in the susceptible population,” said Brett, lead author of the study and a senior research associate in the &lt;a href="https://ecology.uga.edu/"&gt;Odum School of Ecology&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Analyzing nationwide disease data from 2019 to 2023, the researchers found an increase in cases of airborne diseases like influenza and pertussis after COVID. But fewer Americans got the flu during the pandemic and, while more people started to catch flu again when lockdowns lifted, it didn’t make up for the months when social distance kept flu from spreading.  In other words, Americans caught less flu during the pandemic and the years after than would have been expected without a COVID-19 pandemic and the behavior changes that went with it.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It means that the fears of a rebound were valid, but the rebound didn’t cancel out the deficit,” he said. “Obviously, there were negative consequences associated with the lockdowns, but in terms of other infectious diseases, the effect wasn’t negative and was, in fact, a net positive.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Airborne diseases increased slightly, STIs dropped post-pandemic&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Brett and Rohani looked at the number of reported cases of 26 different pathogens, clustering them into three groups related to how they are transmitted: airborne/aerosol transmitted diseases, sexually transmitted diseases and environmentally transmitted diseases, such as food poisoning or illnesses spread by ticks.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;They found that whether other diseases surged after the pandemic depended largely on how the disease is transmitted. Airborne diseases, such as flu, surged more, while STIs were less affected.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Chlamydia and gonorrhea were on the rise leading into the pandemic, for example. But transmission of those diseases dropped in every state during COVID and stayed lower than expected long after the pandemic ended.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image alignright size-medium"&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.uga.edu/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Pejman-Rohani-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://news.uga.edu/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Pejman-Rohani-2-300x202.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-101110" srcset="https://news.uga.edu/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Pejman-Rohani-2-300x202.jpg 300w, https://news.uga.edu/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Pejman-Rohani-2-1024x689.jpg 1024w, https://news.uga.edu/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Pejman-Rohani-2-768x517.jpg 768w, https://news.uga.edu/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Pejman-Rohani-2-1536x1034.jpg 1536w, https://news.uga.edu/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Pejman-Rohani-2-2048x1379.jpg 2048w, https://news.uga.edu/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Pejman-Rohani-2-549x370.jpg 549w, https://news.uga.edu/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Pejman-Rohani-2-1096x738.jpg 1096w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Pejman Rohani (Photo by Peter Frey/UGA)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Notifications of those sexually transmitted diseases flatlined, and we don’t know why,” Brett said. “Explanations could include improved treatment practices post-COVID or a greater investment in public health after the COVID pandemic. Another explanation could be changing behavior. It’s definitely a subject for further study.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“More broadly, this study highlights the important unanticipated effects of public health measures targeted at one infectious disease for other diseases,” said Rohani, Regents’ Professor and UGA Athletic Association Professor in Ecology and Infectious Diseases. “This points to a need to think holistically about the community of infectious diseases.”&lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>UGA Today</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:02:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiX0FVX3lxTE9Ja1BFNEVOSWJzZ3VPUGJiX3NkT0YxN2lwaHlWS3hYYzhBZ2NuajUtRW5NREdMNUlQZENwSEFhcldBeFdPMDlhbFlLOWpkTElyMlVlQjIyQ1VHeU9MTXZJ</guid></item><item><title>阿拉斯加在美国压力最大的州排行榜上名列前茅-研究结果</title><link>https://studyfinds.org/alaska-most-stressed-states/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;&lt;div class="post-featured-image"&gt;&lt;picture&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Alaska-on-map-1200x800.jpg.webp"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Alaska-on-map-1200x800.jpg" alt="Alaska on the map"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;p class="post-featured-image-caption"&gt;(Credit: hyotographics on Shutterstock)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-massachusetts-leads-the-way-when-it-comes-to-lowest-levels-of-stress-in-2025"&gt;Massachusetts leads the way when it comes to lowest levels of stress in 2025.&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-quaternary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-in-a-nutshell"&gt;In A Nutshell&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alaska ranks as America’s most stressed state&lt;/strong&gt;, driven by the nation’s highest suicide rate (28.15 per 100,000), sky-high living costs 25% above the national average, and harsh isolation that limits access to healthcare and legal resources.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Massachusetts residents experience the lowest stress levels&lt;/strong&gt; in the country with the best safety rating, lowest suicide rate (8.58 per 100,000), and strong access to mental health and legal services despite having the highest cost of living.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personal injury lawyers report that state stress levels directly correlate with accident and injury claims&lt;/strong&gt;, as residents in high-stress environments face greater risks from financial strain, poor housing, unsafe working conditions, and delayed medical care.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Alaska is the most stressed state in the nation, according to a new nationwide study that reveals how geography plays a massive role in American mental health. Researchers analyzed everything from crime rates to air quality across all 50 states and found that where Americans live might matter more than previously thought when it comes to daily pressure and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study, conducted by Florida personal injury law firm Anidjar &amp;amp; Levine, shows that Alaska earned the dubious distinction of America’s &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/land-of-the-worried-83-of-americans-very-stressed-over-nations-future/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;most stressed state&lt;/a&gt; with a score of 84.50, more than three times that of Massachusetts, which came in at 24.90. For context, Alaska’s &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/suicide/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;suicide rate&lt;/a&gt; of 28.15 per 100,000 residents is more than triple the national average. Add in a cost of living that runs 25% above the national average and a safety score of just 44.2, and the numbers paint a picture of a population under serious strain.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“High-stress environments show up in our caseload,” says Marc Anidjar, Founding Senior Partner at Anidjar &amp;amp; Levine. “People dealing with constant &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/debt-america-mental-health/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;financial strain&lt;/a&gt;, safety concerns, and poor living conditions face higher rates of accidents and &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/poor-sleep-fuel-mental-health/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;mental health crises&lt;/a&gt;. These pressures compound, affecting their overall wellbeing and often leading to legal situations.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Mental illness affects approximately 51.5 million American adults, or about one in five people. Many of these cases result in stress-related legal claims, and personal injury lawyers are seeing more clients whose health problems stem from chronic pressure and anxiety. But the new research shows that not all states face equal levels of stress.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/close-up-composition-conceptual-creativity-626165-1200x800.jpg" alt="Stress written on notepad in red pencil" class="wp-image-25089"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Alaska, New Mexico and Louisiana lead the way as most stressed states. (Credit: Pedro Figueras / pexels.com)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-makes-a-state-stressed"&gt;What Makes a State Stressed?&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers examined five key factors to determine stress levels: state safety based on crime statistics, suicide rates indicating mental health struggles, cost of living showing financial burden, environmental quality measured through air pollution and waste management, and the share of residents living in extreme poverty. Higher scores indicate greater &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/open-office-seating-linked-to-lower-stress-greater-activity-levels-among-workers/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;stress levels&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;After Alaska, New Mexico claimed second place with a stress score of 81.62, followed by Louisiana at 70.20. Nevada, Oregon, Arizona, Kentucky, Arkansas, Washington, and Hawaii rounded out the top 10 most stressed states.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;New Mexico faces serious safety and poverty concerns. With a safety score of just 39.7, residents experience higher crime rates and less security than most other states. New Mexico also has the second-highest suicide rate at 22.76 per 100,000, signaling deep mental health struggles. An alarming 8.20% of the state’s population lives in &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/poverty-kills-more-americans/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;extreme poverty&lt;/a&gt;, one of the highest rates in the nation. Poor environmental conditions, reflected in a cleanliness score of 35.37, add another layer of daily stress.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“We see how poverty and safety issues intersect in personal injury cases,” explains Anidjar. “When people can’t afford safe housing or reliable transportation, they’re at greater risk for accidents. When they get hurt, they often lack resources for proper medical treatment or legal help.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Most-Stressed-States-1200x480.png" alt="Most Stressed States" class="wp-image-145796" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Most-Stressed-States-1200x480.png 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Most-Stressed-States-475x190.png 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Most-Stressed-States-768x307.png 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Most-Stressed-States-400x160.png 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Top 10 Most Stressed States (Credit: Anidjar &amp;amp; Levine)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Louisiana rounds out the top three with the highest extreme poverty rate in the analysis at 9.00%, meaning nearly one in eleven residents struggles to meet basic needs. While the state’s cost of living index of 92.3 sits below the national average, widespread poverty means many residents still can’t make ends meet. Louisiana’s suicide rate of 15.56 reflects the mental health toll of these combined pressures.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Louisiana’s poverty crisis creates a cascade of legal issues,” Anidjar notes. “&lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/category/debt/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Financial desperation&lt;/a&gt; leads to unsafe working conditions, inadequate housing, and delayed medical care, increasing the likelihood of injuries and accidents. People in these situations often don’t know their rights or how to access legal protections.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-calm-corner-of-america"&gt;The Calm Corner of America&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;p&gt;On the opposite end of the spectrum, Massachusetts takes the top spot as the least stressed state with a score of just 24.90. Residents of the Bay State enjoy the highest safety rating at 60.2 and the lowest suicide rate at 8.58 per 100,000, less than a third of Alaska’s rate. These numbers reflect a population with better access to mental health resources and &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/americans-incarceration-rate/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;safer communities&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts posts a cleanliness score of 80.97. In this index, higher values represent greater environmental stress. However, residents pay for it. Massachusetts has the highest cost-of-living index in the top ten at 141.2, over 40% above the national average. Despite this, only 5.00% of the population lives in extreme poverty, suggesting most residents can afford the higher costs.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Better-resourced states like Massachusetts have stronger safety nets,” Anidjar explains. “People have better access to &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/healthcare/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;healthcare,&lt;/a&gt; mental health services, and legal aid. When accidents or injuries happen, residents can get help more easily, reducing long-term stress and preventing bigger legal problems.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;New Jersey claims the second-lowest stress score at 25.72 and the lowest suicide rate in the country at 7.19 per 100,000. With 4.70% living in extreme poverty and a cost of living index of 115.1, New Jersey residents generally have the financial means to handle life’s challenges.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“New Jersey’s proximity to major metropolitan areas means better access to specialized medical care and legal services,” says Anidjar. “When people can quickly get help after an injury or mental health crisis, it prevents situations from becoming more serious legal matters.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;New Hampshire rounds out the top three with a stress score of 26.14 and the lowest extreme poverty rate at just 3.90%. Fewer residents struggle with basic needs compared to other states. A safety score of 58.2 and cleanliness score of 73.43 show residents enjoy relatively safe, clean communities.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Least-Stressed-States-1200x473.png" alt="Least Stressed States" class="wp-image-145797" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Least-Stressed-States-1200x473.png 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Least-Stressed-States-475x187.png 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Least-Stressed-States-768x303.png 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Least-Stressed-States-400x158.png 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Top 10 Least Stressed States (Credit: Anidjar &amp;amp; Levine)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-alaska-factor"&gt;The Alaska Factor&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Alaska’s isolation creates unique legal challenges that compound stress levels. When someone experiences a stress-related injury or mental health crisis, access to proper medical care and legal resources becomes difficult. Harsh living conditions, &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/sunlight-winter-weight-gain-fat/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;limited sunlight&lt;/a&gt; during winter months, and financial strain make people more vulnerable to accidents and health emergencies.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Basic necessities cost far more in Alaska than in the lower 48 states. Every dollar counts when the cost of living runs 25% above the national average. While Alaska’s extreme poverty rate of 5.60% might seem moderate compared to states like Louisiana, the actual cost of surviving in the Last Frontier makes financial pressure more intense.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Living in a high-stress state affects not only your daily mood, but your physical health, &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/decision-making/"&gt;decision-making&lt;/a&gt;, and overall safety, too,” Anidjar commented. “We’ve seen firsthand how chronic stress contributes to accidents, workplace injuries, and mental health emergencies that require legal support.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;People facing constant &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/category/money/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;financial pressure&lt;/a&gt;, unsafe neighborhoods, or poor environmental conditions need to know that legal protections exist. Whether dealing with a workplace injury, &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/adhd-car-accidents/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;a car accident&lt;/a&gt; caused by poorly maintained roads, or health issues stemming from environmental hazards, Americans have rights that can provide relief.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Many states offer victim compensation programs, workers’ compensation benefits, and personal injury protections that can provide financial relief during difficult times. Free consultations with personal injury attorneys can clarify options without adding financial burden. Understanding legal rights is often the first step toward reducing stress and getting necessary support.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For residents of high-stress states like Alaska, New Mexico, and Louisiana, knowing these protections exist can make a real difference when facing accidents or injuries. Meanwhile, residents of lower-stress states like Massachusetts, New Jersey, and New Hampshire benefit from better infrastructure and resources that help prevent crises before they happen. But regardless of where Americans live, understanding available legal protections remains crucial for &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/stress/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;managing stress&lt;/a&gt; and recovering from unexpected setbacks.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-table"&gt;&lt;table class="has-fixed-layout"&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;State&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Safety Score 2025&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Suicide Rates 2023&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Cost of Living Index 2025&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Cleanliness Score&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Share of Population Living in Extreme Poverty 2024&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Stress Score&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Alaska&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;44.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;28.15&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;124.9&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;27.90&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.60%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;84.48&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;New Mexico&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;39.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;22.76&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;93.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;35.37&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;8.20%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;81.62&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Louisiana&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;40.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;15.56&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;92.3&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;36.70&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;9.00%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;70.22&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Nevada&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;44.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;20.31&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;100.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;37.40&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.80%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;70.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Oregon&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;47.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;19.41&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;111.8&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;42.13&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.90%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;69.4&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Arizona&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;51&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;19.22&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;110.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;49.63&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;6.10%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;64.9&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kentucky&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;47.5&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;17.47&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;92.5&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;42.13&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;7.60%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;64.08&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Arkansas&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;42.1&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;20.23&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;89.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;53.07&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;7.40%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;63.68&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Wash.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;49.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;15.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;114.1&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;36.07&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.20%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;62.86&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Hawaii&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;49.4&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;15.28&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;185&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;57.80&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;6.10%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;62.46&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Colorado&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;53.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;20.89&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;102.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;35.37&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.30%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;62.04&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;West Virginia&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;47&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;18.57&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;88.3&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;44.20&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;7.60%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;62.04&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Alabama&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;47&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;16.8&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;88.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;44.20&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;7.40%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;58.38&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Michigan&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;51.1&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;14.93&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;90.1&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;31.30&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;6.50%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;56.74&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Miss.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;43.5&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;15.53&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;87.3&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;53.07&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;8.50%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;56.32&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Montana&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;55.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;26.65&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;95.5&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;27.90&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;4.70%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;56.34&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Texas&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;47.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;14.25&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;92.1&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;28.53&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;6.00%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;55.92&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Okla.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;46.3&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;21.79&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;86&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;66.63&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;7.20%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;55.1&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Wyo.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;57.9&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;26.31&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;93.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;10.20&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.10%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;54.68&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;New York&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;57.9&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;8.3&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;125.1&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;38.10&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;7.00%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;53.88&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Tenn.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;47&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;17.34&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;90.3&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;59.17&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;6.40%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;52.68&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;South Carolina&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;45.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;14.69&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;94.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;71.43&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;6.60%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;51.84&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;North Dakota&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;54.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;17.75&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;91.4&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;28.57&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.70%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;51.42&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Calif.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;50.5&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;10.16&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;142.3&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;59.83&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;6.00%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;51.44&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;South Dakota&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;54.1&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;20.66&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;91.9&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;36.00&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.20%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;50.22&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Ohio&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;51.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;14.73&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;94.3&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;53.73&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;6.40%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;48.58&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Indiana&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;51.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;17&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;91&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;44.87&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.90%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;47.74&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Missouri&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;51.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;18&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;89&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;53.03&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.90%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;46.5&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Neb.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;52.9&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;14.47&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;92.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;31.97&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.40%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;45.72&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Maine&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;56.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;18.47&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;113&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;58.47&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.00%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;44.48&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Penn.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;57.9&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;14.32&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;97.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;36.03&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.60%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;43.68&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Idaho&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;60.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;23.28&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;99.9&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;44.20&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;4.60%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;43.66&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Georgia&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;51.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;14.77&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;92.5&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;62.57&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;6.20%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;42.86&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;North Carolina&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;52.3&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;14.25&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;97.8&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;63.23&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;6.30%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;42.44&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Florida&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;58.5&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;14.38&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;102.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;51.70&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;6.00%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;42.46&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kansas&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;52.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;19.56&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;88.8&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;44.17&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.10%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;42.46&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Rhode Island&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;52&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;9.41&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;110.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;75.50&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;6.40%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;42.46&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Vermont&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;52.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;17.85&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;113.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;65.97&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;4.00%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;41.62&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Utah&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;57.9&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;21.51&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;102.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;66.00&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;4.50%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;38.78&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Wisc.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;59.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;14.97&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;97.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;39.47&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.10%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;37.96&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Illinois&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;54.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;11.88&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;94.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;53.03&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.90%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;37.56&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Maryland&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;49.8&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;9.26&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;115.4&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;82.97&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;4.80%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;36.32&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Delaware&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;50&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;12.81&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;101.9&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;85.00&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.30%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;35.92&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Minn.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;58.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;13.83&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;95.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;29.90&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;4.60%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;34.70&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Conn.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;52.1&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;9.1&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;113.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;80.97&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.20%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;34.28&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Iowa&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;56.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;15.54&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;89.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;54.40&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.50%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;33.46&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Virginia&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;56.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;13.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;100.8&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;54.43&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5.10%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;32.24&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;New Hampsh.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;58.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;14.56&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;111.4&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;73.43&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;3.90%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;26.12&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;New Jersey&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;59.8&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;7.19&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;115.1&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;59.83&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;4.70%&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;25.72&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-methodology"&gt;Methodology&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers examined stress levels across all 50 US states by analyzing five key factors. Safety ratings from 2025 indicate overall state safety based on crime rates and law enforcement data, measured on an index of 0 to 100, where lower safety levels contribute to higher stress. Suicide rates from 2023 measure the number of suicides per 100,000 residents, with higher values suggesting increased mental and social stress.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The cost-of-living index from 2025 reflects average &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/how-rising-living-costs-changing-way-we-date-live-and-love/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;living costs&lt;/a&gt;, including housing, groceries, healthcare, and utilities, based on a national average of 100, where higher costs indicate higher stress. Cleanliness scores combine three environmental factors from 2023 to 2025: CO₂ emissions data from 2023 measuring total greenhouse gas emissions by state in metric tons of CO₂, air quality index from 2025 showing average annual AQI by state where higher numbers reflect poorer air quality, and landfill density from 2024 measuring the number of active landfills per 10,000 square miles. Each environmental sub-factor was normalized and averaged to create the cleanliness score, with higher scores indicating poorer environmental quality and greater stress contribution.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Share of population living in extreme poverty from 2024 represents the percentage of residents living below 50% of the poverty line, measured as a percentage where higher values indicate greater financial pressure. To calculate the final stress score, all factors were normalized on a scale of 0 to 1, then averaged and multiplied by 100. A higher score indicates higher overall state stress levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Study Finds</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:01:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiYEFVX3lxTE9vWEx5Vnl2STVwbkhEbmV3cmpNb1ExbTd1QlBYYTYyWXlMZlEtSWdEQ3FuelIxdTk5ZGZtbWktaUFud1d0YlBVMVRiQkdfZW5Xbl96VG1PeU9uOHNrQXd6YQ</guid></item><item><title>治愈瘫痪？科学家发现一种可以在脊髓中再生的旧药物-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/cure-for-paralysis-scientists-find-an-old-drug-that-could-regenerate-life-in-the-spinal-cord/articleshow/124962403.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, spinal cord injuries (SCI) have represented one of medicine’s most devastating and irreversible conditions, often leaving patients paralysed for life. Now, a breakthrough study by researchers at the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://today.ucsd.edu/story/bioinformatics-uncovers-regenerative-therapy-for-spinal-cord-injury" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;University of California San Diego (UCSD)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; is offering new hope. Using advanced bioinformatics tools, the team has identified an existing drug, Thiorphan, that shows remarkable potential to regenerate damaged nerve cells in the spinal cord, a discovery that could one day transform the treatment of paralysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Through a combination of computational biology and regenerative neuroscience, scientists have discovered that Thiorphan can stimulate nerve regrowth and restore motor function in animal models. Although still in pre-clinical stages, this finding marks a pivotal step toward therapies that may one day reverse paralysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The challenge of spinal cord regeneration&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The human spinal cord has limited ability to repair itself after injury. While nerves in the peripheral nervous system can regenerate to some extent, the central nervous system (CNS), which includes the brain and spinal cord, lacks the same capacity. This makes SCI recovery extremely difficult, often resulting in lifelong disability. Researchers have long sought ways to reawaken the body’s dormant repair mechanisms, but success has been limited until now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UCSD team turned to bioinformatics, using large molecular databases and computational algorithms to analyse how genes behave during nerve regeneration. They identified specific genetic patterns linked to neuron growth and cross-referenced these with known drugs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thiorphan, a compound previously tested in humans for non-neurological uses, emerged as a top candidate because it triggered a similar gene activation profile associated with nerve repair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Testing the drug on human neurons&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A major technical breakthrough came when scientists managed to grow adult human brain cells in the lab, a notoriously difficult task. When exposed to Thiorphan, these neurons displayed enhanced neurite outgrowth, the process by which nerve fibres extend and reconnect. This provided direct evidence that the drug could stimulate regenerative processes in human neural tissue, not just in animal cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;To validate their findings, researchers tested Thiorphan on rats with spinal cord injuries. The results were striking: the treated animals showed a 50% improvement in fine motor function, and when combined with neural stem cell transplants, recovery rates doubled. This synergy between drug therapy and cell transplantation suggests that a multi-pronged approach could be the key to effective spinal cord repair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thiorphan’s previous safety record in humans could accelerate its path to clinical testing for spinal injuries. This approach, repurposing old drugs using modern computational tools, represents a faster, more efficient model for drug discovery. Instead of starting from scratch, scientists can use gene expression data to identify new uses for existing compounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A turning point for spinal injury treatment&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lead researchers, including neuroscientist Erna van Niekerk, Ph.D., and Professor Mark H. Tuszynski, believe this marks a shift in how we approach neurological repair. By blending AI-driven bioinformatics, gene sequencing, and regenerative cell therapy, they have created a blueprint for future treatments. While human trials are still ahead, the results provide a glimpse into a future where paralysis may no longer be permanent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 17:57:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAJBVV95cUxNQXRwOVhDN0VXN1dLbXBmV0ROSVJQaGl0aEptVTRMMmhjMzJhRUZYLS1xMjRReGE1WWRPX3VOWGprTEl5bDAwQmZ1c2JuZm45QjFMYWxjU0JwVGZhczJCLWt5TXhXR0l1c3l2UmJ1b29VWUU1eVRQcXVQMHdmRkpaQnlZcy1HdVppeGNDRTY1aXIyWGZTQlhaVWFibWw5WXU2WlI1cDlrd3Y3d1dKWWZYZzNFeUpnTTZfNjRpUTBMaFRFMDEzc195U3dYdFMwaGF4eFprZF9iaXZIUmpndW1oQ3QySTFrcEwwMmRzVlNnYk1OSkZ1RW1JdUFfLXBsWlFiS2VuS05LZG5oM21yR0VQM1lWNHZyeVBac1VvdQ</guid></item><item><title>美国肥胖率下降- Slashdot</title><link>https://news.slashdot.org/story/25/10/30/1641222/obesity-rate-declining-in-us</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="firehose-179916176" data-fhid="179916176" data-fhtype="story" class="fhitem fhitem-story article usermode thumbs grid_24"&gt;
		&lt;span class="sd-info-block"&gt;
			&lt;span class="sd-key-firehose-id"&gt;179916176&lt;/span&gt;
			&lt;span class="type"&gt;story&lt;/span&gt;
			
		&lt;/span&gt;







	
	



&lt;div class="body" id="fhbody-179916176"&gt;
	
		
	

	
		
		&lt;div id="text-179916176" class="p"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
			
		 	
				Gallup:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;i&gt; After peaking at a record high of 39.9% in 2022, the U.S. adult obesity rate has &lt;a href="https://news.gallup.com/poll/696599/obesity-rate-declining.aspx"&gt;gradually declined to 37.0% in 2025&lt;/a&gt;. This is a statistically meaningful decrease representing an estimated 7.6 million fewer obese adults compared with three years ago. Meanwhile, diagnoses of diabetes -- a lifetime disease that can be managed but not cured -- have now reached an all-time high of 13.8%. Both metrics are part of the ongoing Gallup National Health and Well-Being Index.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;

[...] Over the past year, more Americans have turned to Type 2 antidiabetic GLP-1 drugs such as semaglutide (brand names Ozempic and Wegovy) for weight loss purposes. The percentage of adults who report taking this class of medicine specifically for weight loss has increased to 12.4%, compared with 5.8% in February 2024 when Gallup first measured it. Usage among women (15.2%) continues to outpace men (9.7%), but both groups have more than doubled their use in the past year. These results dovetail with increased awareness of the drugs used for weight loss, which has risen from 80% to 89% nationally in the same period.&lt;/i&gt;
		 	
		&lt;/div&gt;

		

		

		
			
		
	&lt;/div&gt;
	
	



	&lt;/article&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slashdot</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 17:03:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQUVBnSkZQbDBNT0tuc1pCVHJoQXVUNEVTR2NOd2RjTW9RTnprYkVFZEVTak5UWVVMOVBUVzVGTkMtaDUxVjd1T1pudWFLVVFpZnNjc2ZyUUhJNmFsb3VqZ3VCM2daMkJkdFA0ZFE0QU56ZUhRMFlzMjgtV0JtOFF4aEpkOA</guid></item><item><title>生活会让人感到害怕。恐惧专家建议你做些什么来面对它。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/10/30/how-to-face-your-fears/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-gKAtpF overrideStyles"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-heFNVF font-copy"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="wpds-c-qdfkX wpds-c-hfqIQj font-copy" data-state="closed"&gt;Arash Javanbakht&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; was on the back of a mule at the South Rim of the Grand Canyon when he remembered he is terrified of heights.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="D3F5JB7WLRCVLC334VSYGBA2ZA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“I could see my death at the bottom,” said Javanbakht, a psychiatrist and the director of the Stress, Trauma and Anxiety Research Clinic at Wayne State University. “I tried to distract myself.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE1KYmFLN1dJWl9xUWJpSnFqS2NDY01rc0VxeV9jckliQ2g1ZXFVLXJEa3ZtcVBPUUNvQy1zd3ZfUU5Na1g4a0VJQ244QWlPOTF6ZUpJRDZQRzV5V2w0TFdUYlE4T2RJQWd6Z3prRHhJM0xQMVZtTFNGX1YzTTBONUk</guid></item><item><title>揭穿8项关于乳腺癌筛查的主张：每个女性需要了解的检测信息- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/debunking-8-claims-breast-cancer-screening-woman-detection/story?id=127019458</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;When it comes to early detection, mammograms remain the only screening test proven to reduce deaths from breast cancer in average-risk women, according to the&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/breast-cancer/screening/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt; Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;However, only about 75% of eligible U.S. women schedule regular screenings, according to a &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2840297?utm_source=openevidence&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;JAMA&lt;/a&gt; study published earlier this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Experts believe that misunderstandings about who needs screenings and how often may be part of the reason some women skip mammograms. Here are eight evidence-based facts about breast cancer screening to help set the record straight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;CLAIM: Only women with a family history need screening&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Although some women with family history of breast cancer may need earlier or more frequent screenings, all women need regular screenings, doctors said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Only about five to 10% of breast cancers are hereditary," Dr. Aparajita Spencer, a breast surgical oncologist at CHI Memorial in Chattanooga, Tennessee, told ABC News. "Most women with breast cancer do not have a family history."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;CLAIM: A lump is the earliest sign of breast cancer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Although a lump is one of the most common symptoms of breast cancer, it is not the only sign and can be missed when performing self-examination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"The whole point of the mammogram is to pick up the earliest signs of a breast cancer, which are usually calcifications, not really a mass," Dr. Preeti Subhedar, breast surgery chief at Hackensack Meridian Health in New Jersey, told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"When people come in with a mammographically or image-detected breast cancer, usually it's fairly small and outcomes are really good," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;CLAIM: Breast size affects your cancer risk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Subhedar said that breast size has nothing to do with risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"An average-risk woman has a 12% lifetime risk of developing breast cancer," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;For high-risk women, this increases to over 20%, according to the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.breastcancer.org/risk/breast-cancer-risk-calculators" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Spencer added that breast size and breast density are often confused, but they're not the same. A mammogram will read dense breasts as having a higher proportion of glandular and fibrous tissue compared to fatty tissue. Mammary glands typically produce milk while fibrous tissue forms the breast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;This can slightly raise cancer risk and make tumors harder to catch, which is why the U.S. Food and Drug Administration &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.fda.gov/radiation-emitting-products/mammography-quality-standards-act-mqsa-and-mqsa-program/important-information-final-rule-amend-mammography-quality-standards-act-mqsa" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;finalized a rule in 2024&lt;/a&gt; requiring providers to inform women if their breast tissue is dense and may require additional follow-up screenings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;CLAIM: Younger women don't need mammograms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The National Comprehensive Cancer Network recommends annual screening mammograms starting at age 40 for average-risk women. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;For women with a strong family history of breast cancer or a known genetic mutation, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/breast-cancer/screening-tests-and-early-detection/american-cancer-society-recommendations-for-the-early-detection-of-breast-cancer.html?utm_source=chatgpt.com" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;the American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt; recommends beginning annual screenings with both a mammogram and a breast MRI at age 30, or even earlier if a close relative was diagnosed at a young age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;CLAIM: A negative mammogram means you don't have breast cancer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Experts said a mammogram does not mean a patient doesn't have breast cancer but rather that breast cancer wasn't found on that specific mammogram. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Mammograms occasionally miss early-stage cancers," noted Spencer. "There is always a chance that you have something that pops up between screenings. We can't say 100%, which is why it's really important to get those yearly screenings." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;CLAIM: Mammograms can cause cancer because of radiation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The benefit of early detection far outweighs the tiny risk from the small amount of radiation, experts said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The total lifetime risk for radiation-induced breast cancer is still very low at one in 5,000 -- compared to about &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/breast-cancer/about/how-common-is-breast-cancer.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;one in every eight&lt;/a&gt; women who will develop breast cancer in their lifetime, and roughly one in 43 women who will die from it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;CLAIM: There are safe and effective alternatives to mammograms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"There's no universal replacement for screening mammograms. That is why that is the gold standard," Spencer said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Mammograms are safe -- even during pregnancy when needed, she added. Other diagnostic tools including, an MRI and an ultrasound, may be used to provide additional information, but they do not replace the mammogram. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;CLAIM: A breast biopsy spreads breast cancer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Medical experts agree that breast biopsies are safe, and the benefit of getting an accurate diagnosis far outweighs the minimal risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"It is extremely, extremely important that we get a tissue biopsy when someone comes in with an abnormal mammogram because there's a lot of biological information that we learn about a tumor from that biopsy," Spencer said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Breast cancer is the most common cancer in women after skin cancer and the second leading cause of cancer death, according to the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/breast-cancer/about/how-common-is-breast-cancer.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In 2024, more than 300,000 women were diagnosed with breast cancer, and about 40,000 died from the disease. Today, more than 3 million breast cancer survivors live in the U.S. --  a powerful reminder of the importance of early detection, doctors said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;Allyson Heng, MD, is resident physician in neurology at the University of Alabama at Birmingham and a member of the ABC News Medical Unit.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:46:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxPbVE4OC1FV09Kam8xR2dndGQtZ0lUUWNDVktDMEkycHdjU0U1emJxQkZZLW1oWk1CUTA5d1VwNVRyQWx3STg4Uy1NdFBZWnNiVWRzUVJiaXhNY3ZtcUFsQTlqZEItbWJSNjNRZ0xIUEFQX2l3R05KVllxdlN6Wm12dm1BeUhvbWdlalJnUzBsSzN4d3dlZzRKOTRaaHdyaHJSYnFDMGxmWjU3NXfSAbABQVVfeXFMUGZFcUZYcUtoYlc5bldFUFlnZ1RKaDZza3AycC1tcGhPVFo0ZkZfcmcweEtzVW1LTWlnRWRqRThMbGxQV2V4OEJiSDdEV3M5bTZnbFdWQ2F1bXVVYVF2eGswMnJFMFdqTldwZkl3VlI3NURSak9tQWlpYTVqanptSXFuSkpzV3pMeWdWb25RZWl5cG9kRXNuMjNuRDlXQzRVVTFIeGctb0RHcW92b2RKQXQ</guid></item><item><title>我们可能永远无法控制禽流感或鸡蛋价格— vox.com</title><link>https://www.vox.com/future-perfect/466446/bird-flu-vaccine-eggs-chicken</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="zephr-anchor" class="_1agbrix10"&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;It might now be a distant memory, but by the end of last winter, the average &lt;a href="https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/APU0000708111"&gt;cost of a dozen eggs&lt;/a&gt; soared to a record high of $6.23. (It’s now at $3.49.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The cause was H5N1, a highly pathogenic strain of avian influenza — or &lt;a href="/bird-flu"&gt;bird flu&lt;/a&gt; — that wild birds shed near farms as they migrate for the winter. It’s now surging again in US poultry operations and could result in another winter of high egg prices — and tens of millions of dead birds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Over the last two months, the virus was detected on nearly 50 commercial poultry farms, leading to the &lt;a href="/future-perfect/23963820/bird-flu-surge-us-ventilation-shutdown-veterinarians"&gt;mass culling&lt;/a&gt; of 7.3 million farmed birds — more than during the same period in previous years. Three-quarters of those birds were egg-laying hens from just three egg factory farms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Although that culling involves an enormous amount of animal suffering, the deaths represent less than 2 percent of US egg-laying hens, which, for now, isn’t enough to meaningfully affect egg prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;But given the early wave of mortality across a range of species compared to the last couple years, the sheer number of farms that have reported outbreaks, and the fact that a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/02/08/health/bird-flu-variant-nevada-human-case"&gt;newer bird flu variant&lt;/a&gt; has become dominant, it “doesn’t bode well for a quiet year” for the virus, &lt;a href="https://www.vet.cornell.edu/about-us/people/krysten-schuler"&gt;Krysten Schuler&lt;/a&gt; — an associate research professor of public and ecosystem health at Cornell University — told me in an email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;For nearly four years, bird flu has wreaked havoc on the US poultry industry and the birds themselves. &lt;a href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/sites/default/files/hpai-depopulation-disposal.pdf"&gt;Federal policy&lt;/a&gt; requires that as soon as the virus is detected on a farm, the entire flock must be killed to slow the spread of the disease. So far, poultry farms have killed more than &lt;a href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/livestock-poultry-disease/avian/avian-influenza/hpai-detections/commercial-backyard-flocks"&gt;180 million birds&lt;/a&gt; since the start of the outbreak in early 2022. And the prevailing method of killing is grim: Producers close barn vents and pump in heat to raise the temperature, which slowly — and &lt;a href="https://theintercept.com/2022/04/14/killing-chickens-bird-flu-vsd/"&gt;painfully&lt;/a&gt; — kills the birds via &lt;a href="/future-perfect/23963820/bird-flu-surge-us-ventilation-shutdown-veterinarians"&gt;heat stroke&lt;/a&gt; over several hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The virus has also spilled over to infect &lt;a href="https://www.fao.org/animal-health/situation-updates/global-aiv-with-zoonotic-potential/bird-species-affected-by-h5nx-hpai/en?fbclid=IwY2xjawJBNJVleHRuA2FlbQIxMQABHXjrgdsxDiVY31-svDHVEVzSHa3Sq5_ZzJwMkDOcrTzDxK2n5UNopOtyXQ_aem_zvon3ViBbCJLSSONfXFswQ"&gt;hundreds of other bird species and mammals&lt;/a&gt;, including &lt;a href="/future-perfect/24128700/bird-fludairy-meat-industry-h5n1-cows-milk-eggs-safety"&gt;dairy cows&lt;/a&gt;, foxes, bears, seals, and &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/bird-flu/risk-factors/bird-flu-in-pets.html"&gt;pet cats&lt;/a&gt;. Seventy human cases have been reported in the US, including &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/media/releases/2025/m0106-h5-birdflu-death.html"&gt;one death&lt;/a&gt;. Scientists are increasingly worried that the virus could &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-00245-6"&gt;evolve into the next human pandemic&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;And it’s been a costly disease. The government has spent billions to manage it, including compensating egg and dairy producers for their losses, while consumers have spent an additional &lt;a href="https://innovateanimalag.org/hpai-costs-2025"&gt;$14.5 billion on eggs&lt;/a&gt; in 2024 and 2025 alone, according to one estimate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--block-placement _80slsf2 _80slsf0 duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--highlight _1agbrixl _1lbxzst0"&gt;&lt;p class="_1lbxzst1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="_1lbxzst4"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1 _1lbxzst7"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have questions or comments on this newsletter?&lt;/strong&gt; Email us at futureperfect@vox.com!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Through it all, the egg, chicken, and turkey industries have relied on improving biosecurity on farms — like sealing barn openings and disinfecting vehicles and equipment — in an effort to keep the virus out and killing infected flocks when that doesn’t work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Several effective bird flu vaccines for use in poultry birds have been licensed in the US, which you’d think would be a no-brainer solution to the outbreak. But they’ve yet to be deployed, because they’d disrupt international trade for the chicken meat industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;But now, the egg and turkey sectors — which are disproportionately affected by bird flu — are attempting to change that and are &lt;a href="https://www.agriculture.com/usda-develops-potential-plan-to-vaccinate-poultry-for-bird-flu-11758561?"&gt;pushing for the US Department of Agriculture&lt;/a&gt; to advance a vaccination program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Earlier this year, the trade group United Egg Producers wrote in a &lt;a href="https://hickmanseggs.com/avian-PDF/UEP-Board-Approved-HPAI-Vaccination-and-Surveillance-Plan.pdf"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; sent to the USDA that the approach of killing birds and beefing up biosecurity is “no longer adequate to prevent and control this devastating disease” and that “it is time for a new approach.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p id="the-egg-industrys-bird-flu-vaccine-plan-and-why-it-hasnt-moved-forward" class="_7ka5u1 _7ka5u0 duet--article--standard-heading xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;h2 class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The egg industry’s bird flu vaccine plan — and why it hasn’t moved forward&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;To mitigate the impact of the virus, the egg and turkey industries wouldn’t need to vaccinate all of their 300 million hens or 200 million turkeys. Instead, they would focus on farms located in the &lt;a href="https://www.foodbusinessnews.net/articles/29233-egg-industry-seeks-action-as-hpai-devastates-flocks"&gt;four major flyways&lt;/a&gt; where wild birds migrate and shed the virus, which is where farms have been hardest hit by bird flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;While many egg and turkey producers are eager to start vaccination programs, the US doesn’t let them over concerns that it would impact the chicken meat industry’s bottom line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Last year, chicken meat companies exported &lt;a href="https://www.ers.usda.gov/topics/animal-products/poultry-eggs/sector-at-a-glance"&gt;14 percent&lt;/a&gt; of their product, which is valued at &lt;a href="https://www.feedstuffs.com/livestock-and-poultry-market-news/poultry-and-egg-export-volumes-lower-to-close-out-2024"&gt;$4.7 billion&lt;/a&gt;. But most of the countries that import American chicken meat would &lt;a href="https://www.nationalchickencouncil.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/Letter-to-USDA-Re-HPAI-Vaccine.pdf"&gt;pause those imports&lt;/a&gt; if &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; farmed birds in the US are vaccinated, even if no chickens raised for meat are vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The reason behind these blanket bans stems from importing countries’ concerns around the so-called “DIVA” problem, which is short for “differentiating infected from vaccinated animals.” It represents the challenge of identifying whether a poultry bird is infected with bird flu or simply has avian influenza antibodies from vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;That’s led the chicken meat industry, for now, to firmly oppose vaccination of any poultry birds in the US. “Until we have written assurances and trade protections in place with our trading partners, we will continue to oppose vaccination for Highly Pathogenic Avian Influenza (HPAI),” a spokesperson with the National Chicken Council wrote in an email to Vox. (Losing $4.7 billion in export value would also lead to an oversupply of chicken in the US, which would hurt the industry’s profits.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--block-placement _80slsf3 _80slsf0 duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;div id=":R9abcrib96:" class="duet--article--image-gallery-two-up _1agbrixj"&gt;&lt;div class="_1j8uwx5"&gt;&lt;div class="_1j8uwx8 _1j8uwx7"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="duet--media--caption xptnl10"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup xkp0cg2 xptnl12"&gt;In 2022, over 5 million egg-laying hens were culled after bird flu was detected at a farm in Iowa owned by the egg giant Rembrandt. Here, the dead birds are being sent through a chute into a large truck for disposal.&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;cite class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup xkp0cg2 xptnl11"&gt;Direct Action Everywhere/Open Wing Alliance/We Animals&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="_1j8uwxa _1j8uwx9"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="duet--media--caption xptnl10"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup xkp0cg2 xptnl12"&gt;Bodies of cranes that presumably died of bird flu are seen in the bucket of a wheel loader transporting them over a field near Linum, eastern Germany, on October 24, 2025.&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;cite class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup xkp0cg2 xptnl11"&gt;Ralf Hirschberger/AFP via Getty Images&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;But &lt;a href="/future-perfect/2022/11/22/23472207/bird-flu-vaccine-turkey-prices-chickens-hens-cull-depopulation"&gt;experts&lt;/a&gt; say this concern from trading partners can be overcome through increased disease surveillance combined with testing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Despite the persistent, ongoing spread of bird flu in the US, other countries are able to continue safely importing US poultry products by temporarily suspending imports from certain regions — usually a state or county — actively experiencing an outbreak. The USDA surveils the affected area for bird flu and tests birds until the virus is no longer detected and trade resumes once the US has proven that exports are safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;“It would be the same approach here with the vaccination strategy,” John Clifford, a former USDA chief veterinary officer and current adviser to the USA Poultry and Egg Export Council, told me. The US would show trading partners “how the US would still protect them, and we would not be shipping them any products that would be unsafe.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;There’s precedent for this approach. Since late 2023, France has been vaccinating ducks against the bird flu, which has proven to be &lt;a href="https://www.wattagnet.com/poultry-meat/diseases-health/avian-influenza/news/15768593/france-resumes-hpai-vaccination-program"&gt;highly effective&lt;/a&gt;. But in response, the US and Canada banned poultry imports from France, which the countries lifted early this year after French authorities “succeeded in convincing the American and Canadian authorities of the safety” of vaccination, according to &lt;a href="https://www.euromeatnews.com/Article-United-States-and-Canada-lift-of-embargo-on-poultry-imports-from-France/8118"&gt;Euro Meat News&lt;/a&gt;. The vaccination program has cost French duck producers a little under &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/france-kicks-off-bird-flu-vaccination-despite-trade-backlash-risk-2023-10-02/"&gt;$2 per bird&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;In June, the USDA &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/usda-develops-potential-plan-vaccinate-poultry-bird-flu-2025-06-20/"&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; it was developing a vaccination plan to show to countries that import US chicken meat as a way to gauge whether vaccination would disrupt trade. The update represented forward momentum, but some scientific experts, and some in the egg industry, are becoming increasingly impatient with the USDA’s reluctance to allow egg producers to vaccinate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The agency is, according to them, putting the chicken meat industry’s financial well-being above the massive impacts the bird flu has had on egg, turkey, and dairy producers. I would add that it’s also putting it above American consumers, animal welfare, and broader public health concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The USDA didn’t respond to a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p id="actually-measuring-the-cost-of-bird-flu" class="_7ka5u1 _7ka5u0 duet--article--standard-heading xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;h2 class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Actually measuring the cost of bird flu&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Glenn Hickman, a large egg producer in Arizona who had to cull millions of hens earlier this year, has been direct about how he feels about the status quo. “The reason we’re not vaccinating chickens in this country today is because of trade implications…but I’m past caring,” Hickman &lt;a href="https://www.feedstuffs.com/agribusiness-news/hickman-details-slow-motion-wreck-from-bird-flu"&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; the agricultural publication Feedstuffs in July. “I’d like to vaccinate my chickens and protect my flock, and I cannot because of the obstacles that the poultry meat industry is putting in front of this.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The argument that we shouldn’t vaccinate egg-laying hens and turkeys in order to protect $5 billion or so in chicken meat exports doesn’t sit well with &lt;a href="https://vetmed.umn.edu/bio/college-of-veterinary-medicine/carol-cardona"&gt;Carol Cardona&lt;/a&gt;, a professor at the University of Minnesota’s College of Veterinary Medicine. Cardona told me that when people say the cost of vaccination is too high, she says “the cost of outbreaks is too high.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;“We’re not necessarily measuring” the cost of &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; vaccinating, Cardona said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Those costs, she said, include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--block-placement _80slsf1 _80slsf0 duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;ul class="duet--article--unordered-list _1agbrixi _739u100 xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;li class="_739u101"&gt;&lt;span class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup"&gt;The virus evolving to infect &lt;a href="https://www.fao.org/animal-health/situation-updates/global-aiv-with-zoonotic-potential/bird-species-affected-by-h5nx-hpai/en?fbclid=IwY2xjawJBNJVleHRuA2FlbQIxMQABHXjrgdsxDiVY31-svDHVEVzSHa3Sq5_ZzJwMkDOcrTzDxK2n5UNopOtyXQ_aem_zvon3ViBbCJLSSONfXFswQ"&gt;hundreds of new bird and mammal species&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="_739u101"&gt;&lt;span class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup"&gt;The environmental impact of raising so many poultry birds who are never consumed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="_739u101"&gt;&lt;span class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup"&gt;The burden on human health and the cost of preventing human infections.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="_739u101"&gt;&lt;span class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup"&gt;The mental health impact on farmers, veterinarians, and &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2022/apr/28/egg-factory-avian-flu-chickens-culled-workers-fired-iowa"&gt;farm workers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="_739u101"&gt;&lt;span class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup"&gt;Infections reported at more than 1,000 US dairy farms, resulting in illness for an unknown number of cows and &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-025-61553-z"&gt;economic losses for dairy producers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;There are also, of course, the 182 million birds killed — mostly via painful heat stroke — in the US alone, along with the billions in taxpayer dollars spent to &lt;a href="https://www.usda.gov/about-usda/news/press-releases/2024/05/30/usda-announces-824-million-new-funding-protect-livestock-health-launches-voluntary-h5n1-dairy-herd"&gt;suppress the virus and compensate&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.farmforward.com/publications/subsidizing-the-spread-bird-flu-bailouts-expand-from-poultry-to-dairy/"&gt;egg and dairy producers&lt;/a&gt; for their losses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;As far as I’m aware, no economist has put a comprehensive dollar amount on the bird flu’s annual toll, but it’s likely much higher than the economic damage it would do to the chicken meat industry. Until policymakers take a more holistic outlook on the industry’s bird flu crisis, those most vulnerable to it — animals, farm workers, and consumers — will continue to bear the heavy burden of this deadly virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>vox.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:35:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE9oMGotM3BRMTVSSU5QeDRFRUJ5dGg3MGJHVlRpeXc4ZWE4LVpfNHc3RUtmaEpjdHdIaUhTQ3R6ZGVWNS1fRjQ4bjdHNUNRT0tEVnBIODMwcDY4NmRZYkl1RlZ5Q1hiYXJ5Zmo5U2s1Tllad2FhUVFvZlc1bw</guid></item><item><title>是否需要接种疫苗来实现高接种率？ -半岛电视台</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2025/10/30/are-vaccine-mandates-needed-to-achieve-high-vaccination-rates</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wysiwyg wysiwyg--all-content" aria-live="polite" aria-atomic="true"&gt;&lt;p&gt;US states have relied on vaccine mandates since the 1800s, when a smallpox vaccine offered the first successful protection against a disease that had killed millions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than a century later, Florida’s top public health official said &lt;a href="/news/2025/9/3/florida-top-doctor-pushes-end-to-vaccine-mandates-likens-them-to-slavery"&gt;vaccine requirements&lt;/a&gt; are unethical and unnecessary for high vaccination rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;section class="more-on"&gt;&lt;h2 class="more-on__heading"&gt;Recommended Stories &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;list of 4 items&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;end of list&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You can still have high vaccination numbers, just like the other countries who don’t do any mandates like Sweden, Norway, Denmark, the [United Kingdom], most of Canada,” Florida Surgeon General Dr Joseph Ladapo said on October 16. “No mandates, really comparable vaccine uptake.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s true that some countries without vaccine requirements have high vaccination rates, on a par with the United States. But experts say that fact alone does not make it a given that the US would follow the same pattern if it eliminates school vaccination requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Florida state law currently requires students in public and private schools from daycare through 12th grade to have specific immunisations. Families can opt out for religious or medical reasons. About 11 percent of Florida kindergarteners are not immunised, recent data shows. With Florida Governor Ron DeSantis’s backing, Ladapo is pushing to end the state’s school vaccine requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The countries Ladapo cited – Sweden, Norway, Denmark, the UK and parts of Canada – don’t have broad vaccine requirements, research shows. Their governments recommend such protections, though, and their healthcare systems offer conveniently accessible vaccines, for example.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;UNICEF, a United Nations agency which calls itself the “global go-to for data on children”, measures how well countries provide routine childhood immunisations by looking at infant access to the third dose in a DTaP vaccine series that protects against diphtheria, tetanus and pertussis (whooping cough).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2024, UNICEF and the World Health Organization (WHO) reported that 94 percent of one-year-olds in the United States had received three doses of the DTaP vaccine. That’s compared with Canada at 92 percent, Denmark at 96 percent, Norway at 97 percent, Sweden at 96 percent and the UK at 92 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Universal, government-provided healthcare and high trust in government likely influence those countries’ vaccine uptake, experts have said. In the US, many people can’t afford time off work or the cost of a doctor’s visit. There’s also less trust in the government. These factors could prevent the US from having similar participation rates should the government eliminate school vaccine mandates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="universal-healthcare-stronger-government-trust-increase-vaccination"&gt;Universal healthcare, stronger government trust increase vaccination&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple studies have linked vaccine mandates and increased vaccination rates. Although these studies found associations between the two, the research does not prove that mandates alone cause increased vaccination rates. Association is not the same as causation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-newsletter-slot" data-testid="article-newsletter-slot"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other factors that can affect vaccination rates often accompany mandates, including local efforts to improve vaccination access, increase documentation and combat vaccine hesitancy and refusal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The countries Ladapo highlighted are high-income countries with policies that encourage vaccination and make vaccines accessible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Sweden, for example, where all vaccinations are voluntary, the vaccines included in national programmes are offered for free, according to the Public Health Agency of Sweden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preventive care is more accessible and routine for everyone in countries such as Canada, Denmark, Norway, Sweden and the UK with universal healthcare systems, said Dr Megan Berman of the University of Texas Medical Branch’s Sealy Institute for Vaccine Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the US, our healthcare system is more fragmented, and access to care can depend on insurance or cost,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More limited healthcare access, decreased institutional trust and anti-vaccine activists’ influence set the US apart from those other countries, experts said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of these other countries’ cultural norms favour the collective welfare of others, which means people are more likely to get vaccinated to support the community, Berman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anders Hviid, an epidemiologist at Statens Serum Institut in Copenhagen, told The Atlantic that it’s misguided to compare Denmark’s health situation with the US – in part because Danish citizens strongly trust the government to enact policies in the public interest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By contrast, as of 2024, fewer than one in three people in the US over age 15 reported having confidence in the national government, according to data from the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development, a group of advanced, industrialised nations. That’s the lowest percentage of any of the countries Ladapo mentioned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The effectiveness of recommendations depends on faith in the government and scientific body that is making the recommendations,” said Dr Richard Rupp, of the University of Texas Medical Branch’s Sealy Institute for Vaccine Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="without-mandates-vaccine-education-would-be-even-more-important-experts-say"&gt;Without mandates, vaccine education would be even more important, experts say&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts said they believe US vaccination rates would fall if states ended school vaccine mandates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maintaining high vaccination rates without mandates would require health officials to focus on other policies, interventions and messaging, said Samantha Vanderslott, the leader of the Oxford Vaccine Group’s Vaccines and Society Unit, which researches attitudes and behaviour towards vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That could be especially difficult given that the United States’s top health official, Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F Kennedy Jr, has a long history of anti-vaccine activism and scepticism about vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That makes the US an outlier, Vanderslott said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Governments tend to promote/support vaccination as a public health good,” she said. It is unusual for someone with Kennedy’s background to hold a position where he has the power to spread misinformation, encourage vaccine hesitancy and reduce mainstream vaccine research funding and access, Vanderslott said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people decide to follow recommendations based on their beliefs about a vaccine’s benefits and their child’s vulnerability to disease, Rupp said. That means countries that educate the public about vaccines and illnesses will have better success with recommendations, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, experts said that just because something worked elsewhere doesn’t mean it will work in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matt Hitchings, a biostatistics professor at the University of Florida’s College of Public Health and Health Professions, said a vaccine policy’s viability could differ from country to country. Vaccination rates are influenced by a host of factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If I said that people in the UK drink more tea than in the US and have lower rates of certain cancers, would that be convincing evidence that drinking tea reduces cancer risk?” Hitchings said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Google Translate was used throughout the research of this story to translate websites and statements into English.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Al Jazeera</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:57:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxNRzZiRVFEZWpxLWYxSlVaaGU0VmhCR0RPSk1hWmtfNk8xbndaSFMyeHdIRW9hSUFvWVliVGdzMTlGOTlmVUFqT2FOUFlTdFZhOGlmdzJDU3RaaEt0SElKVUdyODdnekU1OW54UDkyLUZuSmltS003eUc2b2pWYXR5SjZZbWNzTERycTVDNmtlZVdFajZ3SDhHYWRGU3pwNUhRZkdkVGRR0gGrAUFVX3lxTE9wdy1KQ092ZWN6XzZNSVN4MVZ3NDFVOXEwaWE3ZzJ6QVh6akJUc1prc0w0aE1ZM0JtOGhkS2VMcGlCTFJNZlJjSEtyRUZxY19ud3lmRFBLYjdPNkg0elo1LUhmM1NXclgxbUllc0pvZVFtWEY5NXFhMWZ4cEFVV191R29UcmlzS01RaV9lNHdDUUVwMTlWeEJzTHhKbU5RLTV0Y2hUVlVYOUNDdw</guid></item></channel></rss>