<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>埃塞俄比亚确认爆发致命的马尔堡病毒--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/nov/15/ethiopia-confirms-outbreak-of-deadly-marburg-virus</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Ethiopia has confirmed an outbreak of the deadly Marburg virus in the south of the country, the Africa Centres for Disease Control and Prevention (Africa CDC) has said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Marburg virus is one of the deadliest known pathogens. Like Ebola, it causes severe bleeding, fever, vomiting and diarrhoea and has a 21-day incubation period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Also like Ebola, it is transmitted via contact with body fluids and has a fatality rate of between 25% and 80%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The head of the World Health Organization, Ethiopia’s Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus, confirmed on Friday that at least nine cases had been detected in southern Ethiopia, two days after &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/africa" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Africa&lt;/a&gt; CDC was alerted to a suspected haemorrhagic virus in the region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Marburg virus disease (MVD) has been confirmed by the National Reference Laboratory (in Ethiopia),” Africa CDC said on Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Further epidemiological investigations and laboratory analyses are under way and the virus strain detected shows similarities to those previously identified in east Africa.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It said Ethiopian health authorities had acted swiftly to confirm and contain the outbreak in the Jinka area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It said it would work with Ethiopia to ensure an effective response and to reduce the risk of the virus spreading to other parts of east Africa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;An epidemic of Marburg virus killed 10 people in &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/tanzania" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Tanzania&lt;/a&gt; in January before being terminated in March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Rwanda said in December 2024 it had managed to stamp out its first known Marburg epidemic, which caused 15 deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There is no approved vaccine or antiviral treatment for the Marburg virus, but oral or intravenous rehydration and treatment of specific symptoms increases patients’ chances of survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Last year, Rwanda trialled an experimental vaccine from the US-based Sabin Vaccine Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 19:23:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxQS2lrZTV2TVpMb3pLT0gtX2tPLW1INVFXRWVYd1QzMTJlZ0RWaDRON2FOeFh3a1dRbGZBVkdBQnltcnIyck9MMk40bmZDNEhvc0ZaTzJpSlREdWtHTDhtUjN4VFp0VXE0UlBvaGY4SjcyU0NuVEFyS2Mza0tScHFzTG9oUmV5VDdWejhSYkVyVy16U3VVSzVZbzlWSWg</guid></item><item><title>轮椅？助听器？是的。“残疾人” ？不可能。--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/15/health/older-people-disability.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 17:52:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE82RFl6SGJKazFwMG14TjVGZ1dhWmdjbnRydW1MZjhISjZJYnhXcmN0Ri03cTdFWWdsQnJ5aEJpYVl0VFMzeXhyTWswV2NSNnJ6d2tnb0VjUTVvWUdtb04wV1VlU3JlWnM4VmttNUZVV2F1bTQyMzQ4MU1R</guid></item><item><title>多动症的“卡在当下”本质可能植根于特定的大脑网络沟通- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/adhds-stuck-in-the-present-nature-may-be-rooted-in-specific-brain-network-communication/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent study has identified a potential brain-based explanation for the connection between future-oriented thinking and the characteristics of attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder, or ADHD. The research suggests that the strength of communication between specific brain networks is linked to a person’s ability to plan for the future, which in turn is associated with the severity of inattention and hyperactivity. The findings were published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.pnpbp.2025.111427" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Progress in Neuropsychopharmacology &amp;amp; Biological Psychiatry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ADHD is a neurodevelopmental condition characterized by persistent patterns of inattention and hyperactivity-impulsivity that can interfere with daily functioning and development. While often diagnosed in childhood, its effects can extend into adulthood, presenting ongoing challenges. Researchers now often view ADHD not as a simple category but as a spectrum, where individuals in the general population can exhibit varying levels of its associated traits without meeting full diagnostic criteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One cognitive framework that appears related to these traits is known as future time perspective. This concept refers to an individual’s tendency to think about, plan for, and orient their life toward future goals. People with a strong future time perspective are often skilled at self-regulation, connecting their current actions to long-term objectives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous behavioral studies have observed that individuals who report a higher future time perspective tend to show fewer ADHD-related characteristics. The biological underpinnings of this relationship, however, have remained largely unknown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A team of researchers from Southwest University and Anhui Medical University in China, led by Tingyong Feng, designed a study to investigate the neural mechanisms that might connect future time perspective with ADHD traits. Their work aimed to see if differences in brain structure or function could help explain why a focus on the future is associated with lower levels of inattention and hyperactivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The investigation involved 240 healthy university students who completed a series of questionnaires. Participants rated their own tendencies toward inattention and hyperactivity-impulsivity using the Adult ADHD Self-Report Scale. They also completed the Zimbardo Time Perspective Inventory to measure their level of future time perspective. After completing the surveys, each participant underwent a magnetic resonance imaging, or MRI, brain scan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The behavioral results from the questionnaires confirmed the previously observed pattern. Students who scored higher on the future time perspective scale tended to have lower scores for both attention deficit and hyperactivity-impulsivity traits. This established the basic behavioral connection within the study group, setting the stage for the neuroimaging analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To examine the brain’s physical structure, the researchers first used a technique called voxel-based morphometry. This method allows for a comparison of gray matter volume across individuals, essentially measuring the amount of brain tissue containing neuron cell bodies in different regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The analysis showed that a higher future time perspective was associated with greater gray matter volume in two brain areas: the superior medial frontal gyrus and the left precentral gyrus, regions involved in self-reflection and action planning. At the same time, a higher future perspective was linked to less gray matter in the left inferior parietal lobule and the left superior temporal gyrus, areas related to cognitive control and processing information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, the team explored the brain’s functional organization using resting-state functional connectivity analysis. This technique measures how different brain regions coordinate their activity while a person is at rest, providing a map of the brain’s communication networks. The researchers used the brain regions identified in the structural analysis as starting points, or “seeds,” to see which other areas they were communicating with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This analysis yielded a specific pattern. The left inferior parietal lobule, a key node in the brain’s cognitive control network, showed a significant relationship. Individuals with a higher future time perspective exhibited stronger functional connectivity, or communication, between this region and two parts of the medial prefrontal cortex: the dorsomedial prefrontal cortex and the ventromedial prefrontal cortex. These prefrontal areas are central to the brain’s default mode network and are involved in processes like setting future goals and evaluating their personal value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also found that the strength of this communication pathway between the inferior parietal lobule and the medial prefrontal cortex was itself negatively associated with ADHD traits. Stronger connectivity was linked to lower levels of both inattention and hyperactivity. This finding connected a specific brain circuit to both the cognitive style of future thinking and the behavioral traits of ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To integrate all these pieces of information, the team performed a final statistical test called a mediation analysis. This analysis was designed to determine whether future time perspective could explain the relationship between brain connectivity and ADHD traits. The results showed that future time perspective did indeed act as a full mediator. The connection between the brain pathway (inferior parietal lobule to medial prefrontal cortex) and attention deficit traits was entirely accounted for by an individual’s future time perspective score.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A similar mediating effect was found for hyperactivity traits and the pathway connecting the inferior parietal lobule to the ventromedial prefrontal cortex. This suggests a potential sequence: the strength of communication in this brain circuit may influence how much a person focuses on the future, and this level of future focus, in turn, relates to their symptoms of inattention and hyperactivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study does have some limitations. The participants were healthy university students, so the findings may not be directly generalizable to individuals with a clinical diagnosis of ADHD. The research is also correlational, meaning it identifies associations between brain activity, cognition, and behavior, but it cannot prove that one causes the other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research could build on these findings by including clinical populations and using study designs that can provide more information about cause-and-effect relationships. Such work may help in developing new interventions for ADHD that focus on strengthening future-oriented thinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.pnpbp.2025.111427" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Neural basis of the association between future time perspective and ADHD characteristics: functional connectivity between Left inferior parietal lobule and mPFC&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Mingzhen Ding, Rong Zhang, and Tingyong Feng.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 15:09:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxPWGY1VzRVTFlpZUtUMDBhSlN2cWFrTDBHMFNJamxQc0c1VHp5b2k4NlJNUUdqT2duVTFhZjlxWUgxQW1Ra2RFWFp0bEpRcWJnZ2JnYUU1a3k2eE11c3Qza3BBbl9DUWNtZWpIQldSOUljYlhtdVY5OGpyYjRMY205QWhmY1BKR2VRbnJrRXQzVkhmY2RrYkJKSzAyYVNNMjdrN2ZjX3V0dF9tMFVON1pIRTJ3</guid></item><item><title>新药可以预防没有血糖控制的糖尿病并发症，研究提示- Live Science</title><link>https://www.livescience.com/health/medicine-drugs/new-drug-could-prevent-diabetes-complications-not-fixed-with-blood-sugar-control-study-hints</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto paywall-locker"&gt;
&lt;p id="96a17106-a2ee-47b1-8af1-4cb83e894038"&gt;An experimental drug compound could prevent and treat some complications of diabetes, such as poor wound healing and rampant inflammation. And it works regardless of blood sugar control, a new study in mice and human cells suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cornerstone of diabetes care is keeping blood sugar in check through diet and exercise, by maintaining a healthy weight, and by injecting the hormone insulin to help shuttle glucose out of the bloodstream. But while maintaining blood sugar levels in a target range &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://diabetesjournals.org/care/article/32/suppl_2/S357/27160/A-Summary-of-the-ADVANCE-Trial" target="_blank" data-url="https://diabetesjournals.org/care/article/32/suppl_2/S357/27160/A-Summary-of-the-ADVANCE-Trial" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;reduces the chance that diabetes complications&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; will emerge, it doesn't eliminate the risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="96a17106-a2ee-47b1-8af1-4cb83e894038-2"&gt;"The complications of diabetes — which really are the issues that make people sick, that reduce their lifespan, and that just make them unwell — are only partly mitigated by tight control of the blood sugar," said study co-author &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://med.nyu.edu/faculty/ann-marie-schmidt" target="_blank" data-url="https://med.nyu.edu/faculty/ann-marie-schmidt" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Ann Marie Schmidt&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of medicine at the NYU Grossman School of Medicine and director of the Diabetes Research Program at NYU Langone Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="b14400c5-3e34-49b3-a2d4-62ec12ac6867"&gt;That raises questions about what the other drivers of diabetic complications might be and whether they can be treated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, Schmidt and colleagues have sought to answer those questions, and their efforts have led to the development of the new experimental drug. In their latest work, published in October in the journal &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cell.com/cell-chemical-biology/fulltext/S2451-9456%2825%2900291-0" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cell.com/cell-chemical-biology/fulltext/S2451-9456%2825%2900291-0" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Cell Chemical Biology&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the team tested the drug's effects in lab mice and human cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results show that such a drug has "great potential" for limiting or preventing several complications of diabetes, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.path.pitt.edu/people/timothy-n-perkins-ms-phd" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.path.pitt.edu/people/timothy-n-perkins-ms-phd" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Timothy Perkins&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, an assistant professor of pathology at the University of Pittsburgh, wrote in a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cell.com/cell-chemical-biology/abstract/S2451-9456(25)00305-8" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cell.com/cell-chemical-biology/abstract/S2451-9456(25)00305-8" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;commentary&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-9d4a5b6a-c54b-4515-91f5-b7f8dbe1b18e" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="blocking-complications-at-the-source-3"&gt;Blocking complications at the source&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="19f337d0-f3fb-442c-9d96-915923a8682b"&gt;The new drug compound takes aim at a protein called RAGE, which interacts with a second protein called DIAPH1. Schmidt and colleagues &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.jbc.org/article/S0021-9258(18)42138-2/pdf" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.jbc.org/article/S0021-9258(18)42138-2/pdf" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;first described RAGE in the 1990s&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, finding that it plays a role in the vascular complications of diabetes, such as &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/heart-circulation/coronary-artery-disease-cad-causes-diagnosis-and-treatment" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/heart-circulation/coronary-artery-disease-cad-causes-diagnosis-and-treatment"&gt;&lt;u&gt;heart disease&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-u93FrFJrY5BFNMvAs8jLsB" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-u93FrFJrY5BFNMvAs8jLsB slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get the world’s most fascinating discoveries delivered straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The RAGE protein is found in many types of cells, including immune cells and the cells that line blood vessels. It spans the cell membrane, with one end interacting with substances on the outside of the cell and the other relaying signals inside the cell. The external bit of the protein interacts with advanced glycation end products (AGEs) — proteins with sugars stuck to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Once they're stuck on there, they have a gain of function where they can actually perturb and damage endothelial cells, the cells that line every blood vessel in our body," Schmidt told Live Science. It's known that AGEs accumulate in the body with normal aging, and in the context of certain chronic diseases, including diabetes, they build up more quickly than usual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RAGE, which stands for "receptor for AGEs," is activated by this buildup of sugar-coated proteins, and this kicks off harmful changes inside the cell, including processes that ramp up inflammation. It turns out that those changes rely on RAGE's interaction with a second protein inside the cell: DIAPH1. (The team had &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=livescience_us_4421760002319762830&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Flink.springer.com%2Farticle%2F10.14283%2Fjpad.2018.18&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fnew-drug-could-prevent-diabetes-complications-not-fixed-with-blood-sugar-control-study-hints" target="_blank" data-url="https://link.springer.com/article/10.14283/jpad.2018.18" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="skimlinks" data-google-interstitial="false" data-placeholder-url="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Flink.springer.com%2Farticle%2F10.14283%2Fjpad.2018.18&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fnew-drug-could-prevent-diabetes-complications-not-fixed-with-blood-sugar-control-study-hints" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;previously tried blocking AGEs from plugging&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; into RAGE, but didn't find success with that approach.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With guidance from co-author &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.albany.edu/chemistry/faculty/alexander-shekhtman" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.albany.edu/chemistry/faculty/alexander-shekhtman" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Alexander Shekhtman&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a structural biologist at the State University of New York at Albany, the researchers took a closer look at the interaction of RAGE and DIAPH1. They built a detailed model of how the two proteins interact in the presence of AGEs, and also investigated the downstream cellular consequences of that exchange.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They showed that, at baseline, DIAPH1 starts with a cellular brake engaged that holds back its activity, but after it interacts with RAGE, those brakes are ripped off. The full consequences of that aren't yet understood, Schmidt noted, but from what we know, it "appears to have pathological outcomes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Schmidt, Shekhtman and their team had previously looked for molecules that could block the interaction of RAGE and DIAPH1. &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=livescience_us_3126949435606073396&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fsrep22450&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fnew-drug-could-prevent-diabetes-complications-not-fixed-with-blood-sugar-control-study-hints" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.nature.com/articles/srep22450" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="skimlinks" data-google-interstitial="false" data-placeholder-url="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fsrep22450&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fnew-drug-could-prevent-diabetes-complications-not-fixed-with-blood-sugar-control-study-hints" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Among 58,000 molecules&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the team zeroed in on one that looked promising and found in initial mouse experiments that it curbed diabetes complications &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/scitranslmed.abf7084" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/scitranslmed.abf7084" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;such as kidney disease and heart ischemia&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. An analogue of that original molecule was used for the new study, as tests suggested it has a better safety profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In cells from patients with type 1 diabetes, the drug compound blocked the interaction between RAGE and DIAPH1 and subsequently reduced inflammatory signals. In lab mice with diabetes, applying the compound topically to mice's wounds helped to both tamp down inflammation and speed up healing. The researchers also showed that the drug could reduce inflammation in mice with allergies when given by mouth, but they didn't test this oral delivery in diabetic mice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking forward, it will be important to study RAGE in many cell types, because it likely does different things in different types of cells, Perkins noted in his commentary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="3c8f66d9-f0bd-4a83-a6b2-c6110af36043"&gt;Much more work is needed before the drug can be tested in humans, including more tests in lab animals, Schmidt emphasized. But she suggested that, if the drug makes it to approval, it would be best for patients to start using it soon after being diagnosed with diabetes. Ideally, RAGE therapy should be paired with tight blood sugar control, before the snowball effect of AGEs building up could get started, she said. You'd want to "mitigate that spiral of constantly making more AGEs," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond diabetes, RAGE is also known to contribute to inflammatory diseases of the lungs, such as asthma and chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD), Perkins noted. He suggested that those might be additional contexts where drugs that disrupt the RAGE-DIAPH1 interaction might be helpful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mb-6" id="2f2c29d2-08db-4a06-8dcc-879d3aaebdad"&gt;
&lt;div class="[&amp;amp;_a]:text-[#2f6e91] [&amp;amp;_a]:visited:text-[#09c] p-5 bg-[#F5F5F5] text-sm text-[#333]"&gt;

&lt;p class="infoDisclaimer tracking-[.02em] pt-2 font-normal"&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and is not meant to offer medical advice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2gFBVV95cUxNVTBKdVZZTThyUU5vWVBpWUFCemZfUXZaaWRTWjhlQ2Q5aWdOLXNoZXhGSG45ZEdTTzRXZUt5THBQMUt3WnhvbC1EcFZiUUNFTkVRdUpxS3VxWFA1WVBsdHMyUXUySEt3dV96RVFXLUJJRzhYOFUwYUQ2ZF8xbGJEQWRQSTFIQXVES0VWb0ZvdHByeVN1TVVpc2NvQnFvelVtdGRIZ1YyMjN0WlByaC12RGZrN29WbkhwZWhvd1hGRU01Q0RzUVVzT25EZzlRcEZFTnd4cmp6eFNmZw</guid></item><item><title>研究提供了50岁以下女性结直肠癌上升的线索-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/11/15/ultra-processed-foods-polyps-colorectal-cancer/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BENG5AO4RJBUZN5GBCGKW2ETK4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Women who eat more &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/01/02/ultra-processed-foods-identification/" target="_blank"&gt;ultra-processed foods&lt;/a&gt; on a daily basis have a greater risk of developing colorectal polyps before age 50 when compared with women who consume far less of the processed foods, a new study has found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 14:02:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxQeDNObnJxc3JEWm5ibzFXTFdyR2ZvVUNWbENJVWkzSUpobkg5SW9mOG10cXJMZ3BKdzg5ZFBCcmFGcnItSmRXcXh2SEI0Wl9CMER1YnZHU25FZmtnZ0xES19fLTVCM25nZTF5R2U0cGlRaXBvVXVOY1JtbjJ3THN3Mzdkb0NvMGFCaUN2S0otb1Z1VWZlTTA3aTJwVzZiWkk</guid></item><item><title>意见|反疫苗运动蔓延到宠物主人-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2025/11/15/edith-pritchett-cartoon-anti-vaccine-pet-owners/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-fwRMiJ"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="card-kicker" class="wpds-c-jzyMSq wpds-c-jzyMSq-kBYYkb-isHidden-true wpds-c-jzyMSq-iPJLV-css"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p data-testid="author-name-with-optional-link" class="wpds-c-byuVAJ wpds-c-byuVAJ-igwuywd-css"&gt;&lt;span class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-cIdiJW-isLink-false overrideStyles js-itid-click" rel="author"&gt;Amy B Wang&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="wpds-c-kpjDGe wpds-c-kpjDGe-ibWbpCL-css"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p data-testid="author-name-with-optional-link" class="wpds-c-byuVAJ wpds-c-byuVAJ-igwuywd-css"&gt;&lt;span class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-cIdiJW-isLink-false overrideStyles js-itid-click" rel="author"&gt;Aaron Schaffer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="wpds-c-kpjDGe wpds-c-kpjDGe-ibWbpCL-css"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p data-testid="author-name-with-optional-link" class="wpds-c-byuVAJ wpds-c-byuVAJ-igwuywd-css"&gt;&lt;span class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-cIdiJW-isLink-false overrideStyles js-itid-click" rel="author"&gt;Maegan Vazquez&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="wpds-c-kpjDGe wpds-c-kpjDGe-ibWbpCL-css"&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p data-testid="author-name-with-optional-link" class="wpds-c-byuVAJ wpds-c-byuVAJ-igwuywd-css"&gt;&lt;span class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-cIdiJW-isLink-false overrideStyles js-itid-click" rel="author"&gt;JM Rieger&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-gGNwiT wpds-c-gGNwiT-iPJLV-css"&gt;Epstein texted with House Democrat during Cohen hearing, documents show&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 14:01:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxNV19renN1b0JicU1RTVNNLVN5RnZHQ1puT2lBbnRNd1lGM2xId3doWjJLaFpVVy1EcmpjYjFKR0w5MjV4MjI3R291czd5eENCM2Y4UGtCZVlobmdqcHZ3UEw5SmVkVHQxVzlHbGRVWExTaFNMZmxwcG5MUGo4TS1yQm9zaVcyWlc2Z1QzNVdIZEdGdFN6Z3daSHpTakdKcG4w</guid></item><item><title>更年期不能接受激素治疗？还有其他选项-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/menopause-hormone-therapy-hot-flashes-0f3258f1762e1fb3c9a6f7205a43e66e</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;Shilpa Gajarawala struggled with hot flashes, night sweats, sleep problems and brain fog. But given her history of breast cancer, treating these &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/hormone-therapy-estrogen-hot-flashes-fda-5b1f29a73553c142f67b1f88b6656428"&gt;menopausal symptoms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; with &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/menopause-hormones-warning-fda-drugs-pills-women-f26a8208fd3f5174ec96d61140439561"&gt;hormone therapy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; wasn’t an option.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For two years, I tried to kind of power through,” said the 58-year-old physician assistant from Jacksonville, Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But doctors say women like Gajarawala don’t need to suffer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though many women take &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/menopause-blood-pressure-hormones-estrogen-hypertension-994deaa7a320ba02d2b34be4018684bf"&gt;hormone therapy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; medications to ease menopause symptoms, recently announced label changes may encourage even more to start. But others choose not to use these medications that circulate throughout the body. And doctors advise some to avoid them because they have medical problems such as severe liver disease or a history of heart attack, stroke, blood clots or a type of breast cancer that grows in response to hormones such as estrogen.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;For those people, there are lifestyle changes, &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/menopause-drug-hot-flashes-fda-approval-d790530fcd7c63ef0dd7fb9f57001f25"&gt;medications without hormones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and other strategies that can help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The key here is that there’s something for everybody,” said Dr. Stephanie Faubion, medical director at the Menopause Society. “There’s always a solution. We have lots of other options available.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="Infobox" data-module data-gtm-region="This article is part of AP's Be Well coverage, focusing on wellness, fitness, diet and mental health. Read more Be Well." data-align-center&gt;
    
    &lt;div class="Infobox-items RichTextBody"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article is part of AP’s Be Well coverage, focusing on wellness, fitness, diet and mental health. &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/hub/be-well"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Read more Be Well.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Lifestyle changes&lt;/h2&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;Boosting physical activity can make a difference. While exercise hasn’t been shown to alleviate menopausal symptoms directly, it can help to shed pounds, which is associated with reductions in hot flashes and night sweats. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors suggest a mix of aerobic exercise, such as running or walking, and strength training, which slows the loss of bone density.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;Along with exercise, doctors advise watching what you eat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emerging science shows that a “plant-forward diet,” rich in produce and soy and low in oil, may help with managing hot flashes in particular, said Faubion of the Mayo Clinic Center for Women’s Health. Experts aren’t sure why this is true, but some suggest it may be because it also helps with weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Another key, doctors said, is to avoid things in the diet that may trigger hot flashes, like caffeine or alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eating well and exercising also help with other midlife health issues, like rising heart and diabetes risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During menopause, the body’s production of the hormones estrogen and progesterone declines greatly. The drop in estrogen levels can lead to higher blood pressure and cholesterol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s important that we focus on maintaining cardiovascular health” such as stopping smoking, getting enough sleep and watching stress levels, Faubion said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Prescription drugs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond lifestyle changes, some nonhormonal prescription medicines have been shown to ease menopausal symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Antidepressants can help with hot flashes and mood issues. Recent data suggest that a drug for an overactive bladder called oxybutynin may reduce hot flashes while also treating frequent urination that’s common during menopause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And doctors pointed to a new drug on the market – Veozah, a brand name for fezolinetant — which works in the area of the brain that controls body temperature and blocks a source of hot flashes and night sweats. Another nonhormonal drug called elinzanetant — marketed as Lynkuet — was recently approved by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration. It works similarly, except it blocks two molecules in the nervous system instead of one.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;One downside of such medications? Possible side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Veozah’s label includes a federally required warning about the risk of a rare but serious liver injury. Lynkuet’s possible side effects include difficulty staying awake, fatigue and others. Some antidepressants can cause weight gain, although generally in doses higher than those used for menopause symptoms. And oxybutynin can cause dry mouth and, in some people, a condition in which they can’t completely empty the bladder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There’s no medication out there that’s entirely free of risk,” said Dr. JoAnn Manson at Harvard Medical School.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Other nonhormonal options&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over-the-counter products can also treat some menopausal symptoms. Lubricants available at drugstores can help women struggling with vaginal dryness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cognitive behavioral therapy, which focuses on changing unhealthy thought patterns and behaviors, has been shown to help women cope with hot flashes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s not like it’s going to make you not have a hot flash,” Faubion said. “But it makes them less significant for you and less burdensome.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Manson said there’s “moderate evidence” that clinical hypnosis might also help, with some studies showing reductions in the frequency and severity of hot flashes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“That seems a promising option,” she said. “But more research is needed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bottom line is that women don’t have to simply “get through” menopause, said Dr. Juliana Kling, a women’s health expert at Mayo Clinic Alix School of Medicine in Arizona. “I would implore women to have that conversation ... about what treatment might be beneficial for them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gajarawala did that. She now skips red wine, walks at least 10,000 steps a day, practices tai chi and takes an extended-release antidepressant to address her symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;“It’s been a significant improvement,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxOaUtQWUliOUZaNmJHRlBxZGtxbWZwbTFRMmp4a2hRdlhpSlR1UzhNdWE3RFQ4bVJpa3g4QmxPSnNlajBDZmtwWGFzUkhWUjNpc0kxUDkzWVMzaEhpY1VZSVo2bUQ5LTJENVg1aGV4dGJNaDN0RU1Yb3ZuQ2JoSDBzSm5qNEdoOHBUSGwxUzBGT3hmWFFCWGNsWkg0UGdBdw</guid></item><item><title>金县的Mpox感染导致官员再次敦促接种疫苗-西雅图时报</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/mpox-infections-in-king-county-lead-officials-to-again-urge-vaccination/</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivgFBVV95cUxONU9iOFEzQkcwWklrMEo3bGo4aE5TVzdCRWNaUEdVVUxwUUFnR3JyY2NkTl9HMHpwRVVrZ2wya0ptWmxDWUNuaTNoYTVia016dG5ESG5uVDdROHhZZF9BdXVwd1NrZWM3cDVRVVk0Mnk2TFM3VFJiU2lMck1Rbzk5ZTBxUnRwNEZSd3M4WkVOTVBsakpFLUw1cEVyUzZaaTIwOThuV0JvdTBoSjZmWlFseUpVVFpnUTJKUU1XZHRn?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Mpox infections in King County lead officials to again urge vaccination&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxONU9iOFEzQkcwWklrMEo3bGo4aE5TVzdCRWNaUEdVVUxwUUFnR3JyY2NkTl9HMHpwRVVrZ2wya0ptWmxDWUNuaTNoYTVia016dG5ESG5uVDdROHhZZF9BdXVwd1NrZWM3cDVRVVk0Mnk2TFM3VFJiU2lMck1Rbzk5ZTBxUnRwNEZSd3M4WkVOTVBsakpFLUw1cEVyUzZaaTIwOThuV0JvdTBoSjZmWlFseUpVVFpnUTJKUU1XZHRn</guid></item><item><title>一个轻微的症状困扰着一个年轻的爸爸。他患有IV期肺癌。- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/ultramarathon-runner-lung-cancer-non-smoker-northwestern-medicine-michigan/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Endurance athlete Kevin Humphrey was used to discomfort. He regularly participated in ultramarathons and other intense events. Swimming, biking and running dozens of miles at a time was standard for him. His two young sons also kept him active even when he wasn't training. But in January 2024, a persistent back pain kept bothering him. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pain "just would not go away," Humphrey said. He couldn't sleep on his back. At the same time, he started coughing. He was diagnosed with pneumonia, but his symptoms lingered even after treatment. A chest CT scan found "something going on" in his left lung. A biopsy of the organ came back inconclusive, Humphrey said, but he kept pushing for answers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I knew something was off. It just didn't feel right," Humphrey said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey traveled from Michigan to Chicago to seek a second opinion at Northwestern Medicine in May 2024. A bronchoscopy found shocking results: There was a tumor in his lung that was crushing the left side of his windpipe, causing the coughing and pain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was really in disbelief," said Humphrey, who had never smoked and had no family history of lung cancer. "It wasn't even on my radar as a possibility. It wasn't even an option in my mind."  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/06/f1f3737f-130a-4d0f-b495-a0b369072669/thumbnail/620x827/f88db284508abd2590f4cb9b26c2d814/charter.jpg#" alt="charter.jpg " srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/06/f1f3737f-130a-4d0f-b495-a0b369072669/thumbnail/620x827/f88db284508abd2590f4cb9b26c2d814/charter.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/06/f1f3737f-130a-4d0f-b495-a0b369072669/thumbnail/1240x1654/7b71017368333fd7ec47452ccdf4be4e/charter.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Kevin Humphrey. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Kevin Humphrey

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;"A very concerning and dire situation" &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey was diagnosed with Stage IV non-small cell adenocarcinoma, joining the growing number of &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/sanfrancisco/news/why-do-non-smoking-asian-women-have-high-rates-of-lung-cancer-a-ucsf-study-hopes-to-find-out/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;young, non-smoking patients&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; diagnosed with lung cancer. The rise may be driven by &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/radon-odorless-colorless-gas-lung-cancer-what-to-know/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;environmental&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; or lifestyle factors, Dr. Jonathan Villena-Vargas, a thoracic surgeon at NewYork-Presbyterian and Weill Cornell Medicine, &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/lung-cancer-diagnosis-in-non-smoker/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;previously told CBS News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Villena-Vargas, who did not treat Humphrey, said there is no definitive reason for the increase. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further tests found that the cancer had spread beyond Humphrey's lung and had likely been growing for at least a year, Humphrey said. The disease typically has a 37% 5-year survival rate at that point, according to the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/6203-non-small-cell-lung-cancer" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humphrey's tumor was "pretty advanced" and too large for surgery at first, said Dr. Daniel Dammrich, the Northwestern Medicine oncologist who treated him. But doctors were able to identify a "driver mutation" that was encouraging the cancer's growth. These mutations are more common in young, non-smoking patients, Villena-Vargas said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identifying the mutation "really opened the door for some of our more nuanced, targeted therapies," Dammrich said, and "turned a very concerning and dire situation into a much more optimistic one."  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dammrich and Humphrey agreed on an aggressive plan that would combine &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/immunotherapy-cancer-mmrd-tumor-memorial-sloan-kettering-study/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;targeted immunotherapy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; with chemotherapy, in the hopes that the medications would shrink the tumor enough for surgery. Humphrey began immunotherapy immediately, then had chemotherapy in summer 2024. By August, the cancer was operable.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/05/c369cbea-4232-42cb-a67d-fd5df6b267c0/thumbnail/620x805/206fe467ce159fc89fe5ec82ecc7664a/img-4760.jpg#" alt="img-4760.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/05/c369cbea-4232-42cb-a67d-fd5df6b267c0/thumbnail/620x805/206fe467ce159fc89fe5ec82ecc7664a/img-4760.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/05/c369cbea-4232-42cb-a67d-fd5df6b267c0/thumbnail/1240x1610/0c5b061781cfcfe0bb58a67cfc442ebe/img-4760.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Kevin Humphrey receives chemotherapy at Northwestern Medicine.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Kevin Humphrey

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;"The biggest question mark"   &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Removing the cancer meant taking out about half of Humphrey's left lung. The athlete wasn't sure what that would mean for his passion. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"You just had no idea. Can you run again, can you bike, can you do all these endurance sports that I've loved doing?" Humphrey said. "That was the biggest question mark going into surgery." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the unknowns, he focused on the future. Michigan's Ironman 70.3 race — which included a 1-mile swim, 56.1-mile bike ride and a 13.2 mile run — was scheduled to take place a year and a day after his surgery. Humphrey decided to sign up, despite his fears. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/05/f488ec70-90bc-4944-a656-15455f434f4c/thumbnail/620x867/f5012f71cdc1974864bf32f8454953f7/img-4764.jpg#" alt="img-4764.jpg " srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/05/f488ec70-90bc-4944-a656-15455f434f4c/thumbnail/620x867/f5012f71cdc1974864bf32f8454953f7/img-4764.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/05/f488ec70-90bc-4944-a656-15455f434f4c/thumbnail/1240x1734/631e1bb64ba2bb453b55267d8e1b4707/img-4764.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Kevin Humphrey in the hospital.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Kevin Humphrey

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Humphrey had surgery in mid-September. The operation removed most of the cancer, Dammrich said. Recovery was its own battle. Broken ribs and a "pretty big" incision made it difficult for Humphrey to do simple tasks like get out of bed or walk more than a few steps. Running was out of the question for months. But he kept putting one foot in front of the other until his strength and endurance began to slowly return. Even on the hardest days, the upcoming race kept him motivated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It was a great mental thing to put on the calendar and train for," Humphrey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;"Across the finish line" &lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Sept. 14, Humphrey was one of over 1,600 athletes who took part in the Ironman. He finished in just under five and a half hours, coming in &lt;a href="https://www.ironman.com/races/im703-michigan/results" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;411th place&lt;/a&gt;. The race was exhausting and emotional, Humphrey said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're replaying everything that's happened over the past year and the whirlwind it's been," Humphrey said. "For me, when I got to the point of knowing 'I'm going to finish this race' and thinking about my young boys, my wife, the family and the community and support system we've had throughout the whole year, and how grateful I am to not only be here but to continue to do these types of races and events. I certainly did not think that was going to be the case when I received the diagnosis in May of '24." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/05/a632ff93-b348-411e-9be6-ddf9888d651e/thumbnail/620x762/30eb7a5364cca1980695a3a69961ed9e/screenshot-2025-11-05-at-12-07-08-pm.png#" alt="screenshot-2025-11-05-at-12-07-08-pm.png " srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/05/a632ff93-b348-411e-9be6-ddf9888d651e/thumbnail/620x762/30eb7a5364cca1980695a3a69961ed9e/screenshot-2025-11-05-at-12-07-08-pm.png 1x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Kevin Humphrey's son gives him a high-five during the Ironman 70.3 Michigan.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Kevin Humphrey

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Humphrey's medical situation is also positive. He had a complete response to the treatment, and there is currently no evidence of disease in his body, Dammrich said. Regular CT scans and blood tests watch for any new tumor growth. Humphrey remains on immunotherapy with few side effects. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Oct. 12, less than a month after the Ironman, Humphrey ran the Chicago marathon for the sixth time. Over &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/chicago/news/53000-runners-2025-bank-of-america-chicago-marathon/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;53,000 runners participated&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the race. Humphrey &lt;a href="https://results.chicagomarathon.com/2025/?content=detail&amp;amp;fpid=search&amp;amp;pid=search&amp;amp;idp=9TGG96382B1FC0&amp;amp;lang=EN_CAP&amp;amp;event=MAR&amp;amp;event_main_group=runner&amp;amp;search%5Bname%5D=Humphrey&amp;amp;search%5Bfirstname%5D=Kevin&amp;amp;search_event=MAR" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;placed 25,395th&lt;/a&gt;, finishing in about seven and a half hours. It was "40 or 45 minutes slower" than when he ran the same race in 2023, Humphrey said, but he was proud to have finished. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My goal was just to get across the finish line, and that's what we did," Humphrey said. "I was just grateful for the ability to be out there and to run and be doing the things that I've loved doing for such a long time." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/05/b27c8dd7-5e57-4f86-80eb-67150aa53956/thumbnail/620x659/c7967d4391b002138a7cb27f6a113890/screenshot-2025-11-05-at-12-06-23-pm.png#" alt="screenshot-2025-11-05-at-12-06-23-pm.png " srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/05/b27c8dd7-5e57-4f86-80eb-67150aa53956/thumbnail/620x659/c7967d4391b002138a7cb27f6a113890/screenshot-2025-11-05-at-12-06-23-pm.png 1x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Kevin Humphrey's sons cheer him on during the Chicago marathon.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Kevin Humphrey

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  

    

                    
        
  
          
  
  



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

  
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 13:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxPUnowT2pPUC1SNWl1U3o5Mk9HZ2tzYUx3Vm9mOEgyY1psMEloY1ZvcVpMWWVNZHRMZ3U4aVNQaFQ0Qy1rZW5Oclo2VGZZeFhraE9SNm9RZVdacDk0cmkyOUxVZXViRTktem9WVjBzTHA3ZUdjWHBiOGVFZ0JUVlk1LTlpWlZvcWN5RnE4X3A2LURpdE1iUkNHa2RvUTJDYlg5eFBBUW5Ua9IBrAFBVV95cUxNa2pkTE0xQzk0cnJtbTFiRzE5aTJJaXpLTHNfM2FiVDMzNlpIT2NXNE9fU0hWZ0JNa3lHZTlBUDE3ZUZBckhydGtwS1c4WnZmXzE5NFlzTjlZNHhpRFFrUVVBSkJPTk1MNi1McGZuc2Q3OGJaQ1BBODVEb1AwYy1WSnIwbC05SURhZ001MHN1TFNYbjJfaHRXZzFsU1pDdWR4NnNLbzRZaVFRNmpI</guid></item><item><title>关于乳腺癌和节育的巨大新研究表明科学是如何被扭曲的- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/breast-cancer-birth-control-study-science/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As misinformation about women's health spreads faster than ever, doctors say new research on the risks of hormonal birth control underscores the challenge of communicating nuance in the social media age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The massive study, which was conducted in Sweden and tracked more than two million teenage girls and women under age 50 for more than a decade, found that hormonal contraception remains safe overall, but also found small differences in breast cancer risk based on the hormones used in the formulation. In addition, the researchers observed a small, short-term rise in breast cancer diagnoses among current or recent users. Those findings are consistent with prior large studies, including a &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa1700732" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;2017 Danish registry analysis&lt;/a&gt; and a &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10030023/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;2023 meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was published online Oct. 30 in &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaoncology/fullarticle/2840506" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;JAMA Oncology&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors say these study results won't change how they advise patients and that women should not stop using their birth control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, TikTok is flooded with factually incomplete warnings that contraceptives cause cancer and are as dangerous as smoking. Reproductive health advocates warn that studies like this &lt;a href="https://www.euronews.com/my-europe/2025/06/30/fact-checking-viral-claims-that-who-just-listed-the-contraceptive-pill-as-a-carcinogen" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;can easily&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.debatemag.com/single-post/omg-the-pill-causes-cancer-here-s-what-tiktok-isn-t-telling-you" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;be taken&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2024/11/05/social-media-misinformation-is-scaring-women-about-birth-control/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;out of context&lt;/a&gt; online and be reduced to a single alarming number.&lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Case in point: &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaoncology/fullarticle/2840506" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;The study&lt;/a&gt; reported that women who had used hormonal birth control had about a 24% higher rate of breast cancer than women who hadn't. But because &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/breast-cancer-survivor-earlier-screening-younger-women-face-rising-cases/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;breast cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is still uncommon in younger women, that works out to an increase from roughly 54 to 67 breast cancer cases per 100,000 women per year — about 13 extra cases per 100,000 women, or about one extra case per 7,800 users of hormonal contraceptives per year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Co-authors Åsa Johansson and Dr. Fatemeh Hadizadeh, epidemiologists at &lt;a href="https://www.uu.se/en" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Uppsala University&lt;/a&gt;, said the rise is modest and short-term, with risk highest during current use and fading within five to 10 years after stopping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rachel Fey — interim co-CEO of Power to Decide, a group whose mission is to provide accurate information on sexual health and contraceptive methods — said that kind of nuance is exactly what tends to disappear on social media. "I get really angry at this because it's designed to scare people like me away from birth control, which has made my life so much better in so many ways," she said. "It's really frustrating … especially when it's given without context. And then in this era of social media, it can just take off without anybody who knows what they're talking about providing that context."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also found the risk was slightly higher with certain progestins such as desogestrel — found in combined oral contraceptives like Cyred EQ, Reclipsen, Azurette, and Pimtrea — but did not increase with others, such as medroxyprogesterone acetate injections, sold under the brand name Depo‑Provera.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How to interpret the findings&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some experts say the results should be viewed with care because the study counted both invasive breast cancers and early, noninvasive lesions known as in situ tumors, growths that may never become life-threatening. Including these precancerous cases could make the overall risk of clinically significant disease appear higher than it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A substantial proportion of the 'cases' would never have progressed to invasive breast cancer," said Lina S. Mørch, a senior researcher and team leader at the Danish Cancer Institute. Mørch was not associated with the Swedish study. She added that experts should wait for more data separating early-stage and advanced cancers before making new rules or warnings about specific hormones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The doctor-patient conversation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even as scientists debate how to interpret the finer points of the data, physicians emphasize that for most patients, the study reinforces what they already discuss in the exam room: that hormonal birth control is broadly safe, and decisions should be tailored to each woman's needs and values.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Katharine White, chief of Obstetrics and Gynecology at Boston Medical Center, said this study won't change how she talks to her patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When counseling patients about their contraceptive options, I focus on their past experiences with birth control, their medical history, and what's important to them about their birth control method and pregnancy planning (if applicable)," White wrote in an email. "Side effects and risks of methods are already a key part of my counseling about both hormonal and non-hormonal methods."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other doctors noted there are other contraceptive options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Eleanor Bimla Schwarz, chief of General Internal Medicine at Zuckerberg San Francisco General Hospital, said, "For those who prefer hormone-free contraception, the copper IUD offers safe, convenient, highly effective contraception for over a decade after placement, and is rapidly reversible when pregnancy is desired," referring to a type of long-acting intrauterine device.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Mary Rosser, director of Integrated Women's Health at Columbia University Irving Medical Center, said this was a large, high-quality study that looked at many types of hormones over many years. But she added that doctors shouldn't change their advice yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Johansson and Hadizadeh stressed that the results should guide shared decision-making, not cause alarm. "It may be reasonable to consider formulations associated with lower observed risk in our data," they said. They noted that products containing medroxyprogesterone acetate, drospirenone, or levonorgestrel were linked to lower risk, while long-term use of desogestrel-only contraceptives might be best avoided when other options fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Keeping the risk in perspective&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hormonal birth control provides many health benefits beyond pregnancy prevention. It can lighten heavy periods, ease pain from endometriosis, and lower the risk of ovarian and uterine cancers for years after stopping. Mørch noted that even small risks are worth discussing but said decisions should be guided by women's "values and preferences."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;White said it's important to see the big picture. "The risk of an unintended pregnancy is 85% for people who do not use contraception—so any risks of birth control need to be weighed against the risk of an unexpected pregnancy," she wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/about-us/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;KFF Health News&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; is a national newsroom that produces in-depth journalism about health issues and is one of the core operating programs at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/about-us/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;KFF&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; — the independent source for health policy research, polling, and journalism.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    

                    
        
  
    
  
  &lt;aside class="component list recirculation component--type-recirculation component--type-recirculation-collection"&gt;
                    
                                            
        &lt;div class="component__heading-wrapper recirc"&gt;
          &lt;h3 class="component__title"&gt;Breast Cancer Awareness
                          &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/feature/breast-cancer-awareness/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="component__view-more component__view-more--lg" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                More
                &lt;svg viewbox="0 0 32 32" class="icon__caret-right" aria-hidden="true"&gt;
                  &lt;use xlink:href="#icon-caret-down"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                &lt;/svg&gt;
              &lt;/a&gt;
                      &lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
                  
                            &lt;/aside&gt;



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

  
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 12:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE4tTDJ5WUZJU3hnR1ZfeUNxS0JLaUN6Rkc4Yjh2RVpXbGRweTZuRFZqbjhMVjBaRHhncGZReXcyWFhFbFZaQjNXNHZ6OEw3ckxYSVgyZm5tLVBpUndmaWc4OGYxOU1idElkRE1jdWNoMlBJRkN3U1FabDBzRdIBgAFBVV95cUxQZWthVU82emlTNWZ3cWtaYkNnTHpLRGpoQVN0bkRKdkkzYy1yZnNFX1ctdnc0VzdKQlBGT2ZjcnAtZlNPUVVVN2xyTXp0d1JxTE1jNTZKREhWelV5aWotWkljbVJSWE5VY2NQX1dLTkwxSnY4MlJfUW96MlFtc1VjUw</guid></item><item><title>专家表示，老年人需要6种维生素和矿物质- CNET</title><link>https://www.cnet.com/health/nutrition/the-secret-to-healthy-aging-isnt-a-secret-its-these-6-expert-backed-vitamins/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="c-ShortcodeContent c-ShortcodeContent-theme:default sm:u-col-2 md:u-col-6 lg:u-col-12"&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p1"&gt;Here's the hard truth: "aging gracefully" isn't just a state of mind; it's a state of nutrition. As you get older, your body just can't get away with what it used to, and those &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/feeling-off-these-8-body-cues-might-be-nutritional-sos-signals/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;vitamin deficiencies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; you never thought about are suddenly a very big deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p2"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8469089/#sec9-nutrients-13-03163" target="_self"&gt;2021 study&lt;/a&gt; confirmed what we already suspected: not getting the right stuff can make existing issues worse and even trigger new chronic problems. That's why watching what you eat &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/vitamins-and-supplements/dietary-supplements-older-adults" target="_self"&gt;after 50&lt;/a&gt; is really non-negotiable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're not just guessing what you need. We went straight to the doctors to find out which specific vitamins and minerals are most critical for &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/fitness/we-recommend-doing-these-3-exercises-to-stay-young-and-strong/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;healthy aging&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. (But obviously, don't just start popping a bunch of new supplements-talk to your own doctor first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Don't miss any of our unbiased tech content and lab-based reviews. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.google.com/preferences/source?q=cnet.com#link={%22role%22:%22standard%22,%22href%22:%22https://www.google.com/preferences/source?q=cnet.com%22,%22target%22:%22%22,%22absolute%22:%22%22,%22linkText%22:%22%3Cem%3EAdd%20CNET%3C/em%3E%22}" target="_self"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Add CNET&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; as a preferred Google source.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Magnesium&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Magnesium is a mineral that provides several key functions in the body. It keeps your muscles strong, regulates blood sugar levels and contributes to heart health. &lt;a href="https://www.vitality101.com/about-dr-teitelbaum" target="_self"&gt;Dr. Jacob Teitelbaum&lt;/a&gt;, a board-certified internist in integrative medicine, told us that "magnesium is critical for well over 300 reactions in the body."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-small c-shortcodeImage-pullRight"&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said that an unprocessed diet contains about 600 mg of magnesium daily, but the average American diet contains less than 250 mg of magnesium after processing. For reference, the daily recommended amount of magnesium is &lt;a href="https://www.uclahealth.org/news/article/are-you-getting-enough-magnesium" target="_self"&gt;400 to 420mg per day for adult men&lt;/a&gt; and 310 to 320mg for women, but more is needed for those who are pregnant or breastfeeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-all-top spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teitelbaum warned that the effects of low magnesium may include an &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/circulationaha.105.588327" target="_self"&gt;increased risk of metabolic syndrome&lt;/a&gt;. This can lead to heart attacks, strokes and dementia. You may also feel exhausted or experience widespread muscle pain if you're not getting enough magnesium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can find magnesium in a wide range of foods. &lt;a href="https://fatlotofgood.com.au/" target="_self"&gt;Dr. Peter Brukner&lt;/a&gt;, a specialist in sports and exercise medicine, said that magnesium can be found in nuts, seeds, whole grains and leafy green vegetables like spinach. In extra yummy news, you can also get magnesium from dark chocolate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Some older adults or those who take specific medicines (such as diuretics or drugs for acid reflux) may not receive enough magnesium from their diet and might need &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/5-best-magnesium-supplements/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;a supplement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;," he said. "However, too much magnesium can cause stomach issues, so be careful."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. B vitamins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;Laurie Ambrose/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You also need a range of B Vitamins, including B12 and folate (also called folic acid), to maintain your health as you age. Vitamin B-12 works with folate to help your body make new cells, including blood cells and nerve cells. While you don't usually require more B12 as you age, your &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11084641/" target="_self"&gt;body can't absorb it as well&lt;/a&gt; when you get older. Brukner said this is because "stomachs make less acid, and this acid is necessary to take the vitamin from food into the body."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teitelbaum said B vitamins are critical for energy production, and suboptimal levels can affect your health. He warns that B vitamin deficiency has been associated with "a &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8079632/#s5" target="_self"&gt;marked increase of dementia&lt;/a&gt; (especially folic acid) and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0749379715000732" target="_self"&gt;increased risk of heart attack and stroke&lt;/a&gt; (especially in those with elevated homocysteine levels)." Symptoms of B12 deficiency include weakness or poor balance, loss of appetite and numbness and tingling in the hands and feet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;B12 is found in animal proteins, such as meat, fish and eggs. Brukner said that if you don't eat these foods, you may want to turn to foods like cereals and nutritional yeast with added B12. "Older people, especially those having certain stomach issues or taking medicine that lowers stomach acid, might need to take a B12 vitamin supplement," he explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/amelia-ti/" target="_self"&gt;Amelia Ti&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian and diabetes educator in New York, who is also part of &lt;a href="https://www.cnet.com/health/how-we-ensure-accurate-and-reliable-medical-information/" target="_self"&gt;CNET's Medical Review Board&lt;/a&gt;, notes that individuals taking medications that block B12 absorption, such as omeprazole or metformin, may also require a vitamin B12 supplement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Calcium&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The National Institute on Aging says that calcium is especially important for &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/vitamins-and-supplements/vitamins-and-minerals-older-adults#calcium" target="_self"&gt;older people at risk for bone loss&lt;/a&gt;. The Institute recommends 1,000mg each day for men between the ages of 51 and 70, and 1,200mg per day for men 71 and older. &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/best-vitamins-for-women-50-plus/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Women aged 51 and up&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are recommended to take 1,200mg each day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Calcium is well-known for making bones strong, but it is also crucial for muscles to work right," Brukner said. "As people become older, their bodies take in less calcium from food, which can cause bones to become weaker." You can get calcium naturally from sources like milk, yogurt and cheese. The Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health notes that &lt;a href="https://nutritionsource.hsph.harvard.edu/calcium/" target="_self"&gt;calcium is also available&lt;/a&gt; in kale, salmon, tofu, almonds and spinach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for supplements, Brukner said, "If you are at risk for bone troubles or don't get enough calcium in your food, taking supplements might be useful. But too much calcium can cause other issues like kidney stones, so talk with your doctor first."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Vitamin D&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;Malorny/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin D is often referred to as the "sunshine vitamin" because it is typically absorbed through the skin by simply being outside. However, during winter months, if you live in a cloudy climate or avoid natural sunlight as you age, you may not get enough. Your body &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/are-you-getting-enough-sun-heres-what-to-know-about-vitamin-d-supplements/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;needs vitamin D to properly absorb calcium&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, making it a crucial nutrient for maintaining bone health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brukner says that in addition to sunshine, you can get vitamin D from fatty fish like salmon and mackerel, fortified milk and cereals. Your doctor may also recommend a supplement if you're experiencing bone loss or at risk of osteoporosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to bone health, Teitelbaum said vitamin D can help you fight off disease. He said, "Suboptimal vitamin D is associated with &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6047889/#S8" target="_self"&gt;increased autoimmunity,&lt;/a&gt; higher risk of severe infectious diseases and &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3440651/#:~:text=Vitamin%20D%20deficiency%20has%20been,it%20a%20potential%20risk%20factor." target="_self"&gt;increased cancer risk&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Omega-3s&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Omega-3 fatty acids are essential to many of your body's functions. They play a role in both heart and &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/what-to-know-multivitamins-memory-brain-health-age/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;brain health&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. However, as the Cleveland Clinic points out, the body &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/17290-omega-3-fatty-acids#link={%22role%22:%22standard%22,%22href%22:%22https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/17290-omega-3-fatty-acids%22,%22target%22:%22%22,%22absolute%22:%22%22,%22linkText%22:%22isn%27t%20able%20to%20produce%20enough%20omega-3s%20on%20its%20own%22}" target="_self"&gt;is unable&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/17290-omega-3-fatty-acids" target="_self"&gt; to produce enough omega-3s on its own&lt;/a&gt;. This means you need to get more from &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/should-take-omega-3-supplements-benefits-drawbacks/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;the foods you eat&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; or the supplements you take.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Omega-3 fatty acids are very good for heart health and can help lessen swelling, which is important for older people," Brukner explained. "They are also beneficial for brain well-being and might help guard against memory loss and &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4019002/#:~:text=More%20than%20a%20dozen%20epidemiological,as%20Alzheimer's%20disease%20(AD)." target="_self"&gt;diseases such as Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;." Ti adds that omega-3s help lessen swelling by reducing inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fatty fish like salmon are a good source of omega-3 fatty acids. Brukner said you can also turn to flaxseeds, chia seeds and walnuts, but added a warning: "These give a different type of omega-3 that the body does not use so easily." Fish oil and algae oil can also serve as supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. Zinc&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.3402/pba.v5.25592" target="_self"&gt;2015 paper&lt;/a&gt;, published in Pathobiology of Aging and Age-related Diseases, calls zinc an "essential micronutrient for human health in general, and particularly for the elderly." The authors say zinc plays "an important role in the aging process" and that zinc deficiency may be connected to several age-related chronic illnesses, which include hardening of the arteries, degenerative diseases of the nervous system, age-related changes to the immune system and cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When we get older, our immune system becomes weaker, and if we don't have enough zinc, this can make it even worse," Brukner explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can find zinc in shellfish, red meat, poultry, beans, nuts and seeds. Brukner said oysters are particularly zinc-rich. He added, "Some older people might find zinc supplements helpful, especially if they often get sick or do not eat enough foods high in zinc. But taking too much zinc can cause problems with other minerals in the body, so it's important to follow advised amounts."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eating well can help boost your bones, immune system and more as you age. &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/fitness/how-weightlifting-benefits-you-during-the-aging-process/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Along with exercise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and other healthy habits, obtaining the right minerals and vitamins can improve your overall health. Try to get enough magnesium, B vitamins, calcium, vitamin D, omega-3 fatty acids, and zinc in your diet each day. Consult your doctor before taking any supplements to determine how they may interact with your existing medications and health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-cy="shortcodeFaq" class="c-shortcodeFaq g-container-rounded-small"&gt; &lt;div&gt; &lt;div data-cy="shortcodeFaq_sections" class="c-shortcodeFaq_sections"&gt;&lt;div class="c-shortcodeFaqQuestion c-shortcodeFaq_question g-border-thin-light-top"&gt; &lt;div data-cy="shortcodeFaq_answer" class="c-shortcodeFaqQuestion_answer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;While there are many factors that can lead to this, one of the more common reasons is because when you get older your body has a slower metabolism and less stomach acid, meaning absorbing nutrients is harder. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="c-shortcodeFaqQuestion c-shortcodeFaq_question g-border-thin-light-top"&gt; &lt;div data-cy="shortcodeFaq_answer" class="c-shortcodeFaqQuestion_answer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the things you may experience if you're not getting enough of the vitamins listed here include: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Heart problems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Muscle cramps or weakness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anemia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Memory loss&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bone fractures&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Osteoporosis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dry and brittle hair and nails&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fatigue&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are many more symptoms you could experience as a result of vitamin deficiency and any concerns should be brought up with your doctor before taking any supplements or changing your diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNET</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxNUmxLWFJ2dl93aU9yVHE4b0NkZzBZU2pva0hYWnM2Vnp5ZTBGZE9tczFsZmtONGtodzR4cTRwY1BCWVkyT3Z0bWVIR2wyYnU4RjJ0Qmw0S05pYWhyVzZ0UndEb1YyRnlwZVM5RzJhZTdfOUVvbkxGNFltekxmSnZaMlVCVzc0QU1LZ1JGU1ZHZFJ1cUtfT1FjWElDNWlwa0xpcU1iYUZPc09EZnFXc1FkSmVadDNXUQ</guid></item><item><title>携带侵入性疾病的蚊子已蔓延到落基山脉- WIRED</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/a-disease-carrying-mosquito-has-landed-in-the-rocky-mountains-where-it-historically-couldnt-survive/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span class="lead-in-text-callout"&gt;This story originally&lt;/span&gt; appeared on &lt;a href="https://insideclimatenews.org/news/10112025/colorado-invasive-dengue-fever-mosquito/"&gt;Inside Climate News&lt;/a&gt; and is part of the &lt;a href="https://www.climatedesk.org/"&gt;Climate Desk&lt;/a&gt; collaboration.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;It can carry life-threatening diseases. It’s difficult to find and hard to kill. And it’s obsessed with human blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The Aedes aegypti is a species of mosquito that people like Tim Moore, district manager of a mosquito control district on the Western Slope of Colorado, really don’t want to see.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“Boy, they are locked into humans,” Moore said. “That’s their blood meal.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;This mosquito species is native to tropical and subtropical climates, but as climate change pushes up temperatures and warps precipitation patterns, the Aedes aegypti—which can spread Zika, dengue, chikungunya and other potentially deadly viruses—is on the move.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;It’s popping up all over the Mountain West, where conditions have historically been far too harsh for it to survive. In the last decade, towns in &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.nmhealth.org/news/awareness/2018/10/?view=717" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.nmhealth.org/news/awareness/2018/10/?view=717"}' href="https://www.nmhealth.org/news/awareness/2018/10/?view=717" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;New Mexico&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a data-offer-url="https://epi.utah.gov/wp-content/uploads/Utah-Arboviral-Surveillance-Weekly-Report__MMWR39.pdf" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://epi.utah.gov/wp-content/uploads/Utah-Arboviral-Surveillance-Weekly-Report__MMWR39.pdf"}' href="https://epi.utah.gov/wp-content/uploads/Utah-Arboviral-Surveillance-Weekly-Report__MMWR39.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Utah&lt;/a&gt; have begun catching Aedes aegypti in their traps year after year, and just this summer, one was found for the &lt;a data-offer-url="https://adacounty.id.gov/weedpestmosquito/news/canyon-county-has-first-detection-of-invasive-mosquito-species-aedes-aegypti-in-idaho/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://adacounty.id.gov/weedpestmosquito/news/canyon-county-has-first-detection-of-invasive-mosquito-species-aedes-aegypti-in-idaho/"}' href="https://adacounty.id.gov/weedpestmosquito/news/canyon-county-has-first-detection-of-invasive-mosquito-species-aedes-aegypti-in-idaho/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;first time in Idaho&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Now, an old residential neighborhood in Grand Junction, Colorado, has emerged as one of the latest frontiers for this troublesome mosquito.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The city, with a population of about 70,000, is the largest in Colorado west of the Continental Divide. In 2019, the local mosquito control district spotted one wayward Aedes aegypti in a trap. It was odd, but the mosquitoes had already been found in Moab, Utah, about 100 miles to the southwest. Moore, the district manager, figured they’d caught a hitchhiker and that the harsh Colorado climate would quickly eliminate the species.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“I concluded it was a one-off, and we don’t have to worry too much about this,” Moore said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="AssetEmbedWrapper-fkZDUs kHRAYC asset-embed"&gt;&lt;p class="CaptionWrapper-jYrTxZ byeLF caption AssetEmbedCaption-fyuOdR eXMqGf asset-embed__caption standard" data-testid="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;span class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE CaptionText-brNLzD deqABF imSbFE fGraOh caption__text"&gt;Tim Moore, district manager of Grand River Mosquito Control District, explains that managing a new invasive species of mosquito in Grand Junction has required the district to increase spending on new mosquito traps and staff.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE CaptionCredit-eowWKH deqABF kpqIso gxwcqg caption__credit"&gt;Photograph: Isabella Escobedo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixwFBVV95cUxPWm1BNENNU3Z2MFc1akpYc1VOOVVyYUdEY051VXQyTkE2QXNDeXUwY1QxN0JINnBkOTNuRXREQlNXNGpxb3IzTm9aY2N4cDB3NGQzazNscll0VjZURVFJM2dBNEl6b2x2T0tYZVNaVEJxNFdxaHlUNnNOZTFCQWttMWluVWQ3TkdNVEx6MTNuWXEtcFVaSE1CRHJUMGJBSVNFcTdhMjNzVmJHNzZVTEFiTGFDSWhLNHhHelE2TzlieVdBaS1nV25V</guid></item><item><title>为什么全世界的甲状腺癌病例都在增加？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20251114-why-are-thyroid-cancer-cases-increasing-across-the-world</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 kfxpiP"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;What's more, as thyroid cancers have increasingly been diagnosed at earlier stages, and treatment outcomes have improved, Vigneri says you would expect the number of people dying from thyroid cancer to fall. However, the death rate has remained stable at around 0.5 cases per 100,000 inhabitants, and there are signs that, at least in some countries, rates are increasing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-bc40c3a0-0 kXcvpr"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 jJmNMc"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/160xn/p0mgndhv.jpg.webp 160w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/240xn/p0mgndhv.jpg.webp 240w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/320xn/p0mgndhv.jpg.webp 320w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0mgndhv.jpg.webp 480w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/640xn/p0mgndhv.jpg.webp 640w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/800xn/p0mgndhv.jpg.webp 800w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1024xn/p0mgndhv.jpg.webp 1024w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1376xn/p0mgndhv.jpg.webp 1376w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1920xn/p0mgndhv.jpg.webp 1920w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0mgndhv.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Some researchers believe the increase in procedures with higher levels of ionising radiation such as CT scans could be contributing to the rise in rates (Credit: Getty Images)" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Some researchers believe the increase in procedures with higher levels of ionising radiation such as CT scans could be contributing to the rise in rates (Credit: Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;For instance, one study analysed more than 69,000 &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://academic.oup.com/jcem/article/105/6/1770/5804233" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;thyroid cancer patients&lt;/a&gt; diagnosed between 2000 to 2017 in California. The researchers found that both the number of people diagnosed, and the mortality rate increased over the time period. The increase was irrespective of tumour size and stage of the cancer, suggesting that there must be something else at play rather than simply improved diagnosis of extremely small tumours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In 2017, Kitahara and her team also &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2613728" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;examined the medical records&lt;/a&gt; of over 77,000 thyroid cancer patients diagnosed between 1974-2013. The results showed that, while most of the increase in cases was driven by small papillary tumours localised to the thyroid gland, there was also an increase in metastatic papillary cancers that had spread to other parts of the body. While deaths from thyroid cancer are rare, the study also showed these were increasing at a rate of 1.1% per year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"This suggested that there could be something else that could be driving the increase in these more aggressive tumours," says Kitahara.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxPT2tQWjFnb1BYc21zYWlSd3dCQk1tUG5PTXRHQzBOLXJWWjh4SjdrS2JhUlM3Y0F6c2RZelB3a1FSbmFMallKZlpUNDdrcHRhVlpvTGZjbks5S0czMzJQMGJPbzhLaWdaS0g0X3NJa2R2N0FtYVM0aDY4Q25KYTV2U3BuSldYbGdlWk10VWswLW9zcmxGTjhOQllOY1VBMEhUWEE</guid></item><item><title>心碎综合症：了解其症状、隐患以及医生如何治疗患者-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/broken-heart-syndrome-know-its-symptoms-hidden-risks-and-how-doctors-treat-the-suffering-patients/articleshow/125344946.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experiencing intense emotional pain, such as the loss of a loved one or sudden trauma, can feel overwhelming, but for some people it can also trigger a profound physical response in the heart. Medically referred to as Takotsubo syndrome or broken heart syndrome, this condition involves a sudden, reversible weakening of the heart’s left or right ventricle and often closely mimics the symptoms of a heart attack. Although initially considered rare and largely benign, recent research shows that broken heart syndrome can lead to serious cardiovascular complications if it is not recognised and appropriately managed. A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9821117/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;review published in the Journal of Clinical Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; highlights how stress hormones, hormone levels, and the brain-heart connection create measurable effects on cardiac function and overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why does stress affect the heart so strongly?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emerging research indicates that Takotsubo syndrome is frequently triggered by a sudden surge of stress hormones, which temporarily stun the heart muscle and impair its ability to pump efficiently. Activation of the sympathetic nervous system and the release of catecholamines are central features of this response. Other contributing factors include reduced oestrogen levels, particularly in post-menopausal women, altered brain-heart communication, and inflammatory processes involving cardiac immune cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; This intricate interaction between neurological, hormonal, and cardiovascular systems explains why both emotional and physical stressors can precipitate sudden ventricular dysfunction. Takotsubo syndrome demonstrates that the heart is sensitive not only to physical exertion but also to intense psychological stress, making emotional well-being a crucial factor in cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Silent Heart Attack Symptoms Women Often Miss | Spot the Warning Before It’s Too Late | Dr Rajeev Agrawal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Surges of stress hormones can temporarily weaken heart muscle.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Catecholamine release and sympathetic activation are central triggers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reduced oestrogen and inflammatory responses increase vulnerability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Emotional and physical stressors can both precipitate the condition.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How do doctors diagnose broken heart syndrome?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The symptoms of Takotsubo syndrome are often indistinguishable from those of a heart attack, including severe chest pain, shortness of breath, and changes in the electrocardiogram or elevated cardiac enzymes. However, patients typically do not have blocked coronary arteries on coronary angiography. Imaging techniques such as echocardiography or cardiac magnetic resonance can reveal the characteristic “apical ballooning” of the left ventricle, giving the condition its informal name of apical ballooning syndrome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Differentiating Takotsubo syndrome from acute coronary syndrome is essential because treatment approaches differ substantially. A recent illness, surgery, or intense emotional stress can raise suspicion for Takotsubo syndrome, guiding clinicians toward accurate diagnosis and appropriate management while avoiding unnecessary interventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Symptoms often mimic a heart attack, including chest pain and shortness of breath.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coronary arteries generally remain unobstructed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apical ballooning of the left ventricle is a hallmark feature on imaging.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Accurate diagnosis ensures correct and effective management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What are the hidden risks of broken heart syndrome?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although many patients recover fully, Takotsubo syndrome is not entirely harmless. Complications can include heart failure, cardiogenic shock, irregular heart rhythms, and, in rare cases, left ventricular rupture. Early complications occur in approximately twenty per cent of patients, and mortality rates can approach those seen in acute coronary syndrome. Women, especially those who are post-menopausal, are disproportionately affected, while physical stressors such as surgery or severe illness are nearly as common as emotional triggers. The wide spectrum of potential complications underscores the importance of recognising Takotsubo syndrome as a serious cardiovascular condition rather than a symbolic or purely emotional response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Takotsubo syndrome can lead to heart failure, cardiogenic shock, arrhythmias, and rare ventricular rupture.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Early complications occur in about twenty per cent of patients.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Women, particularly post-menopausal, are most at risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Physical stress can trigger the condition as frequently as emotional events.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How is broken heart syndrome managed and treated?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Management of Takotsubo syndrome primarily involves acute monitoring of cardiac function and treatment of any heart failure symptoms. Physicians may prescribe beta-blockers, angiotensin-converting enzyme inhibitors, or angiotensin receptor blockers based on the patient’s cardiac status and existing comorbidities. Because overactivation of the sympathetic nervous system is a central mechanism, treatment aims to support recovery while limiting additional stress on the heart. Long-term strategies often include stress-reduction techniques, lifestyle adjustments, and follow-up imaging to ensure that ventricular function returns to normal. Continued research into molecular mechanisms may allow for more targeted and precise therapies in the future, improving both recovery and prognosis for affected patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Acute care includes careful monitoring and symptom management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beta-blockers or angiotensin-converting enzyme inhibitors can support heart recovery.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stress-reduction strategies and lifestyle modifications are important for long-term health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Follow-up imaging confirms full recovery of ventricular function.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What remains unknown about broken heart syndrome?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite advances, many questions about Takotsubo syndrome remain unanswered. The precise interactions of the brain-heart axis, individual genetic susceptibility, and the reasons for recurrence are still under investigation. Some patients continue to experience persistent cardiac symptoms even after apparent recovery. Interestingly, Takotsubo syndrome can occasionally occur after intensely positive emotional events, a phenomenon sometimes referred to as “happy heart syndrome.” Ongoing research into inflammation, microvascular function, and molecular biomarkers may ultimately allow clinicians to predict susceptibility, anticipate complications, and develop interventions that are tailored to the unique pathways involved in this complex condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for informational purposes only and should not be considered medical advice. Please consult a healthcare professional before making any changes to your diet, medication, or lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/why-too-much-matcha-can-strain-your-liver-heart-and-nutrient-levels/articleshow/125344239.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Why too much matcha can strain your liver, heart and nutrient levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 09:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowJBVV95cUxPRU9ZaXJGOThneGVoUnljUlNobFlOZ2tISDcydTVZOG5fR1h3OTFUX1p3UmRhRzloOHNlSTlKVTNaeGFpNzZYaVJQelJIYVRRLUptOUUxd0FyVmNKNlhoaXZWVFdaZllTSHcxRU95OHFoMzZ0R0g3bzU2NTNoTEdkYTRMaUVOeWRzSWptWURQNV9jLUZMeUpiT0xwdnpLTnREbk9zcmx1ZU8yVnRfWHpzUVl6WkpnWHAtNnpZNDFPSFFrOTNVVEhGVnNUeWJBa01PZnNCT3hrY2NTV0M3eDF6TDNGYzBDamhUcUZfa1drVlM2NmJEcTJIZDREbmhoNmFDVjFHYVF0Sl9xRlVWNkUxY3hUN2c3VkJPZTdjNEpRX0FkSk3SAagCQVVfeXFMTkt0MTRJZ0FnRXI3bVdNdkljR1VZeWc4M2NkZ3lnWXludGZwd1FxcmJIU0FEUDZ2R2tUcVh2QkxPQTNtTTJkTzhCNm8tUGsxYWNmSEoyN3phMTNLYXhvdU8wMzRiWWhKOXA5SDRJVzVxRl9jelRlbURwZmlJOU9ScEpZWkJPZUlPUEpxWnQ4Ti1ySG5wWXJqMDNGLXJHSWI3cFpEdlhhVml1cndGNk5WYUt0dVlIQTF6WmdtNTNGYlVlbUYtTDhuazhyVFA4M21lTHhpQlMtNkxHcW90T3lqLUZmYlIzQ2tHLVl5UzRXa2tmR3lPU2tRd1A1eVdxS3RTOHZBLUxQalVtOFdIbGk3dGJBeVppQU5uM29qVWJBVjhGSGFTNkprZDQ</guid></item><item><title>9个医生批准的习惯，可以帮助自然降低患癌症的风险-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/9-doctor-approved-habits-that-can-help-reduce-the-risk-of-cancer-naturally/articleshow/125344389.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cancer rates continue to rise across the world, and India now sees more than 14 lakh new cases every year according to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pib.gov.in/PressReleasePage.aspx?PRID=2102729#:~:text=Introduction,lakhs%20in%202023%20in%20India." rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;ICMR’s 2023 report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. Many people feel helpless when they hear these numbers, but experts remind us that daily habits shape long-term health. As per &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.who.int/activities/preventing-cancer" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;data released by WHO,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; almost 30-50 percent of cancers could be prevented with steady lifestyle changes. This idea feels powerful because it puts control back in people’s hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors who work in preventive care say that simple shifts in food, sunlight, and movement create a strong defence inside the body. The goal is not perfection but consistency because small actions each day make the body more resilient. These habits, as per Dr Eric Berg, slow chronic inflammation, stabilise hormones, and support immunity, which are three key systems linked with cancer risk. When these systems stay balanced, the body handles stress better and repairs damage faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Cancer is curable if detected early: Signs to pay attention to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Eric Berg, in one of his preventive-health posts, highlighted several science-backed habits that reduce long-term cancer risk. Each point comes from commonly studied pathways like oxidative stress, insulin control, and immune strength. These habits go beyond the routine advice often heard and focus on the deeper mechanisms that keep cells healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Maintain healthy vitamin D levels&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Low vitamin D levels are linked to a higher risk of breast, colon, and prostate cancers in many observational studies, including research published by the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/about-cancer/causes-prevention/risk/diet/vitamin-d-fact-sheet#:~:text=Cancer%20risk.,the%20highest%20levels%20(22)." rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;National Cancer Institute&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. Vitamin D supports immune cells that detect abnormal cell growth. Safe sun exposure for 15-25 minutes a day, depending on the skin tone, helps maintain ideal levels. Foods like egg yolk and fatty fish add support, especially during winter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Try intermittent fasting&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intermittent fasting stabilises insulin and lowers chronic inflammation. A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10509423/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;2023 study in the NIH,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; showed that fasting triggers cellular cleanup called autophagy. This reduces damaged cells that may later turn cancerous. Starting with a 12-hour eating window is gentle and sustainable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Move toward a low-carb or keto pattern&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A low-carb diet keeps blood sugar stable and reduces insulin spikes. Cancer cells depend heavily on glucose for fuel. Several &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3267662/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;studies, including some from the NIH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, have shown that carbohydrate restriction may slow the growth environment for certain tumours. Even small changes like removing sugar-sweetened drinks help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Practice cold therapy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cold exposure activates brown fat and lowers inflammation. Early evidence suggests it improves mitochondrial health. Short cold showers or brief exposure to cooler temperatures boost circulation and reduce oxidative stress, which plays a role in cancer development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Cook smarter and add protective herbs&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cooking at high heat creates compounds like heterocyclic amines, which are linked to colorectal cancer. Using gentler methods like steaming or slow cooking reduces this risk. Herbs such as turmeric, rosemary, garlic, and ginger contain anti-inflammatory compounds that protect DNA from damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Choose &lt;keyword id="30652324" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="natural-anti-cancer-foods" source="keywords"&gt;natural anti-cancer foods&lt;/keyword&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cruciferous vegetables like broccoli and cabbage contain sulforaphane, which helps the body neutralise toxins. Berries offer antioxidants that reduce free-radical damage. Green tea brings catechins that support cell repair. Adding these foods daily strengthens the body's internal defence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Avoid iron utensils and unnecessary iron supplements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excess iron builds oxidative stress, which damages cells over time. People with already normal iron levels do not need iron supplements. Cooking in iron pans adds extra iron to food. Stainless steel or ceramic cookware prevents this overload.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Exercise for cellular health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regular exercise improves immune surveillance, which means the body spots abnormal cells faster. It also reduces insulin resistance. Aim for 30-45 minutes of steady movement like brisk walking, cycling, or yoga on most days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article shares general preventive information for educational purposes. It is not a substitute for medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before making changes to diet, supplements, or lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAJBVV95cUxOd1ZDRXNWS3REb3J2UGJlYUw3b0JiVTdQaHBJVFFxYTFEOEZIdFp6MGdRQ3NZbzlEa1IyWmlySHBiczBBbjY5M2R3OHF6SGJLcElZMHYxc1Z5RkRuREVKa0tFb1kySUY1YmphN3ZkU3pKdlotTGY5UElKc1BITGtsX1FtOHYxVVpvZEN2NlY1a0QyZFFMbjAwWnF5Vmd1ZXhOSm1BeGU2N3Z1ZGcySlZJVGlfVWNGcXdhWkE0MTdLa3luYjRtcjRoRkpGbzNuN3Yzd3hHWkc2d0xBWjdiSHhzWHJSazQyM0xpelU0ZFl6eUNhRXYzV3FVUThwS3NVQ1dkSTVMSw</guid></item><item><title>非洲疾控中心关于埃塞俄比亚南部地区金卡确诊马尔堡病毒病的声明-非洲疾控中心</title><link>https://africacdc.org/news-item/africa-cdc-statement-on-confirmed-marburg-virus-disease-in-jinka-southern-region-ethiopia/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="elementor-widget-container"&gt;
					
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Addis Ababa, Ethiopia, 15 November 2025 —&lt;/strong&gt; The Africa Centres for Disease Control and Prevention (Africa CDC) acknowledges the confirmation by the Federal Ministry of Health of Ethiopia and the Ethiopian Public Health Institute (EPHI) of an outbreak of Marburg virus disease (MVD) in Jinka, Southern Region.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As of 14 November 2025, Marburg virus disease (MVD) has been confirmed by the National Reference Laboratory.Further epidemiological investigations and laboratory analyses are underway, and the virus strain detected shows similarities to those previously identified in East Africa.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The initial alert of a suspected viral haemorrhagic fever was shared with Africa CDC on 12 November 2025.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Federal Ministry of Health, EPHI, and regional health authorities have activated response measures, including enhanced surveillance, field investigations, strengthened infection prevention and control, and community engagement efforts. Africa CDC commends their swift action and transparent communication, which have enabled early confirmation and containment efforts.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Africa CDC has been a long-standing partner of EPHI in strengthening Ethiopia’s molecular diagnostic and genomic surveillance capacity — critical capabilities that were immediately deployed in response to this outbreak. Through this collaboration, Africa CDC has provided genome-sequencing equipment, sequencing reagents, PCR detection kits (including Marburg-specific assays), and extensive training for laboratory personnel in genome sequencing, bioinformatics, biosafety, PPE use, and safe sample handling.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The core genomics facility at EPHI has been strengthened by Africa CDC, together with partners such as the Global Fund, WHO and the UK Health Security Agency, supporting rapid laboratory confirmation and enhancing Ethiopia’s overall outbreak readiness.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As a leading Ethiopian research institution, the Armauer Hansen Research Institute (AHRI) has also seen its research and genomics capacity significantly strengthened through Africa CDC’s support, including the provision of equipment, reagents and targeted training. AHRI is therefore well positioned to play a central role during this Marburg outbreak. This response presents a unique opportunity not only to improve care for affected communities but also to generate critical innovations in Marburg prevention, diagnostics and treatment.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To further strengthen coordination, Africa CDC and the Ministry of Health will integrate Marburg virus response efforts with ongoing mpox preparedness and surveillance. This joint approach is designed to optimise resources, accelerate early detection and reduce the risk of regional spread.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Africa CDC Director-General, H.E. Dr Jean Kaseya, will meet with the Minister of Health of Ethiopia to assess additional support needs and reinforce cross-border readiness with neighbouring countries. Africa CDC will continue to work closely with the Government of Ethiopia and partners to ensure a rapid, coordinated and effective response.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Further updates will be provided as more information becomes available.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;##&lt;/strong&gt;#&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Africa CDC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Africa Centres for Disease Control and Prevention (Africa CDC) is a public health agency of the African Union. It is autonomous and supports member states in strengthening health systems. It also helps improve disease surveillance, emergency response, and disease control. Learn more at: &lt;a href="http://www.africacdc.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;http://www.africacdc.org&lt;/a&gt; and connect with us on &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/14792760/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://x.com/AfricaCDC" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/africacdc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/AfricaCDC" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Media Contacts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Margaret Edwin&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Director of Communication and Public Information&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:EdwinM@africacdc.org" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EdwinM@africacdc.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Africa CDC</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 08:02:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxPX3lfMDBNaDRneHQwa2NQb2F2dXZwc1AyYWNCckp0X1JuZ2c4NkVBN19yRDMwME5tOGpabkZLT1hfMEF6Um5iRzBySk5GZnNsVFlwdjU2M2tuUGcwU0pITk05dHZQSE1ZemFLTDVRM0M3b2thZ0lseHFNZ3hneml6WG9MVUctWUYyZ0FVV1N0RDROUU5tX1g5OUpMdktOUjRONGp1M0laSmt0Q01SSE5lcFFHbEJoSm1lblR4NVkzaw</guid></item><item><title>不健康的肠道如何使您的更年期症状恶化-如何改变这种状况- Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://www.fitandwell.com/nutrition/how-an-unhealthy-gut-could-be-making-your-menopause-symptoms-worse-and-what-to-do-to-change-that</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p id="7eca01a1-2cc1-460c-9b67-eee8b2c4d48b"&gt;A healthy gut is crucial for the body to run well, affecting everything from immunity, sleep and mood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A rich, balanced community of gut microbiome is generally linked to resilience,” explains Dr Jenna Macciochi, director of science and innovation at &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=92X1626907&amp;amp;xcust=fitandwell_gb_7834516529124741839&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fancientandbrave.com%2F&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.fitandwell.com%2Fnutrition%2Fhow-an-unhealthy-gut-could-be-making-your-menopause-symptoms-worse-and-what-to-do-to-change-that" target="_blank" data-url="https://ancientandbrave.com/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="skimlinks" data-google-interstitial="false" data-placeholder-url="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=92X1626907&amp;amp;xcust=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fancientandbrave.com%2F&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.fitandwell.com%2Fnutrition%2Fhow-an-unhealthy-gut-could-be-making-your-menopause-symptoms-worse-and-what-to-do-to-change-that" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;Ancient + Brave&lt;/a&gt;, which sells gut health supplements, like &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.awin1.com/awclick.php?awinmid=54585&amp;amp;awinaffid=103504&amp;amp;clickref=fitandwell-gb-2597894065960855585&amp;amp;p=https%3A%2F%2Fancientandbrave.earth%2Fproducts%2Ftrue-biome" target="_blank" data-url="https://ancientandbrave.earth/products/true-biome" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="hawklinks" data-google-interstitial="false" data-placeholder-url="https://www.awin1.com/awclick.php?awinmid=54585&amp;amp;awinaffid=103504&amp;amp;clickref=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;p=https%3A%2F%2Fancientandbrave.earth%2Fproducts%2Ftrue-biome" data-merchant-name="Ancient + Brave" data-merchant-id="448939" data-merchant-network="AW" data-merchant-url="ancientandbrave.earth" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;True Biome&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="7eca01a1-2cc1-460c-9b67-eee8b2c4d48b-2"&gt;“It’s kind of like having lots of good players on a sports team—so no single species dominates or allows pathogens (disease-triggering micro-organisms) to take over in the body and make you sick.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.fitandwell.com/tag/menopause" data-auto-tag-linker="true" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.fitandwell.com/tag/menopause"&gt;menopause&lt;/a&gt; can impact the gut in a number of unwanted ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“During the menopausal transition, levels of the hormone estrogen decline and this can reduce the variety and types of bacteria that live in the gut,” says Macciochi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The change in estrogen can also negatively affect something called barrier integrity, which Macciochi explains “is how well the gut lining keeps the contents of the intestine, such as bacteria and toxins, separate from the bloodstream. Good integrity means a strong ‘wall’ with no gaps and this protects the body against infections and illnesses.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During menopause, women also produce fewer short-chain fatty acids (SCFAs). “These are chemical messengers that feed gut cells, keep the gut lining strong, and impact the immune system and metabolism,” says Macciochi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-CPw4NM7AkNkL67e8N2tdjn" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-CPw4NM7AkNkL67e8N2tdjn slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A drop in SCFAs can lead to inflammation and negative impacts on digestion, bowel regularity and nutrient absorption. It can also increase the risk of weight gain. Ultimately, this can have knock-on effects to common experiences of menopause, including mood, stress levels and sleep quality.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what you eat can contribute to better gut health, so if you’re going through, or approaching, the menopause, it pays to give your microbiome a fighting chance by including these four types of food in your diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-what-to-eat-to-improve-gut-health-during-menopause" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-what-to-eat-to-improve-gut-health-during-menopause"&gt;&lt;span&gt;What to eat to improve gut health during menopause&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;a id="elk-7026d531-0d82-4371-8759-f6c3b321fadd" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="high-fiber-vegetables-and-wholegrains-3"&gt;High-fiber vegetables and wholegrains&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check id="da04dfe1-2260-4912-b09d-d184c66cc8a2"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="inline-layout "&gt;&lt;div class="caption-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fiber in broccoli feeds beneficial microbes in your gut&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images / Tod Novak)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="6c711375-6daa-4c0d-a73f-a46afd89c201"&gt;“Fiber such as broccoli, lentils and oats acts as a prebiotic, meaning it feeds beneficial gut microbes,” says Macciochi. “When these microbes ferment fiber during the digestive process, they produce SCFAs that strengthen the gut lining, support immunity and help regulate blood sugar.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-e28a6f60-fb92-4d2a-a5fc-b61a3c5d070f" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="polyphenol-rich-foods-3"&gt;Polyphenol-rich foods&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check id="5b58e6ed-659b-415e-844a-57c3fde937e9"&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images / Nitas)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="64eeb3a6-6f7b-4474-a7fb-a706e5f34e2b"&gt;Blueberries, dark-skinned grapes, green tea, coffee, pomegranate and extra virgin olive oil are all rich in polyphenols. These are plant compounds that are full of antioxidants, nourish good gut health by feeding certain microbes and they have anti-inflammatory properties that protect the body against chronic diseases, says Macciochi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-de81c05e-2b4e-4c47-b5ed-359e7d2d7add" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="fermented-foods-3"&gt;Fermented foods&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check id="7e5a1223-de12-4aff-bfc8-c990a8b6dbbb"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="inline-layout "&gt;&lt;div class="caption-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greek yoghurt is a fermented food that introduces helpful live cultures to your gut&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images / fcafotodigital)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="06978600-db8a-4d30-938a-a934f5f46ee0"&gt;Eating fermented foods makes it easier for nutrients to be absorbed by breaking down natural sugars and starches in food before the digestive process begins. “Greek yogurt, kefir, kimchi and sauerkraut introduce helpful live cultures that can temporarily add to gut diversity and support digestion,” says Macciochi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-ceadbe34-6a4a-4be6-8eea-473223d90845" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="nuts-seeds-and-legumes-3"&gt;Nuts, seeds and legumes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check id="7ccc3ce4-216b-4e48-aef3-5c677e27114f"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="inline-layout "&gt;&lt;div class="caption-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nuts provide a mix of fiber, plant protein and minerals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images / eternalcreative)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="7ec0310e-d3b3-4afe-aaa7-19167a096203"&gt;“These provide a mix of fiber, plant protein and minerals that keep bowel movements regular, and help to stabilize blood glucose and energy levels,” says Macciochi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizgFBVV95cUxPdlhsV0dFNGdfX1hZbTNJZmdCLVU1TVgzdnZQZFFOMHQ0M2d6TXB2TTFtclhtRW5SaElYY2JyQUNnVS1HQVVTQlpqeUVRVEVDTF9tQ2tZUDFwOEpmNHlIUmlhWVI4a3Z2WGw4N0dUMy12LVo3NGxkMGkyUEZtTllaaUVIYmEyYVY1dFYwLUlKYk5lMTI3SkR2cFo4alhpZUlmMmNwQnpFTElUZVdYTEVndnUxYzNWaEVHeXZzUEl5OTVpVGg2dWpfUUpWV2hFZw</guid></item><item><title>埃塞俄比亚报告埃博拉表亲马尔堡首次爆发未接种疫苗疫情--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2025/11/14/marburg-virus-ethiopia/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BULUJMTEDRBSFFF4ZESMJ7SGAE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;At least nine people in southern Ethiopia have been infected with the deadly Marburg virus, a clinically similar cousin to Ebola, in the East African country’s first outbreak of the highly contagious disease, &lt;a href="https://www.afro.who.int/countries/ethiopia/news/ethiopia-confirms-first-outbreak-marburg-virus-disease" target="_blank"&gt;the World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt; said Friday. Ethiopia’s health ministry also confirmed the outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 06:31:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE11Ymo1TkpZZmNYdHBIRlZQblFITXVxUDhnUHhGeGlIQmxld2FJTDlEaHl0ekdmc1llbnpVY2VnaGI1OTcyWmE5TTl5VmNXNjVTS2tvalREa3FLWkNBc2Jvcm5zZUxzQ0F0bVh0TW45SlphMTk1eHZJUllGRQ</guid></item><item><title>夏威夷州应对第二例禽流感确诊病例-檀香山Star-Advertiser</title><link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2025/11/14/breaking-news/state-agencies-respond-to-2nd-confirmed-case-of-highly-pathogenic-avian-influenza/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-content" class="post col-12 col-md-11 clearfix"&gt;
                                &lt;div class="hsa-paywall"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three state agencies are on alert after a second case of highly pathogenic avian influenza was confirmed in a migratory duck, this time on Maui.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Offiicals said it is the first confirmed detection of H5N1 on Maui.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Northern pintail, or koloa mapu, was found along the Wailea shoreline and submitted to the U.S. Geological Survey’s National Wildlife Health Center-Honolulu Field Station, according to a joint news release today from the state Department of Land and Natural Resources, the Department of Health and the Department of Agriculture and Biosecurity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Samples were sent to the National Wildlife Health Center in Madison, Wis., where it tested positive for influenza H5, the release said. The National Veterinary Services Laboratories in Iowa later confirmed the bird was infected with the H5N1 virus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“H5N1 is a highly infectious and often lethal subtype of influenza A that primarily affects birds but can sometimes be transmitted to humans,” the release said. It was first detected in Hawaii in November 2024 in a backyard flock in Central Oahu and subsequently in a hybrid duck from the north shore of Oahu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Maui case follows last month’s confirmation of H5N1 in another koloa mapu found on the University of Hawaii’s Manoa campus on Oahu, the release said.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;div id="breaking-news-signup-form" class="email-form rounded my-3 px-4 py-3"&gt;
                &lt;div class="row"&gt;
                    &lt;div class="col-12 col-md-6 mb-2 mb-md-0 text-center text-md-start"&gt;
                        &lt;h6 class="fs-4 mt-0 mb-1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don't miss out on what's happening!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;
                        &lt;p class="email-form-blurb m-0"&gt;Stay in touch with breaking news, as it happens, conveniently in your email inbox. It's FREE!&lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    
                    
                &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year to date, the USGS has tested 77 birds for influenza, all of which have been negative except for the Maui koloa mapu. Given the data, the risk of infection to humans and poultry remains low and DOH does not recommend limiting outdoor activity, the release said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Routine influenza vaccines in humans do not protect against H5N1; officials said the best prevention is avoiding contact with sick or dead birds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The three state departments “continue coordinated monitoring of public health reports, poultry operations and wild bird populations for any signs of virus spread.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“During the Hawaiʻi migratory bird season, migratory birds may carry diseases to the islands, so the public should remain vigilant,” the release said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you encounter sick or dead birds such as waterfowl:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Avoid touching or handling wild birds, especially waterfowl or shorebirds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; If capture of a dead or sick bird is necessary for investigation or handling is necessary by wildlife professionals, use gloves, minimize contact and follow biosafety protocols.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; To report multiple or unusual illnesses in poultry, livestock or other wild birds or animals, contact the Department of Agriculture and Biosecurity’s Animal Industry Division at 808-483-7100, Monday to Friday from 7:45 a.m. to 4:30 p.m., or 808-837-8092 during nonbusiness hours and holidays. You may also e-mail HDOAIC@hawaii.gov.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information, visit &lt;a href="https://health.hawaii.gov/docd/disease_listing/avian-influenza/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://health.hawaii.gov/docd/disease_listing/avian-influenza/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;                                
                                
                                
                                                                
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Honolulu Star-Advertiser</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 06:00:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1AFBVV95cUxPMmZ2M1VmY1lVOVcyRk5JLWNIdkxGd0pQdjZBR3Itb01iSWY2T2ktSWRiR3laNVRiWGc1cy1IQmMwb1RTdHptaTRPTmR3VFQ2bVREY1JEclE4a0d2NmwzYndXeXo3czJZNlQ5YWROZXllS1ZlVE92THhIMXo5STZhTGkzdU8zaFRpdWFIWDlTNGFWTHRCTy1OMy1QV0RYQWtTU3hRLUNkRzdyUXRTbGRCUVluXzM5bzFUZTY5eG9MMkJKQzFkTnltc0hOV2RFc25RdDh1VA</guid></item><item><title>5种可能损害肾脏的常见药物及其替代品-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/5-types-of-medications-that-can-damage-the-kidneys-and-what-should-be-done-instead/articleshow/125321419.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kidneys quietly do a lot of heavy lifting, they filter waste, balance fluids, control blood pressure, and more. But sometimes, medicines meant to help us can backfire and harm these vital organs. In India, the burden of chronic kidney disease (CKD) is growing fast: according to a recent &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736%2825%2901853-7/fulltext" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study published in The Lancet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, about 138 million Indians are estimated to have CKD in 2023. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between 2018 and 2023, the prevalence among adults rose to approximately 16.4 %, up from about 11.2% a few years ago, as per a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39763170/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study published in the NIH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Don’t Ignore Silent Kidney Damage: How to Detect Issues Before It’s Too Late | Dr Sanjeev Bagai&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is important, not just because kidney disease is common, but because for many people, it's silent until things go badly wrong. Part of the problem is drug-induced damage. Certain medications can stress or injure the kidneys, especially if used long-term or without careful monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Here are six types of medicines that are known to potentially harm kidneys, how they do it, and what to watch out for.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Non-Steroidal Anti-Inflammatory Drugs (NSAIDs)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Painkillers like ibuprofen, naproxen, diclofenac, and other NSAIDs are widely used. While they ease pain, they also block the production of prostaglandins, molecules that help dilate blood vessels in the kidney, according to a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30281062/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study from NIH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. Without enough prostaglandins, kidney blood flow can drop, especially when someone is dehydrated or has low blood volume, leading to acute kidney injury. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long-term use can trigger chronic damage: NSAIDs may cause interstitial nephritis (inflammation in the kidney), papillary necrosis, or even gradual decline in kidney function. A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/iphr/fulltext/2021/53030/retrospective_pharmacovigilance_analysis_of.2.aspx" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;pharmacovigilance study in India&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; even linked extended NSAID use with chronic kidney disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr Umesh Gupta, Director Nephrology, Aakash Healthcare, said, "Nonsteroidal Anti-Inflammatory Drugs (NSAIDs), while useful for pain relief can damage the kidneys by reducing blood flow to the kidneys when taken regularly and in high doses. It is best to use them only when needed and at the lowest effective dose for the shortest time possible."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Risk factors: older age, dehydration, existing kidney disease, heart failure, or using other drugs that affect kidney perfusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tip: Use the lowest effective dose, for the shortest duration possible, and talk to a doctor if you need NSAIDs frequently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Aminoglycoside antibiotics&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aminoglycosides are a class of antibiotics (like gentamicin, tobramycin, amikacin) used for serious bacterial infections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;These drugs accumulate in the proximal tubule cells of the kidney. Over time, they generate reactive oxygen species (free radicals), &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/2043284/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;damaging those cells and causing necrosis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. Once the drug is stopped, kidney function often recovers, but not always completely, especially with higher cumulative doses or long therapy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Risk factors: dehydration, existing CKD, liver disease, low albumin, or when used together with other nephrotoxic drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tip: When aminoglycosides are necessary, clinicians often monitor drug levels, adjust dose, ensure good hydration, and avoid other harmful drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Vancomycin and other glycopeptides&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vancomycin is a powerful antibiotic often used to treat resistant bacterial infections. But it's not harmless: it has a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4892398/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;known risk of kidney toxicity,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; especially when used at high doses or combined with other nephrotoxins (like aminoglycosides).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mechanism isn’t always simple, sometimes the patient’s illness (for example, sepsis) also contributes, but vancomycin independently increases the risk of acute kidney injury. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Risk factors: high trough levels, prolonged therapy, and co-use of other kidney-stressing drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tip: Drug dosing needs precision, and kidney function should be monitored closely during therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Radiocontrast agents&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contrast dyes used in imaging (CT scans, angiography) can sometimes spark contrast-induced nephropathy. These agents can reduce kidney blood flow, generate oxidative stress, and cause direct tubular toxicity. This is especially risky if someone already has &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/2043284/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;impaired kidney function or is dehydrated&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Risk factors: diabetes, existing CKD, dehydration, repeated contrast exposures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tip: Before any diagnostic scan that uses dye, discuss your kidney health. Preventive measures include hydration, using the lowest contrast dose, and possibly alternative imaging strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="78"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Drugs that affect kidney hemodynamics (ACE Inhibitors / ARBs Combined with Other Risks)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="80"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;ACE inhibitors (like lisinopril) and ARBs (like losartan) are often life-saving drugs for hypertension, heart failure, and kidney disease, but under certain conditions, they can worsen kidney function transiently. These medicines dilate the efferent arteriole (part of the kidney’s blood filter), which lowers glomerular pressure. In most cases, that’s beneficial, but if combined with dehydration, NSAIDs, diuretics, or sudden drop in blood volume, it can contribute to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4975270/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;acute kidney injury&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="85"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although this kind of decline is often reversible, it requires close monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="87"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Adding to this Dr Gupta said, "ACE inhibitors and ARBs, such as lisinopril, enalapril, and ramipril, help regulate excessive blood pressure and protect the heart. They too can occasionally cause renal impairment, particularly if you are dehydrated or on other kidney-damaging medications. Diuretics drain excess fluid from the body and are often used to treat high blood pressure and edema. However, if not utilized properly, they can cause dehydration, putting stress on the kidneys and perhaps causing damage."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="89"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="90"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="91"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tip: Never stop these medicines abruptly, but always inform your doctor if you’re vomiting, dehydrated, or taking other high-risk drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="93"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="94"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What we need to know&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="95"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hidden risk in “safe” meds: Over-the-counter painkillers (NSAIDs) are often underestimated. People think they’re harmless, but over time and especially in vulnerable individuals, they can quietly erode kidney function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="98"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Synergy of harm: It’s not just one drug, the real damage often happens when multiple “almost safe” medicines interact (for example, NSAIDs + ACE inhibitors + diuretics).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="100"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A person on painkillers long-term may not even realise their kidneys are being stressed, because the early signs are subtle. Empowering patients with knowledge (especially in India, where self-medication is common) could prevent a lot of silent damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="102"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for educational purposes only and does not replace medical advice. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before changing or stopping any medication, especially if you have existing kidney issues or other health concerns.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="104"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="105"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="106"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 03:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwJBVV95cUxNOGRHUHhtRmF1bHdFV2V1Vi03U2EzbEx1R09XWHZsVUdmelQzV2RCQlU2NDNXUHcxUVRlYjZ3SUhNYzJRMGRhcVZPRUhBUV9oMFVJVy1tVzh3RGNwd2prazRzR3QxM21ub3pBWUFRX1I1SWwxU0trQkJCb192QXNGMVUxZGNlX2U4YWJLNGNxWUxHRnBpVmR4UE9Fa2UxOFY0SFpOSE4tbFNjSGxMRkQ0d3Zya05KbGN4RHVPblotaFh4T2hMS3pKZG9BNUtNTTkwTDBNMVM0eWJxOEttdktXUzQwV2s5cnFkNk1zemk4RUYyNW1OM3RPNzNKQlhhMk9kaE9lYmFoSTZCQ19MZ0J3</guid></item><item><title>高血压可导致无声脑损伤：医生分享保护技巧-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/hypertension-damages-the-brain-more-quickly-than-you-think/articleshow/125340690.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly half of Americans have hypertension, also known as high blood pressure. More than &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/drugs/special-features/high-blood-pressure-understanding-silent-killer" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;119 million US adults have high blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, according to the US Food &amp;amp; Drug Administration’s 2024 data. However, only one in four of those people has their condition under control. While many assume hypertension is harmless, the truth is far from it. A groundbreaking study has now found that hypertension damages the brain even before the fluctuations show up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new research from Weill Cornell Medicine found that &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/neuron/abstract/S0896-6273(25)00799-8" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;hypertension damages the brain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; days before blood pressure increases. These findings could reshape how doctors treat the condition. The preclinical findings are published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Neuron&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Surprisingly easy ways to protect your brain and prevent stroke&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Hypertension affects the brain much earlier than expected&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new preclinical study by Weill Cornell Medicine investigators found that hypertension impairs blood vessels, neurons, and white matter in the brain even before the condition causes a measurable rise in blood pressure. These findings help explain why hypertension is a major risk factor for developing cognitive disorders, such as vascular cognitive impairment and Alzheimer’s disease. The study also found that the condition may induce early gene expression changes in individual brain cells that could interfere with thinking and memory. These findings could pave the way for medications that both reduce blood pressure and prevent cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though people with hypertension have a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/JAHA.124.039849" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;1.2- to 1.5-fold higher risk of developing cognitive disorders&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; than others, the reason behind this wasn’t known. While many medications successfully lower high blood pressure, they have little or no effect on brain function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We found that the major cells responsible for cognitive impairment were affected just three days after inducing hypertension in mice—before blood pressure increased. The bottom line is that something beyond the dysregulation of blood pressure is involved,” senior author Dr Costantino Iadecola, director of the Feil Family Brain and Mind Research Institute, professor of neuroscience and Anne Parrish Titzell Professor of Neurology at Weill Cornell, said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Early cellular damage&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team, co-led by postdoctoral associate Dr Anthony Pacholko, used advanced single-cell technology to examine how hypertension affects different brain cell types at the molecular level. The researchers induced hypertension in mice using angiotensin, a hormone that raises blood pressure in humans. On the third day, they analysed the brain cells—this was even before blood pressure increased. When they checked again on day 42, the blood pressure was elevated and cognitive function had declined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;At day three, gene expression changed dramatically in endothelial cells lining blood vessels, interneurons regulating nerve signals, and oligodendrocytes that maintain myelin sheaths around nerve fibres. They also noticed premature ageing in endothelial cells, with reduced energy metabolism and higher senescence markers. They observed early signs of a weakened blood–brain barrier, which potentially allows harmful molecules into the brain while restricting nutrients. They also observed changes similar to patterns seen in Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The extent of the early alterations induced by hypertension was quite surprising. Understanding how hypertension affects the brain at the cellular and molecular levels during the earliest stages of the disease may provide clues to finding ways that can potentially block neurodegeneration,” Dr Pacholko said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to prevent brain damage from hypertension &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers tested losartan, an antihypertensive drug that inhibits angiotensin receptors. They found that the medication reversed early hypertension effects on endothelial cells and interneurons in mice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In some human studies, the data suggest that angiotensin receptor inhibitors may be more beneficial to cognitive health than other drugs that lower blood pressure,” Dr Iadecola said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Hypertension is a leading cause of damage to the heart and the kidneys, which can be prevented by antihypertensive drugs. So, independent of cognitive function, treating high blood pressure is a priority,” Dr Iadecola said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment, or before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 03:29:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7wFBVV95cUxPbjRYLW03aURJQndST0ZEbnBLVUcwLW5LV0xONm95QjV1N2tmNUU3eTlhbnN2dHViQmNGUHZoTmx4cVJEakFJVGduamVwSGtDVWFQSGlFTDFaam5Ic0QxVWFnQlBFSC1jNkZ4SlVSSktMWDY4d2ZzZnZmWmlQbk5mdkprNjB6Mm9Jem5qSzBRTG4xZXhRMXRSLTZrRGhfeWVRRkR3M21kSFBXYWRXTEw2YlI0WW1kYzBjWDFQRndpekZfOU9mR2lQVDRtM29HRXNBd1g3RGdTZjF1VnRsa3RPUmdfakgzNjZ1Z2hhanhodw</guid></item><item><title>科学家逆转小鼠肾脏损伤，下一步寄希望于人类- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/11/251114094525.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Serious injury to short-term kidney function, known as acute kidney injury (AKI), can be life-threatening and also raise the likelihood of developing permanent chronic kidney disease. AKI can occur after major stressors such as sepsis or heart surgery, and more than half of all intensive care patients experience it. No approved medications currently exist to treat this condition.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers at University of Utah Health (U of U Health) have discovered that fatty molecules called ceramides initiate AKI by damaging the mitochondria that supply energy to kidney cells. By using a backup drug candidate designed to alter how ceramides are processed, the team protected mitochondrial structure and prevented kidney injury in mice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We completely reversed the pathology of acute kidney injury by inactivating ceramides," says Scott Summers, PhD, distinguished professor and Chair of the Department of Nutrition and Integrative Physiology in the University of Utah College of Health and senior author on the study. "We were stunned -- not only did kidney function stay normal, but the mitochondria were unscathed," Summers says. "It was truly remarkable."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results are published in &lt;em&gt;Cell Metabolism&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ceramide spikes may serve as an early warning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier studies from the Summers lab showed that ceramides can harm organs such as the heart and liver. When the researchers measured ceramides in AKI models, they found a strong connection: levels rose sharply after injury in both mice and in human urine samples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Ceramide levels are very elevated in kidney injury," says Rebekah Nicholson, PhD, first author on the work, who completed the research as a graduate student in nutrition and integrative physiology at U of U Health and is now a postdoctoral fellow at the Arc Institute. "They go up quickly after damage to the kidneys, and they go up in relation to the severity of the injury. The worse the kidney injury is, the higher the ceramide levels will be."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These findings indicate that urinary ceramides could act as an early biomarker for AKI, giving clinicians a tool to identify vulnerable patients, including those preparing for heart surgery, before symptoms begin. "If patients are undergoing a procedure that we know puts them at high risk of AKI, then we can better predict whether or not they're actually going to have one," Nicholson says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Altering ceramide production protects kidney function&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team nearly eliminated kidney injury in a mouse model by modifying the genetic program that controls ceramide production. This change produced "super mice" that did not develop AKI even under conditions that typically cause severe damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers then tested a ceramide-lowering drug candidate created by Centaurus Therapeutics, a company co-founded by Summers. Mice treated ahead of time avoided kidney injury, maintained normal kidney function, remained active, and had kidneys that appeared close to normal under the microscope. Nicholson notes that their model places extreme stress on the kidneys, making it "really remarkable that mice were protected from the injury."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"These mice looked incredible," Summers adds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team found that ceramides harm mitochondria, the parts of the cell responsible for energy production. Damaged mitochondria in kidney cells become distorted and function poorly. Adjusting ceramide production, whether genetically or with the drug, kept mitochondria intact and working even under strain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potential for future therapies targeting mitochondrial health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summers explains that the compound used in this study is closely related to, but not identical to, the ceramide-lowering drug that has entered human clinical testing. He emphasizes that mouse results do not always predict human outcomes and that further research is needed to confirm safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We're thrilled by how protective this backup compound was, but it's still preclinical," Summers says. "We need to be cautious and do our due diligence to make sure this approach is truly safe before moving it into patients."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even so, the researchers are encouraged by the findings. If the results extend to people, the drug could potentially be administered ahead of time to individuals who face a high risk of AKI, including patients undergoing heart surgery, where about one quarter experience the condition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because the drug appears to work by maintaining mitochondrial health, the team believes that the approach may have relevance for other disorders linked to mitochondrial dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Mitochondrial problems show up in so many diseases -- heart failure, diabetes, fatty liver disease," Summers says. "So if we can truly restore mitochondrial health, the implications could be enormous."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results are published in Cell Metabolism as "Therapeutic Remodeling of the Ceramide Backbone Prevents Kidney Injury."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding and disclosures&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This work was supported by a NCRR Shared Instrument Grant, the Kidney Precision Medicine Project, and several branches of the National Institutes of Health, including the National Cancer Institute (P30CA042014, CA272529), the National Institute of Diabetes and Digestive and Kidney Diseases (DK115824, DK116888, DK116450, DK130296, DK108833, DK112826, 1F31DK134088 and 5T32DK091317), and the National Institute of General Medical Sciences (3R35GM131854 and 3R35GM131854-04S1). Additional support came from the Juvenile Diabetes Research Foundation (JDRF 3-SRA-2019-768-A-B and JDRF 3-SRA-2019-768-A-B to WLH), the Burroughs Wellcome Fund Postdoctoral Diversity Enrichment Program (1058616), the American Diabetes Association, the American Heart Association, the Margolis Foundation, and the University of Utah Diabetes and Metabolism Research Center. The authors state that the content is their responsibility and does not necessarily reflect the views of the National Institutes of Health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scott Summers and Jeremy Blitzer are co-founders and shareholders of Centaurus Therapeutics. Liping Wang is also a shareholder. DN and Blitzer are listed as inventors on US Patents 1177684, 11597715, and 11135207 licensed to Centaurus Therapeutics, Inc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 02:42:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE9oWm5CV1Z2OUprdS1hdTNGRnFicHRDZzhCS0UwWldJMUZvdnhfdmNNU200djl4N2gzN0FXMDJZVEpkYWZzRGJWbzlId20wczVIZGViTnR4TWR2MG9YRXpkeGtrdlpoZ3JSdXZaS2hCaw</guid></item><item><title>华盛顿州9个月内首例美国确诊的人类禽流感病例-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/11/14/human-bird-flu-washington-state/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3OFSDQ62I5BJ3MC3KSO7DNQ3FY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Health officials in Washington state said Friday they have confirmed the first U.S. human case of bird flu since February, with a strain that has previously been reported in animals but never before in humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 01:30:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOaGp0bkl2YThuQ1ljTjA4bHotU2EySUNnMEZOYmU2c21WVnRITUlJM3ZJQWhiR19qMFBEWGNBSVljLVpFcWNkUzFLWWhrck54c2NVS01rbGczQVZxMGZhOEF1eHVrVHNRUVh1WGVXRElmX1B5dnNLYnNGVVB2akpmVHEtemFDdzVM</guid></item><item><title>精神科医生在人脑中发现令人不安的发现后发出警报： “我花了三年时间改变自己的习惯” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/psychiatrist-sounds-alarm-disturbing-discovery-001500665.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When the topic is plastic pollution, it usually revolves around the ocean or wildlife. But a &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/connecting-neurons/202510/plastics-in-the-brain-what-science-is-revealing" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:report;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; from Psychology Today showed it's much closer to home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;St. George's University psychiatrist Dr. Elizabeth Ryznar used to view plastic as an ocean problem, but when the pandemic slowed life down, it became personal. She cooked more at home, hiked often, and noticed plastic piling up in her kitchen and along the trails.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"That made the issue personal, and I spent three years changing my own habits to be low-plastic," she told the publication. The change also motivated her to study plastics closely and learn how they impact human health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Scientists have detected microplastics and nanoplastics — the minuscule plastic bits from clothes, packaging, and tires — in human brains. They reported that these plastics move through the blood and trigger inflammation typical of brain illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Dr. Ryznar stated that the smaller particles can even reach the brain through the lungs and nose, using the same nerves people use to smell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Related studies on inhaled microplastic fibers and respiratory health have shown how common breathing plastic dust has become.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why is finding plastic in the brain concerning?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Plastic in the human brain — or in any part of the body — isn't normal. These studies turn plastic waste from an ecological issue into a human health crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There are tons of chemicals in plastics, such as bisphenol A, per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances, and phthalates, that make them sturdy and flexible. But these chemicals can disrupt hormones, triggering mood swings and slowing brain growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;These tiny plastics are just one of several environmental stressors that may affect mental and brain health. For example, some studies show how heat affects those who are on psychiatric medications. Others tie air pollution to children's brain development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Microplastics accumulate over time in both the environment and the human body. One plastic straw can last about two centuries, &lt;a href="https://www.wwf.org.au/blogs/the-lifecycle-of-plastics/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:according;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;according&lt;/a&gt; to WWF Australia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Meanwhile, a study published in the Journal of Hazardous Materials &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33130380/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:estimated;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;estimated&lt;/a&gt; that people take in up to five grams of microplastics weekly through water, food intake, and other sources.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's being done about plastic exposure?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Dr. Ryznar suggested making small daily choices to &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/journeys/use-less-plastic/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:cut plastic exposure;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;cut plastic exposure&lt;/a&gt;. Something as simple as heating food in glass containers or &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/actions/ditch-plastic-food-containers/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:skipping plastic cups;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;skipping plastic cups&lt;/a&gt; for hot drinks can help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Additionally, &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/actions/repurpose-containers-and-packaging/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:repurposing old packaging;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;repurposing old packaging&lt;/a&gt; and switching to sturdy, natural fabrics can help limit human exposure to microplastic fibers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She also noted that while personal effort counts, real change needs rules that limit single-use plastics and push for safer designs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/tech-newsletter/?recNQwYXjc9AHj69u" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for weekly updates on the latest innovations &lt;strong&gt;improving our lives&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;shaping our future&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxNenlaNFcwYlVqR0hWOFNuNzljcGNXQi1Lcmhmc3NqN2FtVzJNQ2F0WkV0b0VVSVdTdXplTmkyT195NkVsdURlNnVIRDZkZW9CQ0tZWktZOTJPSlE2YWxYRjVQMmVKRHFadm05U2s4T3hLb3ptcmtqaVAzem9JbTFTdmxaUXVEQ3g4REhTY2NVbUVxYi0yRlhCMll0UVhKQQ</guid></item><item><title>如何清洗超细纤维毛巾，让它们不会失去魔力-南方生活</title><link>https://www.southernliving.com/how-to-wash-microfiber-towels-11847617</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="southernliving-sc-page_1-0" class="comp southernliving-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Microfiber towels are one of the &lt;a href="https://www.southernliving.com/uses-for-microfiber-cloths-11722756" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;greatest products to use&lt;/a&gt; when cleaning your home. They leave behind &lt;a href="https://www.southernliving.com/why-your-windows-are-always-streaky-8757877" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;streak-free windows&lt;/a&gt;, pick up dust, and are ultrasoft to touch. But, like regular linens, they need to be cleaned every now and then to remove residue to keep working effectively.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Before you toss your microfiber towels in the wash with clothes or &lt;a href="https://www.southernliving.com/how-to-wash-towels-8667565" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;other towels&lt;/a&gt;, it's important to know the proper process for cleaning these essentials to keep the fibers intact. We spoke to several cleaning experts for their professional tips on how to wash microfiber towels the right way to keep from ruining them.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When it comes to cleaning your microfiber towels, there are two ways you can go about this: a simple toss in the washing machine or washing by hand. We've broken down the two process step by step so you know how to use both options.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-step-by-step-washing-machine"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block southernliving-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Step-By-Step: Washing Machine &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-startgroup mntl-sc-block-group--OL"&gt;
&lt;li id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-startgroup mntl-sc-block-group--LI"&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block southernliving-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Separate Microfiber Towels &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It may seem smart to wash your microfiber towels with other bath linens and bedding sheets to knock them all out at once, but microfiber towels need to be washed in their own load.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Because of the fiber material, microfiber towels are notorious for attracting lint that can come from other materials in the wash.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-startgroup mntl-sc-block-group--LI"&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block southernliving-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Add In a Gentle Cleaner &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Before running your cycle, you'll want to add in a gentle cleaner to remove dirt, grime, and residue from your microfiber towels. "Many commercial (grocery store) detergents contain harsh chemicals that degrade the towel fibers," says Ceconi. "We recommend using a gentle detergent that's concentrated, pH-neutral to protect fabric and skin, and cleans with natural detergent enzymes."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-startgroup mntl-sc-block-group--LI"&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block southernliving-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Run a Normal Cycle &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While you need to be more cautious about what's in your microfiber towel load and the cleaner you use, know that it's okay to run a normal setting for the actual wash. Ceconi recommends selecting a lukewarm setting for the wash to preserve your fibers.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block southernliving-sc-block-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-tips callout--bordered" data-text="Tip" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ceconi says it's extremely important to never wash your microfiber towels with chlorine bleach or fabric softener. He says chlorine bleach will damage and face your towels, while fabric softener doesn't soften your towels at all. "The truth is that fabric softeners don't soften fabric. Instead, they deposit a waxy coating over the fibers that damages your towels absorbency."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-step-by-step-handwashing"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block southernliving-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Step-By-Step: Handwashing &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-startgroup mntl-sc-block-group--OL"&gt;
&lt;li id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-startgroup mntl-sc-block-group--LI"&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block southernliving-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Prep Your Wash Solution &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To wash your microfiber towels, Cohoon says you will need a bucket or sink that is filled with warm water mixed with a few drops of gentle dish soap. "Avoid fabric softeners and bleach, as they can coat or break down the fibers," she says.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-startgroup mntl-sc-block-group--LI"&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block southernliving-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Soak &amp;amp; Agitate the Towels &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Next you will need to soak your towels in the solution for 10-15 minutes. Once the time is up, Cohoon says to gently rub them together with your hands to clean off the dirt, grime, and residue from your towels.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-startgroup mntl-sc-block-group--LI"&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block southernliving-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Rinse Thoroughly &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; After you've washed all your towels, drain your soapy water and then rinse each towel completely under running water until the soap suds are completely gone. Then, ring out the excess water.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-drying-dos-and-donts"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block southernliving-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Drying Dos And Don'ts  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Like washing your microfiber towels, you have two drying options: tossing in the drying machine or air drying. "Air drying is best for microfiber towels," Cohoon says. "All you need to do is hang each towel until they're fully dry, but them out of direct heat."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you have limited space or want your towels to dry faster, it is possible to run them through a drying cycle, but of course there are a few precautions. "Microfiber towels should be dried on as low a heat as possible to preserve the integrity of the fibers and the durability of the bindings/finishes on the towels," says Ceconi.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; But if you choose this method, there's one product Ceconi says you should never add to the dryer with your microfiber towels. "Also, as I mentioned above with fabric softener, never use dryer sheets. These work in essentially the same way as liquid fabric softener by depositing a waxy coating on your towels that will ruin their feel, look, and performance over time."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-microfiber-towel-storage-tips"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block southernliving-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Microfiber Towel Storage Tips &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Once your microfiber towels are clean, you'll want to store them properly so their fibers stay strong and effective. Here are a few storage tips to keep your microfiber towels in prime working condition:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Store in a cool, dry place.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep your towels in a ziplock bag to prevent moisture from building up.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Never put your towels in a humid or high-heat environment to prevent mold and mildew.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Don't store microfiber towels with other linens to prevent the transfer of lint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-when-to-replace-microfiber-towels"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block southernliving-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; When To Replace Microfiber Towels &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_63-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Like most things around the house, you'll need to &lt;a href="https://www.southernliving.com/home/cleaning-and-housekeeping/when-to-get-new-towels" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;replace your microfiber towels&lt;/a&gt; after an extended period of time. Once your microfiber towels begin to lose their softness or functionality, especially with water absorption, it's time for a fresh set. You'll also know it's time to swap out your microfiber towels when they begin to fray or pull apart.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_64-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block southernliving-sc-block-faq mntl-sc-block-universal-faq theme-expanded"&gt;&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-frequently-asked-questions-19b49ee7-f4c2-4842-8aac-abb7eaacab75"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__title"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;noscript id="universal-faq-noscript_1-0" class="comp universal-faq-noscript mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content mntl-accordion "&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item is-active" data-ordinal="1"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="-1" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_1-0-section-0"&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Can I wash microfiber towels with other laundry?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No, it's better to wash microfiber towels alone. If washed with other items, lint can transfer to them and be difficult to remove.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item is-active" data-ordinal="2"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="-1" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_2-0-section-1"&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;What temperature should I use to wash microfiber?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_2-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use lukewarm water to wash microfiber towels. This keeps the fibers intact while killing bacteria, without risking shrinking or damage from too much heat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item is-active" data-ordinal="3"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="-1" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_3-0-section-2"&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Can I use vinegar or baking soda when washing microfiber?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_3-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, you can use vinegar and baking soda to wash microfiber towels. They help remove odors and buildup naturally. Just be sure to avoid fabric softeners or harsh commercial products that can harm the material.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item is-active" data-ordinal="4"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="-1" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_4-0-section-3"&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;How do I get odors out of microfiber towels?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_4-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To eliminate odors from microfiber towels, add vinegar and baking soda to your wash. They effectively break down smells for fresh, clean towels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item is-active" data-ordinal="5"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="-1" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_5-0-section-4"&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;How often should microfiber towels be washed?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_5-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aim to wash your microfiber towels after each use or every three uses to keep them clean and in good condition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;noscript id="accordion-noscript_1-0" class="comp accordion-noscript mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Southern Living</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:55:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE9BNGdiWkRfdkl5VHhvRXF0aGZsZTJQS3ZIYTJrMV9hWW43VlRvZmNlU3lNdy1hMVlJZElvWldQQ1NKdFpFaUN5Y0V3alltcXJ2VXFYZmNSbDZKTkFCcTI2ZEU1SkUyTW9haEJ4OFY4NjNYNlY5Rm51LQ</guid></item><item><title>华盛顿居民感染了不同类型的禽流感-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/bird-flu-infection-washington-h5n5-b8921d13aa7d96330654a960f80453c3</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A Washington state resident has bird flu, and it’s a different type than what was seen in previous infections, state health officials said Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is the nation’s first human case of bird flu since February. The older adult with underlying health conditions remains hospitalized. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;State health officials &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/bird-flu-h5n1-poultry-human-case-5732c6be85f45c9f61a11a7aa2f0eef3"&gt;had announced&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; the preliminary bird flu diagnosis on Thursday. On Friday, they said it had been confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The person was infected with a bird flu called H5N5, state officials said. State and federal health officials said it appears to be the first known human infection with the H5N5 bird flu virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That version is not believed to be a greater threat to human health than the H5N1 virus behind a wave of 70 reported human infections in the U.S. in 2024 and 2025. Most of those have been mild illnesses in workers on dairy and poultry farms. &lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;“These viruses behave similarly,” said Richard Webby, a prominent flu researcher at St. Jude Children’s Research Hospital in Memphis, Tennessee. “My gut instinct is to consider it the same as H5N1 from a human health perspective.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention on Friday issued a similar statement that said no information would suggest “the risk to public health has increased as a result of this case.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The agency is awaiting a specimen from Washington to conduct additional testing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The distinction between H5N5 and H5N1 lies in a protein involved in releasing the virus from an infected cell and promoting spread to surrounding cells.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;“Think along the lines of different brands of car tires. They both do the same job, it’s just each is better tuned for specific conditions, which we don’t fully understand,” Webby wrote in an email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;H5N5 may have a different preference for which kind of birds it most readily infects, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Grays Harbor County resident, who has not been identified, has a backyard flock of domestic poultry that had been exposed to wild birds, health officials said. They believe the domestic poultry or wild birds are the most likely source of exposure, but say they are still investigating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNMm1zSlZGX2tMbG5aeFd3d0ctcWNYLXNDMUk0czlOeVdPN3ljV09GX3BpcVhVRkN1aTBMc3JKdU5oWkFVSkNvU0dIS0NDa0NpNTlySWNtS1FTODlWVE9SWkk4UjA4VFRzbkR1Y0dPcC1JVV80UTJWWXdESHVtWU9oNEIzRTRqa05ZRHp1QVNfbGt6ZjJmcUpWU2NR</guid></item><item><title>你不是疯子：凤凰城的蚊子今年变成了香蕉-凤凰城新时代</title><link>https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/news/phoenix-mosquito-populations-boom-heavy-rainfalls-40620890/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content"&gt;
									
&lt;p&gt;Every time you step outside, you pick up two or three bites. You’re swatting miniature pests left and right, and it seems like something is always buzzing in your ear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, you’re not crazy. The mosquitoes in Phoenix have been fucking awful this year.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Mosquito complaints made to the Maricopa County Vector Control Division, which monitors and deals with mosquito populations, have increased 400% compared to a year ago. In 2024, the county received about 1,500 complaints, division manager John Townsend told Phoenix New Times. This year, complaints have skyrocketed to 6,000 — so far.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class="fundraising-thermometer-block wp-block-vmg-fundraising-thermometer"&gt;
			&lt;div class="container"&gt;
				&lt;div class="fundraising-thermometer-wrapper"&gt;
											&lt;h2 class="fundraising-thermometer-headline"&gt;
							&lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When news happens, Phoenix New Times is there —&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Your support strengthens our coverage.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;						&lt;/h2&gt;
					
											&lt;p class="fundraising-thermometer-body"&gt;
							We’re aiming to raise $30,000 by December 31, so we can continue covering what matters most to you. If New Times matters to you, please take action and contribute today, so when news happens, our reporters can be there.						&lt;/p&gt;
					
											
					
					
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
					
								
					
&lt;p&gt;Townsend also said that while the Valley has typical mosquito complaint hotspots — particularly in the East Valley — complaints have come from all over the county this year. Vector Control sets traps to monitor mosquito activity at 850 sites across the Phoenix metro area and is finding a lot of mosquitoes where they usually are not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Typically, in the southeast Valley — Queen Creek, Chandler, Gilbert and Mesa, and areas with flood irrigation — we get a lot of mosquitoes and complaints because they’re irrigating their property every two weeks,” Townsend said. “This past month, it’s been more widespread. We have a lot of areas collecting water that normally don’t.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mosquito problem in Phoenix hasn’t been this bad in nearly a decade, he said. “The last time it was close to this activity was eight or nine years ago,” Townsend said, “when, later in the year, three different hurricanes came up from Mexico.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking, “Huh, we’ve had a lot of rain this year, too” — congrats, you’re on your way to earning a mosquito PhD. Phoenix’s mosquito situation was remarkably worse than usual this October because of all the rain the Valley got at the end of September.&lt;/p&gt;
				
									
					
&lt;p&gt;Those storms left standing water that settled all over the Valley, creating a perfect egg-laying environment for mosquitoes. The warm (but not excessively hot) temperatures in late October provided ideal conditions for those pesky buggers to thrive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Bite-Getty.jpg?w=1024" alt="a mosquito biting someone's skin" class="wp-image-40620893" srcset="https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Bite-Getty.jpg 2119w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Bite-Getty.jpg?resize=300,200 300w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Bite-Getty.jpg?resize=768,512 768w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Bite-Getty.jpg?resize=1024,683 1024w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Bite-Getty.jpg?resize=1536,1025 1536w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Bite-Getty.jpg?resize=2048,1367 2048w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Bite-Getty.jpg?resize=1019,680 1019w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Bite-Getty.jpg?resize=742,495 742w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Bite-Getty.jpg?resize=450,300 450w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Bite-Getty.jpg?resize=400,267 400w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Bite-Getty.jpg?resize=550,367 550w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Bite-Getty.jpg?resize=800,534 800w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Bite-Getty.jpg?resize=1200,801 1200w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Several different species of mosquito live in the Valley.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-meet-the-mosquitoes"&gt;Meet the mosquitoes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One type of mosquito has thrived more than others.&lt;/p&gt;
				
									
					
&lt;p&gt;More water in unusual places, like buckets or empty pots, means that floodwater mosquito populations have popped off. Thankfully, floodwater mosquitoes bite during the day and don’t carry diseases as much as other species in the Valley. These annoying, smaller insects are what experts consider to be a “nuisance mosquito,” Townsend said, ready to  “ruin your picnic or barbeque” but not your health. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But not all mosquitoes are created equal. Kelsey Lyberger, a mosquito ecology researcher at Arizona State University, said that the mosquito explosion has been diverse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Interestingly, it wasn’t just a single species,” Lyberger said. “We’re seeing a whole bunch of species, like floodwater species to Yellow Fever-carrying mosquitoes (Aedes aegypti), to a couple of Culex species, which transmit West Nile Virus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those species, unlike the floodwater mosquitoes, tend to live in and around more permanent bodies of water. Their activity has also increased substantially. The Valley has seen 46 cases of West Nile Virus this year, more than double the figure last year. In addition, one person tested positive last week for St. Louis Encephalitis, another disease carried by Culex mosquitoes.&lt;/p&gt;
				
									
					
&lt;p&gt;However, Lyberger isn’t too worried about the ongoing threat of those viruses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s late enough in the season that we don’t expect West Nile to be a big threat anymore,” she said. “Once those temperatures cool, those populations are going to drop off very quickly.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same pattern is expected with floodwater mosquitoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Hopefully, as the weather cools down, this floodwater mosquito activity will start to subside,” Townsend said. “We’re still seeing some in our traps, but not anything like what we were seeing a month ago.”&lt;/p&gt;
				
									
					
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Swarm-Getty.jpg?w=1024" alt="a swarm of mosquitoes in the sky" class="wp-image-40620894" srcset="https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Swarm-Getty.jpg 1999w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Swarm-Getty.jpg?resize=300,225 300w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Swarm-Getty.jpg?resize=768,576 768w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Swarm-Getty.jpg?resize=1024,768 1024w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Swarm-Getty.jpg?resize=1536,1153 1536w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Swarm-Getty.jpg?resize=906,680 906w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Swarm-Getty.jpg?resize=660,495 660w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Swarm-Getty.jpg?resize=400,300 400w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Swarm-Getty.jpg?resize=550,413 550w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Swarm-Getty.jpg?resize=800,600 800w, https://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/Mosquito-Swarm-Getty.jpg?resize=1200,900 1200w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;A swarm of mosquitoes.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-almost-over"&gt;Almost over?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a complicating factor, though: rainstorms are expected to grip the Phoenix metro area intermittently from Saturday until the following weekend. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mosquito survival — our human sanity — may depend on whether the moisture or the lower temperatures have a bigger effect on the bugs. The rain could lead to another wave of heightened mosquito activity, or the cooler temperatures could bring a drop. &lt;/p&gt;
				
									
					
&lt;p&gt;“I still think temperature is going to win out,” Lyberger said. “There might be a nice habitat, but I don’t expect to see any huge numbers in the following few weeks.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even when temperatures drop for winter, the current mosquito problem could come roaring back next spring. As both experts noted, mosquitoes can lay eggs that lay dormant for months — or, in some cases, a year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If it’s a relatively mild winter, I do think you’d see boosted spring populations,” Lyberger said. “But if it’s a cold winter and they die out, I would go back to baseline prediction.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to prevent another mosquito-pocalypse, Townsend has an easy tip to stop floodwater mosquito populations from running wild in your space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“After a rain, do yourself a favor and turn anything over in your backyard that’s holding water,” he said. “You’ll do yourself a favor by not having these mosquitoes bugging you all the time.”&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;
																									&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phoenix New Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 22:35:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxNTVFyMjBvU3dLaGp5RGpzcE9BM0hBTWVXUklSaUdvV19MZ2ZFN0pVR3BtNVFHT1FqQnNLd3ZFNVFPRnVWMUhNTmxvWWNNQmItd1dXWndrX1JMVThfQktZTFZscTF1X3lNdEZRQndHdGtvMWpDUXR3N25QXzRIdFNiY2FlaXRLZkVIdmpIS3RMaWozYzVSU3laeldMaUk</guid></item></channel></rss>