<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>借助YouTube和TikTok ，牙医正试图让Z世代出现--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2026/01/11/dentists-gen-z-skipping-dental-care/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="PPQGDSX4PVEALAHLYFIOZJQJOM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;When Usman Ahmad talks to Gen Z patients about going to the dentist, he makes one case: “It’s about the future.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3TABBN5KEZCQVCLJG5SNYHVY7Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;If they don’t want a missing tooth, or a marred smile, or difficulty eating later in life, he tells them, keep coming back to the dentist’s chair. Sometimes he uses TikTok or YouTube to help make his point, finding that young adults are more responsive to videos — showing how food builds up between teeth without flossing, for example, or how gingivitis inflames gums and where that can lead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:01:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQWE1jdGVtRHNidTl0M0tCdTdLbzRlRGNjOThRanFzUTNBUGs2T0k4RnpQYWhQMzhFVmNlZTJnelkwNjdwdmphRkN0ZWxPR050cFk3M19Nck1PcG5tV3A5d0hwb0FrNEU5ZUxDblUyYkQzVy1xeUpFS080ZDRDcjlWbjh6YXd6eGJoNEVBYk1R</guid></item><item><title>专家希望您采用的一种睡眠习惯--《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation/one-sleep-habit-experts-wish-you-would-adopt/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-content" class="article-content entry-content"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;“How did you sleep?” You might answer that question by weighing how many hours you slept or how often you woke up throughout the night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there is a third, often neglected, element of sleep to consider, experts say. It’s the consistency of your sleep schedule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleep consistency refers to how well you maintain the same bedtime and wake-up time, give or take 30 minutes — and that includes weekends, said Jean-Philippe Chaput, a professor of medicine at the University of Ottawa in Ontario.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research suggests that most adults in the United States do not have a consistent sleep schedule. And that may be harming their health, Chaput said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What the research indicates &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much of the science on the link between inconsistent sleep and poor health is based on observational studies, which can’t prove cause and effect. Their results are also often restricted by various limitations (including if the study was performed on a small number of people, or on people of only certain ages, ethnicities or occupations). It’s also difficult to accurately track people’s sleep patterns over months or years, and some studies define sleep consistency in different ways. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these limitations, scientists have found some patterns. Those who tend to deviate most from a consistent sleep schedule seem to be at higher risk of certain health conditions such as cardiovascular disease, obesity, mental health issues like depression and anxiety, and dementia. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a 2020 study, researchers analyzed the sleep patterns of nearly 2,000 adults aged 45 to 84 in the United States. They concluded that those with the most irregular sleep schedules were more than twice as likely to develop cardiovascular disease than those with more regular sleep patterns. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In another study published in 2024, researchers analyzed sleep data from more than 88,000 adults in the United Kingdom and assigned “sleep regularity” scores to all of them. Those who scored lowest, meaning they had the most irregular sleep schedules, were about 50% more likely to develop dementia than those who scored in the middle of the range. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists aren’t sure how frequent or how severe your sleep irregularity has to be to increase your health risk, said Soomi Lee, an associate professor of sleep and aging at Penn State. But the more you deviate from your typical sleep time — whether that’s within a 24-hour period or across weeks or months — the more the risks seem to increase, she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a large review of studies published in 2023, a group of sleep scientists concluded that there was enough evidence to recommend maintaining a regular sleep schedule to help protect metabolic, mental and cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why inconsistent sleep may put health at risk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers are still untangling why inconsistent sleep patterns might negatively affect health, but their leading theory has to do with the body’s circadian rhythm, Lee said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your circadian rhythm makes up a roughly 24-hour internal clock that governs your sleep-wake cycle as well as the ebbs and flows of your hormones, metabolism, cardiovascular function, immune system, appetite and mood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you stray from your typical sleep schedule, the bodily functions that rely on those rhythms are thrown off, too. For example, staying up late or sleeping in may affect your hormone levels. Cortisol, which regulates stress, could be released at odd times or in more erratic ways. This can increase stress and inflammation throughout the body that, over time, may affect cardiovascular or metabolic health, Chaput said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A misaligned circadian rhythm may also cause you to feel hungry outside of your regular mealtimes, said Dr. Andrew Varga, an associate professor of medicine at the Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai in New York City. That could lead you to eat at unusual hours, such as late at night, possibly resulting in digestive issues or, in the long run, weight gain or obesity, he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to keep sleep consistent &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With work, school, parenting demands and social obligations, it can be challenging to sleep consistently. But experts have some tips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="userMessagingInset" class="user-messaging animate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Setting an alarm to go off an hour before your bedtime every night can remind you that it’s time to start getting ready for sleep, Varga said. Doing something relaxing during that hour, such as reading or meditating, can help you wind down for bed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s also important to expose yourself to sunlight every morning — ideally for 20 to 30 minutes at the same time every day, said Dr. Nishay Chitkara, director of sleep medicine at NYC Health + Hospitals/Bellevue. While standing in front of a window can be beneficial, he said, it’s best to go outside to do this, even if it’s cloudy. A bright artificial indoor light, like a light therapy box, can help, too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Light is the main cue that regulates your circadian rhythm. When it hits your eyes in the morning, your body begins its countdown to later that evening — when it releases hormones telling your body it’s time to go to bed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may not feel exhausted from inconsistent sleep in the same way you might after a night of tossing and turning, Lee added. But try your best to stick with a sleep routine regardless. The more consistent you are, she said, the better your health will be in the long run. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;p id="userMessagingIn-story"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class="extended-byline"&gt;&lt;div class="single-byline"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story was originally published at nytimes.com. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/05/well/health-benefits-sleep-consistency.html" target="_blank"&gt;Read it here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:01:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxQZ2JPY0dsSGl4T0dwaTN4UFI1SE4zN1FWcWUxV29uYm5CQUdGdm9PX0VTaWRjTTVjcmNOdGxSZnZiUEdxMWhoQnROc2Y5dnpVeEhENTFJMEJ1dW43RlZRVVZ2VEE4dG9LSmpfZ0hLbHljdEk1MC0zOWZidjRXcTR3bzJNU28wQ2NpVE9TYzNQQU1ycEFBbE1QWTRB</guid></item><item><title>美国模仿丹麦的疫苗指南—但忘记了社会安全网- Salon.com</title><link>https://www.salon.com/2026/01/11/were-not-denmark-experts-react-to-childhood-vaccine-change/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="article__content page-article"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week, the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services changed its recommended childhood vaccine schedule to model that of Denmark. The new recommendation means &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2025/07/12/bonus-shots-the-benefits-of-vaccines-no-one-tells-you-about/"&gt;fewer vaccine recommendations&lt;/a&gt;. Health officials will continue to recommend the measles, mumps and rubella vaccines and those against polio, chickenpox and HPV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But now they are only recommending vaccinations against meningococcal disease, hepatitis B, and hepatitis A to children who broadly face a higher risk of infections. The move is not a surprise to health officials nationwide, as it was &lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2025/12/18/health/hhs-childhood-vaccine-changes"&gt;reported by CNN late last month&lt;/a&gt;. But it does reflect a bigger fallacy that has long surrounded the vaccine debate and been a talking point of anti-vaccine campaigns: if they do it in Europe, they can do it in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“A major fallacy is assuming that policies that work in one country will automatically work in another,” Josh Michaud, the associate director of global health and public health policy at KFF, told Salon. “European countries differ significantly from the U.S. in terms of demographics, health care systems, social safety nets, and public health infrastructure, all of which shape their policy choices.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Michaud said the U.S. has its own scientific institutions and experts who are capable of reviewing evidence and developing guidelines specific for the country. “Relying on guidelines developed elsewhere risks overlooking local conditions and realities that matter for effective public health policy,” Michaud said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michaud pointed out that when it comes to European comparisons, there is also “selected use” of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="right_quote"&gt;
&lt;p class="insert-quote"&gt;“Relying on guidelines developed elsewhere risks overlooking local conditions and realities that matter for effective public health policy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Many European countries have universal health coverage, stronger social welfare programs, and stricter gun laws than the U.S., yet those policies are rarely cited as models by officials here,” he said. “Instead, the focus has been narrowly placed on Denmark’s vaccine recommendations.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michaud said that experts across peer countries generally agree on “the underlying science of vaccine safety and efficacy.” It’s not that Denmark doesn’t recommend some vaccines because they’re not safe, but instead because of differences of the data and how that data is applied within the context of each country and its population.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/why-does-denmark-recommend-so-few-childhood-vaccines-danish-scientist-explains"&gt;Science&lt;/a&gt; spoke to Jens Lundgren, an infectious disease specialist at the Copenhagen University Hospital, who said vaccine schedules should be based on a population’s needs. For example, when asked about meningococcal diseases, Lundgren said it’s not really a “public health problem” in Denmark. “We feel that there are other vaccines that should be higher on the list at the moment, at least in the Danish context,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Start your day with essential news from Salon.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/newsletter?utm_source=onsite&amp;amp;utm_medium=organic&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crash-course-edit-signup" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Sign up for our free morning newsletter&lt;/a&gt;, Crash Course.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s problematic to base U.S. vaccine policy on simply copying another country,” Michaud said. “Vaccine decisions depend on factors that vary widely across nations, including health care delivery systems, insurance coverage, public health capacity, and national priorities.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He added Denmark is not a good model for the U.S. to follow because it is “an outlier among peer countries.” Of the countries that the HHS compared the U.S. to, Denmark is the only one to recommend vaccines against as few as 10 diseases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The American Academy of Pediatrics said the move from the HHS was “dangerous and unnecessary.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The United States is not Denmark, and there is no reason to impose the Danish immunization schedule on America’s families,” Dr. Andrew Racine, AAP’s president, said in a statement. “America is a unique country, and Denmark’s population, public health infrastructure, and disease-risk differ greatly from our own.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Racine said that the AAP will continue to publish its own childhood vaccine recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What concerns many public health experts is the confusion this will cause parents in America.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Reclassifying vaccines for six diseases from routine recommendations to “shared clinical decision-making” adds complexity for both providers and parents,” Michaud said. “Combined with mixed messaging from the CDC, clinicians and other groups, this change risks reducing vaccination rates and increasing cases of vaccine-preventable diseases.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="layout_template_wrapper read_more"&gt;
&lt;div class="red_white_box"&gt;
&lt;p class="red_box"&gt;Read more&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="white_box"&gt;about children’s health&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Salon.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:00:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNVDlFYkZYek1NYVFNZHFTcXYzTFprOWlwZEZYQjcyR1pxN1lIb2ZkTmtkRHJjd0NRZVBqQS1GVGRxTENqbVcxMVBOVmJUWkRCQ2xHTWpCR25EeDJIQmlzQWg5QkNvMGVOUS1wMlpHQ2FuM1hxU1NIVmxueGtSLVVrbnNCZ2RpMjlyamdOTmFaN0RqQVBFM3VR</guid></item><item><title>它是全国增长最快的零食之一。它还伴随着一个相关的风险。- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/protein-rich-snack-meat-sticks-carcinogen_l_6961173ee4b0120ab25d18a4</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have you gotten enough protein today? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;This question may have crossed your mind recently, as more and more Americans are becoming &lt;a href="https://www.foodandwine.com/american-protein-trend-11839783" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="obsessed with their intake of the macronutrient" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6961173ee4b0120ab25d18a4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.foodandwine.com/american-protein-trend-11839783" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;obsessed with their intake of the macronutrient&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The craze has ushered in a slew of new protein-packed products — from bars and powders to popcorns and pancake mixes — and has sent many of us scrambling to the meat department at our grocery store to get our fix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, one &lt;a href="https://www.cargill.com/doc/1432277049818/the-2025-protein-profile.pdf" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="recent study found" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6961173ee4b0120ab25d18a4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cargill.com/doc/1432277049818/the-2025-protein-profile.pdf" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;recent study found&lt;/a&gt; “U.S. meat consumption grew from 109 kg to 117 kg per capita between 2018 and 2023 and is projected to grow to 122 kg per capita in 2027.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;But should we be thinking twice about where our protein comes from and what dangers might be lurking if we jump mouth-first into a diet full of meat?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s what we — Raj Punjabi-Johnson and Noah Michelson, the hosts of &lt;a href="https://shows.acast.com/am-i-doing-it-wrong" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="HuffPost’s “Am I Doing It Wrong?” podcast" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6961173ee4b0120ab25d18a4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://shows.acast.com/am-i-doing-it-wrong" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;HuffPost’s “Am I Doing It Wrong?” podcast&lt;/a&gt; — asked &lt;a href="https://www.elizabethgdunn.com/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Elizabeth Dunn" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6961173ee4b0120ab25d18a4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.elizabethgdunn.com/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Elizabeth Dunn&lt;/a&gt;, a food journalist who’s written widely about nutrition, when she recently dropped by our studio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Press play to hear the full episode:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There definitely is this kind of perception online that if you’re going to live a high-protein life, that involves a lot of meat,” Dunn told us. “What you don’t hear talked about a lot in those contexts is the downsides to eating a lot of meat. The data is very, very clear — I mean, like decades of &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3712342/#:~:text=Introduction,)%2C2%20and%20certain%20cancers." target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="large-scale, reputable studies" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6961173ee4b0120ab25d18a4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3712342/#:~:text=Introduction,)%2C2%20and%20certain%20cancers." data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;large-scale, reputable studies&lt;/a&gt; that show that the higher in meat your diet is, the higher your chances are of getting cancer, of getting diabetes, of all-cause mortality — meaning just basically dying younger. So there really are pretty big health consequences to eating a very meat-heavy diet, especially a very red meat-heavy or processed meat-heavy diet.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s one popular protein-forward snack that especially concerns Dunn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One of the fastest growing snack categories right now is meat sticks,” she said. “Obviously, the protein trend is driving that, [and though] they also are very delicious, what really surprises me, especially because we’re in this very healthy, nutritious, conscious moment right now, is that people aren’t aware of the fact that processed meats are &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/questions-and-answers/item/cancer-carcinogenicity-of-the-consumption-of-red-meat-and-processed-meat" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="class one carcinogens — Group 1 carcinogens" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6961173ee4b0120ab25d18a4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.who.int/news-room/questions-and-answers/item/cancer-carcinogenicity-of-the-consumption-of-red-meat-and-processed-meat" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;class one carcinogens — Group 1 carcinogens&lt;/a&gt;. So that’s a World Health Organization classification, and it means that we know that they cause cancer in humans. So this is really something that I think more people should think about.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dunn noted that the average American doesn’t need to supplement their diet with extra protein because they’re probably already getting the recommended daily allowance in their meals. However, if we are looking for more protein, she urged us to get it from whole foods, rather than processed ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;She added that there’s protein in most foods, which means even people who don’t eat meat shouldn’t need to work too hard to get their daily needs met.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As long as you’re making a concerted effort as a vegetarian to eat a lot of different plants, like, you’re gonna get as much protein as you need,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michelson noted that “a cup of spinach ... has five grams of protein in it, a cup of raw peas has eight grams of protein ... wild rice has six grams of protein in a cup.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whole grains are also a “huge source of protein,” Dunn said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’m not just talking about quinoa — oats have a lot of protein in them, things like seeds, like hemp seeds and chia seeds, have a lot of protein ... It adds up a lot faster than you think.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;So if you’ve been anxious about not getting enough protein, worry not! You probably are, but if you want an extra boost, reach for whole foods — and maybe skip processed meats as a regular part of your diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;We also chatted with Dunn about why we’re wasting our time and money if we’re getting too much protein, which nutrient we should probably be focusing on instead of protein, and much more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Listen to the full episode above or &lt;a href="https://pod.link/1707391801" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="wherever you get your podcasts" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6961173ee4b0120ab25d18a4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://pod.link/1707391801" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;wherever you get your podcasts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question or need some help with something you’ve been doing wrong? Email us at AmIDoingItWrong@HuffPost.com, and we might investigate the topic in an upcoming episode.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 13:43:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxQaFdZdXdwckRLQ2NaMkJOampfeHRlaWM5NEx6eHBhTEVqZzBCSG9mdWNsTTFfYVFsYUJnbkxnSkRnMl8tb2VwdElvQ1M0dVlmdk9mU3Q2c0htU0RUVkwwU1BkcS1kck1mNWVNOHFsQUVHY1FHRFRqU0Q0YW5HSlptQ19VbVhBWnlsMlVIZGlfa3VxTDdTdXBKR0kydlNrVjBz0gGmAUFVX3lxTFBfaVJIWXRQR2VuYVREeHR1MVhmcnRyQ0ZXQzZIdG04cDc0QXNGMzlhdVQzYWw4LTYtZmpRbHdBWVlhNlIxQ2o0Q0F6OU1pWDFLVUFLWEV2aGhDc0l4R1NhTV9NNmtLeXM3M0NCMFhyWWU1eVhSV09FRmhoUTVBU0FKWGNsSWk3MlZwSXRvNlI2Z1VMeUotSXVHb2djbkQ2T0FVYmZiYlE</guid></item><item><title>“颠簸”是您需要尝试的步行趋势。原因如下。- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/rucking-walking-trend-benefits-goog_l_695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/topic/walking" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="Walking" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/topic/walking" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;Walking&lt;/a&gt; remains an accessible and &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/fitness/walking/why-is-walking-the-most-popular-form-of-exercise" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="popular exercise" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/fitness/walking/why-is-walking-the-most-popular-form-of-exercise" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;popular exercise&lt;/a&gt; for many reasons — you don’t need any fancy equipment, it’s good for your heart health, helps you sleep better, feel better and is a simple way to get your daily dose of fresh air. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of methods that can help keep your walks engaging and interesting. Lately, “rucking” ― a new walking trend ― has &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@awholelottahealth/video/7231784096458886443?q=rucking&amp;amp;t=1724702142428" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="picked up steam" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.tiktok.com/@awholelottahealth/video/7231784096458886443?q=rucking&amp;amp;t=1724702142428" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;picked up steam&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@mrs.space.cadet/video/7310036227011530014?q=rucking&amp;amp;t=1724702606810" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="social media" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.tiktok.com/@mrs.space.cadet/video/7310036227011530014?q=rucking&amp;amp;t=1724702606810" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;social media&lt;/a&gt; as a way to spice up your regular daily stroll.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Rucking is simply just walking with weight on your body ... weight on your back, technically,” said &lt;a href="https://6fd8eefb.streaklinks.com/CFZiojLu7kQ8TMseaQlpLD1e/https%3A%2F%2Fwww.linkedin.com%2Fin%2Fnichele%2F" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Nichele Cihlar," data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://6fd8eefb.streaklinks.com/CFZiojLu7kQ8TMseaQlpLD1e/https%3A%2F%2Fwww.linkedin.com%2Fin%2Fnichele%2F" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;Nichele Cihlar,&lt;/a&gt; the director of training at &lt;a href="https://go.skimresources.com/?id=38395X987171&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;xcust=695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.goruck.com%2F" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="GORUCK" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://go.skimresources.com/?id=38395X987171&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;xcust=695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.goruck.com%2F" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;GORUCK&lt;/a&gt;, a rucking gear company. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like regular walking, rucking is an accessible exercise — and you probably even have all of the necessary gear in your house right now. All you have to do is put on a weighted backpack or rucksack and start moving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s a low-impact exercise that is pretty much based on military training — think about how the military trains a lot for endurance, they do a fair amount of running, but they also have to carry a lot of heavy equipment, so that’s kind of how rucking started,” said &lt;a href="https://www.hss.edu/rehab-staff_Welch-Matthew.asp" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Mathew Welch" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.hss.edu/rehab-staff_Welch-Matthew.asp" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;Mathew Welch&lt;/a&gt;, an exercise physiologist at the Hospital for Special Surgery in New York.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s more, this exercise offers some extra health rewards on top of a regular walking regimen. Here’s what experts say you should know about rucking and how to try it out:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rucking adds resistance training to your walk, and has a host of other fitness benefits, too.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rucking brings more of a challenge to your daily walk, which is a good thing for someone who is looking to work their body in a new way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Physically, walking is awesome, but sometimes we want to amplify that, and the easy way to do that is adding weight,” Cihlar said. “Resistance training is key, especially as we age, in helping our bone health and our muscle growth because that naturally deteriorates as we get older, starting in our 30s.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rucking takes your walk from a cardio exercise to&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;cardio plus resistance training. It’s recommended that &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/10/12/well/move/strength-training-beginners-guide.html" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="you do 20 minutes of strength training" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/10/12/well/move/strength-training-beginners-guide.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;you do 20 minutes of strength training&lt;/a&gt; twice a week, but &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30458949/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="research shows that" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30458949/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;research shows that&lt;/a&gt; most people do not hit that minimum. Rucking can be one way to achieve that goal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rucking is also good for your cardiovascular endurance, Welch said. Specifically, rucking benefits your “cardiac output, it’s going to help with the efficiency of your heart pumping the blood out,” Welch explained. This can help lower your blood pressure and improve your heart rate, so it’s a win-win all around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s also good for your posture and back strength. “The ruck is kind of pulling you back, so it really forces you to maintain your posture,” Welch said, who added that it’s a good way to offset the hours and hours and hours of sitting you likely do every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Westend61 via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Westend61 via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Going for a walk with a weighted backpack or rucksack on your back is a good way to add resistance training to your walk.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plus, rucking is good for your mental health.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rucking is an exercise you do outdoors, and getting outside in itself is great for your mental health. According to &lt;a href="https://mhanational.org/surroundings/outdoors-nature" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Mental Health America" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://mhanational.org/surroundings/outdoors-nature" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;Mental Health America&lt;/a&gt;, getting outside is linked to lower levels of stress and a better mood overall. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2290997/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="the body produces vitamin D" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2290997/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;the body produces vitamin D&lt;/a&gt; when exposed to sunlight, which is important for bone health and can even help &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC9468237/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="curb depression and anxiety symptoms" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695fcff6e4b05f1e1aabecf4" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC9468237/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;curb depression and anxiety symptoms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You’re going to always say you never come back from a ruck in a bad mood. It gives you time to clear your head,” Cihlar said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are simple ways you can start rucking.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting rucking doesn’t have to be complicated. “What’s nice is you can literally start with a backpack you have in your closet and ... throw some magazines in it ... your water bottle,” Cihlar explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also get a rucksack and rucksack weights if you want to use something that is officially made for the sport. Both experts said a rucksack is preferable because it’s safer. A regular backpack can sit pretty low on your back, which can cause issues if you’re carrying around a heavy bag. If you do decide to opt for a backpack, just make sure it isn’t sagging too low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to how much weight you’ll want to carry on your back, that depends on your strength level and your size. “I always say start low because you can always grow from there,” Cihlar said. “You don’t want to start heavy and get discouraged.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you aren’t a frequent exerciser or weightlifter, starting with just 5 or 10 pounds and building on that is a good idea, she said. As for distance, start with a mile and see how you feel, Cihlar said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Now, if you’re someone that is regularly active and you lift weights, you could probably do a 20-pound plate, a 30-pound plate in your ruck,” Cihlar said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting with a mile is a good idea here, too, said Welch, but you can bump it up to a mile and a half or more if you don’t feel challenged. For an additional challenge, take your workout to hilly terrain, Welch added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the end, you can design your own rucking workout regimen to fit your workout goals and fitness level. You can start small with light weights and a short walk, or, if you’re up for it, take a heavier backpack on an incline walk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;As long as you listen to your body and know your limits, there’s no wrong way to start incorporating this exercise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The original version of this story was published on HuffPost at an earlier date.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:00:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPSVQyb0wzVVFyR1RqV1U0bG9Vbm1kb1VldEd4S2NwVXRvNV9SOTFwQlhyY3ZoVExsRTVCM2RrYjBwdjZyMHhQMmVXSzM0Y1d2MkVRRy1JVW5KTDhwMGVmNGswSlNJWW9BZjlxQmhkSFRKaFgyOWc4aEFtWHQ4UTY3elpuT081LXVyTFdud01hYjRGcENFUzQxatIBngFBVV95cUxPMTVXYVp5bi1nY0RwZlZzbk1mT0FxRDBzbk1MYlk0LXdVZWFCS0pfNHQ3UENOaWJLT3dTMVN0SXZoTDlOd0JYX3RYNzhvb0hkU3RsWmFvWkh2R1dOMFc3aHo1dWozRWRtRjFEb2t1QU5yNGphQXduYzAzQ3NqdExjUFhHcURKNGMyNGM1Q1phOWpKRkNmWUtNcnI0NGZydw</guid></item><item><title>缅因州西部医生被流感淹没： “完美风暴” -刘易斯顿太阳报​​ ​​​ ​​​</title><link>https://www.sunjournal.com/2026/01/11/western-maine-hospitals-and-doctors-swamped-by-flu-perfect-storms/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;

		
			&lt;figure class="post-thumbnail"&gt;

				&lt;img src="https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/42694587_20250804_CMMC-3_a45d3d.jpg?w=1200" class="attachment-newspack-featured-image size-newspack-featured-image wp-post-image" alt="" data-hero-candidate="1" fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" srcset="https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/42694587_20250804_CMMC-3_a45d3d.jpg 5712w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/42694587_20250804_CMMC-3_a45d3d.jpg?resize=300,200 300w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/42694587_20250804_CMMC-3_a45d3d.jpg?resize=768,512 768w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/42694587_20250804_CMMC-3_a45d3d.jpg?resize=1024,683 1024w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/42694587_20250804_CMMC-3_a45d3d.jpg?resize=1536,1024 1536w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/42694587_20250804_CMMC-3_a45d3d.jpg?resize=2048,1365 2048w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/42694587_20250804_CMMC-3_a45d3d.jpg?resize=1200,800 1200w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/42694587_20250804_CMMC-3_a45d3d.jpg?resize=2000,1333 2000w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/42694587_20250804_CMMC-3_a45d3d.jpg?resize=780,520 780w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/42694587_20250804_CMMC-3_a45d3d.jpg?resize=400,267 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;			&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;span&gt;The entrance to the Central Maine Medical Center emergency room in Lewiston is pictured in August. Experts say flu cases are continuing to rise in western Maine, causing more emergency room and acute care visits as doctors stretch to meet demand.(Libby Kamrowski Kenny/Staff Photographer)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
			
			&lt;/figure&gt;

		
		&lt;p&gt;Flu cases continue to rise in western Maine, causing more emergency room and acute care visits as doctors stretch to meet demand.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sunjournal.com/2025/11/25/california-nonprofit-can-acquire-central-maine-healthcare-in-lewiston-state-says/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Central Maine Healthcare&lt;/a&gt;, which owns Central Maine Medical Center in Lewiston as well as a variety of care facilities and physician practices, said Friday that the system is experiencing more hospital admissions and emergency and outpatient visits amid &lt;a href="https://www.centralmaine.com/2025/12/24/flu-cases-spiking-in-maine/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;the season’s earlier-than-usual surge&lt;/a&gt;. Experts say the region’s most common strain, Influenza A, H3N2, is typically more contagious and severe than other strains.&lt;/p&gt;


	
	


&lt;p&gt;Statewide, approximately &lt;a href="https://www.maine.gov/dhhs/mecdc/sites/maine.gov.dhhs.mecdc/files/MaineILIweek2553.pdf" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.maine.gov/dhhs/mecdc/sites/maine.gov.dhhs.mecdc/files/MaineILIweek2553.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;8% of doctor’s office visits&lt;/a&gt; last week were for influenza-like symptoms, according to the Maine Center for Disease Control and Prevention. This time last year, it was &lt;a href="https://www.maine.gov/dhhs/mecdc/sites/maine.gov.dhhs.mecdc/files/MaineILIweek2501.pdf" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.maine.gov/dhhs/mecdc/sites/maine.gov.dhhs.mecdc/files/MaineILIweek2501.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;less than 4%.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Maine’s doctors are experiencing the increased demand through appointment waitlists, call delays and staffing shortages, said Michael Stadnicki, a doctor at Central Maine Family Medicine in Lewiston.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Everyone that works in health care also has the ability to get sick,” Stadnicki said. “There’s more people on the team that are out, so less hands to answer phones, less people to get patients in rooms and be seen, and providers that may succumb to this as well.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Androscoggin County had 102 positive cases and 17 flu-related hospitalizations last week — the fourth highest in the state. York County had the most positive cases at 246, and Kennebec County had 82 cases but only one hospitalization.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There have been 10 deaths statewide from flu this season, including three in the last week.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Unlike COVID-19, experts say the flu comes on abruptly. A patient might feel fine one hour and be overcome with exhaustion and chills the next, making it easier for the virus to spread undetected in the day before symptoms start and the days after they end. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It’s typical to see an increase in the flu after the holidays, but this year’s spike began in the middle of December, causing “missed school time and holiday plan interruptions for our pediatric patients,” said Lara Walsh, medical director of MaineGeneral Pediatrics in Augusta.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While younger residents ages 5 to 24 are reporting the most positive cases, those 65 and older have had the most hospitalizations due to flu. Three long-term care facilities in Androscoggin County have reported outbreaks this season, and Stadnicki said that number could rise into February.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The flu seems to be more intense for people this year, especially for folks that have underlying vulnerabilities like heart disease or COPD, or are taking some medications that might suppress their immune system,” said Amy Madden, medical director for HealthReach, which operates community health clinics across central Maine. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Not a great time,” she added. “Get your flu shot.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This year’s vaccine protects against three main seasonal flu viruses. While there’s a slight mismatch in the vaccine due to viral mutation, experts say it still offers strong protection against severe illness and hospitalization.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;At the same time, vaccine fatigue and hesitancy are on the rise nationwide. Coupled with less exposure to common colds during the pandemic, Stadnicki says it’s become more difficult for people to naturally fight the flu.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt; “I think this really is one of those culmination of perfect storms: ‘I haven’t had natural colds and flu in a handful of years,’ maybe someone’s skipping the vaccine this year or last year or both, and now we’re starting to finally mix more and more,” he said. “So you’re definitely getting hit.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Express care facilities in central and western Maine report high numbers of patients with flu or flu-like symptoms. Jason Brown, senior medical director of MaineGeneral Primary Care, said staff is working to meet increased demand for same-day visits.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Madden said HealthReach clinics are seeing more patients with acute onset of respiratory symptoms and those who say they have been sick at home for a week and are “just not getting better.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Patients who already have the flu are advised to rest, hydrate, stay home and speak to their primary care doctor about medication to treat symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But prevention is the best tool to fight the flu, experts say. People should regularly wash their hands, avoid touching their faces and support their immune systems through adequate sleep, exercise and a balanced diet. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“You don’t want to miss living your life,” Stadnicki said. “So whether it’s a vacation, a get-together, a night out, anything that anyone’s looking forward to — if you don’t do the right things to mitigate your risk, you might miss something that you actually want to do because you don’t feel well enough to do it.”&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

	

	
			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>​​Lewiston Sun Journal​​ ​​​ ​​​</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxNSTc2b0RvbGNoeDJfczFSQVN2UEZCbUZ0bU1EamIwSnQyWFpfeGc2WVRGZUdCX19HN29Nb0hoY2wtS1ZPZEZHUkFjVlZoVm5iMk43cE5iVWZ0MWZtYVZfaXZBd3dIbnBFNlVhdG5CUG8xZkRYbl9id0RLTUhIa2VSV2dCd3FfUV8wV1diTTd5NVEyNGl0WTBVcTFuaGljR3RLbXdJNjdORQ</guid></item><item><title>难以集中注意力？科学说这个简单的习惯真的有效- Ynetnews</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/health_science/article/b19tatxhbg</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="ArticleHeaderComponent" class="ArticleHeaderEngComponent1280 selectableShareable for-print" role="header" aria-label="article header"&gt;&lt;p class="mainTitleWrapper"&gt;&lt;h1 class="mainTitle"&gt;Struggling to focus? Science says this simple habit really works&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="subTitleWrapper"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span disabled class="subTitle" contenteditable="false"&gt;A major new study finds physical activity significantly improves concentration; here is why exercise is critical for attention, when to work out for real gains and which workouts work best — spoiler: not running&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 03:01:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE5sQ0pYS0hLcEZDUjVHSVFPOS1nZDZpaUZBVzAzVHA5WlNxTmdfcVp5X2NGMkhNMjlHV0JZMFo2SXoxVkpfY3l3VnI0dzFsVmpFMGlvMkNxOXJxaUgzTC1kelVUaFBnSk9Ha3c</guid></item><item><title>亲爱的Annie ：人们称我为癌症“幸存者” ，但我很沮丧，不想只是克服它- OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/advice/2026/01/dear-annie-people-call-me-a-cancer-survivor-but-im-depressed-and-dont-want-to-just-get-over-it.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZAPLZQ6ZG5FCNMB2MPC4AVT44A"&gt;Dear Annie: I was diagnosed with breast cancer a few months ago. I’ve been through surgery and radiation treatments. According to the oncologists, I should now consider myself a “survivor.” Since I have scars, I’m taking medication for the next 10 years that has potentially really bad side effects, and the chance of reoccurrence is a definite possibility, I don’t feel like a “survivor.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XD4BJ2HF3FBZ5J2CPP5JQHI7O4"&gt; I readily admit that I’m depressed. I maintain that this is a perfectly reasonable reaction to something bad that has upended and changed my whole life for the foreseeable future. I’m not suicidal, and although some mornings are hard, I get up every day, shower, brush my hair and teeth and maintain my usual schedule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XERLV72NB5EBJH7PYWHXBBWHNQ"&gt; The worst thing to me about cancer is that I can’t talk to anyone because I’ve gone from an actual person with thoughts and interests to people only wanting to know about the cancer. It’s all anyone asks about. That being the case, I tried to talk to people about how I feel, but the word “depressed” freaks people out more than “cancer.” Now I just say I’m fine or OK to make others feel comfortable, which applies to my doctors as well. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EVCETBQZUBDAVCVRLFHY22F5KE"&gt; I don’t need medication, and I tried online and in-person group discussions a few times, and they aren’t for me. I’ve noticed the same thing with people who lose a loved one or have something else bad happen -- they aren’t allowed to be depressed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4KTRIQBNONECLLFFZOFPZ2XSEA"&gt; When did it become shameful and something that needs to be fixed when people have a true human emotion to events? Sad things should understandably make us sad -- and maybe depressed? Please note, I’m not talking about people with real diagnosed clinical depression or other mental issues. -- Sad “Survivor”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NSUUG75AIVF2RC2CHTH3J7C6CE"&gt; Dear Sad “Survivor”: The word “survivor” may sound triumphant, yes, but it doesn’t cancel out the fear, pain and lifelong change you’ve endured to get here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XBLJEFBKRFHXZCPE2QWRGL3XAE"&gt; It is a victory to be where you are today, and there’s nothing troubling about feeling conflicted. What is troubling is feeling you have to hide it -- especially from your doctors, who need the full picture, whether it’s pretty or not. You’re allowed to say, “I’m getting through it, but it’s still hard,” and you deserve people in your corner who can hear that without panicking or minimizing it, no matter how uncomfortable it may make them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AKRN73MG2VE67LXA5ZZLBRXBWA"&gt; Healing doesn’t happen overnight. Give yourself permission to feel whatever comes and ask honestly for the support you need. A survivor isn’t someone who feels strong all the time; it’s someone who keeps going despite hardship. By that measure, you absolutely are one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:SFE3ARRPA5AV7LDCAUW5LN3ZYY" data-fusion-component="SFE3ARRPA5AV7LDCAUW5LN3ZYY"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:SFE3ARRPA5AV7LDCAUW5LN3ZYY" data-fusion-component="SFE3ARRPA5AV7LDCAUW5LN3ZYY"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KBS5BB2UAFFXZAS3VFHZOZ5FEI"&gt;Dear Annie: After 15 years, my wife says she is filing for divorce. I’m disabled and don’t drive. I work part time and receive disability money. My wife has always helped me get to and from work because I don’t drive myself, and she also handles our bills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YY5ND5DMORFBBCNY37KUMJE2JM"&gt; I still love her, and I need to know why she has become so bitter toward me. And why did she wait till now, after I sank so much money into this life we’ve been building? What changed? -- Stunned Spouse&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LWPUFL55R5HGLFOQWTESK55EQE"&gt; Dear Stunned Spouse: I’m so sorry. The end of a marriage is always sad, but when you don’t see it coming, it can feel especially blindsiding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4XDI4BKEQBCCLNTPVGL63RHRTE"&gt; Perhaps the question isn’t what suddenly changed but what has built up over a long time. From what you describe, your wife has carried a lot of the day-to-day -- transportation, paying bills, keeping everything afloat -- which can wear a person down. That doesn’t mean this is your fault, but it might explain some of the “bitterness” you’ve picked up on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="E7SMOALE6JECLG2L3WDDCOEMCU"&gt; If she’s willing, ask for an honest conversation. You might not be able to change her mind or salvage the relationship, but getting some answers can help you at least make sense of its ending.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4CW6RMWCIVCHPAVGLW7QR4VF5Q"&gt; In the meantime, focus on building independence where you can -- transportation alternatives, financial management, legal advice. It’s important to start planning how you’ll take care of and protect yourself going forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3NZ6WOLDINBPHLN7MMXO3DMGXU"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Send your questions for Annie Lane to &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:dearannie@creators.com"&gt;&lt;i&gt;dearannie@creators.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6ECHFSPXGNGLHONECDZRWKCEIY"&gt;COPYRIGHT 2023 &lt;a href="http://creators.com/"&gt;CREATORS.COM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2AFBVV95cUxQR2VaZW8zOENZam02Y2IzamFjS0M0Z0Uyc0VBV0JHNjc3b19qdWpsSFR6bFQ3X1NwZkw5ZXhYRDJodXY3dGJFb3JRNnBXT3FYRUpkbWd3Z1owV0IzTm5MdjdQYW5wUVJ6dk9VdncycXlRVGpuSUxYYnVJRmphem9OTUhQbnNQYjI5WGlqZVZsNzNYSzhubTl5enNyTllFMUhNZ0ktbUgyTjc2Rkg0T1ZOSlZGX0RaR2xnamFfams2U0I0TnA4azNid3pJemVHUnN1M25zWlJobmjSAewBQVVfeXFMTW5uLUdCZjdUTFE2WjhnbU1OcV9KSHlzeUIzQ0xqRGZlLUdQSms1WVVfLU5qb1pvWUZIa2pFcFJvYTM2a252bW9wNDB1ZEphTTdoNVA4YW5fS1ZTclNzOWhvTkdTcnpqVDR4Qlh5LWNTTnVRTkJaMkFKU3oyR0xZSUl6SzhKNnd0WXQ3cndETFJpbzk2d2IwNWdEYjVLUzRnc01BNWZjVnc5VGVZTS1RWGFyMnE5c1BOTlFBbVVHOVFIaFR0czhFX2dncWJGbFBBei1qQkotUlZSUXF4aHg3UkpBTVB0dEFEaG1NeEU</guid></item><item><title>加拿大神秘脑部疾病之战-英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c623r47d67lo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;'The answer cannot be nothing': The battle over Canada's mystery brain disease&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 ciiGlA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 kdBCdE"&gt;Joel Gunter,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 eDNgSC"&gt;senior international reporter, New Brunswick&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-9 keGieE"&gt;and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-1" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 ciiGlA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 kdBCdE"&gt;Nadine Yousif,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-1-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 eDNgSC"&gt;senior Canada reporter, New Brunswick&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5804/live/de44b020-ed77-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC Graphic showing a photograph of Dr Marerro against a stylised black, white and yellow background. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;BBC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;b id="five-hundred-people-in-a-small-canadian-province-were-diagnosed-with-a-mystery-brain-disease.-what-would-it-mean-for-the-patients-if-the-disease-was-never-real?" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;Five hundred people in a small Canadian province were diagnosed with a mystery brain disease. What would it mean for the patients if the disease was never real?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In early 2019, officials at a hospital in the small Canadian province of New Brunswick noticed that two patients had contracted an extremely rare brain condition known as Creutzfeldt-Jakob Disease, or CJD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;CJD is both fatal and potentially contagious, so a group of experts was quickly assembled to investigate. Fortunately for New Brunswick, the disease didn't spread. But the story didn't end there. In fact, it was just beginning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Among the experts was Alier Marrero, a soft-spoken, Cuban-born neurologist who had been working in the province for about six years. Marrero would share some worrying information with the other members of the group. He had been seeing patients with unexplained CJD-like symptoms for several years, he said, including young people who showed signs of a rapidly progressing dementia. The number of cases was already more than 20, Marrero said, and several patients had already died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Because of the apparent similarity to CJD, Marrero had been reporting these cases to Canada's Creutzfeldt-Jakob Disease Surveillance System, or CJDSS. But the results had been coming back negative. Marrero was stumped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;More worrying still, he was seeing a dizzying array of symptoms among the patients, according to his notes. There were cases of dementia, weight loss, unsteadiness, jerking movements and facial twitches. There were patients with spasms, visions, limb pain, muscle atrophy, dry skin and hair loss. Many said they were suffering with both insomnia and waking hallucinations. Patients reported excessive sweating and excessive drooling. Several exhibited Capgras Delusion, which causes someone to believe that a person close to them has been replaced by an identical-looking imposter. Others appeared to lose the ability to speak. One patient would report that she had forgotten how to write the letter Q.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero ordered test after test. But he was at a loss. "I just kept seeing new patients, I kept documenting new cases, and I kept seeing new people dying," he recalled. "And an image of a cluster became more clear."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Many of the cluster patients believe industrial poisoning has affected New Brunswick's environment. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Over the coming months, Marrero and the CJDSS scientists began to suspect that instead of a small cluster of CJD patients, the province of New Brunswick might have on its hands a much larger cluster of people suffering from a completely unknown brain disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Over the next five years, Marrero's cluster would balloon from 20 to an astonishing 500. But there came no scientific breakthrough, no new understanding of neurology, no expensive new treatments. Instead, last year, a bombshell research paper authored by several Canadian neurologists and neuroscientists concluded that there was in fact no mystery disease, and that the patients had all likely suffered from previously known neurological, medical, or psychiatric conditions. The New Brunswick cluster was, one of the paper's authors told the BBC, a "house of cards".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;To report this story, the BBC spent time with Marrero and spoke to a dozen of his patients or their relatives — some of whom are telling their story for the first time — as well as key scientists, experts, and government officials, and reviewed hundreds of pages of internal emails and documents obtained by freedom of information requests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;We can reveal that at least one cluster patient has now opted for death via medical assistance in dying — legal in Canada since 2016. The diagnosis on the death certificate, according to the doctor who signed it off, was "degenerative neurological condition of unknown cause". At least one other cluster patient is currently considering assisted dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The research paper published last year could have marked the end of a strange chapter in Canadian science. Except, hundreds of the patients disagree. Defiant, fiercely loyal to Marrero, and backed by passionate patient advocates, they argue that the paper is flawed and reject any notion that the cluster might not be real.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Many believe instead that they have been poisoned by an industrial environmental toxin, and that the government of New Brunswick has conspired against them to cover it up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I'm not a conspiracy theorist type person, at all, but I honestly think it's financially motivated," said Jillian Lucas, one of the patients. "There's all these different levels."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Lucas first met Marrero back in early 2020, after her stepfather, Derek Cuthbertson, an accountant and military veteran, began experiencing cognitive and behavioural problems including sudden rage and loss of empathy. He was referred to Marrero, who ordered a battery of tests but was unable to explain his symptoms. Cuthbertson became one of the early cluster patients — the so-called "original 48".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Lucas had just gone through a divorce and suffered a bad concussion, and she moved back in with her mother and Cuthbertson in their rural community near the city of Moncton. Soon she began experiencing her own symptoms and went to see Marrero for herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"He ran so many tests, so much blood work and scans and spinal taps," Lucas recalled. "We were trying to rule absolutely everything out and we just kept coming up with more questions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Short on answers, Marrero added Lucas to the cluster. Over the coming months, her symptoms worsened and new symptoms appeared. She experienced light sensitivity, tremors, terrible migraines and issues with her memory and ability to speak clearly, she said. She felt unexplained stabbing pains. Cold water felt scalding hot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Jillian Lucas and her stepfather Derek Cuthbertson. Both were diagnosed by Marrero with the mystery illness. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero, though, was attentive and caring. He took her symptoms seriously. "He made me feel seen and that what I was experiencing was important," Lucas wrote in a Facebook post about her struggle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It was a sentiment that seemed to be shared by everyone who saw Marrero. He held their hands during appointments. He remembered them, cried with them. He was "the only one listening to them," said Lori-Ann Roness, one of the cluster patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"He's an incredible human and physician," said Melissa Nicholson, whose mother died last year after being diagnosed with the mystery disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Watching our mom go through it was hard enough," Nicholson said. "But he was such a pillar of support."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In March 2021, with Canada still in the grip of the Covid pandemic, the cluster suddenly became news. New Brunswick's chief medical officer had sent a memo to doctors alerting them to the apparent syndrome and suggesting they contact Marrero with possible cases. The memo leaked and the story hit the papers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero found himself inundated with new patients. But he was also drawing support from the highest levels of Canadian science. The working group set up to respond to the original CJD cases had evolved into a multi-disciplinary group studying the cluster, and the possibility of a mysterious new neurological condition seemed, at times, irresistible to the scientists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's like reading a movie script," emailed one researcher to colleagues, about an early story in the Toronto Star.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We are all in the movie!", a senior federal scientist replied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Dr Marrero at home in New Brunswick. "I kept documenting new cases and I kept seeing new people dying," he said. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;At the heart of the working group was Marrero, along with Dr Michael Coulthart, the head of the CJD Surveillance System; Dr Neil Cashman, a leading Canadian neurologist; Dr Michael Strong, the head of the Canadian Institutes of Health Research (CIHR); and Dr Samuel Weiss, one of the CIHR's senior neurologists. All agreed that Marrero needed considerable support. Strong said he could arrange additional staff and offered himself up as a consultant. The CIHR offered the province of New Brunswick C$5 million ($3.6m; £2.7m) to investigate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And the mystery disease got a name: the "New Brunswick Neurological Syndrome of Unknown Cause". In an email to Marrero in April 2021, Strong called it "one of the most unusual constellations of findings I have ever seen".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We all owe you a debt of gratitude," he wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But not everyone was on board. Dr Gerard Jansen, a neuropathologist who was attached to the CJD Surveillance System, had noticed something unusual when referrals from Marrero's office started piling up. Jansen recalled feeling "flabbergasted" at Marrero's notes, which he said featured an array of broad and unrelated clinical observations — a "diarrhea of symptoms".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jansen saw clues in the patients' files that he said pointed to already defined neurological diseases. When he examined brain tissue samples of a few cluster patients who had died, he found signs of Alzheimer's disease and Lewy body dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He was alarmed. His superior, Coulthart, appeared to believe something unexplained was happening in New Brunswick, Jansen said. Keen to get his concerns down in writing, he sent Coulthart a long and detailed email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"All available evidence and logic" pointed to a collection of different diseases, Jansen wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The patients are real, but the clustering as a mystery disease is not."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The early cases seemed to be grouped around two locations: Moncton and the Acadian Peninsula. Suspecting an environmental link, the scientists and officials considered various possible culprits, from a rare moose-borne parasite to blue-green algae blooms to Agent Orange sprayed on the province in the 1970s. Nothing bore fruit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero said he had observed an uptick in cases in late summer and early autumn — forestry spraying season — and he zeroed in on a controversial herbicide called glyphosate. Chronic exposure to glyphosate, which is used extensively by New Brunswick's forestry industry, has been linked by some studies to neuroinflammation and Parkinson's disease. (Forest NB, an industry body, told the BBC that glyphosate was used in compliance with regulations and was "not expected to pose risks" to human health or the environment.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;According to Marrero, many of his patients were showing highly elevated levels of both glyphosate and various heavy metals. Though when asked by the BBC what proportion of his 500 or so patients had concerning results, he refused to say. "I don't want to provide exact numbers of anything, but let's say it's an unusual number. Beyond 100."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;By April 2021, the focus was firmly on a possible environmental toxin. Strong, the CIHR director, said he thought a full "boots-on-the-ground" investigation was needed. The same month, a specialist clinic — the Mind Clinic — was set up in New Brunswick with Marrero at the helm to treat the cluster patients. With the $5m on offer from the CIHR, and the backing of Strong and other top federal scientists, all the conditions appeared set to get to the bottom of the mystery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But then, everything changed. In May, New Brunswick effectively suspended the collaboration with the federal scientists. The province also decided not to take up the $5m on offer from the CIHR. According to Marrero, the decision killed off any prospect of finding an answer. "Everybody received that email like a cold shower," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;None of the provincial officials involved agreed to talk to the BBC on the record. But it is clear there was concern about Marrero's methods and about the nature of his contact with Coulthart, Strong and the other federal scientists. The view of some at senior levels of the New Brunswick government was that the informal working group, seduced by the possibility of a scientific mystery, was circumventing the province.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But the decision to leave the money on the table, rather than spend it investigating, fuelled suspicions that New Brunswick wanted to avoid scrutiny of its environment. According to Kat Lanteigne, the executive director of Canadian health non-profit Bloodwatch and a tireless supporter of Marrero, the actions of the province amounted to a full-blown cover up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They pulled the plug because they just don't want anybody looking," Lanteigne said. "Full stop."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Taking control of the process, New Brunswick mounted two investigations into the original cluster of 48 — one telephone questionnaire and one study of the patients' medical records by an oversight committee of six provincial neurologists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jansen, the neuropathologist who had raised concerns, had by that point examined the autopsies of eight cluster patients and firmly believed they all had known, diagnosable illnesses. Troubled, he passed his conclusions on to the oversight committee and presented them to the Canadian Association of Neuropathologists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Not long after that, the New Brunswick government finished its investigations, concluding in February 2022 that there was no common environmental cause and no common condition among the patients. In other words, no mystery disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;A protest sign in New Brunswick. Some residents are angry about pesticide use in the province. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But the government had decided against examining any of the patients in person, an omission that outraged those who believed they were part of the cluster. The patients — now 105 in number — were attending sporadic appointments with Marrero at the Mind Clinic but seeing little progress. Jillian Lucas's symptoms were worsening at such a rate that she had begun to weigh something once unthinkable to her: medically assisted dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;At the clinic, appointments with Marrero could be strangely conspiratorial, patients said. During one appointment, Lucas's stepmother Susan recalled, Marrero put his hand up, told them to stop talking, and went to the door to listen. "He said, 'I believe we are being recorded'."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Stacie Quigley-Cormier, whose stepdaughter Gabrielle was the youngest member of the cluster, said Marrero always spoke in a hushed tone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The experience with Dr Marrero — and other patients talk about this too — is you make sure you start talking after the door is closed, and there's a quiet tone to his voice, and you make sure you're not talking in the hallways and things like that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero declined to discuss it. "Some patients actually thought that way. And I… We wondered… But I don't want to comment."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In August 2022, Marrero was sacked from the Mind Clinic. "Despite our repeated attempts to inform you of our expectations and the deficiencies in your performance, you have not demonstrated a sustained ability to meet our expectations," wrote John Dornan, then-CEO of the health network. The 105 cluster patients each received their own letter, telling them they could stay at the clinic, with all the resources it had to offer, or strike out alone with Marrero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Many were offended on behalf of their neurologist. "When they called me to ask my choice, I said, it's not a choice, it's an ultimatum," Lucas said. "And I choose him."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Jillian Lucas at home with one of the family's 15 parrots. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She wasn't alone. Of the 105 patients, 94 chose Marrero. Just 11 people decided to stay with the clinic and get a second opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Outside of the clinic, increasingly isolated, Marrero continued to diagnose the mystery disease. He was sending patients for so many tests, for such obscure toxins or conditions, that some reported being met with an increasingly quizzical eye at the testing clinic, as if to say, "What now?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Others found it difficult to get an appointment with Marrero or even speak to his assistant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I've messaged a couple of times but they're so busy, you can't even hardly get a hold of them by email," said Lucas. "He just has so many patients."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;As the cluster generated more news coverage in Canada, little attention was paid to the 11 patients who had decided to stay with the Mind Clinic, and their stories have never been told.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Kevin Strickland's partner April was referred to Marrero after she stopped her car in the middle of the road one morning and apparently forgot how to drive. April, then 60, had already been showing some dementia-like symptoms, but the driving incident scared Strickland. Marrero ran a series of tests on April and diagnosed the mystery illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"He told me it was the mystery illness and he wanted to look further into it, but he never really did much after that," Strickland said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Kevin Strickland at home with his rescue dog. His partner April was diagnosed by Marrero with the mystery illness. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The couple waited eight months to get important test results from Marrero, Strickland said, as April's condition worsened. Soon Strickland could no longer manage her care. But to get her a place in assisted living he needed a letter of support from Marrero. "I think I waited four months for that letter," Strickland recalled. "I kept phoning and asking."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Eventually he gave up and turned to the Mind Clinic, he said, and got the letter. And the Mind Clinic neurologists gave April something else she needed — a firm diagnosis. She was suffering from a form of frontotemporal dementia. In the end, Marrero "did nothing for April," Strickland said. "I guess he was more interested in proving the mystery illness than he was helping his patients," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Sandi Partridge also chose to remain with the Mind Clinic. She felt a deep sense of loyalty to Marrero, but she also saw simple common sense in getting a second opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Partridge had first seen Marrero in 2020, after suffering headaches and balance issues. He ordered a barrage of tests — according to Partridge she had two MRIs, two EEGs, a SPECT, a CAT scan and a spinal tap, as well as more than a dozen different antibody tests. "It was mostly a lot of testing with Dr Marrero," she recalled. "Every time he would see me, it would be an hour and a half, sometimes two hours, and he would retest me every single time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But every test came back negative. Partridge had also provided Marrero with a video of her having a seizure at home, which he studied. He diagnosed her with the mystery illness. "Those were the words he used," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Sandi Partridge in a park near her home. "It was mostly a lot of testing with Dr Marrero," she said. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;One thing Marrero never mentioned to Partridge was functional neurological disorder, which was her eventual diagnosis. FND is a complex condition; previously known as psychosomatic or psychogenic illness, it describes physical symptoms with a psychological root. It presents a challenge to doctors, who have to guide patients through the stigma associated with it to an understanding that they have a real condition that requires complex treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Partridge's neurologists at the Mind Clinic also reviewed the seizure video she had shown to Marrero. "As soon as Dr Abdellah saw my seizure he said, that's FND," Partridge recalled. (Abdellah declined to speak to the BBC). Partridge threw herself into researching the condition. "And I thought, that's me, that's me, that's me, that's me," she said. "I hit every single marker."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Partridge is now on a multi-faceted FND treatment programme involving neurology, neuropsychology and occupational health. And she is at peace with her diagnosis. "The stigma is difficult," she said, "but I've accepted it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Gabrielle Cormier, the youngest patient in Marrero's cluster, would also receive a diagnosis of FND, but her journey would follow a different path.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Cormier has featured heavily in the media coverage of the cluster, becoming a kind of poster child for the mystery disease. She was first referred to Marrero at just 18. A high school student, dancer and competitive figure skater, she had begun to experience fatigue-like symptoms and muscle soreness and then passed out at school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Cormier was already taking anti-anxiety medication, and the hospital emergency room doctor told her the incident was anxiety-induced. Unhappy with his assessment (he told Cormier, who is gay, that she "just needed to find a boyfriend", she said), the family looked to Marrero for answers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Gabrielle Cormier was diagnosed by Marrero at just 18. "I've done nothing with my life since I got sick," she said. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero was different — empathetic, caring. As he had with other patients, he ran Cormier through a gauntlet of tests. When nothing showed up, he diagnosed her with the mystery illness. Canada was deep in the isolation of the Covid lockdown, but Marrero reassured them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"He said, there's a dozen other people at least that are experiencing similar things to what you're experiencing, and I don't have answers for it yet," stepmother Stacie Quigley-Cormier recalled. "He told her that she wasn't alone."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There was one test Marrero couldn't secure: a PET scan, because the hard-up province was largely reserving them for cancer patients. So Cormier's parents took her to Toronto for the scan and a second opinion by a leading neurologist there, Dr Anthony Lang.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;After a multi-day evaluation at a specialist neurology centre, Lang diagnosed Cormier with FND. Her tests showed that conscious movements were weak but forced reflex or automotive movements were normal and healthy. It pointed to psychology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The Quigley-Cormiers were initially prepared to accept the FND diagnosis, they said. But they left Toronto unhappy after Lang told them to stop treating Cormier as though she had a terminal illness because it was reinforcing her condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A few weeks later, Lang called Cormier to inform her that a delayed test result had shown some reduced blood flow in her brain — something Marrero had also observed — and which can be caused by various medical or psychological issues including depression. Lang told Cormier the abnormality was slight and bore no relation to her symptoms, so she shouldn't worry about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The call didn't sit well with the Quigley-Cormiers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"There was no reason to call her personal phone when he knew she had memory problems," said her father Andre, angrily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bc5c/live/9cdddc70-ed44-11f0-8cc8-8329494b82ad.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Global News Jillian Lucas and other patients stand in front of a government building holding signs saying 'We are not a mystery, 'We stand by Doctor Marrero' and other slogans. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Global News&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Gabrielle Cormier, in her wheelchair, with other patients calling for suppport. Jillian Lucas is far left. (Global News)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The call pushed the Quigley-Cormier family away from Lang and his FND diagnosis and back towards Marrero, who the family had come to believe in deeply. Marrero had never crossed "any kind of line," Stacie said. "He's pristine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"That's why all his patients like him," Andre said. "Love him, maybe."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero continued to test Cormier repeatedly. He prescribed anti-seizure medication to prevent possible seizures, though she had not had any. He referred her for a round of intravenous immunoglobulin treatment — which she said caused severe headaches, aches, nausea, dizziness and aseptic meningitis — and prescribed a powerful intravenous immunosuppressant used for blood cancers and autoimmune illnesses. Neither improved her condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Cormier once dreamed of studying pathology. But her illness caused her to drop out of university and for years she has gone everywhere either in a wheelchair or with a cane, living, for a 24-year-old, a restricted life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I've had this idea that my life has been wasted, or that I've done nothing with my life since I got sick," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"So, yeah, it kind of feels like I've been robbed of that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Lang, the Toronto neurologist, came away from his interaction with the Quigley-Cormier family troubled. His call to Cormier was not only appropriate, he said, he was ethically bound to communicate with her directly because she was a mentally competent adult who did not ask for her parents to act for her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Over the coming months, Lang watched with concern as the purported cluster ballooned in New Brunswick. He emailed Marrero and left messages with his secretary offering help, but never heard back. In late 2023, frustrated by what he saw as cluster misinformation everywhere, Lang decided with colleagues to mount a study. The results — published in May 2025 in the Journal of the American Medical Association, JAMA — landed in New Brunswick like a hand grenade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Lang and his co-authors — including several former Mind Clinic colleagues of Marrero and the concerned neuropathologist, Gerard Jansen — found that all 25 patients in their study had suffered from previously known conditions, from functional neurological disorder to dementia to cancer. The probability of there being no new disease was close to 100%, they said. The real cause of the cluster, they concluded, was serial misdiagnosis by Marrero, compounded by credulous media reporting, the limitations of New Brunswick's public health system, institutional distrust sown by the pandemic and the actions of a small group of people "co-opting the crisis to suit their agenda".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Dr Lang was the leading author on a paper casting doubt on the cluster. (Sammy Kogan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The cases in the JAMA paper consisted of 14 live patients and 11 autopsies. Most of the live patients were people who had chosen to remain at the Mind Clinic, like Sandi Partridge. A few, including Gabrielle Cormier, were included via a consent waiver — a legal process which allows researchers to use patient data without their express consent provided certain anonymity criteria are met.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The study's conclusions incensed the most vocal patients and patient advocates, including Kat Lanteigne and Stacie Quigley-Cormier, who allege that the research was unscientific and unethical. The Quigley-Cormiers are furious that Gabrielle's data was used for the study, and their lawyers have sent letters to Lang and to the journal alleging the paper was a violation of her privacy. JAMA declined to comment on the dispute. Lang said that the research was legal, ethical and appropriately anonymised. As for the alleged violation of privacy, he pointed out that the only reason anyone knew Cormier's data was used was because her father and stepmother had told the media, along with many other details about her life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;On a bright morning this past September, Marrero was sitting in his home office in a large cottage-style house on a plot of land just outside of Moncton. A stone fountain burbled softly in his Japanese-inspired peace garden. Birds sang in his own patch of forest — untouched by herbicides or pesticides, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Marrero is undeniably charismatic. He has a warm smile and demeanour. He speaks gently, but with authority. He remembers small details about people he barely knows and asks about their wellbeing in a manner that conveys genuine care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Settled in his office chair, he recalled with obvious pleasure that not so long ago, some of Canada's top scientists had sat with him around that very desk, ready to take on a scientific mystery. But now, Marrero seemed increasingly isolated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They are trying to present me as it," he said, dejectedly. "I was part of it, but I was not it. The only difference is, when the table was empty, I stayed."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Of Marrero's early federal collaborators — Drs Coulthart, Cashman, Strong, and Weiss — only Coulthart agreed to speak to the BBC about the cluster. He denied ever having been convinced by the idea of a unified, mystery syndrome. "As a scientist, I use the word convinced very, very sparingly," he said. "But don't let anybody kid you — if anyone says they know what's going on or isn't going on in New Brunswick, they're either lying or grossly mistaken. Because nobody has the facts."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Dr Marrero in his home office. "I was part of it, but I was not it," he said. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;An upcoming provincial report could offer some answers. Unlike the previous studies, it will examine the claims of elevated glyphosate and heavy metals in the patients. At times, the stakes seem impossibly high. "Lives hang in the balance," read a recent letter to Premier Susan Holt, signed by 72 of the patients. "It is within your power to honour them, cherish them, and care for them," the letter said. "Or you can abandon them and let them wither, fade, and ultimately die. Please join us on the right side of history."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The patient advocates, led by Bloodwatch director Kat Lanteigne, have arguably done more than anyone to keep the story of the cluster going, with an operation that includes lobbying the government, briefing the press and sending legal letters to scientists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Lanteigne has publicly attacked both Jansen and Lang over the JAMA study, branding their work inaccurate and unethical. She denied harassing Jansen, saying she had never spoken to him directly and emailed him only once. "I have a record of speaking truth to power and I have always worked with integrity and honesty," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Both Lang and Jansen are standing their ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"What we have here is a case of misdiagnosis, evolving to misinformation, and sadly resulting in suffering for patients and families," Lang said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I would even go further," Jansen said, regarding the alleged misdiagnosis of the patients. "I would say they are being abused."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Few others are willing to criticise Marrero so openly. Privately, former senior government officials and colleagues of Marrero have questioned whether he should have been investigated. The Royal College of Physicians told the BBC it could not comment on whether there had been complaints against any individual physician, and none have been made public in relation to Marrero. Any sanction process would typically begin with a complaint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And that was the issue, one former senior health official said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It has to be a patient complaint," they said. "And all his patients love him."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The last time Jillian Lucas saw Marrero was more than a year ago. He tested her again, but she is yet to see the results. During the appointment, he told her that just getting a common cold could kill her, she said. So she rarely leaves the house — a cramped and densely cluttered property that the family shares with 15 parrots. "She spends 90% of her time in her bedroom," her stepmother said. "It's a very limited life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Kat Lanteigne told the BBC that Marrero "deserves the Order of Canada for what he has done for these people." But many patients, like Lucas, are languishing. Largely untreated, they have undergone test after test in search of the mystery disease and ended up back where they began, or somewhere worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In response to criticisms in this story, Marrero said that he would not comment on patients or fellow physicians. "The focus must remain on the hundreds of suffering patients, their families and communities who need to be the heart of our attention and care," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Jillian Lucas in her back garden. "I don't want to be in a nursing home, or be a burden," she said. (Chris Donovan/BBC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jillian Lucas has now seen a second doctor, but only because she has pushed ahead with her decision to explore medical assistance in dying, which requires two physicians to sign off. Canada has among the world's most permissive laws for assisted dying, allowing people to pursue it without a terminal diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;When Lucas told Marrero her plan, he became "choked up", she said. "It eats him up, he's fighting back tears."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And yet, Marrero agreed to support her application, despite her not having a concrete diagnosis or testing positive for any known condition. (Marrero told the BBC he "took the utmost care to abide by" the laws around Maid and had "never proposed it" to a patient.) After all the years of uncertainty with the unknown neurological syndrome, the option of dying gave Lucas some sense of control. "I have a limit in my mind of how far I can go," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Sitting in his garden office, the sun streaming in, Marrero had no such limits in mind. "I keep going because I know," he said, confidently. He had been able to meet "with some of the best scientists in the country," he said. He had more than 500 cluster patients now, and every week the number was going up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:23:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE00b0FrMWhDd2xNaUZfZG10SW5WeWxkMk10UWVhb0pGQnZJcmJQazJNeDBlMDY0S3hHVTJJOGg3Qm1UbW1EakFOWkZEdkd5ZjFmdmphMU5MV2ZZUdIBX0FVX3lxTE1oWXM1LWw5WExGVkczRlM0WWNoUXhxcndjNWZ4akFxVXVIcVdvdU1DMENQUXdfWV9TS2RkUlo4LTAyb0V1cEJ6VnhLanQ0VUdTWWtIaTl1Uko2QV83emVj</guid></item><item><title>“Super-K”流感变种正在澳大利亚蔓延。以下是它“不寻常”的原因- SBS澳大利亚</title><link>https://www.sbs.com.au/news/article/what-you-need-to-know-about-the-super-k-flu-variant/tdpgmr6b2</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleBodyLayout_articleContentBody__bS_cb"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;A new strain of influenza known as 'Super-K', or the subclade-K variant, could be responsible for an unusual spring and summer boost in flu cases, epidemiologists say.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"The unusual thing here for Australia is the timing," WHO Collaborating Centre for Reference and Research on Influenza director Patrick Reading told SBS News.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"The not unusual thing is probably the symptoms," he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ArticleBodyAdContainer_adContainer__fvTT2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reading recalls the subclade-K variant emerged towards the end of Australia and New Zealand's typical flu season, circulating in September rather than the winter months.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"That was responsible for elevated influenza cases throughout the spring and actually throughout the start of our summer in December as well."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to the Global Initiative on Sharing All Influenza Data (GISAID), the total lab confirmed cases of subclade-K in Australia so far currently sits at 1,083.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A new report by the Australian Centre for Disease Control (ACDC) stated that subclade-K's rapid spread has the potential to put increased pressure on Australian health care services over the summer and into the 2026 influenza season.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Current case numbers for influenza are higher than usual for this time of year compared to previous seasons," an ACDC spokesperson said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;So far this year, over 4,100 cases of influenza have been confirmed by laboratories, with the true number of flu cases likely to be higher.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;By comparison, in the first quarter of last year, an average of around 3,300 cases were confirmed weekly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rich-text override-heading-font MuiBox-root mui-exul89"&gt;&lt;h2 data-testid="embed-heading" id=""&gt;What was the cause of the subclade-K flu variant?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Every few decades, a flu virus can undergo a much larger genetic change called antigenic shift, which can lead to a pandemic, but this is not what has happened with super-K," University of South Australia epidemiology professor Adrian Esterman said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Instead, super-K is best understood as a drifted version of the familiar H3N2 virus, with enough changes to allow it to spread more widely in populations with existing immunity."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The ACDC report noted Australian subclade-K viruses may have originated in or been imported from the US, following detections in the US in June and July last year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reading said there's no current evidence that the variant is more severe than a regular flu. What experts are seeing, however, is that it easily transmits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"It appears that it's probably going to have an ability to at least be slightly less sensitive to antibody or vaccine-mediated protection," he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Deakin University epidemiology professor Catherine Bennett told SBS News: "This new subvariant of the H3N2 is that bit more immune evasive with these latest mutations in the part of the virus that allows it to invade our cells, making us more susceptible."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bennett said the 2025 flu vaccine included H3N2, but not this specific class.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Flu vaccines wane in effectiveness, so people vaccinated back in April-May and only getting infected now won't have the same benefit," she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;However, the 2026 flu vaccine for the southern hemisphere has already been updated to include this variant, and will likely be available around April, Bennett said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Esterman said the flu vaccine remains worthwhile and provides important protection.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"It still significantly reduces the risk of severe disease."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rich-text override-heading-font MuiBox-root mui-exul89"&gt;&lt;h2 data-testid="embed-heading" id=""&gt;What does a typical flu season look like in Australia?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"When we get seasonal influenza every year in Australia, or anywhere, it's a combination of three viruses," said Reading. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are two influenza A viruses — a H3N2 and H1N1 — and one influenza B virus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to the Australian Centre for Disease Control, there were 365,261 reports of the flu in 2024. Cases spiked between May and August, and drastically dropped following the winter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;"As we move into spring, flu generally comes down in Australia, and then it's very low during summer," said Reading.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Last year there were 502,493 reports of influenza, with cases clearly continuing until the end of the year following those winter months.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to GISAID, H3N2 subclade-K is driving an estimated 90 per cent of cases in the United States.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"What we saw around September [in Australia] onwards is the H1N1s and B viruses decreased, but we saw an increase in H3N2 viruses," Reading said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rich-text override-heading-font MuiBox-root mui-exul89"&gt;&lt;h2 data-testid="embed-heading" id=""&gt;How can I avoid catching the flu?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"People who are unwell should consider testing and should avoid mixing with other people as much as possible," Bennett said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Keep homes well-ventilated, hold gatherings outdoor if possible, and wear a mask in busy public indoor spaces if susceptible to more severe respiratory infections."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;NSW Health advises getting the annual flu vaccine, as well as practising good hand hygiene — including handwashing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SBS Australia</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:13:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQLXl5ZzdBT2hYWkVncFVCanlhVEw4M25RRHYwYnlWNDZvRjlxS1B6TUxoc2NyZUFnOWwzM0lRZEotYjdCdjFFbHowRlFfOXVtazJ0LXVuenZLWUFJeDJUdDZPcGFFV1cyYjhIZWJCc24tVzBzUktPT0NYY0MtZWRCN0JOUGxtVUJCQ1UycW55VE9MUlNrVWozV2lsMTlkUQ</guid></item><item><title>俄勒冈州确认2026年首例麻疹病例，公众敦促审查疫苗接种- KATU</title><link>https://katu.com/news/local/oregon-confirms-first-measles-cases-of-2026-public-urged-to-review-vaccinations-rfk-jr-hhs-us-donald-trump-disease-cdc</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;LINN COUNTY, Ore. (KATU) — &lt;/span&gt;Health officials in Oregon have confirmed the state's first measles cases of 2026, with two people diagnosed in Linn County. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Oregon Health Authority (OHA) and Linn County public health officials are investigating the cases and have identified two locations where the public may have been exposed to the virus: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lebanon Community Hospital Emergency Department on Jan. 6 from 8:53 p.m. to 7 a.m. on Jan. 7.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Albany General Hospital Emergency Department on Jan. 7 from 4:59 a.m. to 8:15 a.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Howard Chiou, medical director for communicable diseases and immunizations at OHA’s Public Health Division, emphasized the importance of vaccination, stating, "Measles is here in Oregon and rates are increasing nationally, which is why we encourage everyone to make sure they’re protected by talking with their providers about being up to date on vaccinations."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Oregon's 2025 cases&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oregon's&lt;a href="https://katu.com/news/local/oregon-confirms-first-measles-case-of-2025-in-multnomah-county-cdc-washington-disease-vaccination-health-authority-sickness-illness-infection-rash-symptoms-unvaccinated" target="_blank"&gt; first measles case in 2025 &lt;/a&gt;was confirmed in June, when a person was hospitalized in the Portland area with a rash and conjunctivitis after they contracted the disease during international travel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last May, the OHA reported that Oregon had a record-high nonmedical vaccine exemption for kindergartners, but most families continued to vaccinate their kids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://public.tableau.com/app/profile/oregon.immunization.program/viz/OregonMeaslesImmunizationData/StateRates" target="_blank"&gt;record &lt;/a&gt;9.7% of kindergartners in the state have claimed nonmedical exemptions from school vaccination requirements for the 2024-2025 school year, marking the highest rate ever recorded in the state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This increase continues an upward trend from 8.8% in 2024, when Oregon had the fourth-highest nonmedical exemption rate in the&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank"&gt; United States&lt;/a&gt;, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Symptoms and 'immune amnesia'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles spreads through the air after an infected person coughs or sneezes, with the virus lingering for up to two hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms typically start with a fever, cough, runny nose, and red eyes, followed by a &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/signs-symptoms/photos.html?utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_source=govdelivery" target="_blank"&gt;rash&lt;/a&gt;. Complications can include ear infections, lung infections, and, rarely, brain swelling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles is one of the most contagious diseases, and is known to cause a dangerous and unique phenomenon called "&lt;a href="https://asm.org/articles/2019/may/measles-and-immune-amnesia" target="_blank"&gt;immune amnesia&lt;/a&gt;," in which the infected patient's immune system goes through a reset, effectively "forgetting" any immunity it had towards other diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to studies, in a room full of people exposed to measles, 90% who are unvaccinated will develop the disease. In addition, it can linger in the air for up to 2 hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even in healthy people, measles can cause the following:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 out of every 1,000 measles cases will develop acute encephalitis, which often results in permanent brain damage.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 to 3 out of every 1,000 children who become infected with measles will die from respiratory and neurologic complications.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subacute sclerosing panencephalitis (SSPE), a rare but fatal degenerative disease of the central nervous system characterized by:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Behavioral and intellectual deterioration.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Seizures that generally develop 7 to 10 years after measles infection.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public health officials advise those experiencing &lt;a href="https://www.oregon.gov/oha/PH/DISEASESCONDITIONS/DISEASESAZ/Pages/measles.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;symptoms &lt;/a&gt;not to visit medical offices unannounced. Instead, they should call ahead to arrange a safe entry plan to prevent exposing others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms typically appear seven to 21 days after exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The virus can be particularly dangerous for infants, young children, adults over 20, pregnant individuals, and those with weakened immune systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Push for vaccinations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In March of 2025, U.S. Senators of Oregon &lt;a href="https://katu.com/news/local/senators-urge-hhs-to-launch-national-measles-vaccination-campaign-merkley-wyden-oregon" target="_blank"&gt;Ron Wyden and Jeff Merkley &lt;/a&gt;called on Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. to take immediate action to curb the spread of measles in the United States. The plea followed the first measles-related deaths in the country in a decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://katu.com/news/local/senators-urge-hhs-to-launch-national-measles-vaccination-campaign-merkley-wyden-oregon" target="_blank"&gt;letter&lt;/a&gt; to Secretary Kennedy, the senators highlighted the urgency of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although Secretary Kennedy chaired the anti-vaccine nonprofit Children's Health Defense from 2015 to 2023, he wrote an&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/opinion/robert-f-kennedy-jr-measles-outbreak-call-action-all-us" target="_blank"&gt; op-ed last year for Fox News&lt;/a&gt; in which he called MMR vaccines "crucial" to avoiding deadly disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Measles outbreak is call to action for all of us," the op-ed is titled. "Vaccines not only protect individual children from measles, but also contribute to community immunity, protecting those who are unable to be vaccinated due to medical reasons," he wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The measles vaccine is highly effective, with two doses of the MMR vaccine providing 97% protection against the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The&lt;a href="https://katu.com/news/nation-world/us-has-twice-as-many-measles-cases-so-far-this-year-than-in-all-of-2024-04-06-2025" target="_blank"&gt; resurgence of measles&lt;/a&gt; is linked to global spikes in cases, increasing the likelihood of unvaccinated travelers bringing the virus back to the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles was once a major health threat in the U.S., especially for children, with hundreds of thousands of cases and hundreds of deaths annually before the 1960s. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The introduction of the measles vaccine in 1963 led to a dramatic decline in cases, deaths, and serious complications. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By 1981, less than 1% of the previous number of cases were reported, and only 10% of U.S. counties saw any cases at all, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/history.html" target="_blank"&gt;according to the CDC.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KATU</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:07:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3wFBVV95cUxOUEx4dWhLNGRiU184VDhxUUFYVEJKVEJYeVpBQ3pReDYtWU5WaThCcnhuVXhqdThvY1FfZVpTUkhyYlM0MjdUY04tbFc4TTBUOXA3aVZ6N1lZbUphdFcxUTNUZ2N2M3RNWkM2bS1CLW1yQWxpdEtCYlhfNDZzdG9ORW1GMjA0dU9RdWxQTHVuek5tV214ZWxOQzlnZWpFdUdocmIzTDdIWGhJR3l3dVFZc3VtN0dZMVBIb2QyMGdnMjdlb01QM01YOTJOV0ptVmxpOWdUb0VUM1hTUDNaQXo0</guid></item><item><title>60年代和70年代的7种常见做法今天是非法的（或可耻的） - VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/r-t-7-common-practices-from-the-60s-and-70s-that-would-be-illegal-or-scandalous-today/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;The 1960s and 70s are often remembered as decades of freedom, rebellion, and experimentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They were loud, expressive, and full of cultural shifts that still influence how we live today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But they were also surprisingly casual about things we now see as dangerous, unethical, or flat-out unacceptable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking back isn’t about moral superiority, it’s about noticing how quickly norms change once we understand the consequences of our choices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you zoom out, it becomes a lesson in psychology more than history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What we tolerate says less about right and wrong, and more about what we’ve collectively agreed not to question yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are seven everyday practices from that era that would never make it past today’s laws or social standards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1) Smoking everywhere&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to overstate how normal smoking once was. Cigarettes weren’t just common, they were embedded into the physical design of public spaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You could smoke on airplanes, in offices, in restaurants, and in hospital waiting rooms. Ashtrays were built into desks and armrests, and nobody thought twice about lighting up indoors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What’s striking is that the issue wasn’t just people choosing to smoke. It was everyone else being forced to participate whether they wanted to or not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/10644-secondhand-smoke-dangers" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Secondhand smoke&lt;/a&gt; wasn’t widely discussed, and the idea that it could seriously harm others hadn’t yet entered the mainstream conversation. If you didn’t like it, that was your problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/s-bt-9-things-boomers-did-in-their-30s-that-would-get-someone-fired-arrested-or-divorced-today/"&gt;smoking indoors&lt;/a&gt; in most public places is illegal, and socially it’s often frowned upon even outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The shift feels obvious now, but at the time it required a complete reframing of what personal choice actually means.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a great example of how cultural blindness works. When a behavior is everywhere, it fades into the background and stops registering as harmful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2) Corporal punishment in schools&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was a time when physical punishment in schools wasn’t controversial. It was policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Teachers openly hit students with paddles, rulers, or straps as a form of discipline. Parents often supported it, believing it built character and respect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What we now understand about child psychology tells a very different story. Fear may produce compliance, but it also produces &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/basics/anxiety" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;anxiety&lt;/a&gt;, shame, and long-term stress responses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most schools today ban &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/z-if-you-survived-these-9-parenting-styles-from-the-70s-youre-either-incredibly-resilient-or-deeply-traumatized/"&gt;corporal punishment&lt;/a&gt; outright, and where it still exists, it’s heavily criticized. The idea of striking a child in the name of education now feels deeply unsettling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What’s uncomfortable is realizing how confident adults once were that this was the right approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Authority plus tradition created a shield that protected the practice from scrutiny.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s a reminder that just because something is common doesn’t mean it’s healthy, especially when the people affected have no voice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3) Drinking and driving as a social norm&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the 60s and early 70s, drunk driving wasn’t treated as a serious crime. It was often brushed off as bad judgment or even a funny story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Movies played it for laughs, and police responses were inconsistent at best.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In some cases, officers would simply follow a driver home to make sure they got there safely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The idea that you should not drive after drinking simply hadn’t solidified yet. Alcohol and cars coexisted with little friction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, this behavior is both illegal and socially condemned. DUI laws are strict, and public awareness campaigns have made the risks impossible to ignore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What changed wasn’t just legislation. It was perception.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once society collectively agreed that drunk driving wasn’t normal or funny, behavior shifted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/k-bt-if-youve-ever-said-no-to-these-5-types-of-invites-psychology-says-youre-mentally-stronger-than-most/"&gt;Social pressure&lt;/a&gt; turned out to be just as powerful as legal consequences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4) Casual prescribing of powerful drugs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-78422" src="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly.png" alt="" srcset="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly.png 1600w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-300x158.png 300w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-1024x538.png 1024w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-768x403.png 768w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-1536x806.png 1536w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-1200x630.png 1200w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-857x450.png 857w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-900x473.png 900w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-420x221.png 420w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/sickly-840x441.png 840w" sizes="(max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pharmaceutical culture of the 60s and 70s was shockingly relaxed by today’s standards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doctors regularly prescribed amphetamines, tranquilizers, and sedatives with minimal oversight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stimulants were given to boost productivity. Sedatives were handed out to help people &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/r-lc-7-behaviors-that-seem-normal-but-are-secretly-stress-responses-according-to-psychology/"&gt;cope with stress&lt;/a&gt; or boredom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was enormous trust in medical authority, and very little emphasis on informed consent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Patients rarely questioned prescriptions, and doctors rarely explained long-term risks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, that level of casual prescribing would raise serious red flags. We now require clinical trials, disclosures, and ongoing monitoring for good reason.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From a decision-making perspective, this shows how power imbalances work. When one side holds all the knowledge, the other side is unlikely to push back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It also shows how good intentions can still lead to harm when systems lack accountability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5) Workplace behavior with no boundaries&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Office culture in the 60s and 70s operated under rules that would be unacceptable today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sexual &lt;a href="https://thinkhumanrights.ca/know-your-rights/what-is-harassment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;harassment&lt;/a&gt; laws were minimal or nonexistent, and power dynamics were largely ignored.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unwanted comments, inappropriate touching, and relationships between bosses and employees were often dismissed as normal office life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Complaints, if they were voiced at all, were rarely taken seriously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, much of that behavior would result in immediate disciplinary action or legal consequences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The shift didn’t happen overnight, but it happened once language caught up to experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once people had words for harassment and coercion, they could finally name what felt wrong. And once something is named, it becomes much harder to ignore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Psychologically, this matters because &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/s-t-8-signs-youre-intelligent-enough-to-see-problems-everywhere-but-not-emotionally-equipped-to-enjoy-anything/"&gt;naming a problem&lt;/a&gt; is often the first step toward dismantling it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6) Children roaming freely without supervision&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many people feel nostalgic about how free childhood once was. In the 60s and 70s, kids often left the house in the morning and came back at dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They played far from home, rode public transportation alone, and sometimes hitchhiked. Parents trusted that things would work out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, that level of freedom would likely trigger concern or even legal consequences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parents can now be accused of negligence for situations that were once routine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our perception of risk has shifted dramatically. We are far more aware of worst-case scenarios, and that awareness shapes how we parent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s an ongoing debate about whether we’ve &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/dna-8-quiet-behaviors-that-suggest-you-dont-trust-easily-no-matter-what-you-say/"&gt;become too cautious&lt;/a&gt;. But regardless of where you land, the contrast between eras is undeniable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It shows how fear and safety evolve alongside information, media, and cultural narratives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7) Advertising that openly manipulated or lied&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Advertising in the 60s and 70s played fast and loose with the truth. Cigarettes were marketed as healthy, and sugary foods were framed as essential to a balanced diet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gender stereotypes were blatant, and &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/nat-8-signs-someone-is-emotionally-manipulative-but-doesnt-realize-it-according-to-psychology/"&gt;emotional manipulation&lt;/a&gt; was unapologetic. Regulations were limited, and accountability was rare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, advertising laws are stricter, and consumers are more skeptical. Companies are still persuasive, but outright false claims are more likely to be challenged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What really changed was media literacy. People slowly learned how persuasion works and how easily emotions can be exploited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you understand framing and repetition, you don’t consume messages the same way. That awareness has forced brands to evolve, even if reluctantly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking back at the 60s and 70s isn’t about shaming the past. It’s about understanding how flexible our sense of normal really is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What feels obvious today once required decades of debate, research, and resistance. And what feels acceptable now may one day be questioned just as intensely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The real takeaway is simple. Staying curious and willing to reexamine our assumptions is one of the most practical skills we can develop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-1119277622"&gt;&lt;p&gt;				 &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong data-start="380" data-end="431"&gt;VegOut Magazine’s November Edition Is Out!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;In our latest Magazine “&lt;em&gt;Curiosity, Compassion &amp;amp; the Future of Living&lt;/em&gt;” you’ll get FREE access to:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;– 5 in-depth articles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;– Insights across Lifestyle, Wellness, Sustainability &amp;amp; Beauty&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;– Our Editor’s Monthly Picks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;– 4 exclusive Vegan Recipes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/magazine-november-2025/"&gt;&lt;button class="buttonStyle buttonStyleAlternate"&gt;Learn more&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="g-ytsubscribe" data-channelid="UCdGKHK52616Dpj-FpFjeNSg" data-layout="full" data-count="hidden"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 			&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:04:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxOOVp4cks0SVlpZGNXVWtpamxacm15YnVoTlhvUlM2eW9nZ2JXWXZSMlRsOV9BaGF1YnEzX2kyZzlpWkdQUHdXcVVEWkppdDc2Mm9wZ3VNM3V0bkZMUWp3Q1BCRVRDZVFjYUFQNlpNSERHNFU5SDVTWS1RVVdrMTJ5NkQyZmQ0aVlpdmt2Tl9FUTdYMUEwV2Z4RGxuX05VcWUzYVZFRl9fYWYxcGJmYUZMSEN5TXJGZWNPOWc</guid></item><item><title>血色素沉着症：成千上万的北爱尔兰人正在接受凯尔特诅咒检测- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cx2wgl01wxgo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;'I'd never heard of Celtic curse until I was diagnosed'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 gXJgDY"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 gqeTMs"&gt;Niall McCracken&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 bIfajQ"&gt;Mid Ulster reporter, BBC News NI &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/aca5/live/2a2d5100-ed68-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Haemochromatosis UK Finbar Polin is staring intently at the camera. It is a close up of his face against a black background. He has short grey hair and blue eyes." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Haemochromatosis UK&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Finbar Polin was diagnosed with haemochromatosis in 2020&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Thousands of people in parts of Northern Ireland are being offered free testing for a disorder commonly known as the Celtic Curse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Haemochromatosis is the most common genetic disorder in Northern Ireland and is mostly found in people of Irish and Scots ancestry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The disorder means a person is more at risk of absorbing too much iron and it can start to damage other parts of their body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Symptoms can range from chronic fatigue, joint pain, memory issues, abdominal pain and skin conditions. If left untreated it can lead to serious long-term health complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Neil Irwin works for Haemochromatosis UK and was diagnosed with the condition seven years ago&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;BBC News NI previously reported on &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-northern-ireland-64813957" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;concerns that not enough people were being tested for it in Northern Ireland because of the cost&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The Department of Health's current policy is to screen for genetic haemochromatosis when a patient shows symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But a charity has said it is hoping to capture more information on areas of Northern Ireland where people may be undiagnosed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Haemochromatosis UK will offer up to 23,500 households free genetic screening in Irvinestown, Portadown, Ballymena and Magherafelt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Neil Irwin works for Haemochromatosis UK and was diagnosed with the condition seven years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He says early diagnosis is key to allow people access to effective treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt; "In recent years we have had anecdotal evidence from areas like Mid Ulster where people have been contacting us saying their area seems to have high rates of haemochromatosis," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"But there is a lack of official data, so we're looking to fill in some of those blank spots in Northern Ireland that have never screened before, to paint a more detailed picture of the prevalence of the condition."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;'I knew something was wrong'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Collette McKnight is a mother of three who lives in rural County Down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She was diagnosed with haemochromatosis in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I would have had severe fatigue and pains, but I just would have put it down to being busy with the children and things like that, "he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"But then I started to develop heart palpitations and I knew something else was wrong."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Collette McKnight was diagnosed with haemochromatosis in 2019&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She added: "When the tests came back confirming haemochromatosis, I hadn't a clue what it was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Everyday is different. Some days it's joint pain, other days it's breathing problems, but it's always dealing with the severe fatigue and that can be very difficult."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She is now treated with therapeutic blood removal, which helps lower iron levels and ease symptoms caused by the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;What is the Celtic curse?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The gene mutation that causes most cases of hereditary haemochromatosis is believed to have originated in the Celtic population of Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;DNA analysis of the genomes of a Bronze Age farmer on Rathlin Island off the coast of County Antrim showed that it was already established by that period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Earlier still, the remains of a Neolithic woman found at Ballynahatty near Belfast show that she carried a different variant &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-35179269" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;also associated with an increased risk of the disorder.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7517/live/afe4acb0-eccf-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Daniel Bradley, Trinity College Dublin A yellowish skull with the bottom jaw missing. It has A64 written on the forehead. There is a brown tag which says Ballynahatty and Fragile. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Daniel Bradley, Trinity College Dublin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Excavated near Belfast in 1855, the Ballynahatty woman lay in a Neolithic tomb chamber for 5,000 years&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;As part of the latest screening campaign, Haemochromatosis UK is bringing a touring photographic exhibition to Northern Ireland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The exhibition, We are Overloaded, opens to the public at the Millennium Court in Portadown on 19 January.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It features a photographs of people living with haemochromatosis by &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-northern-ireland-68735037" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Pulitzer Prize-winning photojournalist Cathal McNaughton&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Finbar Polin, from Gilford, is featured in the exhibition and was diagnosed with haemochromatosis during the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5c73/live/89c90250-ecd0-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="BBC News Three separate shots of Finbar Polin. Two are headshots - he has grey hair and looking intently at the camera. The other is a black and white photo of him sitting on a chair with a camera and light in the foreground, and a white screen behind him." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;BBC News&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Finbar Polin is from Craigavon and is featured in the exhibition&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Speaking to BBC News NI, he said: "I'd never heard of the Celtic curse until I was diagnosed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's scary initially because it affects you mentally; you don't know where you are going with it, but being part of the charity and meeting other people with it has really helped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"That's where I think the exhibition is really powerful, each picture is a person with a story."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;On the issue of screening, the Department of Health said it was guided by advice from UK National Screening Committee (UK NSC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Among its recommendations on haemochromatosis, UK NSC stated that there was "limited evidence on whether treatment is more effective in individuals without symptoms, compared with those who have symptoms".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But Haemochromatosis UK believe it is important to create an accurate picture as possible of the number of people living with the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;The We are Overloaded exhibition features the photos and stories of people living with haemochromatosis&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Previous research by the charity suggests that as many as one in 10 people are at risk in Northern Ireland of genetic haemochromatosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The charity previously ran a campaign to fund and offer thousands of households in Belfast, Carrickfergus and Londonderry with free self-test kits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A Haemochromatosis UK genetic testing kit usually costs about £130.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The latest kits being rolled out by Haemochromatosis UK were purchased with donations and funding received by the charity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Haemochromatosis UK will offer up to 23,500 households free genetic screening&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Businessman James Hagan, founder of Hagan Homes, is one of the donors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He said: "Someone very close to me was recently diagnosed with genetic haemochromatosis — despite having no symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Their experience highlights exactly why this campaign is so important. Most people affected have no warning signs, yet the potential consequences can be extremely serious if the condition goes undetected."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Haemochromatosis UK has said that in the coming weeks and months , households in the relevant postcodes will receive information about genetic haemochromatosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In the package they will be offered a free genetic test, alongside access to counselling to help them understand their results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:02:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5UVjV1QlYzd1ZuSmVBTkJjV1VtZHVCemgzSjZEb0VyTXMzUWpQdl9Pa3RmellJV2djUnlaaWtFLVFmclZRSzNlMlFCa3dvUjR1WE56S1g4OEp6d9IBX0FVX3lxTE56aGk0RVJoalZrS2xUZlBQanpDYmFOVWxIWVhkdUV2dFozQXZzZ25TTUpMcmNWZE5OWFJDa1ZqYW8xdkl4TGNXcG5aVXBVVVpVRXpHdTZicURlQUdRS2Fv</guid></item><item><title>萨米特县报告首例小学生麻疹病例- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51431382/summit-county-reports-its-first-case-of-measles-in-elementary-school-student</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;COALVILLE — Summit County confirmed its first case of measles Saturday in a South Summit School District student.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The student attended school or school activities while infectious at South Summit Elementary School, the Summit County Health Department said in a statement, adding that exposures may have occurred during school hours on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The health department is working closely with the school district to provide notification and guidance to parents, students and faculty. Health officials, meanwhile, are taking immediate action to investigate and limit further spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our staff and school district partners have taken proactive measures for months to plan and prepare for our first measles case," Summit County Health Director Dr. Phil Bondurant said. "We encourage residents and their family members who are not already vaccinated against measles to consider the MMR vaccine, which is the most effective way to protect against measles."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Summit County health officials are encouraging those who are experiencing symptoms of measles to contact their health care provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Utah Department of Health and Human Services' &lt;a href="https://files.epi.utah.gov/Utah%20measles%20dashboard.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;dashboard&lt;/a&gt; said the measles case count statewide is now at 176 as of Saturday, after the count stood at 156 &lt;a href="https://www.ksl.com/article/51426212/utah-measles-cases-rise-to-156-amid-ongoing-national-outbreak" rel="follow" target="_blank"&gt;on New Year's Day&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 23:17:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxOVjVpcWtUZHl3WGJmbmExX3o3TW1acHJNcFpCeHNqUHhDeHlGN3JZbnNuODZVYjVYVlZ4cUg0c0IxMThNeUNlLTQ4R0xXdGRKUXlFU2JjUl9acDE5MmRjQTJPYmhZcEJTaVhYTEJVek40Q2tOQmh0VXFxamZTeDNFN3BJa2o0MEt2Y0NlbWpWVDB3eExPM3RnWXpydW92cWRSaUtHSjhzSnJJZ19QZmxLQ3ZCUQ</guid></item><item><title>南峰学区的学生麻疹检测呈阳性- KUTV</title><link>https://kutv.com/news/local/student-in-south-summit-school-district-tests-positive-for-measles</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h2 class="StoryPage_headline__AP3j8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Student in South Summit School District tests positive for measles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="ByLineContainer_storyBylineContainer__0JNT7" id="js-Story-Byline-0"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="ByLine_storyByLineText__cze7l"&gt;by Jonathan May, KUTV &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="ByLineContainer_storyDatelineText__yS9e8"&gt;Sat, January 10, 2026 at 3:33 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="ByLineContainer_storyDatelineText__yS9e8"&gt;&lt;span class="ByLineContainer_updatedText__0D6FY"&gt;Updated &lt;/span&gt;Sat, January 10, 2026 at 4:02 PM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="UserWayButton_userWayButton__h8S9a ByLineContainer_userWayButton___vCFL"&gt;&lt;img alt="UserWay icon for accessibility widget" src="/resources/defaults/news_3.0/icons/accessibility/userway-transparent.svg"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KUTV</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:34:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxONmJqajZEQjdxaERadFRTME1ycldqUTlTMk4xMUpjV1B5OTloTnpUUlJRX0FBMHB4elVFU3VuNkQ3SWRNbHc4US1TdE9mR0dPTUwwVV9Bc18zbnZuUXFEaFh2eVlsekh5U0NTdUlWeC01MWtxZlRGUm1wVnpwSm1nZ2s3dWRhUzNvalpCUXpQTlYtTFM2RTV4cGJR</guid></item><item><title>TAU在皮肤癌研究中取得突破-《耶路撒冷邮报》</title><link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/article-882897</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;section id="section-0" class="article-default-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel is fortunate to enjoy sunny days most of the year, but a downside is that overexposure to and lack of protection from its ultraviolet rays can cause melanoma – the most &lt;a href="https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/article-881682"&gt;serious and deadliest kind of skin cancer&lt;/a&gt;, which develops from pigment-producing cells called melanocytes that give skin its color.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section id="section-1" class="article-paragraph-wrap"&gt;&lt;p class="article-paragraph-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;Melanoma typically starts on skin that’s often exposed to the sun, such as the arms, back, and face. It can form in the eyes. Rarely, it can happen inside the body, such as in the nose or throat. Tanning beds are also responsible for the development of the malignancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section id="section-3" class="article-default-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although it can appear anywhere – including palms, soles, or under nails – the major signs involve changes in moles or new spots with irregular shapes, borders, colors, or slowly developing bleeding or itching – so early detection is crucial as it’s more likely to spread than other skin cancers. &lt;a href="https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/article-879904"&gt;Treatment&lt;/a&gt; usually involves surgery, potentially followed by immunotherapy, chemotherapy, or radiation if it has spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section id="section-6" class="article-paragraph-wrap"&gt;&lt;p class="article-paragraph-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;Although Israel has a relatively high incidence of melanoma compared to many countries – partly due to frequent sun exposure (intentional when getting a sunburn) or unintentional, and the prevalence of unprotected fair skin among many residents – the mortality rates are relatively low thanks to early detection and good treatment outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section id="section-8" class="article-paragraph-wrap"&gt;&lt;p class="article-paragraph-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;According to the Health Ministry, there are between 1,700 and 2,000 new diagnoses of this type of skin cancer in Israel every year. Worldwide, there are about 200,000 cases – half of them noninvasive and the rest invasive – with some 8,000 deaths per year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section class="article-paragraph-wrap"&gt;&lt;section id="section-10" class="article-body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;figure class="article-image-in-body"&gt;&lt;img alt="MELANOMA CELLS (green) are shown in co-culture with the patient’s own immune cells from Sheba Medical Center." loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" src="https://images.jpost.com/image/upload/f_auto,fl_lossy/c_fill,g_faces:center,h_537,w_822/701234"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="article-image-caption article-image-credit"&gt;MELANOMA CELLS (green) are shown in co-culture with the patient’s own immune cells from Sheba Medical Center. (credit: TAU)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;h3 id="section-11" class="article-header-section article-body-paragraph injected"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research breakthrough with major implications for treatment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;section id="section-12" class="article-default-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there is good news: A major achievement with far-reaching implications for treating deadly skin cancer has been discovered by &lt;a href="https://www.jpost.com/science/article-882401"&gt;Tel Aviv University scientists and colleagues&lt;/a&gt;. They discovered a mechanism that allows melanoma cancer cells to paralyze immune cells by secreting extracellular vesicles (EVs), which are tiny, bubble-shaped containers secreted from a given cell. The research team believes that this discovery has far-reaching implications for possible treatments for melanoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section id="section-14" class="article-default-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This dramatic breakthrough was led by Prof. Carmit Levy of the human genetics and computational medicine department at TAU’s Gray Faculty of Medical and Health Sciences – in collaboration with research teams from the Weizmann Institute of Science, the Technion – Israel Institute of Technology, Tel Aviv Sourasky Medical Center, Hadassah-University Medical Center, Rabin Medical Center, Wolfson Medical Center, &lt;a href="https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/article-882606"&gt;Sheba Medical Center&lt;/a&gt;, the University of Liège (Belgium), Massachusetts General Hospital, Paris-Saclay University, and the University of Zurich.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section id="section-15" class="article-default-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study’s findings have just been published in the prestigious journal &lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt; under the title “HLA export by melanoma cells decoys cytotoxic T cells to promote immune evasion.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section id="section-17" class="article-default-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Levy, who received a master’s degree in pharmacy and a Ph.D. in biochemistry from the Hebrew University, plus post-doctoral studies at Harvard University, has worked on this project for almost six years. She said in an interview with &lt;em&gt;The Jerusalem Post&lt;/em&gt; that it was known that there are immune cells in metastases biopsies of melanoma, but it was not known if and how they could kill the immune cells that attack. “When we made our discovery, it was very surprising to us and everybody in the field,” she said. She and her lab team start working on other cancers as well. “It will take time to reach the bedside, but we are eager to take a step forward.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section id="section-18" class="article-paragraph-wrap"&gt;&lt;p class="article-paragraph-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;In the first stage of the disease, melanocytic cells divide uncontrollably in the epidermis, which is the skin’s outer layer. In the second stage, the cancer cells invade the inner dermis layer and metastasize through the lymphatic and blood systems. In previous studies, Levy discovered that as they grow in the epidermis, melanoma cells secrete large EVs called melanosomes, which penetrate blood vessels and dermal cells, forming a favorable niche for the cancer cells to spread. The new study found that these vesicles also enable cancer cells to paralyze the immune cells that attack them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section id="section-19" class="article-default-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We began studying these vesicles,” Levy told the &lt;em&gt;Post&lt;/em&gt;, “and I noticed that on the vesicles membrane there was a ligand – a binding molecule that is supposed to bind to a receptor found only on immune cells called lymphocytes that can kill cancer cells when coming into direct contact with them. I thought that this ligand latches onto lymphocytes that come to kill the melanoma. This was an innovative and odd idea and we started investigating it in the lab.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section id="section-20" class="article-paragraph-wrap"&gt;&lt;p class="article-paragraph-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;When the TAU team collected more evidence that this idea was correct, she contacted colleagues around the world. All came together in a joint effort to decipher the cancer’s behavior – and the achievement is enormous. “We discovered that the cancer essentially fires these vesicles at the immune cells that attack it, disrupting their activity and even killing them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section id="section-21" class="article-paragraph-wrap"&gt;&lt;p class="article-paragraph-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;Levy’s research focuses on the molecular and cellular mechanisms underlying the development, progression, and microenvironment interactions of melanoma and other cancers, including the role of microRNAs, particularly in melanocyte differentiation and malignant transformation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section id="section-22" class="article-paragraph-wrap"&gt;&lt;p class="article-paragraph-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;She received her doctorate from the Hebrew University of Jerusalem, completed post-doctoral studies at Harvard University, and in 2019 was awarded with the Young Investigator Award by the Society of Melanoma Research Congress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section id="section-23" class="article-paragraph-wrap"&gt;&lt;p class="article-paragraph-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;Levy stressed that the extraordinary discovery is promising, but that more work is needed to translate it into a new therapy. “We still have a great deal of work ahead of us, but it is already clear that this discovery can have far-reaching therapeutic implications,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section id="section-24" class="article-paragraph-wrap"&gt;&lt;p class="article-paragraph-section article-body-paragraph"&gt;“It will enable us to strengthen immune cells so they can withstand the melanoma’s counterattack. In parallel, as we successfully did in a mice model, we can block the molecules that enables vesicles to cling to immune cells, thereby exposing the cancer cells and making them more vulnerable. Either way, this study opens a new door to effective immunotherapeutic intervention. “Our study highlights a novel immune evasion mechanism,” she concluded, “and proposes a therapeutic avenue to enhance tumor immunity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Jerusalem Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:41:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZ0FVX3lxTE5ySk1YQVRIVnllVHdxZk4tLUdYYmo0QTJsNkoxS0JWWFUtZVJsbmlGdlFDT0R1STlfRDNMaHc4cHRDb3Vody1BWXJVaThrRXJPQkV0MmRWM0UyRDdFZlduQk4xMDBlbmc</guid></item><item><title>根据心理学，在这8项日常任务中挣扎的人通常比95%的人更聪明- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/r-t-people-who-struggle-with-these-8-everyday-tasks-are-often-more-intelligent-than-95-of-people-according-to-psychology/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;There’s a quiet shame that comes with struggling at things everyone else seems to do without thinking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You miss deadlines, forget small details, or feel oddly out of place in situations that look simple on the surface.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve felt that shame before, especially in my twenties when I was working in luxury food and beverage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The environment demanded polish, speed, and social ease, and yet some of the sharpest minds I met were the ones quietly wrestling with basic, everyday stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Psychology backs this up in a way that feels almost comforting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intelligence doesn’t always show up as efficiency, smoothness, or consistency, and in many cases it shows up as friction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever wondered why your brain seems to trip over things others breeze through, this list might explain more than you expect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1) Making small talk&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/s-if-small-talk-makes-you-want-to-scream-you-probably-have-these-7-rare-personality-traits/"&gt;Small talk&lt;/a&gt; is one of those social skills that’s treated like a basic requirement for adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you struggle with it, people assume you’re awkward, unfriendly, or lacking confidence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But for highly intelligent people, the issue usually isn’t social fear. It’s boredom mixed with a hunger for substance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research suggests that people with higher &lt;a href="https://www.happyneuronpro.com/en/info/what-are-cognitive-abilities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;cognitive ability&lt;/a&gt; tend to seek meaning, patterns, and depth in conversation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When an interaction offers none of that, their brains disengage almost immediately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve sat through countless dinners where the conversation revolved around weather, surface-level work complaints, or recycled anecdotes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My mind would drift not because I disliked the people, but because my brain was itching for something more nourishing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For some minds, small talk feels like empty calories. It fills time but leaves no mental satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2) Sticking to rigid routines&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a popular idea that discipline looks like doing the same thing at the same time every day. Wake up early, follow a strict schedule, repeat forever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highly intelligent people often struggle with this kind of rigidity. Their minds crave novelty, variation, and flexibility more than repetition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Psychological studies have linked higher intelligence with &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2937090/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;openness&lt;/a&gt; to experience and sensitivity to stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That combination makes rigid routines feel mentally suffocating over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve tried hyper-optimized &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/d-bt-8-morning-routines-that-give-you-an-unfair-advantage-in-life/"&gt;morning routines&lt;/a&gt; more times than I care to admit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They work for a short burst, then my brain starts rebelling and asking why everything has to happen in the same order every day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t mean you lack discipline. It often means your mind is wired to adapt rather than repeat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3) Finishing simple tasks quickly&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know the task should take five minutes. Somehow, it takes thirty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highly intelligent people &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/k-t-you-can-tell-someone-was-raised-by-emotionally-distant-parents-if-they-do-these-8-things-in-relationships/"&gt;tend to overanalyze&lt;/a&gt; even the smallest decisions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their brains naturally explore multiple possibilities, outcomes, and implications before settling on action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Psychologists sometimes call this &lt;a href="https://www.goodrx.com/health-topic/mental-health/how-can-i-stop-overthinking-everything?srsltid=AfmBOoq8lTC3kABWsWxXDcSxluyiK_NG9O-viqLMtDd_RBaP3Qs0jmoR" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;overthinking&lt;/a&gt;, but that label misses the point. It’s not anxiety driving the process, it’s depth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve caught myself spending way too long choosing what to order at a restaurant, thinking through flavor combinations, portion sizes, and regret minimization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the server is just trying to move the table along.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When your brain is built for complexity, simplicity doesn’t come naturally. Even basic tasks get upgraded into mini thought experiments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4) Letting go of mistakes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-90934" src="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking-.png" alt="" srcset="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking-.png 1600w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--300x158.png 300w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--1024x538.png 1024w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--768x403.png 768w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--1536x806.png 1536w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--1200x630.png 1200w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--857x450.png 857w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--900x473.png 900w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--420x221.png 420w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Thinking--840x441.png 840w" sizes="(max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some people mess up and move on instantly. Others replay the moment in their head for days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highly intelligent people are far more likely to struggle with this. Their brains &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/z-lc-8-signs-youre-not-a-perfectionist-youre-just-terrified-of-being-seen-failing/"&gt;treat mistakes as data&lt;/a&gt; that needs to be analyzed and integrated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From a psychological standpoint, this makes sense. Intelligence is closely tied to learning, and learning depends on noticing errors and adjusting behavior.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In high-pressure kitchens, mistakes are expensive and visible. You either reflect on them deeply or repeat them and fall behind fast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The challenge is that the same mental habit that helps you grow can also trap you in self-criticism if you don’t consciously let the lesson end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5) Falling asleep easily&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your mind lights up the moment your head hits the pillow, you’re not alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highly intelligent people often struggle to fall asleep because their brains don’t naturally slow down on command.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/psychology/articles/10.3389/fpsyg.2025.1476840/full" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Studies&lt;/a&gt; have linked higher cognitive engagement with increased nighttime mental activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When external stimulation disappears, internal processing ramps up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve had nights where a single idea snowballed into a full mental outline for an article, a career plan, or a half-baked business concept.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Great for creativity, terrible for rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn’t a failure of discipline or routine. It’s a brain that’s &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/gen-if-you-think-in-these-8-complex-ways-your-mind-operates-differently-than-95-of-people/"&gt;wired to think deeply&lt;/a&gt; whenever it has space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6) Remembering mundane details&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highly intelligent people often have &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/s-t-10-childhood-details-only-people-with-exceptional-memory-still-remember/"&gt;excellent memory&lt;/a&gt; for concepts, patterns, and ideas. Strangely, they tend to struggle with basic, everyday details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Psychology suggests this comes down to &lt;a href="https://www.verywellmind.com/what-is-selective-attention-2795022" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;selective attention&lt;/a&gt;. The brain prioritizes information it deems meaningful and filters out the rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ask me about a book I read years ago and I can recall its core argument with ease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ask me where I put my keys an hour ago and I’ll need to retrace my steps like a detective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t mean your memory is bad. It means it’s optimized for meaning, not logistics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7) Staying present in boring environments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Long meetings, repetitive lectures, or conversations that go nowhere can feel physically uncomfortable for highly intelligent people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their minds disengage quickly when stimulation drops below a certain threshold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research links intelligence with a tendency toward &lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/374102703_Intentional_mind_wandering_is_objectively_linked_to_low_effort_and_tasks_with_high_predictability" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;mental wandering&lt;/a&gt; in low-engagement environments. The brain seeks complexity when none is provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve mentally planned meals, workouts, articles, and entire trips while sitting in painfully dull settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the outside, it might look like disinterest, but internally the brain is just staying busy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This trait can be a liability in structured environments. It can also be a powerful source of creativity if you learn how to channel it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;8) Finally, turning off self-criticism&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, one of the most overlooked struggles of highly intelligent people is their relationship with themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intelligence brings awareness, and awareness often brings harsh self-evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You notice gaps others miss. You see inefficiencies, flaws, and missed opportunities with uncomfortable clarity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Psychology has long noted the connection between intelligence and heightened &lt;a href="https://paradigmpersonality.com/resources/self-monitoring-psychology-101/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;self-monitoring&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The same mind that analyzes the world with precision turns inward with equal force.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve met incredibly capable people who &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/n-t-8-behaviors-of-people-who-have-lost-their-self-worth-without-realizing-it/"&gt;downplay their achievements&lt;/a&gt; while obsessing over minor missteps. Externally impressive, internally relentless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learning to soften that internal voice isn’t about lowering standards. It’s about recognizing when analysis has stopped being useful and started becoming noise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Struggling with everyday tasks doesn’t automatically mean you’re failing at life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In many cases, it means your brain is optimized for depth, complexity, and meaning in a world that rewards speed and surface-level competence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you understand this, the shame starts to dissolve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You stop trying to force yourself into systems that don’t fit and start building ones that actually support how your mind works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intelligence isn’t always visible. Sometimes it shows up quietly, in the friction between a deep mind and a shallow world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you recognized yourself in this list, you’re not broken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’re just wired differently, and that difference can become a strength once you learn how to work with it instead of against it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-4240840399"&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong data-start="380" data-end="431"&gt;If You Were a Healing Herb, Which Would You Be?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each herb holds a unique kind of magic — soothing, awakening, grounding, or clarifying.&lt;br data-start="521" data-end="524"&gt;This 9-question quiz reveals the healing plant that mirrors your energy right now and what it says about your natural rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;✨ Instant results. Deeply insightful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="g-ytsubscribe" data-channelid="UCdGKHK52616Dpj-FpFjeNSg" data-layout="full" data-count="hidden"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:04:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6AFBVV95cUxQcUJSdzFRN1JoT3cxVGNKeUNIbVFqRlRkWFVXN1lmakM2R3lsbmRMc1Fvd3ExS1htNHlFZ09weGxyQ2Fic1ROT1c3MEsxYS02YVZ0aXNBNWFWRTlmWTVQSUlCV0hUNVBvTmZIQ1k3bjMtdnNJeUEzWm1acFpHZE1WanlsQVI5bk5vS1JqZ1JnRVMxdEJtS3JiX2xjOFJyaDNrdGd4ZFdVX1ozRi0xaEgyczVVcktlZ1dRbXV6UDVZMlh3UERuYmFpT3UtSkwwbmFQay1EVi0yY0tnUmFoX2VCaWtocGg1VHUx</guid></item><item><title>俄勒冈州警告林恩县两家医院可能有麻疹暴露- OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2026/01/oregon-warns-of-possible-measles-exposure-at-two-linn-county-hospitals.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3S2377OGL5ESND5FFG2AT6R7GQ"&gt;People who visited two hospitals in Linn County during specific times this week may have been exposed to &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/06/oregon-confirms-first-measles-case-of-2025-linked-to-international-travel.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/06/oregon-confirms-first-measles-case-of-2025-linked-to-international-travel.html"&gt;measles&lt;/a&gt;, a highly &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2019/10/measles-makes-your-body-forget-how-to-fight-other-diseases.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2019/10/measles-makes-your-body-forget-how-to-fight-other-diseases.html"&gt;infectious virus&lt;/a&gt; that spreads through the air and in rare cases can be fatal, Oregon officials said Saturday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IFOELF33PZDLHIFAKSL6HNJU3Q"&gt;The two people with Oregon’s first confirmed measles cases in 2026 developed &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2019/10/measles-or-flu-know-the-symptoms.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2019/10/measles-or-flu-know-the-symptoms.html"&gt;symptoms&lt;/a&gt; — a rash, fever, cough and runny nose — on Jan. 5. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4S2PAWGN75DPJMRJKMOADR7BOE"&gt;The measles virus can linger for up to two hours after an infected person leaves an area. The Oregon Health Authority said that people who visited one of two hospitals Jan. 6 or Jan. 7 could have been exposed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7FQZDSJG6NBG5KNCHVVLE6Z4K4"&gt;People could have been exposed to measles if they were at:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="article__unordered-list"&gt;&lt;li id="CLGYDNMOXVA7TML446UUQPLU6Y"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Lebanon Community Hospital Emergency Department between 8:53 p.m. on Jan. 6 and 7 a.m. on Jan. 7&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="WITNM2ETFFD5VAR4A33NT4YCA4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Albany General Hospital Emergency Department between 4:59 a.m. and 8:15 a.m. Jan. 7&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3HQI4QB5SVB7NAQKQA6V4RZQJM"&gt;Anyone who was at either of those hospitals during those times should immediately tell their doctor they may have been exposed to the measles virus, the health authority warned. Their doctor will then be able to determine whether they are immune to the virus based on their vaccination record and other factors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:SLTSWQF3NZCUTNLS2YLKIUU4CA" data-fusion-component="SLTSWQF3NZCUTNLS2YLKIUU4CA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:SLTSWQF3NZCUTNLS2YLKIUU4CA" data-fusion-component="SLTSWQF3NZCUTNLS2YLKIUU4CA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KSPDMSID3BGUBHIHUEUE4DIGZE"&gt;Measles symptoms usually appear seven to 21 days after exposure and include fever, cough, runny nose and red eyes, followed by a rash that starts on the face and spreads to the rest of the body, the health authority said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6CNW7SEOZ5C77N5XPE5X7AV5LI"&gt;Most people infected with measles survive without complications. But the disease is nonetheless dangerous and can cause brain swelling and even death. The disease is particularly dangerous for infants and people with weakened immune symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GOUB3OJ5QRDANMRKGUXJPUUKBE"&gt;Measles &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/04/there-are-800-measles-cases-in-the-us-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-outbreaks.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/04/there-are-800-measles-cases-in-the-us-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-outbreaks.html"&gt;has been on the rise nationally&lt;/a&gt;, with the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention recording the &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/07/measles-cases-in-the-us-reach-highest-levels-in-33-years-cdc-reports.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/07/measles-cases-in-the-us-reach-highest-levels-in-33-years-cdc-reports.html"&gt;worst year for measles spread&lt;/a&gt; in more than three decades just halfway through 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ABTYCRID2VHO5IQAXS2QOPA5YM"&gt;The agency reported 2,144 confirmed cases nationwide by the end of the year, including three that were fatal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GOSPBTJE7FAKTJ6Q7EJOLFH3EQ"&gt;Oregon had &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/06/oregon-confirms-first-measles-case-of-2025-linked-to-international-travel.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/06/oregon-confirms-first-measles-case-of-2025-linked-to-international-travel.html"&gt;just one confirmed measles case&lt;/a&gt; last year, according to CDC data. But the state reported 31 confirmed infections in 2024, according to CDC data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BKDS7OP3XBBR5IJ5GVYB5GU23M"&gt;The measles vaccine is highly effective, with two doses of the measles-mumps-rubella vaccine preventing 97% of infections, according to the Oregon Health Authority. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MEJDXXK2WBCWNCJZ3WIA6W6DVY"&gt;Distrust in government and misinformation erroneously linking vaccines to autism have contributed to declining vaccination rates and a concomitant increase in infections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZEU7Y65MYNHTTDG3FGTLXW7OGA"&gt;The health authority continued to urge Oregonians to get themselves and their children vaccinated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JFQALZUMYFGSBAOMBKZE4YU5J4"&gt;“Measles is here in Oregon and rates are increasing nationally,” said Dr. Howard Chiou, OHA’s medical director for communicable diseases and immunizations. “We encourage everyone to make sure they’re protected by talking with their providers about being up to date on vaccinations.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:22:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxNM1dBdkhEUG9fZXNaTzl4Zl9wVmFQeFptTDlreFFGM2V3bVFiVTE3bVJIdllWWS1adWZLem1XenFqVG03VmtxMVota0Iyc0JJZ0JhanVPR0NUVDUwc1k3b1FGSUNFbU9VVUhELTYyV0RUcGdZblozT0V2eDNWbjFFQk1XZ25uRU8tUUJ1dWhpYzN0MFF3QS1nMHJPOUJHdlB1aU9RelVzMWdnaHFWeElxSlZjSFkxQk1S0gHMAUFVX3lxTE50NVJlVERWc0M2XzlVY211WW42VDhCbWtXd1RfMG5NU1NmN1BqMnlpN2NBWGN3X05raDlqVnE5T1FJbWVLTE13QWJ2NTB1MDZseTZjdGVveW5iSVdqeE5ULUt5R2dJRFBfeFZzbGI3ZEw2djF0ZUZ6dlBuLWtOMVBDZTNKVFpFb2xzY3BKTDFENHcxRkpCV1poamR1MGQ3T2xqWUJDSDRsSFRnWEl6NVRLSXlUaHlxN0RIbzlMQzJ1Y2N6VzBZMU56dmxkZw</guid></item><item><title>2000年的坟墓揭示了神秘的红色毒性惊喜，确认了一次未知的古代埋葬实践-汇报</title><link>https://thedebrief.org/2000-year-old-grave-reveals-mysterious-red-toxic-surprise-confirming-once-unknown-ancient-burial-practice/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;
																										&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/category/archaeology/"&gt;Archaeologists&lt;/a&gt; have made an unexpected discovery within a 2,000-year-old grave in Ukraine that may reshape our existing knowledge of ancient &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/burial-pits-in-france-reveal-grisly-evidence-of-brutality-during-warfare-and-captivity-in-neolithic-europe/"&gt;burial traditions&lt;/a&gt; in the region.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The discovery of a red pigment within a grave located at Chervony Mayak, an ancient &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/scientists-analyzing-ancient-scythian-artifacts-have-made-a-gruesome-discovery/"&gt;Scythian&lt;/a&gt; cemetery in the southern part of the country, has revealed the presence of cinnabar, according to researchers who say the &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/60000-year-old-projectiles-are-the-worlds-first-poison-arrows-extending-earliest-use-in-africa-by-thousands-of-years/"&gt;toxic&lt;/a&gt; mineral has never been previously identified within burial sites associated with the Late Scythian period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The pigment was found to be a thin layer covering sediment composed of quartz, microcline, albite, and calcite,” report the authors of a recent study that appeared in &lt;em&gt;Antiquity &lt;/em&gt;describing the discovery, who note that the sample was comprised of small, sharp-edged particles amid “chemical compounds present in the grave fill” at the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The discovery is significant because it illustrates what appears to be a previously undocumented aspect of burial customs from the period. Presently, researchers believe the use of cinnabar at the location was intentional, possibly with &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/ancient-ritual-sacrifice-archaeologists-are-unraveling-the-enigma-of-an-ancient-ecuadorian-burial/"&gt;ritual&lt;/a&gt; significance that has yet to be determined.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Study in Scarlet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cinnabar, sometimes also known as “cinnabarite” or “mercurblende,” bears a striking bright red coloration. A form of mercury sulfide, it is also the most abundant ore used in the refinement of elemental mercury. Past discoveries already recognize the mineral as having been used prevalently in the &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/mysterious-figurines-from-sardinias-bronze-age-reveal-an-unexpected-discovery-about-the-ancient-world/"&gt;ancient world&lt;/a&gt; for its bright scarlet coloration, which was incorporated into a variety of pigments used in the ancient world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite its striking appearance that attracted its use in colorful pigments, people in the ancient world also knew about the toxic properties of cinnabar, with some theories even suggesting that &lt;a href="https://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/love-of-wine-leads-to-chance-discovery-of-widespread-mercury-poisoning-in-copper-age-180979091/"&gt;it may have been intentionally ingested&lt;/a&gt; under some circumstances as part of ritual ceremonies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The archaeological team behind the recent discovery in Ukraine says the toxic mineral was found in grave 155, a location at Chervony Mayak where the remains of two women had been found. Evidence indicates their burials occurred at different times, and near the skull of the older of the two women, three small deposits of red material were found, alongside other items that included beaded jewelry and items made from copper alloy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analyzing a Toxic Discovery&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the appearance of red substances in graves from the period is not particularly unusual, past testing of their composition—if it occurs at all—had never previously identified the toxic mineral in question, according to study lead author Olena Dzneladze of the National Academy of Science of Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this instance, the presence of cinnabar was confirmed following testing that included examination of the substance using scanning electron microscopy and X-ray diffraction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_43327" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-43327" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-43327 lazyload" data-src="https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/cinnabar-site.jpg" alt="cinnabar" data-srcset="https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/cinnabar-site.jpg 1864w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/cinnabar-site-300x177.jpg 300w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/cinnabar-site-1024x603.jpg 1024w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/cinnabar-site-768x452.jpg 768w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/cinnabar-site-1536x905.jpg 1536w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/cinnabar-site-770x454.jpg 770w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/cinnabar-site-1400x825.jpg 1400w" data-sizes="(max-width: 1864px) 100vw, 1864px" src=""&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-43327" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Detail view of cinnabar sample recovered from the site (Image Credit: Olena Dzneladze/Antiquity/Open Access)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It is not currently possible to determine precisely the function(s) of cinnabar and the other red pigments found in Late Scythian graves, but their deposition in graves appears intentional,” Dzneladze and colleagues write in their paper. “Different pigments may have had distinct functions, although more broadly they likely had a ritual, germicidal, as well as cosmetic and pharmaceutical role,” they add.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tracing Ancient Scythian Cinnabar &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although the location from which the cinnabar may have originated has not yet been determined, the team says that it is known to be found in southern Ukraine, and that its origin may be determinable through future studies, which may help to provide context for its appearance in the burial at Chervony Mayak, as well as how it might have been used in trade during this period in history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“These results highlight the vital role of archaeometric analyses in examining and correcting the interpretation of mineral substances discovered at some archaeological sites,” Dzneladze and the team conclude.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The application of such analyses is still rare, and further discussion of the function and provenance of pigments can proceed only with additional analyses and when the reference database is extended,” they add.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team’s &lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/antiquity/article/mysterious-red-cinnabar-from-the-chervony-mayak-burial-ground-ukraine/99A5ECFAA469E559488E1736BC694AEB"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt;, “Mysterious red: cinnabar from the Chervony Mayak burial ground, Ukraine,” was published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Antiquity &lt;/em&gt;last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Micah Hanks is the Editor-in-Chief and Co-Founder of The Debrief. A longtime reporter on science, defense, and technology with a focus on space and astronomy, he can be reached at&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:micah@thedebrief.org"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;micah@thedebrief.org&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Follow him on X &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/MicahHanks"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;@MicahHanks&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;, and at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.micahhanks.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;micahhanks.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Debrief</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:15:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiyAFBVV95cUxONDBuVDhyUXdNRlh3N3NOT1J1WXpLM0Q5RmdYc3A2VEI2SDJCTzk5cEMtZTgxN2xzQUhWUjBiMVp4Nm5jM0ktQjhvVGlucUFlQ3dRT0xydXRJb2dCZVRNQ2hZV0NEazJRakNvNTFzRUxDSU9pckhRd0pJRnBkdnpYbUhkUGpsU2txX3JrMV9kSlFiMjlJbkw1b1l6MjBnb1NRcklsTnVucFA4N0hYYnFiNTJhWWRMTlNBRXRUU2t0MGl5amFaUWdlQg</guid></item><item><title>流感季节流泪穿越弗吉尼亚州北部- InsideNoVa.com</title><link>https://www.insidenova.com/news/fairfax/nasty-flu-season-tears-through-northern-virginia/article_b885e69b-eb59-424e-b1a5-b119d986e754.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;It’s that time of year again, but this time it’s particularly bad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Respiratory illnesses, especially influenza, are tearing through Northern Virginia, accounting for 22% of ER visits in the week ending Jan. 3, &lt;a href="https://www.vdh.virginia.gov/epidemiology/respiratory-diseases-in-virginia/data/"&gt;according to the Virginia Department of Health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;A particularly nasty strand of influenza A, subclade k, is driving this flu season, which peaks from December to February. The mutated strand emerged after the 2025 flu vaccine was developed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;The U.S. Centers for Disease Control &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-52.html"&gt;estimates&lt;/a&gt; there have been at least 11 million cases of flu this season nationwide. The CDC also estimates 120,000 hospitalizations and 5,000 deaths. The spread is rated at high or very high in 48 states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Dr. Meredith Porter, medical director for Inova-GoHealth Urgent Care in Northern Virginia, said there are “very high acute respiratory illness levels” across the region. The urgent care system is a joint venture between Inova and GoHealth and operates 23 centers across the region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="opscoad-nvm_instory_ad" data-unit="/22545743209/insidenova/news/fairfax/instory" data-targeting='{"pos":"nvm_instory"}'&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;The urgent care system is increasing support staff and extending virtual visit hours to midnight to meet demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;“We’re trying our best to avoid people going to the emergency room,” Porter told InsideNoVa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;There might be a light at the end of the tunnel, Porter said. Statewide, the number of respiratory-related cases at ERs dropped from the week ending Dec. 27 to the week ending Jan. 3.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;This flu season started picking up after school was out and people started traveling for the holidays, Porter said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="opscoad-nvm_instory_ad" data-unit="/22545743209/insidenova/news/fairfax/instory" data-targeting='{"pos":"nvm_instory"}'&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;“When you are around a lot of people, you may not yet know that you’re starting to get sick,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Porter said the typical flu symptoms start, and “you almost feel like you’ve been hit by a bus.” That includes body aches, fever, cough and fatigue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Unless you’re having difficulty breathing, chest pain, dehydration or changes to your lucidity, Porter recommended going to a primary care or urgent care first. Those providers can provide early testing and antiviral treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;If you’ve got the flu, rest as much as possible and stay hydrated. If you’ve got to go out into the world, Porter recommended wearing a mask and staying as far from others as possible. The first three days after the onset of symptoms are when people are the most contagious, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="opscoad-nvm_instory_ad" data-unit="/22545743209/insidenova/news/fairfax/instory" data-targeting='{"pos":"nvm_instory"}'&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;For everyone else, Porter recommended using hand sanitizer, washing your hands frequently, wipe down things like grocery store carts and keep your distance from people who look symptomatic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;“If you’re standing in that check out line,” she said, “give yourself a bit of space.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="clearfix"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>InsideNoVa.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:51:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1AFBVV95cUxOQlpGUkdDdHNaREdWTUJxLXd6MlRsZjYyMS1ySmJkMUp3WjRrSGRwV0RZYTVnRktvWWdDY0ItQ3Ntb25PdksxUmJkX3JyaHJ6cW5sY0o2endnN1pZN1E0YlJPdnFNODVzZVdRVVAyTUZxSEVHZ2Z2ZkV5YXo4Y1FrSjVpTU5CR0tvVTYwWUxyc3BHbzlsaWtWVDh4VmY5QUN2bzFiSk5OU1R4SFVvRFpOcm9GUm5objFlSmpEQ2stQzdwU3QwQldmdWdFS3hJUlpkNjdERg</guid></item><item><title>科学家警告新的生物风险，并呼吁召开国际峰会- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-warn-of-new-biological-risk-mirror-life-call-for-global-summit/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thirty-eight researchers from around the world are urging caution over mirror life – a hypothetical form of biology built from mirror-image molecules that could behave unpredictably in natural systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In response, a major biomedical research institute in Paris is convening an international summit to examine the risks and consider early boundaries before the science moves closer to reality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-the-summit-matters"&gt;Why the summit matters&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 1847, while working at the &lt;a href="https://www.pasteur.fr/en/chirality-and-life" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Pasteur Institute&lt;/a&gt;, Louis Pasteur described chirality – molecules existing in two mirror forms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That same institute has spent generations tracking microbes and immunity, giving credibility when it flags new dangers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2025, a public symposium on mirror life streamed from Paris. Organized with the Mirror Biology Dialogues Fund, it opened the discussion to scientists, policymakers, and the public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-a-risk-worth-naming"&gt;A risk worth naming&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2024, authors warned that &lt;a href="https://pure.manchester.ac.uk/ws/files/361362332/Accepted_Version_for_SDR_Confronting_risks_of_mirror_life.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;mirror bacteria&lt;/a&gt; – bacteria made from reversed biomolecules – should not be created, even if such work remains a decade away. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These worries sit inside synthetic biology, engineering living systems for new functions, where creativity moves fast and mistakes can scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike most lab creations, a reproducing microbe can spread on its own, meaning even a small release can escalate into a large problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-molecules-with-handedness"&gt;Molecules with handedness&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earth shows &lt;a href="https://ntrs.nasa.gov/citations/20060047634" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;homochirality&lt;/a&gt;, with life using one molecular handedness. Proteins are built from L-amino acids, and DNA is made from D-sugars. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cells run on enzymes that grab the right shapes, so flipped molecules can slow reactions or stop them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chemists call each mirror version an enantiomer, one of two mirror molecular forms, and whole cells rely on that consistency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-defenses-recognize-threats"&gt;How defenses recognize threats&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Immune cells rely on receptors, cell sensors that bind specific molecules, and mirror surfaces could slip past them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vaccines and past infections train memory using natural proteins, so mirror-made proteins might not trigger the same alarms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many lab tests depend on polymerase, an enzyme that copies &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/oldest-human-genome-reveals-lrj-group-lived-europe-80-generation-then-vanished/"&gt;DNA&lt;/a&gt;, and mirrored DNA might not be readable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-when-ecology-fails"&gt;When ecology fails&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In soil and water, bacteriophages, viruses that infect bacteria in nature, help keep microbial populations from exploding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If mirror bacteria were hard for predators to recognize, normal ecological checks could weaken, giving them extra room to grow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When mirror bacteria evade these pressures, they could reshape nutrient cycles, altering soil health and stressing crops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-containment-is-tricky"&gt;Containment is tricky&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers discuss &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/medicine-and-dentistry/biocontainment" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;biocontainment&lt;/a&gt;, engineered limits that block survival outside labs. Mirror organisms, however, might bypass familiar tricks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Labs also use physical barriers and careful training, yet accidents happen, and microbes do not respect lab schedules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once a novel microbe spreads, detection and response must move quickly, and waiting for harm is risky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-safer-uses-of-mirror-chemistry"&gt;Safer uses of mirror chemistry&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drug developers already make some mirror-image molecules because natural enzymes break them down slowly, which can extend treatment time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those molecules can help researchers test immune responses, and they do not multiply or spread on their own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The risk jumps when chemistry turns into a living system, because living systems can evolve and travel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-soon-is-soon"&gt;How soon is soon&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Building a mirror organism would require mirror versions of &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-inject-40000-year-old-neanderthal-dna-gli3-gene-into-mice-with-incredible-results/"&gt;DNA&lt;/a&gt;, proteins, and metabolism, plus a way to assemble them reliably.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As chemical synthesis improves and automation spreads, more labs can make unusual biomolecules, and interest can grow quickly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This raises the question of how to set limits early enough to matter, while still leaving room for safe discoveries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-rules-before-building"&gt;Rules before building&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is where governance, shared rules and oversight for research, enters, because lab capability often outruns public debate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clear biosecurity, preventing harmful use or release of biology, can focus on steps that enable organisms, not basic chemistry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because microbes cross borders, international coordination matters, and a shared baseline can reduce pressure to cut corners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-who-must-be-involved"&gt;Who must be involved&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This debate needs stakeholders, people affected and involved in decisions. These include &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/mental-health-disorders-reduce-life-expectancy-by-up-to-20-years/"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; agencies, farmers, conservation groups, and industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also needs security voices, because dual-use work, research that can help or harm, sits at the center of this topic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public access matters too, since trust depends on understanding, and people deserve to know what researchers are considering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-workshops-tackle"&gt;What workshops tackle&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Invite-only workshops brought biologists, policymakers, legal experts, ethicists, and social scientists into focused discussions on risk mitigation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants compared possible safeguards, from funding rules to lab standards, and they flagged the hardest unanswered scientific questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A shared record of those discussions can guide future meetings and help align rules across countries and research fields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-signals-for-funders"&gt;Signals for funders&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Funding agencies and philanthropies can refuse projects aimed at building mirror organisms, while supporting safer chemistry and monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grant terms can require open reporting, outside review, and clear stopping points if research starts moving toward risky &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/prototaxites-the-mystery-fossil-from-a-lost-branch-of-life/"&gt;organisms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even mundane choices, like who receives key reagents, can matter when a field is young and competitive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-questions-still-open"&gt;Questions still open&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists still debate how mirror microbes would find nutrients, interact with hosts, and compete in real environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some questions can be tested with nonliving components and computer models, which can sharpen estimates without creating organisms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What level of uncertainty should society accept before saying no, and who gets to make that call?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-transparency-helps"&gt;Why transparency helps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Secrecy can hide problems until they explode, while openness lets peers spot hazards and slow risky momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public livestreams and plain-language &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/fish-that-live-in-the-oceans-twilight-zone-are-the-missing-links-between-sharks-and-their-prey/"&gt;summaries&lt;/a&gt; let non-specialists follow decisions, and that reduces rumor-driven fear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clear language matters, because labeling every new tool a disaster makes people tune out when real warnings arrive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The safest path keeps research on mirror molecules and other basic science open, while drawing a firm line at organisms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early discussions make it easier to agree on limits, before money, national pride, or secrecy pushes risky work ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:36:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPYTJqMGhGQjctekJfLVdHbmhSUXVFXzQwbU10cTNsckV5Q2NwN1JnMGRtbHFfWE1rSWYxYnJEUGtLd05IckVEZHVQaFJraG5GYnZqZGRHRDNhalJqWDRnV09SZkx5ajREOHhGQkFOUURnTExWMFpXeF9LdlVTamM2UjVMNE9OdlJfSXgwZC1WS0R1T3R6ZTB3d0VxVUNqcngyaGZJ</guid></item></channel></rss>