<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>像Adderall这样的多动症药物不像医生和科学家以前认为的那样起作用- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/adhd-stimulant-medications-like-adderall-do-not-work-like-doctors-scientists-believed/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stimulant medication like Ritalin and Adderall are often given to children with ADHD. In the United States, about 3.5 million children between 3 and 17 years old take these medicines, and the number keeps growing as more children are diagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people think the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/adhd-medication-lowers-risks-of-suicide-accidents-and-crime/"&gt;drugs&lt;/a&gt; help children pay attention better, but new research shows that this is not exactly how they work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A large study from Washington University School of Medicine (&lt;a href="https://medicine.washu.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;WashU Medicine&lt;/a&gt;) found that these medicines do not directly change the parts of the brain that control attention. Instead, the drugs make the brain feel more awake and make tasks feel more interesting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a child feels more alert and finds a task more rewarding, it becomes easier to stay with that task, even though their basic ability to focus has not changed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-stimulant-medications-don-t-help-focus"&gt;Stimulant medications don’t help focus&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For many years, clinicians and researchers believed stimulants helped children focus by strengthening brain regions responsible for attention control. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Benjamin Kay, an assistant professor of neurology at WashU Medicine, noted that this view shaped his own medical training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I prescribe a lot of stimulants as a child neurologist, and I’ve always been taught that they facilitate attention systems to give people more voluntary control over what they pay attention to,” said Dr. Kay. “But we’ve shown that’s not the case.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of seeing changes in attention networks, the research team observed the strongest effects in areas related to arousal and reward. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These regions influence how awake the brain feels and how worthwhile an activity appears, both of which strongly affect behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-adhd-medications-change-the-brain"&gt;ADHD medications change the brain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To understand how stimulants change brain activity, the researchers analyzed resting state functional MRI data from 5,795 children aged eight to eleven who participated in the Adolescent Brain Cognitive Development study (&lt;a href="https://abcdstudy.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;ABCD Study&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Resting state scans measure brain activity when no specific task is being performed, allowing researchers to examine underlying brain organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/common-plastics-chemical-bpa-linked-to-autism-adhd-in-children/"&gt;Children&lt;/a&gt; who took stimulants on the day of scanning showed increased activity in brain regions linked to wakefulness and reward. In contrast, regions classically associated with attention did not show significant changes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pattern appeared consistently across the large dataset. Dr. Kay explained why this matters for how improvement is interpreted. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Rather, the improvement we observe in attention is a secondary effect of a child being more alert and finding a task more rewarding, which naturally helps them pay more attention to it,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-same-effect-in-adults"&gt;Same effect in adults&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team validated these results in a controlled experiment involving five healthy adults who did not have ADHD and did not regularly take stimulant medication. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each participant underwent resting state brain scans before and after taking a dose of methylphenidate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once again, the medication altered arousal and reward related brain networks rather than attention circuitry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This confirmation helped rule out explanations tied only to childhood development or ADHD diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-motivation-drives-improvement"&gt;Motivation drives improvement&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Essentially, we found that stimulants pre-reward our brains and allow us to keep working at things that wouldn’t normally hold our interest – like our least favorite class in school, for example,” said study senior author Dr. Nico U. Dosenbach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This increase in perceived reward helps explain why stimulant medications often improve persistence and reduce hyperactivity. Tasks that once felt unrewarding no longer trigger the urge to disengage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These results also provide a potential explanation for how stimulants treat &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/dog-adhd-impacts-learning-but-small-changes-can-help/"&gt;hyperactivity&lt;/a&gt;, which previously seemed paradoxical,” noted Dr. Dosenbach. “Whatever kids can’t focus on – those tasks that make them fidgety – are tasks that they find unrewarding.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-sleep-affects-adhd-stimulant-benefits"&gt;Sleep affects ADHD stimulant benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleep emerged as a critical factor in the study. Many children in the dataset did not get the recommended nine or more hours of sleep each night. Short sleep duration was linked to poorer school grades and altered brain connectivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children with ADHD who took stimulant medication performed better academically than peers with ADHD who did not take stimulants. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children who slept too little but took stimulants also showed better grades than sleep-deprived children who did not take medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We saw that if a participant didn’t sleep enough, but they took a stimulant, the brain signature of insufficient sleep was erased, as were the associated behavioral and cognitive decrements,” said Dr. Dosenbach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-reevaluating-adhd-medications"&gt;Reevaluating ADHD medications&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The experts emphasized that stimulants cannot replace healthy sleep. “Not getting enough sleep is always bad for you, and it’s especially bad for kids,” said Dr. Kay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He noted that sleep deprivation can mimic ADHD symptoms, including difficulty paying attention and declining school performance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some cases, stimulant medication may appear to help by mimicking the effects of adequate sleep while leaving the long term consequences of sleep loss unaddressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings suggest a shift in how stimulant medications should be understood. Rather than directly improving attention, these drugs increase alertness and make tasks feel more &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/autism-and-adhd-disorders-directly-linked-amount-of-time-kids-spend-on-screens/"&gt;rewarding&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That combination can improve persistence and performance, especially in children with ADHD or those who do not get enough sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By separating attention from arousal and motivation, this research offers a clearer explanation for how stimulant medications shape behavior and brain activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01373-X" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:49:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxPLTNaWlpWM2F5UkNqam9MeGhhalZwcnJ6Y05QUEs3YzhJT3hQN3JPa3NRUHM2ZEZVMlNDem9rUlg2d0ZZYUV2WHlVMWVJaUpSNThNQlIyNHdnVzFwd09tVGx5RVJ4enQ3dHFtNmJyX2FmYU5ZZjZjSHRKeDJPZnpJLTdvaVF3dHhfZDQzSE9DT2lBcGNTRlctRWZNMEpWMF96amVfeUxJWVRpNXJhTGgxamVoYw</guid></item><item><title>在呼吸道疾病增加的情况下，地区医院暂时实施访客限制- WHIO TV</title><link>https://www.whio.com/news/local/temporarily-visitor-restrictions-place-area-hospitals-amid-increase-respiratory-illness/K4OXQGZYENAVJJJN32DJRWUZXA/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="default__ArticleBody-sc-tl066j-1 jPcFTl article-body-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;MIAMI VALLEY — Today, 29 hospitals and health systems across the region are implementing temporary visitor restrictions amid a recent increase in respiratory illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[DOWNLOAD: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.whio.com/mobile-apps/" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.whio.com/mobile-apps/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free WHIO-TV News app for alerts as news breaks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Area hospitals are currently seeing higher-than-normal volumes of patients with positive cases of respiratory illnesses, including influenza, COVID-19, and other seasonal viruses, according to the Greater Dayton Area Hospital Association (GDAHA).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;TRENDING STORIES:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more" class="taboola-read-more"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;As part of the restrictions, anyone ill with any respiratory symptoms, including coughing, fever, chills, headache, vomiting, sore throat, muscle aches, or diarrhea, will not be allowed to visit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;The same goes for anyone under the age of 14, even if they have received the seasonal vaccine or received the appropriate vaccine when it becomes available. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Hospitals are asking community members to postpone visiting if they are feeling unwell, especially if experiencing symptoms such as fever, cough, sore throat, or congestion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;As reported at &lt;b&gt;News Center 7 at 5:00&lt;/b&gt;, visitor restrictions are temporary and will be reviewed regularly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more-8" class="taboola-read-more-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[SIGN UP: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://membercenter.whio.com/newsletters" target="_self" rel="" title="https://membercenter.whio.com/newsletters"&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHIO-TV Daily Headlines Newsletter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph body-copyright"&gt;©2025 Cox Media Group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WHIO TV</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:41:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4AFBVV95cUxNUVphZWdleW5OZkFRSHBDeDdTVDI1V3pWRUpFMGFpT1NXYXVacHdHWVNsV3FRRy1QVV9QVG5URjFudC1VbExUdDBHYUZicklxeE04UlZpazNEbTd5bENLTE9uVVdSWFpacFh2QTY5dTZKekFJUy1wZEE3M0piNTdLNjBuWUpqZHd0dXNtQ1cxbXFGY1RkcHl4VkN1LTB5TmQxM0o2N1o3MnFycGh1OWZtUUtrZ01VWVdBX3RKMnpVd1RnNTdYZU5TNjVMWUI1dnhXQWFZdGlmVDkxdGRmbnZqdNIB9AFBVV95cUxQNUc0aTRwQXNJc2gzYjA0X2ZWMGJIMDdvOFFRSFdRODNtS1NqaU43c05fVDJtV2REZXdhNG95am82eklYclFvNFB5cHVEYm1tclJTWWtRNE9DTHhXZE1xbTdyYW40b0NMVkUwcXUxelVPVzFCc1VnQVFqdHZOZ3czbjBma1E5WWc2Z3hTLXhPUHBXMFRoLW82VFRRMk1NOEVUMi1TcktVQUtMRWkxTTFHQ1pKTHpYYXhxTVZIUDRJTGUxVjJNSC1XeF9GQ0xTMTZiTUU1YlY1M2JuUEVPeU9OVVVhLU1lVzJUcmFNd0w4WkZtSnFa</guid></item><item><title>因受感染旅客而向纽瓦克机场发出麻疹暴露警报- NJ.com</title><link>https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2025/12/measles-exposure-alert-issued-for-newark-airport-due-to-infected-traveler.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CT3OV3IGIJABLNLGNRK55CDEHM"&gt;New Jersey health officials are warning travelers who passed through Newark Liberty International Airport on Dec. 19 that they may have been exposed to measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GMADHBHS3BC4VNRRBQH2LUDCOE"&gt;A passenger, who is not a New Jersey resident, traveled through at least two of the airport’s terminals, state Department of Health officials said Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6GGMKTA26FH4NJLIT6BMRHHINM"&gt;Anyone who was in Terminal B at 7 a.m. or Terminal C at 7 p.m. on Dec. 19 may have been exposed to the highly contagious virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CJBFP7PCCBEZRLJUVII6JRV26E"&gt;Health officials said they do not have information about where the infected person was between those times. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VLWNB7HI75AKNIUMMXCXCLUDXQ"&gt;People who were exposed could develop symptoms as late as Jan. 2. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3EHX34MJQZBDDCW6H7LU7Y2K4I"&gt;Anyone who suspects exposure or illness should call their local health department or health care provider before visiting any medical facility, officials said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SDWDCYVYSZHR7FPA5R7HB5BFUM"&gt;Special arrangements can be made for evaluation while protecting other patients and medical staff from possible infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="K6REKCNTXRHSXIMDM2RKKE7CPU"&gt;Measles symptoms include a high fever, cough, runny nose, watery red eyes and a rash that typically appears three to five days after symptoms begin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MKY4CSVLSBBFDHBQUGULRMSXTU"&gt;The rash starts as flat red spots on the face at the hairline and spreads downward to the neck, torso, arms, legs and feet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZLKMHNNPONEIBELPK4N2L7EMIE"&gt;Serious complications can include pneumonia and encephalitis. Pregnant people face risks of miscarriage, premature birth or a low-birth-weight baby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PA6AVEDXFVDLBGHVHMAERXMIIQ"&gt;The virus spreads easily through the air when someone coughs or sneezes and can remain airborne for up to two hours after an infected person leaves an area. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QDF7W5GKLNBF7GWPBIZ3PV42PM"&gt;People can also contract measles through contact with mucus or saliva from an infected person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EMT3UMPVWFCHJDZMOUPPOCDJ2M"&gt;New Jersey has had 11 confirmed measles cases in 2025, compared with seven cases in 2024. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6IFEPNSXLRERRHYIAIZTPJLGYI"&gt;Nationally, measles cases have soared to 2,012 across 44 jurisdictions as of Dec. 23, the highest levels reported since 1992. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NEEPQFK3ZBGAHHPKBGVUQY36EM"&gt;The state health department is working with local officials on contact tracing and efforts to notify people who might have been exposed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DXC2R7V4L5CVHJVZEPXBW57PUU"&gt;Those at risk include people who have not been fully vaccinated or have not had measles in the past. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ODW4JAS3DJD35LN6QMXDKA4MHM"&gt;The MMR vaccine, administered in two doses, is the most effective way to protect against measles, mumps and rubella&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:YPZZQHHIRVCEPGYFBVNCZDU5OA" data-fusion-component="YPZZQHHIRVCEPGYFBVNCZDU5OA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:YPZZQHHIRVCEPGYFBVNCZDU5OA" data-fusion-component="YPZZQHHIRVCEPGYFBVNCZDU5OA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NJ.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:57:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxNYUFpZWlhSzZwMzVLRVVhZmcybTdWMnFmbjR5WWpGZVBhN1l5N2MweDFEaHJuVklxY1ZlcHZjLVpwbC1vaE5NckdjRXRQNVJiU0pSUGR3d3psdV9NQTZ2MkFQTjJiTG8zZVlDeHViVnpQbkdvWTdZQXBYRXVKYU4yWk02bF9tMzJ5aHhpZmI2TkRiRnpEcTFzS2tQX2V6UWhLNTR4R1U4RzB3RjI1NjVDeFBRanZXQQ</guid></item><item><title>Prisma Health暂时禁止儿童探视住院患者- WIS新闻10</title><link>https://www.wistv.com/2025/12/26/prisma-health-temporarily-restrict-children-visiting-hospitalized-patients/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body | article w-100"&gt;&lt;p class="text | text-start article-text"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE: The above video is a livestream of WIS featuring current newscasts, Soda City Living and Gray Media’s Local News Live.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="divider | border-bottom mx-auto w-75 my-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | text-start article-text"&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (WIS) - Prisma Health announced it will temporarily restrict children’s visits to hospitalized patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Prisma Health said this is due to increased rates of community influenza and other respiratory illnesses. Prisma Health will restrict anyone 15 and younger from visiting hospitalized patients as of Tuesday, Dec. 30.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;“By taking this proactive step, we can help ensure our hospitals remain safe places for our patients to receive high-quality care,” said Jacie Volkman, executive director of Prisma Health’s Department of Infection Prevention. Exceptions may be allowed for circumstances such as the imminent death of a loved one, she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="w-100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Visitors who feel sick should not visit their hospitalized loved ones. Prisma Health recommends that all visitors wear masks to help avoid the spread of respiratory illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention estimates there have been at least 1,900 deaths from the flu so far this season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention recommends everyone 6 months and older get vaccinated against the flu. For more information about the flu, visit the &lt;a href="https://dph.sc.gov/diseases-conditions/infectious-diseases/flu" target="_self" rel="" title="https://dph.sc.gov/diseases-conditions/infectious-diseases/flu"&gt;&lt;u&gt;S.C. Department of Public Health&lt;/u&gt;’s flu resource site&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | text-start article-text"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Feel more informed, prepared, and connected with WIS. For more free content like this, subscribe to our &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wistv.com/newsletter/" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;i&gt;email newsletter&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;, and &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wistv.com/page/apps/" rel="noreferrer"&gt;&lt;i&gt;download our apps&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;i&gt;Have feedback that can help us improve? &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:wis-webproducers@gray.tv?subject=[please%20include%20the%20article%27s%20headline%20here]" rel="noreferrer"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Click here&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="copyright |"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Copyright 2025 WIS. All rights reserved.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIS News 10</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:50:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxPLTJET0NFblNGc0l1OHdidGhBNXZrdmFTS3dIVWxBQlI2VmNCRF9iWHg4V0xnVVJBU1g4YVQyVEZveTBJdjNHcFE1aERhSHhDLWxDWDMyeXhCMHNMTDdVYUMzc09ySFVUbV9YTzRtNnlfLWxXeUZmVF93bXhaZnUtTHRXNjBKTldFajBoOHhjYVlkM2QwSzcxcXZ5NEVyRTE3MW1oWEtvaGlIaW5z</guid></item><item><title>纽约州报告创纪录的每周流感病例数- Bloomberg.com</title><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-12-26/new-york-state-reports-record-number-of-weekly-flu-infections</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="box main"&gt;
                &lt;h2 class="main__heading"&gt;We've detected unusual activity from your computer network&lt;/h2&gt;
                &lt;p class="continue"&gt;To continue, please click the box below to let us know you're not a robot.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p id="px-captcha"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/section&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bloomberg.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:22:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxPZlgtS2V1dkdlallIdTNjakhLUF9BTmVaQ2puNG9DZGZ4cjBCSER6QUN3VWEtRHAxeEtuWUx4aS11OVRMdENraDR1cU41REdDRmlEdTVTcklvbnNOS0EtRmliR3R2YjZIcUNvcGxJVDlGX3hwR2RCSDFET3hZSzZvWnphM0xtVFZNRTloR1NKSG9LUGNjNGxTbHozdUwwamRlT25YYXhlTEZjUTU0SUs3M0Rn</guid></item><item><title>间歇性禁食与人脑活动的变化有关- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/intermittent-fasting-linked-to-changes-in-human-brain-activity/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:46:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxORHlBYXgxbEpObVRfam9aNVpmMko1WmJKVDktOWtqajZEd3FKY1hYd2V2TFltbExtcy15UlRtS2JrTHRRQWtNbmZCSVNUUVVhWnZkOEdNS2djTzNuRHRQcE5idnh5SVdrcWRBN2NfMENpZnFJbUFSaG9WLVBfejBWZGNscGZka2xEQ2xhdzNlUDcwQQ</guid></item><item><title>令人惊讶的突破，以色列科学家发现癌症可能有助于治愈衰退的心脏-以色列时报</title><link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/in-surprising-breakthrough-scientists-in-israel-find-cancer-may-help-heal-the-failing-heart/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="the-content"&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;A discovery by Prof. Ami Aronheim and his team at the Technion–Israel Institute of Technology shows that the growth of cancerous tumors may actually combat cardiac dysfunction and reduce fibrosis, the scarring process that stiffens the heart muscle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The failing heart can beat much better in the presence of cancer cells or a tumor,” said lead investigator Aronheim, dean of the Technion’s Ruth and Bruce Rappaport Faculty of Medicine, speaking to The Times of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is very surprising,” Aronheim said.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p id="gpt-passback"&gt;
        
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;Currently, no drugs exist that can reverse fibrosis or improve the heart muscle once it has been damaged, he explained.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new findings could open the door to the development of innovative and groundbreaking therapeutic approaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter newsletter-article" data-website="timesofisrael" data-from="In surprising breakthrough, scientists in Israel find cancer may help heal the failing heart"&gt;
	&lt;div class="newsletter-article-inner"&gt;
		&lt;p class="newsletter-article-text newsletter-article-part"&gt;
			&lt;span&gt;Get The Times of Israel's Daily Edition&lt;/span&gt;
			&lt;span&gt;by email and never miss our top stories&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class="newsletter-article-form-wrapper newsletter-article-part"&gt;
			
			&lt;div class="newsletter-article-terms"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
				By signing up, you agree to the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="/terms"&gt;terms&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p class="newsletter-error newsletter-article-error"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
		
&lt;p&gt;PhD students Lama Awwad and Laris Achlaug led the research, which was recently &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2666087325001607"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in JACC: CardioOncology, a peer-reviewed journal of the American College of Cardiology.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;figure id="attachment_3716966" class="wp-caption  alignnone"&gt;&lt;a href="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/12/Ami-Lama-Laris.jpeg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-3716966" src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/12/Ami-Lama-Laris-640x400.jpeg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;From left to right: Prof. Ami Aronheim, dean of the Technion-Israel Institute of Technology’s Ruth and Bruce Rappaport Faculty of Medicine, PhD students Lama Awad and Laris Achlaug.(Courtesy)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heart disease and cancer are the two most significant causes of death in Israel, according to the Health Ministry. While they have been considered separate diseases, researchers now confirm that they are highly connected — and they affect each other’s outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The diseases also share similar risk factors, including smoking, obesity, diabetes, environmental factors and aging.&lt;/p&gt;
               
           
           
        
&lt;p&gt;“These are two diseases that are all around us, and that people we know suffer from,” Awwad, 28, told The Times of Israel in a recent Zoom interview together with Achlaug.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moreover, Awwad said, the two conditions share similar mechanisms, which involve inflammation, growth signals, and survival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Heart disease is a cancer-spreader&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2772976125002120"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; conducted by Aronheim’s lab five years ago, the scientific team found that a stressed heart can actually accelerate the growth and spread of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When we first looked at how heart failure affects cancer, we showed that a damaged heart can make the cancer more aggressive and more metastatic,” Aronheim said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This can happen because cytokines, chemical messengers that immune cells use to communicate with one another, are released by the heart. These cytokines promote the growth and spread of cancer cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, while doing these experiments, the researchers noticed an unexpected — and inverse — result. In tumor-bearing mice, heart failure was “much less pronounced.”&lt;/p&gt;
               
           
           
        
&lt;p&gt;“This led us to start to think about studying the other direction, how cancer affects heart failure,” Aronheim said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scientists implanted cancer cells in mice with heart failure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We were surprised to find an improvement not only in the ability of the mice’s hearts to pump blood but also an improvement in the muscular system,” said Achlaug, 31. “It was very motivating.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;We were surprised to find an improvement not only in the ability of the mice’s hearts to pump blood but also an improvement in the muscular system&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moreover, the extent of fibrotic, or scarred, tissue was significantly decreased in a short period of time.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This was a breakthrough for us,” Aronheim said. “Of course, it was clear to us that it’s not a possible treatment to use another disease for the sake of repairing heart dysfunction. So we had to study the mechanism.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers hypothesized that exposing immune cells to cancer cells can yield a process called “immunomodulation,” which enables the immune system to regenerate and begin fighting inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To test their hypothesis, the scientists injected serum extracted from the blood of the tumor-bearing mice into heart-diseased mice. These mice exhibited rapid improvements in cardiac function and reduced fibrosis.&lt;/p&gt;
               
           
           
        

	&lt;figure id="attachment_2877553" class="wp-caption  alignnone"&gt;&lt;a href="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2022/11/iStock-990873330.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-2877553" src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2022/11/iStock-990873330-640x400.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;3D Illustration of Human Heart Anatomy&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers analyzed the molecules in the serum and found that the cytokines were released from natural killer cells, also known as NK cells. These are a type of immune cell that attacks foreign cells when activated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cytokines activated macrophages, a type of white blood cell that plays a crucial role in consuming pathogens. The cytokines helped reprogram the macrophages into anti-inflammatory, healing-focused cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The work of Aronheim’s lab has shed light on the common biological pathways between cancer and heart disease, said Izhak Kehat, head of the department of physiology, biophysics, and systems biology, in the Technion’s Faculty of Medicine, who was not involved in the project.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;figure id="attachment_3717045" class="wp-caption size-fullscreen alignright"&gt;&lt;a href="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/12/izhak.jpeg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-3717045 size-full" src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/12/izhak.jpeg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Prof. Izhak Kehat, head, Department of physiology, biophysics and systems biology, Faculty of Medicine, Technion-Israel Institute of Technology. (Courtesy)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tumors can release signals that affect the whole body’s repair and immune response,” Kehat said. “And some of these signals can be harnessed to improve heart disease.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Awwad said the research team has a patent on the serum with “a cocktail of positive factors.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We have to test its toxicity and prove that it’s safe to use,” Achlaug explained.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Breaking down social — and scientific — barriers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Awwad, who lives in Tamra, an Arab town in the Galilee, and Achlaug, who lives in Kfar Kama, a Circassian town 60 kilometers (37 miles) away, spoke about their challenges as researchers and as mothers of small children.&lt;/p&gt;
               
           
           
        
&lt;p&gt;They credited their husbands, who are both engineers (Awwad’s husband works at Google and Achlaug’s husband works at Apple), and “who can sometimes work from home during the week,” Achlaug said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And also when we take our work home on weekends,” Awwad added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She noted that approximately 50 percent of the Technion’s graduate students are women, and about 50% of those are Arabs. However, she said there are few female researchers because of the “long hours we spend in the lab.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the Circassian community, which numbers 5,000 in Israel, Achlaug said there are only two other women who have PhDs.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;figure id="attachment_3552193" class="wp-caption  alignnone"&gt;&lt;a href="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/05/PHOTO-2025-05-18-21-45-38.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-3552193" src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/05/PHOTO-2025-05-18-21-45-38-640x400.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Illustrative: A Circassian woman commemorates the Circassian Mourning Day in Kfar Kama on May 21, 2024. (Courtesy/Adam Choshha)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When they attend scientific conferences abroad, Awwad said that people are less curious about them as women and more interested in their lives as Arabs in Israel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“People ask me a lot of questions about ‘what’s really happening,'” Awwad said. “It’s good because I like to calm them down.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Achlaug said they never encountered hostility at conferences, but she was “a little nervous” when presenting her paper to a group of scientists from Beirut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But there’s a sense of honor among researchers to focus on science,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then, afterwards,” Awwad said, “they can have their opinions.”&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;/div&gt;

				
				

					
			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of Israel</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:29:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxPdnlTTkFOYU5pSlZoRWp3dE5FSXB1ckRYRVl3NlVFVWpTTkR1THhqdnNseGxVQ181S3hHWkltWkxoMnZpMzkxLVJ1dXJFZjFlV2NVWG0tUWNQdTZfX1oxbVU4ejNxS0dLTHNUZDFUSEJsNTRvMm93RWd6MnMxLV83eGRLeUdwU3pfOEhjaDFxakU5TkJpT2ttQkEzM3NZMUQ5ZDZnVzZTdEJyWDBrTnY3dEd2Mlh1cjNxcEdBNVNtMNIBxAFBVV95cUxOdnlvdjRqTmowLVZabmEwS3BzZkQ5TFNyTDV0SFQyMXVFak9FV1Bnc01INGVIb29FYmZtZVZxa0VaZzNfVTVneGhpSUJ0N1J2Y0trODZqakd3MkY0QWRzclVBQXBfWTJ6T1g1QkFoamVPUmo3VFc0clgyWVFneDVZZnllb1pJZ29DNVFMM0VidDJBTnJxUWhCXy1vRk1YVkZhYzA3ZGZiUXg2RFFubUNqT05LTUVFTXFjbnpTaWwyY3NCUmwx</guid></item><item><title>我一直感到焦虑和疲惫……我把责任归咎于忙碌的生活，但这是更险恶的事情--《每日邮报》</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15396579/anxious-tired-thyroid-cancer-young-people.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In her early twenties, Rachel Christensen was doing what most college students do, juggling deadlines and her personal life while trying to stay on top of her health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When exhaustion and anxiety began plaguing her, the South Carolina sales tech worker assumed her on-the-go lifestyle was to blame. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But then, in 2023, she noticed a lump in her neck that she tried to ignore, hoping it would go away on its own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When it didn't nine months later, in March 2024, Christensen finally saw an ear, nose and throat specialist who ordered a CT scan, which revealed three swollen lymph nodes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Swollen lymph nodes are usually benign or a sign of a minor infection, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-13451183/GP-said-cold-thyroid-cancer-listening-instincts-saved-read-definitive-guide-thyroids-know-somethings-wrong.html"&gt;but in rare cases&lt;/a&gt;, they could indicate more sinister conditions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Weeks of uncertainty followed until April 2024, when biopsy results showed papillary thyroid carcinoma (PTC), the most common form of thyroid &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-2507e490-dc3f-11f0-9755-2f916346a035" class=""&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And because it had spread to other lymph nodes, her cancer was metastatic, which makes it harder to treat.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'In my gut, I felt something may be wrong,' Christensen, now 24, said. '[It was] terrifying. It honestly did not feel real. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I have the worst hypochondria, so when I read the diagnosis in my portal it was really scary.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Rachel Christensen (pictured here), 24, was diagnosed with thyroid cancer last year after mistaking her symptoms for exhaustion from a busy lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Christensen is one of a growing number of young Americans diagnosed with thyroid cancer. Recent estimates found the disease spiked 240 percent between 1973 and 2002 in all age groups overall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Additionally, a 2025 study found incidence in children, adolescents and young adults ages 15 to 39 in the US surged 137 percent from 1995 to 2014. The highest rate of increase in the study was for PTC, which increased 5.5 percent per year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts believe environmental contaminants like microplastics and pollution, along with growing rates of obesity, could be to blame for the surge, though scans to detect the disease have also become more common. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The American Cancer Society estimates 44,000 new cases of thyroid cancer have been detected in 2025, and 2,300 Americans have died. About 80 percent of thyroid cancers are PTC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The disease is almost three times more common in women, which could be because the female sex hormone estrogen is thought to stimulate the growth of thyroid cancer cells.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The thyroid is a butterfly-shaped gland in the neck that produces hormones responsible for regulating the body's temperature, energy use, heart rate, digestive health and skin, hair and nail growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Like Christensen, most PTC patients have a painless lump near the thyroid gland but have few or no other symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The overall five-year survival rate for thyroid cancer is 99 percent. In cases like Christensen's where the disease has spread to other areas, that rate is about 71 percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Christensen, pictured here with her mother, had to have her entire thyroid removed to treat her cancer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Christensen, pictured here after surgery, now has to take hormone therapy to replace hormone levels lost from her thyroidectomy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Less than a month after hearing the life-changing diagnosis, Christensen faced a major five-hour surgery to remove her thyroid and the affected lymph nodes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I honestly just wanted to get it over with,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Seeing my scar for the first time was definitely scary as well,' she added. 'It’s about two to three inches long on my neck and all I could think about is how it would heal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Now I don’t even care if you can see it. It reminds me of my strength.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The operation was a success with surgeons removing her thyroid and all traces of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Christensen is now considered cancer-free following the surgery, but she was faced with a daunting new reality: living without a thyroid to produce vital hormones necessary for regulating metabolism, energy, body temperature and heart function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;People without a thyroid gland are forced to take hormone replacement therapy to ensure they get adequate levels of the hormone synthetic thyroxine (T4). Without this, patients can suffer from fatigue, dry skin, brittle hair and nails, irregular periods and a slow heart rate, among other issues. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Left uncontrolled, low thyroid hormones can lead to high cholesterol, heart failure, infertility, depression and cognitive decline.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Christensen, pictured here, is now working to raise awareness of thyroid cancer warning signs for other young people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Christensen said: 'My body is constantly fluctuating, so listening to my body is very important. It has been super frustrating both physically and mentally, so I try to give myself some grace and more credit for what I have been through at such a young age.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Despite the ordeal, she says she is healthier now than when she was first diagnosed. She wakes up at 6am each day and has bloodwork every few weeks to manage her thyroid levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She is also working with a naturopathic doctor to evaluate her diet and focus on her microbiome, a network of healthy bacteria living in the gut that influences digestion, immune health and metabolism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Christensen also credits her family for being her 'biggest support system.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said: 'My mom is my biggest advocate and still to this day. [She] helps me navigate this and researches so that I can get to feeling my best.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now that she is cancer free, Christensen has also begun posting about her story on social media to help raise awareness for other young people who may dismiss the warning signs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I am finally learning to give myself more grace and credit because living with this is very hard,' she said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:25:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxPTWZtc2NZdzJqbTljU2ZMaEpmYkFvXzRWVTVtZzBlNmc2Nzh2Z181c0JRS2IwM3d1X1E2M1ZVLTd6a1J1Z2E3Q0JMLVhnOEEtdWU5dTdmZ1F6RVZ1cERQQ0R6WW1fOVpDRVRsZl9qczJtVmlROW1ZSjltOUJvclJsUWxVVHhlWC1UMkpxUXJmTE5keXFYRHVxenZXRUNVczjSAaQBQVVfeXFMTXlLTzBHRVRocjBuV3hUcEtlOEwwMzNRUldDeDZ4ZzAtMzZqUnk0Z0NVTFRUQ2Rtd3hYMmlZeXFNOWhPeWM4Q3V6aTR5U0VWTmFDeFpaclFGQ2dIbVZ1eHFENEgtemNvc2xUTXFoLU9iZVlXNzhNZnNBOWpPVnBkVmlZX2hScTNTY1ZPcGpFMlR6WnE0ZHJVN2xFTGhZRWtlWWVDX1o</guid></item><item><title>年轻人的结肠癌发病率正在飙升。以下是原因，以及如何降低风险-达拉斯新闻</title><link>https://www.dallasnews.com/business/health-care/2025/12/26/colon-cancer-rates-are-spiking-among-young-people-heres-why-and-how-to-lower-your-risk/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Dr. Bethany Malone has treated a lot of colorectal cancer patients. The youngest, not counting those with genetic conditions, was 19 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Colorectal cancer used to be considered a cancer of older age. Not anymore. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Patients in their teens and early 20s still aren’t the norm, exactly, but are becoming more common.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;“I have not gone a year in practice without taking a colon cancer out of someone in their 20s,” Malone said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="dmnc_features-cta-social-article-cta-social-module__sI3E3 p-7 mb-6 w-full h-64 border-t border-b border-black flex flex-col gap-7"&gt;&lt;div class="dmnc_features-cta-social-article-cta-social-module__2nIGz flex items-center justify-center gap-x-7"&gt;&lt;div class="dmnc_features-cta-social-article-cta-social-module__VBR0d flex-auto w-full flex flex-col"&gt;&lt;p class="dmnc_features-cta-social-article-cta-social-module__jO6ca secondaryBold secondaryBold-8 text-center"&gt;Business Briefing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dmnc_features-cta-social-article-cta-social-module__3beff secondaryRoman secondaryRoman-20 text-center text-gray-dark"&gt;Become a business insider with the latest news.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="dmnc_features-cta-social-article-cta-social-module__WpP95 flex flex-col gap-7 items-center"&gt;&lt;p class="dmnc_features-cta-social-article-cta-social-module__8MgJa flex flex-wrap text-gray-dark secondaryRoman secondaryRoman-10 text-center justify-center"&gt;By signing up, you agree to our &lt;a class="dmnc_features-cta-social-article-cta-social-module__lU9-l border-b border-gray-dark hover_border-0 focus_border-0 active_border-0" href="/help/terms-of-service/"&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="dmnc_features-cta-social-article-cta-social-module__lU9-l border-b border-gray-dark hover_border-0 focus_border-0 active_border-0" href="/help/privacy-policy"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Malone is a colon and rectal surgeon and the associate program director for the general surgery residency at Texas Health Harris Methodist Hospital Fort Worth. Her experience in North Texas reflects a worldwide trend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Colorectal cancer — which includes cancer of the colon and of the rectum — is considered early onset when diagnosed in people under the age of 50. While the majority of diagnoses are still among people aged 65 or older, early onset rates have been increasing worldwide, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7994182/" rel=""&gt;particularly in high-income countries&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;In a 2023 report, the American Cancer Society wrote that the trends of decreasing incidence in older people and increasing incidence in younger people are “&lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/content/dam/cancer-org/research/cancer-facts-and-statistics/colorectal-cancer-facts-and-figures/colorectal-cancer-facts-and-figures-2023.pdf" rel=""&gt;rapidly shifting the patient population younger&lt;/a&gt;.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;In 2020, &lt;i&gt;Black Panther&lt;/i&gt; actor Chadwick Boseman died from colon cancer at age 43. More recently, former Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders choreographer Criscilla Anderson &lt;a href="https://www.dallasnews.com/arts-entertainment/pop-culture/2025/12/04/former-cowboys-cheerleaders-choreographer-criscilla-anderson-dies-after-cancer-battle/" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.dallasnews.com/arts-entertainment/pop-culture/2025/12/04/former-cowboys-cheerleaders-choreographer-criscilla-anderson-dies-after-cancer-battle/"&gt;died of colon cancer&lt;/a&gt; at age 45.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Also locally, &lt;a href="https://www.dallasnews.com/arts-entertainment/2024/12/26/joshua-ray-walker-on-fighting-cancer-and-rallying-back/" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.dallasnews.com/arts-entertainment/2024/12/26/joshua-ray-walker-on-fighting-cancer-and-rallying-back/"&gt;Dallas musician Joshua Ray Walker&lt;/a&gt; was diagnosed with colon cancer in late 2023, at age 33. (About 10 months later, after treatment and surgery, he announced that he was &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/joshuaraywalkermusic/posts/pfbid027McWfGGqiwUYkxeMXdG9h8HB9H4QxtjAouLUKvhgytUkd8PAd9SnRw63sT1EEpJNl" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.facebook.com/joshuaraywalkermusic/posts/pfbid027McWfGGqiwUYkxeMXdG9h8HB9H4QxtjAouLUKvhgytUkd8PAd9SnRw63sT1EEpJNl"&gt;cancer-free&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Here’s what medical experts say about the rising rates of colorectal cancer in younger people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="body-text-header"&gt;Why are colorectal cancer rates rising among younger people?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Medical experts say there isn’t one reason why colorectal cancer rates are rising in the below-50 age groups. But there are some contributing factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;First, it’s not because of genetics. Dr. Radhika Kainthla, a medical oncologist at Parkland Memorial Hospital in Dallas, said that about 20% of early onset colorectal cancer patients have a genetic tie-in. That means 80% do not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;“There’s a misconception a lot of times that if it’s a young person being diagnosed with cancer, it must be genetic,” Kainthla said. “But that’s not actually what we’re seeing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;All three experts who spoke with &lt;i&gt;The Dallas Morning News&lt;/i&gt; pointed instead to a combination of environmental factors and lifestyle factors, such as diets high in red meat, diets packed with ultra-processed foods and lack of regular exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Malone at Texas Health Fort Worth said fiber intake especially tends to be low for Americans, which can increase the risk for colorectal cancer. Fiber does a lot of work in the gut, Malone said, including feeding a healthy microbiome and helping to flush carcinogens out of the body before they’re absorbed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Malone noted that the “lifestyle” factors are not always easily controllable. The U.S. food system has shifted significantly toward ultra-processed foods, which tend to be low in necessary nutrients such as fiber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;There are also environmental factors at play, said Dr. Emina Huang, a professor of surgery and a colorectal surgeon at UT Southwestern Medical Center. For instance, living near a superfund site — which are hazardous waste sites — has been shown to increase the risk of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="body-text-header"&gt;How can I reduce my risk of colorectal cancer?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Reducing the risk of colorectal cancer, the three experts said, comes down to a lot of the standard advice that medical professionals recommend for general health, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;The three experts said that folks should focus on getting regular exercise, avoiding smoking, moderating alcohol intake and eating a diet that’s low in red meat but rich in fruits, vegetables and fiber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Obesity is also a risk factor for colorectal cancer, the experts said, although Malone cautioned against focusing on weight loss alone. Restrictive diets may also end up being low in fiber, which is harmful rather than helpful for colorectal cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;And, of course, patients should pay attention to their bodies and seek medical care if they notice abdominal pain or changes in their bowel movements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="body-text-header"&gt;When should I start getting screened for colorectal cancer?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Because of the rising rates of colorectal cancer among younger people, the U.S. Preventive Services Task Force advises regular screenings beginning at age 45. The gold standard of screening is a colonoscopy, but stool tests and scans can also be used for screening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;The age 45 recommendation, however, is for patients who have a standard risk for colorectal cancer. Some people may be at higher risk due to personal or family history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;People with a first-degree relative — a sibling, parent or child — diagnosed with colorectal cancer or colorectal polyps may be advised to begin screenings at a younger age. In general, medical professionals advise beginning screening when a patient is 10 years younger than their relative was at the age of diagnosis. For instance, if your father was diagnosed with colorectal cancer at age 48, you should begin screenings at age 38.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Patients with such a family history should start screenings no later than 40.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Similarly, patients who have personal histories of Crohn’s disease or ulcerative colitis are at higher risk of colorectal cancer, too, and should also begin screenings at an earlier age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Kainthla, at Parkland, also noted that there are other types of screenings besides colonoscopies, such as blood tests and stool tests, that may be a useful option for some patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="body-text-header"&gt;What are the warning signs of colorectal cancer?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Medical experts are quick to point out that, for most young people, abdominal or gastrointestinal symptoms are unlikely to indicate colorectal cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Still, some symptoms should serve as red flags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;The most common early symptoms are stomach pain that doesn’t go away, changes in bowel movements with no improvement or blood in the stool. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-text-paragraph"&gt;Sometimes, these symptoms can indicate hemorrhoids or other relatively benign conditions. However, if a patient is treated for a benign condition but symptoms do not improve, that’s a sign that something more may be going on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="dmnc_features-article-body-embeds-subject-tag-list-with-images-list-with-images-module__bZ-w3 py-5 px-7 border border-gray-light my-8 clear-both"&gt;&lt;div class="dmnc_features-article-body-embeds-subject-tag-list-with-images-list-with-images-module__mrnG- w_full py-5 border-t border-gray-light flex"&gt;&lt;a class="dmnc_features-article-body-embeds-subject-tag-list-with-images-list-with-images-module__P4zn3 inline-block pr-8 shrink-0 w-auto flex flex-col" href="/news/investigations/2025/12/26/what-researchers-have-discovered-about-maternal-infant-health-under-texas-abortion-laws/"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" class="dmnc_features-article-body-embeds-subject-tag-list-with-images-list-with-images-module__6H-hI dmnc_images-modern-image-module__QFaG- max-w-full h-auto text-white dmnc_images-modern-image-module__9Zlll bg-gray-light object-contain" src="https://dmn-dallas-news-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/QGTTZXLTDZC57GLYYYR77HJ3IQ.jpg?auth=2d275643f203ee73d6499b4ef0bc365b25266f17ac91f92a0f151940324b5b05&amp;amp;quality=80&amp;amp;height=127&amp;amp;width=190&amp;amp;smart=true" alt="Abortion rights supporters and opponents clash while demonstrating in downtown Dallas on..."&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;div class="dmnc_features-article-body-embeds-subject-tag-list-with-images-list-with-images-module__DfYNg inline-block w-auto"&gt;&lt;p class="dmnc_features-article-body-embeds-subject-tag-list-with-images-list-with-images-module__T453o mt-2 w-full break-normal text-gray-dark secondaryRoman secondaryRoman-15"&gt;In the four years since Texas introduced abortion bans, researchers have identified negative health impacts for mothers and babies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="dmnc_features-article-body-embeds-subject-tag-list-with-images-list-with-images-module__mrnG- w_full py-5 border-t border-gray-light flex"&gt;&lt;a class="dmnc_features-article-body-embeds-subject-tag-list-with-images-list-with-images-module__P4zn3 inline-block pr-8 shrink-0 w-auto flex flex-col" href="/news/public-health/2025/12/25/food-storage-holidays/"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" class="dmnc_features-article-body-embeds-subject-tag-list-with-images-list-with-images-module__6H-hI dmnc_images-modern-image-module__QFaG- max-w-full h-auto text-white dmnc_images-modern-image-module__9Zlll bg-gray-light object-contain" src="https://dmn-dallas-news-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/UMOHTTBNKRDU3ATYEGO7RXD5BE.jpg?auth=891deac63192cacedb533c73ea10fb11f3b59917ddcd7ccec11d7517f102b1a9&amp;amp;quality=80&amp;amp;height=127&amp;amp;width=190&amp;amp;smart=true" alt="Bananas and various products seen on the shelf of Catholic Charities Dallas and North Texas..."&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;div class="dmnc_features-article-body-embeds-subject-tag-list-with-images-list-with-images-module__DfYNg inline-block w-auto"&gt;&lt;p class="dmnc_features-article-body-embeds-subject-tag-list-with-images-list-with-images-module__T453o mt-2 w-full break-normal text-gray-dark secondaryRoman secondaryRoman-15"&gt;Proper storage can extend food life, preserve nutrients, and help families save money, experts say&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Dallas News</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:02:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3wFBVV95cUxPRE9RSlRNX3VxU0ZTZEZEUGs5OFg5WlNTdHk1R3B0NTItbnNhNVlPWEJ5QlRLdFNQRENpV2lkcXNqa3FVczRsbGgtUFZjVVphb1dvZGFzamZNM29hUDQwVkxBVlBPeF8tcmhPSWQzQ3V1MktsRXlPUWF0akxBRFAwU2pTVHVlc2tVeHdELUFKc2RNYTlJaEZUVEY3UXN3T3Z2MUQ5SlRxVnlCNDhKVS04LUM3SVYtTzBCcVZvU3h3aGRyOENnSEdrWkhDTHQxZVpLa3pmX09MWDNCckFBWGhN</guid></item><item><title>甲型流感在德克萨斯州中部蔓延- KWTX</title><link>https://www.kwtx.com/2025/12/26/flu-spreading-central-texas/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body | article w-100"&gt;&lt;figure class="media-item | figure media-item-image article-image w-100"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="figure-caption mt-1 px-1"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;Baylor Scott &amp;amp; White Waco&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="caption-credit"&gt;(Baylor Scott &amp;amp; White Waco)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;WACO, Texas (KWTX) - The holidays bring loved ones together — but those gatherings can also bring unwanted illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Doctors in Central Texas are reporting a recent up tick in influenza cases, and are urging caution as we head into the new year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;“Over the last week, just nationwide we’ve had a 14% increase in hospitalizations from flu, just flu by itself,” Dr. Van Wehmeyer, Family Physician at Baylor Scott &amp;amp; White.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="w-100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Health officials are tracking a new strain this season — flu A (H1N1) across Central Texas — which is producing symptoms similar to other strains but with some notable additions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;“Just the typical symptoms of the fever which can be high 103° or 104° in some people, most people it’s a low grade fever; sore throat, runny nose, but then also there’s this whole throwing up and diarrhea that comes with flu A as well that we’re seeing in a certain amount of people," Dr. Wehmeyer said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Flu vaccines remain the best defense - however the shot isn’t a perfect match for the new strain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;“If you’re 65 and older that vaccine can decrease serious illness. The serious illness is unfortunately death or hospitalization by greater than 60 to 70% if you’re 65 and older. If you’re two years old and under 17 can decrease serious illness by 50%.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Washing your hands and wearing a mask can also help reduce the spread of illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="copyright |"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Copyright 2025 KWTX. All rights reserved.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KWTX</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibEFVX3lxTE9tZXZJZFduRkhUR3NFWWZUVHM3YzJIMGVqdU1mWkF0ZGQ3RE10MEoyUGxybVdLTGxJMElkenZ4eW5WZ0l6X3pGTVhJLUFpX2NXWjZIR2UxRGxRVmNyMFdEdV9oVXZ4bWNVOXZqYtIBgAFBVV95cUxQNTdGcnlVcGY2RTU4WnF6c2dwTmFZVGhrNkJkRzdpSXh4MUxuUl9mUXAxNWd5dktEeDR2TThCUTNialpteGpCejNPZ1N0cV91UVRza3JpSWswM2lOaUJQUk1nYXUwZ0NyU2ZMY0FXbmgzWV9hU3dBVEwzWGZxMEltcw</guid></item><item><title>Orange Cat对麻醉药物的无价反应非常有趣- Yahoo Life UK</title><link>https://uk.style.yahoo.com/orange-cats-priceless-response-anesthesia-164500225.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Taking a pet to the veterinarian may not be anyone's idea of fun, but it's necessary for every animal's health. Even though virtual vet visits can help reduce the number of stressful in-office appointments, many exams and treatments, such as scans and vaccinations, still require in-person care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Fortunately, nervous animals like Crowley the&lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/articles/sweet-orange-cat-rescued-sister-204500909.html" data-ylk="slk:orange cat;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt; orange cat &lt;/a&gt;can take medication to make these visits easier. As Crowley's friends at Honnas Veterinary have witnessed, though, these medications can have some bizarre side effects! The Austin, Texas, veterinary office shared a video of Crowley's hilarious anesthesia reaction on December 20, and millions of people are talking about it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Look at him go! This restless kitty needed some extra help relaxing for his ultrasound and echocardiogram, but even with the medication, he wasn't entirely resting. Luckily, his vet and vet techs could work around his &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/articles/outdoor-orange-cat-offers-gentlest-234500831.html" data-ylk="slk:air swimming;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;air swimming&lt;/a&gt; with no issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"He's going to be so mad when he wakes up with a full Brazilian," one commenter joked. He may be too drugged up to notice for a while! Luckily, neither of his scans is an invasive procedure, so a naked belly will be this &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/cats-deep-slumber-being-menace-124500951.html" data-ylk="slk:sleepy cat;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;sleepy cat&lt;/a&gt;'s biggest concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/precious-pit-bull-waking-anesthesia-234500740.html" data-ylk="slk:Related: Precious Pit Bull Waking Up From Anesthesia Has Sweetest Response to Hearing Mom's Voice;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;Related: Precious Pit Bull Waking Up From Anesthesia Has Sweetest Response to Hearing Mom's Voice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As for everyone else, they're too busy laughing out loud at his sleepy dance to be concerned about anything! Even though viewer @terryconklin1 warned, "This is actually really dangerous because the cat could discover glow sticks and start going to EDM festivals," Honnas Vet knows it's too late for this party kitty. In their own words: "He craves the rave."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Do Orange Cats Need More Medication?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Many people with naturally red hair require more anesthesia or sedation during medical procedures, but what about orange cats? As it turns out, the MC1R gene that is responsible for giving humans red hair is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; the &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/gene-behind-orange-fur-cats-found-last" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:same gene;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;same gene&lt;/a&gt; that gives orange cats their fiery fur color, so their anesthesia response is likely not related to their red fur.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When a commenter asked a similar question, Honnas Veterinary answered, "It depends on the kitty. Crowley requires pretty heavy sedation for us to be able to do his scans," but this isn't the case for every &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/unbothered-orange-cat-lives-bear-224500922.html" data-ylk="slk:ginger cat;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;ginger cat&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Even though coat color doesn't affect a cat's reaction to anesthesia, other factors, like energy level and fear, certainly can. Whether it's sedation for a surgery or for a short scan like Crowley's, medication is the safest choice for many cats—and for the vet staff who care for them!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/dog-face" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🐶;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;🐶&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/newsletters/parade-pets" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SIGN UP to get “pawsitivity” delivered right to your inbox with inspiring &amp;amp; entertaining stories about our furry &amp;amp; feathered friends;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIGN UP to get “pawsitivity” delivered right to your inbox with inspiring &amp;amp; entertaining stories about our furry &amp;amp; feathered friends&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/paw-prints" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🐾🐾;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;🐾🐾&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally published by &lt;a href="https://pethelpful.com/pet-news/orange-cats-priceless-response-to-anesthesia-medication" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PetHelpful;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;PetHelpful&lt;/a&gt; on Dec 26, 2025, where it first appeared in the &lt;a href="https://pethelpful.com/pet-news" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Pet News;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Pet News&lt;/a&gt; section. Add PetHelpful as a &lt;a href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=pethelpful.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Preferred Source by clicking here.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Preferred Source by clicking here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Life UK</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQdjJpLUs2ZEdNNE9yLTVwX2RTbFU3WGpBbkEzcFVNcGVudWJYbXRmOFFyNlRmdzFHeHlnOHVrVHpFeGYzX0VYaDBya0FlZDR4aDlMa1BBUkZGWWxPR1lGaC04Z3BHRkZQYmdreko0TERkcmx0cXQ4eWhVQzREZHlfdkM2V1lBeWRuZlBV</guid></item><item><title>妈妈拍了一段女儿吃苹果的视频。她没有意识到自己正在捕捉过敏反应（独家） -雅虎加拿大新闻</title><link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/mom-took-video-her-daughter-164415043.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A mom filming her toddler’s birthday excitement accidentally recorded the early moments of an allergic reaction&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The child later learned she could eat peeled apples but not the apple peel itself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The viral video prompted a deeper conversation about how easily allergies can be missed and how families adapt over time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;One mom's &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@lovethelarkins/video/7568607538934041870" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:video;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;video&lt;/a&gt; is only a few seconds long, but it captures a moment that still stops viewers in their tracks: a toddler mid-bite, mid-celebration, and unknowingly in the earliest stages of an allergic reaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Simmy Larkin, a 33-year-old stay-at-home mom from Langhorne, Pa., never intended to document anything more than her daughter’s excitement about an upcoming birthday. “If you saw the apple in the video, you saw that a significant portion had been bitten off, and that was her very first time biting into an apple,” Larkin shared exclusively with PEOPLE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Just days earlier, her daughter had watched cousins bite directly into apples, something Larkin had never let her do before. With her second birthday eight days away, the family was counting down as they often did, asking Alexa how many days were left and capturing the joy that followed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Larkin remembers pulling out her phone because her daughter’s excitement felt like something worth saving. Instead of the smile she expected, her daughter began scratching her neck and asking to be picked up, behavior that initially didn’t set off alarms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“She has eczema, so that’s nothing out of the ordinary, and that’s why it kind of took me a little bit to catch on,” Larkin explains. It wasn’t until she picked her daughter up and saw her from a different angle that the truth became clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;From that new lighting, the hives were suddenly visible, spreading across her daughter’s skin. “As soon as I picked her up, I saw the hives, and I was like, oh, she’s having an allergic reaction,” Larkin says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Because food allergies were already part of their daily life, Larkin knew exactly what to do next. She gave her daughter Zyrtec, and the reaction subsided without escalating further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simmy Larkin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Simmy Larkin's daughter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;At the time, Larkin didn’t realize apples were the trigger, let alone something as specific as the peel. Like many parents watching the video later, she initially assumed the reaction could have been caused by something else in the environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“She has broken out into random hives before, and I did not have any explanation why,” Larkin says. Later testing revealed allergies to dogs and dust, things that had been affecting her daughter without the family fully understanding the cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The family dog, for instance, had unknowingly been a trigger. “Whenever he licks her, she breaks out in hives, and we didn’t know that,” Larkin says, explaining why the apple peel didn’t immediately register as the problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It wasn’t until a second reaction, this time off camera, that the pattern became impossible to ignore. After giving her daughter another apple with the peel on, the same symptoms appeared, prompting Larkin to contact her allergist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“That second time is when I realized that, oh, she must be allergic to the apple peel,” she says. From there, more testing followed, and the list of allergens continued to grow. Now her daughter's list of allergens now contains common foods like steak and eggs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Beef was one of the earliest and most surprising discoveries. “I’ve never heard of anyone ever being allergic to steak, so that situation was like, wow, she’s got a rare allergy,” Larkin says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The apple peel diagnosis only deepened her awareness of how unpredictable allergies can be. “I’ve never even heard of an apple peel allergy, like that’s why I didn’t catch on the first time,” she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Since sharing the video on TikTok, Larkin has heard from countless viewers with similar stories. Many told her they developed the same allergy later in life, after years of eating apples without any issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“A lot of people commented and said they grew up eating apple peels, and then as an adult they started to react,” Larkin says. Reading those stories only reinforced how vigilant she now feels she has to be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Today, that vigilance shapes nearly every part of their routine. Meals are adjusted, ingredients are swapped and familiar foods are approached with caution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“We substitute ground turkey for a lot of beef recipes, even though I don’t like the taste of it,” Larkin says, laughing. She adds that the family now eats far less red meat overall, something she views as a small silver lining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simmy Larkin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Simmy, her husband, and two daughters&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Social situations require even more planning. At birthday parties or cookouts, Larkin often brings her daughter’s food rather than risk cross-contamination on shared grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;At school, the differences are especially emotional. “I feel bad knowing that she can’t have cupcakes,” Larkin says, explaining how her daughter’s teacher keeps candy bars on hand so she still gets a treat during celebrations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Despite her own worries, Larkin believes her daughter has adapted better than she has. “I don’t think she feels as bad as I feel for her,” she says, noting that her daughter often turns down allergy-friendly substitutes anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Over time, Larkin has learned that reactions don’t always come from food. A blanket at a play space once caused hives, later traced back to dust, another confirmed allergy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“It’s like, wow, now I know that something in the blanket could have caused it,” Larkin says. Moments like that have taught her that reactions can come from anywhere, not just the kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Her daughter carries an EpiPen, though it hasn’t been needed yet. “She has to show two symptoms, and when she just has hives, that’s only one,” Larkin explains of their emergency plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Beyond the immediate reactions, eczema has become another daily challenge. Larkin says they are still learning how much her daughter’s allergies contribute to flare-ups that affect her comfort and sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simmy Larkin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Simmy and her family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Recently, her daughter began a new treatment to help manage the condition. “We haven’t really seen any improvements yet, but they say it takes several weeks,” Larkin says, hopeful but realistic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;For Larkin, sharing the viral video wasn’t about fear but awareness. She hopes parents and caregivers come away understanding how subtle allergic reactions can be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Be more mindful of giving kids things and ask their parents,” she says, recalling moments from daycare that could have gone very differently if allergies had been involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Even something as common as Goldfish crackers can carry risks, she notes. “It could have impacts on the kid’s health and the type of reaction they have,” Larkin says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/mom-records-daughters-allergic-reaction-without-realizing-it-exclusive-11873786" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Canada</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:44:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE9NZjFKMHZiSEUxRllscWllaFdKc2dEVjRyOThjWDhRVlRsZ1VKWS1fYW5sbXNVWVhaMVJsS3psOXFzY3NXdXZzbXVFdHBoUjhCWUEwdWtjUXcybXVYRkNFM0RwRm83amlHWU1WUDRXMGxHMm15NDhn</guid></item><item><title>纽约市正受到“超级流感”的严重打击-最糟糕的情况尚未到来- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/nyc-is-getting-hit-hard-by-the-super-flu-and-the-worst-is-yet-to-come-2000703455</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl prose-science dark:prose-science"&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;It’s beginning to look like a lot like a flu Christmas. Surges of influenza are hitting parts of the U.S. hard, and the worst is yet to come.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Various regions of the country have reported a dramatic climb in cases lately, including New York City. Overall activity is on the rise nationwide, as are flu-related hospitalizations and deaths. This season is being fueled by an unexpected strain of “super flu.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;The “super flu”&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;A typical flu season is nothing to brush off. Annually, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu-burden/php/data-vis/past-seasons.html"&gt;influenza&lt;/a&gt; sickens millions of Americans, hospitalizes hundreds of thousands, and kills tens of thousands. But this winter has brought along an especially nasty variant of the H3N2 flu known as subclade K.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The variant is noticeably different on a genetic level from the flu strains scientists predicted would be circulating this season, meaning our vaccines aren’t as effective against it as usual. Subclade K emerged towards the end of the winter in the Southern Hemisphere, and since then, it’s quickly supplanted other strains of H3N2 and other flu viruses in general worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;K already caused the flu season to arrive weeks ahead of schedule in &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/a-surprise-flu-variant-threw-off-the-vaccine-get-ready-for-a-brutal-winter-2000686095" target="_blank" rel="false noopener"&gt;European&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/influenza-general/japan-sees-early-flu-activity-school-closures" target="_blank" rel="false noopener"&gt;Asian&lt;/a&gt; countries. In the UK, it’s helped cause a spike of hospitalizations and an &lt;a href="https://www.england.nhs.uk/2025/12/nhs-facing-worst-case-scenario-december-amid-super-flu-surge/" target="_blank" rel="false noopener"&gt;“unprecedented wave of super flu.”&lt;/a&gt; And now it’s clearly making its mark in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Several school districts have had to &lt;a href="https://www.kcrg.com/2025/12/09/iowa-school-district-cancels-classes-due-flu-outbreak/"&gt;temporarily&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.wmur.com/article/new-hampshire-school-influenza-outbreak-121725/69802064" target="_blank" rel="false noopener"&gt;shut down&lt;/a&gt; due to flu outbreaks, while some hospitals &lt;a href="https://news4sanantonio.com/news/local/san-antonio-hospitals-see-surge-in-emergency-visits-as-super-flu-strain-hits-early" target="_blank" rel="false noopener"&gt;are&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.wgrz.com/article/news/health/flu-cases-surging-at-oishei-childrens-hospital-as-doctors-warn-of-severe-season/71-f8ed7826-af48-41e2-ba06-841310abc6b6"&gt;reporting&lt;/a&gt; an alarming rise of cases. Data &lt;a href="https://a816-health.nyc.gov/hdi/epiquery/visualizations?PageType=ps&amp;amp;PopulationSource=Syndromic" target="_blank" rel="false noopener"&gt;collected&lt;/a&gt; from the NYC Health Department shows that nearly 10,000 emergency room visits of flu-like illness were reported last week—the largest weekly peak seen in at least a decade.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;According to the CDC’s &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-50.html" target="_blank" rel="false noopener"&gt;latest flu surveillance data&lt;/a&gt; (covering up to Dec. 13), the majority of new infections are being caused by H3N2. Flu activity is “very high” or “high” in 17 regions of the U.S., including NYC, and “moderate” in another 8 jurisdictions. Two more pediatric deaths were reported that week, rising the total to 3 deaths so far this season. And we almost certainly haven’t reached the peak yet.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;What to do&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;There are some silver linings to this bad flu season.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For starters, subclade K doesn’t seem to have any mutations that make it more likely to cause severe illness compared to other H3N2 strains. And though the seasonal flu vaccine is mismatched to the variant, it’s not worthless. UK data has &lt;a href="https://www.eurosurveillance.org/content/10.2807/1560-7917.ES.2025.30.46.2500854#html_fulltext:~:text=Despite%20the%20emergence,cohorts%20%5B26%5D." target="_blank" rel="false noopener"&gt;found&lt;/a&gt; that the vaccine is still providing significant protection from serious complications, especially in children.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;This means that vaccination remains a crucial tool against flu this winter. So it’s still worthwhile to get your flu shot even now, though you should keep in mind that it takes around two weeks for the vaccine’s protection to kick in.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You should also practice good hygiene like regularly washing your hands, trying to stay home if you’re sick, and potentially wearing a mask in higher-risk situations for added protection. Well-fitting, high-quality masks such as a KN95 or N95 are the most effective.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:15:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOUHJWT1F6R0hOSlRKMEd3d1NTRzNyQ29MTGlXdktONDF5MWJnQTRDLTZrUEVObloxeWgyMkRYbHZFVElrZGl4SkY3S05oNUlNUnNvbDNYX1MyV01IaTFQVHA0dzhQOF9oSEZYUEM4U1FxdkdWUC1NWk95UUVoTmozeGNXNEt5Y3c0VEp1LXpoYmZEbVZlUk1aQVZoRDBGbzB6V3c</guid></item><item><title>常见补充剂现在已经让科学家们完全相信它还可以增强大脑和心脏功能- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/common-supplement-creatine-boosts-energy-also-improves-brain-heart-health/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many health-conscious people start their day by taking supplements and vitamins as part of their morning routine, right alongside breakfast or a cup of coffee. They do it to boost energy, immunity, bone strength, or overall wellness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Creatine is one such supplement that has become a common staple in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/blue-green-microalgae-spirulina-supplement-has-more-vital-b12-than-milk-or-meat/"&gt;supplement aisles&lt;/a&gt;. It has reputation of being something only necessary for people who work out heavily. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Athletes use it to sprint harder, lift heavier, and recover faster, so plenty of people treat it as a “gym thing.” In simple terms, creatine acts like a quick-charge backup system for cells that burn through energy fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-creatine-and-cellular-energy"&gt;Creatine and cellular energy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cells run on energy every second of every day, then they spend it in a form called Adenosine triphosphate (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Adenosine_triphosphate" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;ATP&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ATP works as the main “spendable” energy molecule, but cells burn through it quickly during intense exercise, illness, missed sleep, or other high-demand stress. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Creatine helps by storing energy in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/chemistry/phosphocreatine" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;phosphocreatine&lt;/a&gt;, which can help rebuild ATP when demand spikes. This setup works as a “quick-recharge system.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One report also links this backup to cell protection during metabolic stress, when tissues need fast energy support to stay stable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-creatine-energy-and-safety"&gt;Creatine, energy, and safety&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;People still ask, “Is creatine safe?” A major safety analysis led by a long-time creatine researcher focuses on results from controlled scientific studies instead of word-of-mouth warnings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr. Richard Kreider, a professor and director of the Exercise &amp;amp; Sport Nutrition Lab at &lt;a href="https://education.tamu.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Texas A&amp;amp;M University&lt;/a&gt;, creatine is crucial for human bodies to function at full capacity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When the body is stressed, like in exercise or under metabolic conditions like some diseases, creatine phosphate is needed to maintain energy in the cell, and therefore has a lot of protective and health benefits, in addition to the exercise performance effects that have been seen,” explained Kreider, who has spent more than 30 years studying creatine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href="http://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/15502783.2025.2488937#d1e242" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;comprehensive study&lt;/a&gt;, Kreider’s team reviewed hundreds of clinical trials and compared side effects in people who took creatine with people who took a placebo. They did not see meaningful differences in side-effect rates between the groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of the loudest claims of side effects come as personal stories: “My friend felt bloated,” “Someone online said it hurt kidneys,” “A coach warned me about cramps.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kreider’s study refutes those claims, showing that creatine can actually help the body hold onto more fluid, and that may reduce cramping in some situations. People vary, but the strongest evidence does not match the most common fears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-food-vs-supplements"&gt;Food vs. supplements&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your body can make creatine from amino acids and move it through the bloodstream to tissues that need quick energy support. Kreider’s study puts that internal production at about one gram each day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the recommended daily amount is to get two to four grams of creatine per day, depending on muscle mass and activity levels.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You only get about a gram of creatine per pound of red meat or fish, like salmon, so it’s expensive and takes a lot of calories to get a gram,” Kreider noted. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is a lot of food if your main goal is simply to raise creatine intake, which helps explain why creatine supplements exist. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vegetarians and vegans often start with lower creatine stores because they get little creatine through diet, so they may see a more noticeable benefit when they supplement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-studying-creatine-and-the-brain"&gt;Studying creatine and the brain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://news.vt.edu/articles/2025/06/research_fralinbiomed_chenacd_0625.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;separate study&lt;/a&gt; from Virginia Tech explains that creatine plays a vital role in the brain’s energy system, but it also points to effects beyond “energy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Creatine is very crucial for energy-consuming cells in skeletal muscle throughout the body, but also in the brain and in the heart,” said Chin-Yi Chen, a research scientist at Virginia Tech’s &lt;a href="https://fbri.vtc.vt.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Fralin Biomedical Research Institute&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chen is working with a research team that is developing a new way to send creatine directly into the brain using focused ultrasound. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The project takes place in the lab of Cheng-Chia “Fred” Wu, an assistant professor at the Fralin Biomedical Research Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-creatine-and-brain-function"&gt;Creatine and brain function&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/dopamine-enhances-brain-function-during-exercise/"&gt;human brain&lt;/a&gt; works nonstop. Neurons fire, support cells keep the chemical environment steady, and energy demand stays high from morning to night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Creatine can influence neurotransmitter systems, especially pathways involving &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/GABA" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;GABA&lt;/a&gt;, a major inhibitory neurotransmitter that helps prevent neurons from becoming overly excitable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This fact is important because brain function depends on both steady fuel and balanced signaling. When neurons lose either one, circuits can misfire or struggle to adapt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That helps explain why many studies associate creatine with learning, &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/common-and-inexpensive-supplement-prebiotic-fructooligosaccharides-protects-your-brain-from-dementia/"&gt;memory&lt;/a&gt;, brain development, and seizure control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-blood-brain-barrier"&gt;Blood-brain barrier&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brain sits behind the blood-brain barrier, a tight filter built from cells that line brain blood vessels. It blocks many toxins and pathogens from reaching brain tissue, and that protection saves lives. It can also limit access for helpful compounds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wu’s study at Virginia Tech describes people with creatine deficiency disorders who can improve muscle mass and body weight with supplements, yet still struggle with &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/common-plastics-chemical-bpa-linked-to-autism-adhd-in-children/"&gt;neurodevelopmental&lt;/a&gt; challenges. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These include difficulties with speech, reading, or writing because the brain does not receive enough creatine through normal routes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That challenge puts the creatine delivery system at the center of their work. The researchers describe a project that uses therapeutic focused ultrasound to temporarily open access across the blood-brain barrier in a precise, targeted way. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Focused ultrasound uses carefully aimed sound waves to create a short window that can let treatments reach specific brain areas without damaging nearby healthy tissue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The report notes that the lab has explored focused ultrasound approaches in other contexts, such as pediatric brain cancer, and now sees potential for creatine deficiency conditions as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-creatine-energy-and-brain-function"&gt;Creatine, energy, and brain function&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite strong scientific evidence, Kreider says people have misunderstood creatine for years and often spread false claims about it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He is one of the members of the &lt;a href="https://www.sportsnutritionsociety.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;International Society of Sports Nutrition&lt;/a&gt; who recently signed a letter stating that creatine is safe and effective and calling on policymakers not to limit public access to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There’s absolutely no data supporting any negative side effect anecdotally reported about creatine on the internet and in the media,” Kreider enthused. “Creatine is safe, and it’s important for everybody, not just bodybuilders and athletes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The work keeps moving from “Does it work?” to “Can we deliver it where it’s needed most?” That question changes the discussion from sports performance to medical delivery, where the details of human biology decide what happens next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:13:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQWXVVdk00VFRWVUFOWjJRakJqWHBVa2tjaFFncUQ0bFVhNUFNZ01yU1l6VS10eUU3ZUFkRkkwQUR3ZTV1WGgwTXRkdzdHajZPcW8zY0VnbzAyVjV4MDdwYWN3MkhzaW9ZYUlmRC1XN3BOY2RhYnRkX21GcVpNVlFHOFdQT1dneVhZQ0FmZjN0SU5XYXczXzZNYzBYUzYwczd5RnNz</guid></item><item><title>完美的早晨例行公事：如何建立一个快乐、健康的一天开始--从淋浴到阳光明媚--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2025/dec/26/perfect-morning-routine-happy-healthy-start-showers-sunshine</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;he first thing to say about the ideal morning routine is that it probably doesn’t exist. Yes, endless influencers promise that they have tweaked, tested and fine-tuned the process of revving up for the day, but how history’s most productive people &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; get things done is so varied that it’s hard to draw definitive conclusions. Beethoven, reportedly, used to count out exactly 60 beans for his morning cup of coffee, while Victor Hugo downed two raw eggs after reading a daily missive from his mistress. Mark Wahlberg, on the other hand, wakes at &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/shorts/Ej-o9ooFqcQ" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;3am&lt;/a&gt; for pre-workout prayer, chasing up his gym time with a few holes of golf and a jolt in the cryo chamber before he even thinks about doing any work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It is clear, though, that having some sort of routine is key: a set of automatic actions that you do every day, to ease you into your responsibilities with a bit of momentum and a fresh frame of mind. And there is some stuff that seems beneficial enough that everyone should be doing a version of it, even if individual methods differ: one person’s meditative bean arithmetic, after all, is another’s mindfulness. But if you want to finesse your routine, the key is to add one change at a time. &lt;strong&gt;“&lt;/strong&gt;When you focus on a single behaviour,” says the behaviour change specialist Dr Heather McKee, “you build confidence through quick wins, and give your brain the clarity and dopamine hit it needs to automate that action. Once that habit feels natural, you free up mental space to layer in the next change.” But what habits should you be building?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="5b7d789a-a77e-4871-acb8-11ba2837fc53" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Dogs are the perfect excuse to get a dose of morning light.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Posed by model; Olga Rolenko/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 id="get-up-get-out" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get up, get out&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;First things first: there’s no single best time to get up. If you have the luxury of picking your own window, it’s probably best to start by roughly working out your chronotype, which boils down to if you feel and perform best earlier in the day, you can probably get away with getting up a bit earlier (if you do your best work at night, of course, it would be ideal to sleep in).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Most adults need between seven and nine hours’ sleep to feel fully functional, and you probably have a good idea of where you fall in that range. In an ideal world, you shouldn’t need an alarm to wake up: if that means going to bed at 10 so you’re feeling fresh by 6am, that’s the way forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Ellie Hambly, a clinical psychologist specialising in helping families deal with stress, advises getting outside in the morning light. “This is getting harder with daylight hours reducing, but trying to manage your diary around getting some daylight can make a huge difference in your mood.” Morning exposure to natural sunlight plays a key role in keeping our body clock working properly. It suppresses melatonin, boosts serotonin, gets you ready for the day – and &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39077837/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;seems to help people sleep better&lt;/a&gt; at night. If you have a dog or a running habit, great – but it’s even worth poking your head out of the door while you enjoy your morning coffee. “If you can make the time for a short walk without your phone in the morning, the combination of movement and lack of stimulation can help to activate your brain’s default mode network – the set of brain regions engaged in introspection and daydreaming,” says Hambly. “That can help with creative problem-solving and coming up with new ideas. If you don’t have time for a walk, even taking a shower without a podcast can work.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="efb00c4b-f635-4ec5-836e-3364af22114f" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Getting outside in the morning light can make a huge difference.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Posed by model; Brook Pifer/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 id="put-the-kettle-on" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;Put the kettle on&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Recently, it’s become fashionable among self-optimisers to claim that you should wait 60-90 minutes to drink your first coffee to avoid an afternoon crash. This sounds plausible, but a &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/10.1080/15502783.2024.2323919?url_ver=Z39.88-2003&amp;amp;rfr_id=ori:rid:crossref.org&amp;amp;rfr_dat=cr_pub%20%200pubmed" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;review of studies&lt;/a&gt; published in 2024 concluded that there’s no evidence this happens – and caffeine has also been shown to increase exercise performance in a variety of ways, so it’s definitely worth having a coffee if you’re going to work out (giving it 20-30 minutes to let the effects kick in). Otherwise, just do what’s most comfortable for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="08c288e0-01f8-4543-a6b5-913030a24ad4" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Go with your natural flow.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Posed by models; Thomas Barwick/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Should you exercise first thing? If you can face it, yes: at least a bit. The best time of day to hit the gym seems to vary depending on your chronotype, specific goals and preferred workout style: morning exercise, for instance, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26844280/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;can help with burning fat&lt;/a&gt;, and strength-building sessions are also &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/27863207/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;probably slightly better&lt;/a&gt; if your aim is muscle. But it’s possible that you can “retrain” your body to work out more effectively at different times of day by doing it consistently (&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25631930/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;one study on swimmers&lt;/a&gt; found that both chronotype and habitual training time are important). However, morning workouts seem to have a host of benefits all of their own, from &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40419564/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;reducing body fat to improving sleep&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;On a more basic note, it’s also just easier to ensure you get your workouts done if you schedule them first thing, with no chance of a random pub invite or work demand getting in the way. If you can’t face a full-on run or dragging the dumbbells out from under the bed, it helps to have a pre-set, full-body routine that’s simple enough to do in your living room while everyone else dashes around eating toast and doing last-minute homework. The “slow” burpee is a winner here: squat down low, put your hands on the floor (between your feet if you can), then step one foot back at a time until you’re in a plank position. Do a press-up if you’ve got it in you, then reverse the whole process to come back to your feet: a handful of these will hit your arms, legs and core while also helping you stretch out stiff joints. Start with five, and work your way up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;Read a line of poetry, sip your tea, write a quick reflection, or get through a couple of pages of a book&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;h2 id="cold-comforts" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;Cold comforts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;How cold should your morning shower be? Again, this depends on what you’re going for. There is some evidence that hosing yourself down with frosty water in the morning can offer physiological benefits: cold exposure can trigger the release of endorphins and help your parasympathetic nervous system (the restful one) kick in, so even if it doesn’t feel like it in the moment, it’s probably cheering you up. On the flipside, a cold shock is potentially going to jolt you out of any default mode network thinking that’s helping you to solve problems or think creatively. But there’s a best-of-both-worlds approach. “I recommend to my coaching clients that they introduce hot and cold cycling as part of their morning routine for both the physical and mental benefits,” says the wellness expert Tana Hoffman Cook. “For people who are just starting out, even ending your shower with a cold blast can offer health benefits – cold exposure has been linked to increased dopamine levels, making it a powerful addition to anyone’s morning routine when they want to start their day feeling alert, clear-headed and with a mood-boost.”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props="{&amp;quot;index&amp;quot;:16,&amp;quot;listId&amp;quot;:6060,&amp;quot;identityName&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;how-to-have-a-better-day&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;description&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Sign up to our 16-part series and get expert advice on how to improve your life - from morning to night&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;How to have a better day&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;frequency&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Twice weekly, for eight weeks&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;successDescription&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;You're signed up to How to have a better day.&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;theme&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;features&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;idApiUrl&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://idapi.theguardian.com&amp;quot;}"&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="b6aa2ace-6a53-45b2-b357-9a1d8b1dd80f" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Judgment-free scribbles can boost physical and psychological health.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Posed by model; Luis Alvarez/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 id="scribble-it-out" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;Scribble it out&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;What about journalling, which is frequently recommended? A 2018 &lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/advances-in-psychiatric-treatment/article/emotional-and-physical-health-benefits-of-expressive-writing/ED2976A61F5DE56B46F07A1CE9EA9F9F" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;review of studies&lt;/a&gt; found that writing about stressful or emotional events for a few minutes resulted in improvements in physical and psychological health in non-clinical and clinical populations. “Morning pages”, as they’re sometimes known, can work as a sort of lower-stakes version of that: aiming to fill a page or two with judgment-free scribble (that you’re definitely allowed to throw away afterwards) might help you reorganise your thoughts before you go about your day, or at least get your biggest worries down on paper. If you’re struggling to get anything out, use a prompt as an easy starting point: “What’s the biggest thing I’m worried about?” or “What’s one thing I want to focus on today?” Or you could be more specific with something like: “How am I actually going to get this project done on time?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="mindfulness-on-the-go" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;Mindfulness on the go&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure id="b6ea70a8-6560-4841-8ee3-bcf0f350683e" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Meditation can be alternated with breathing techniques.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Posed by model; pixdeluxe/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;As for meditation, the benefits are &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10355843/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;well established&lt;/a&gt; – they range from reduced anxiety to a boosted immune system – but if your mornings are too chaotic to sit in a quiet space (or plug into an app for 10 minutes), it might be worth starting with something a bit simpler. “I use something called the Ease morning routine to start the day with nervous system regulation rather than jumping straight into hustle mode,” says the wellbeing coach and yoga teacher Chloe Markham. “We begin with an Exhale, or stillness. If I don’t have time to meditate, I’ll use the 4-7-8 breathing technique: breathe in gently through your nose for a count of four, hold for seven, and breathe out through your mouth for eight. Next, we Anchor – this is where we clock in with the way our body feels and maybe set a soft intention for the day.” Spend a second listening to your body, she suggests, and maybe change your goals accordingly. “If you’re feeling energised, great! If not, maybe scale things back a bit. The next step is movement, or Shift – this is about moving our bodies in ways that feel good – and the final step is to Engage in something nourishing: read a line of poetry, sip your tea, write a quick reflection or get through a couple of pages of a book.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;You could try to sneak in a bit of mindfulness while you do the washing-up&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Whether it takes five minutes or 95, she says, “this sort of routine cannot only prepare us for a calmer day, but also can strengthen our nervous system’s ability to self-regulate more quickly. The magic comes from consistency rather than perfection.” And if all that takes too much time, you could try to sneak in a bit of mindfulness while you do the washing-up: in &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s12671-014-0360-9" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;one paper from Florida State University&lt;/a&gt;, a group of volunteers who read a text that encouraged them to focus their thoughts on the sensations evoked by the activity they were doing reported increases in elements of “positive affect” (such as inspiration) and decreased nervousness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“You don’t need a 5am wake-up call or a one-hour ritual to have a ‘good’ morning,” says the yoga teacher Maysun Hassanaly. “What matters is consistency. Think small daily doses of feelgood moments to lift your mood, that are useful and doable. Think of your mornings in three layers: must-do, nice-to-have and optional. On busy days, stick to your must-dos: the simple actions that ground you or energise you. On slower mornings, add a nice-to-have or two. It could be something as small as putting on your favourite song and having a quick dance, walking one extra bus stop, or taking a moment to notice the morning light. Tiny rituals like these help you feel calmer and in control of your day, without sacrificing sleep or overloading your to-do list.” You can’t micromanage everything that’s going to happen for the rest of the day, or everything that’s going on in the world – so for 10 minutes after you wake up, why not just be a bit nicer to yourself?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQc1BuYWVYc29TaEM1RWQtLW5BSHJOMEZnVjhPNjlMTjFIU1lnYVBHTjhoYV9mWHhiLUt6MVVIQ3ZXMks4R2lVZnh1Vmx5aV9DeWlCdUtqYlJ3eG14dTkyU0pZSy1RQ3hvOWZESkhLaHNqZjBfSTVJWEVxVWdKZmRLWXFvRjhVZ3dsV01tRnhVdXd3RUMxeEduUnoybm15b01DUmVxQU1kRGVkSzJnN3E1elphdw</guid></item><item><title>为什么人类大脑的成熟速度比灵长类动物慢- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-human-brain-matures-slower-primate.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxNTVhmbG5WaHg4dUt5R0QtYTJtcER0ekFTTVZWMF9QRzJILVk4SmpDZDhScS01djVUb2FyVjIydW1LZmU2Tko4WmwyT3U3VmtZYmozYWxCOHh0TUtYWUR0US1keHBZSkZxbTRiTzdNY1JkTDRmLTdjS2ZDZzRPYVAxTlJCRWc</guid></item><item><title>饮用石榴汁促进血压和心脏健康的最佳时间- Verywell Health</title><link>https://www.verywellhealth.com/best-time-to-drink-pomegranate-juice-11870165</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="health-sc-page_1-0" class="comp health-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content article-content expert-content right-rail__offset lock-journey" data-sc-sticky-offset="60" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[400, 1400, 1400, 1700, 2000, 2200, 2400, 2600, 2800]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="health-sc-block-callout--key-takeaway_1-0" class="comp health-sc-block-callout--key-takeaway health-sc-block-callout-base mntl-sc-block-callout mntl-block theme-key-takeaway theme-key-takeaway" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block-callout-heading_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-heading mntl-text-block"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block-callout-body_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-body mntl-text-block expert-content"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drink pomegranate juice daily for heart health benefits.  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drink it in the morning or early afternoon for easier digestion.  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Check with your doctor if you're on blood pressure or blood-thinning drugs before drinking pomegranate juice.  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Pomegranate juice is rich in antioxidants and may offer blood pressure and heart health benefits when you drink it daily.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The best time to drink it depends on your individual health, but you may consider having it in the morning or early afternoon for easier digestion and more energy.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-when-to-drink-pomegranate-juice"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; When to Drink Pomegranate Juice &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As long as you drink it consistently, there is no ideal time to consume &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/pomegranate-juice-11839039" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;pomegranate juice&lt;/a&gt; for heart health, according to &lt;a href="https://health.usf.edu/publichealth/overviewcoph/faculty/lywright" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Lauri Wright, PhD, RDN&lt;/a&gt;, director of nutrition programs and an associate professor at USF College of Public Health.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "What matters most is consistent intake, because the heart-healthy compounds, especially &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/polyphenols-5217399" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;polyphenols&lt;/a&gt;, work by gradually improving blood vessel function and reducing oxidative stress," she said.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; However, Wright said that people with stomach sensitivities may want to drink pomegranate juice in the morning or early afternoon for easier digestion. Drinking it in the morning can also provide you with energy for your day.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-when-not-to-drink-pomegranate-juice"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; When Not to Drink Pomegranate Juice &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re prone to reflux, drinking acidic juices like pomegranate right before bed may worsen heartburn, said &lt;a href="https://www.missouristate.edu/SHS/profile-display.aspx?p=natalieallen" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Natalie Allen, RD&lt;/a&gt;, a clinical associate professor of nutrition and dietetics at Missouri State University.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And if you have diabetes or insulin resistance, drinking it on an empty stomach, especially first thing in the morning, may cause a sharper blood sugar rise. In that case, it's best to pair pomegranate juice with a meal or protein-rich snack, according to Wright.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/pomegranate-11828597" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Pomegranate juice&lt;/a&gt; may also interact with certain blood pressure, statin, or blood-thinning drugs, so anyone on these medications should check with their healthcare provider before adding it to their daily routine.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Overall, there’s no single 'wrong' time," Wright said. "Just choose a time when it feels best for your digestion and blood sugar control."&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-why-consistency-matters-most-for-heart-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Why Consistency Matters Most for Heart Health &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When trying to get the most benefit from drinking pomegranate juice, consistency matters more than timing.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Drink it regularly to see health benefits," Allen said. "Studies showing blood pressure benefits typically look at daily intake, not the timing of when you drink the juice."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Generally, fruits and vegetables that are brightly colored are high in &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/foods-with-more-antioxidants-than-pomegranate-seeds-11835037" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;antioxidants&lt;/a&gt;, Allen explained, and pomegranates are no exception. Pomegranate juice is loaded with polyphenols, which help keep blood vessels smooth.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Pomegranates also help the body make and use nitric oxide, a compound that relaxes blood vessels.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "I like to think of it this way: drinking pomegranate juice is like a gentle massage for your arteries," Allen said. "We want them flexible, relaxed, and smooth, and this juice helps support just that."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Some studies also show modest reductions in LDL oxidation, which is helpful for long-term cardiovascular health.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; But keep in mind that these effects typically occur with regular intake over weeks, Wright said, not from just one glass.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-much-should-you-drink"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Much Should You Drink? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Most clinical studies on the blood pressure and vascular benefits of pomegranate juice used 4–8 ounces (½–1 cup) of 100% pomegranate juice, with no sugar added, per day.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "That’s enough to provide beneficial polyphenols without excessive sugar or calories," Wright said. "So you don’t need a large bottle; just a small daily glass is sufficient."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As with all nutrition, Allen said pomegranate juice works best alongside overall heart-healthy habits, such as eating more fruits and vegetables, staying active, and managing stress.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Don’t forget about pomegranate arils; they're also great for overall health," she added. "Toss them onto a salad, add to a yogurt parfait, or mix with avocado and mango for a festive salsa."&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="post-article_1-0" class="comp post-article mntl-block"&gt;
&lt;div id="sources_1-0" class="comp sources mntl-block"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-article-sources_1-0" class="comp mntl-article-sources mntl-expandable-block" data-scroll-offset="70"&gt;&lt;div class="loc expandable-content"&gt;&lt;div id="source-guidelines_1-0" class="comp source-guidelines mntl-text-block"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verywell Health uses only high-quality sources, including peer-reviewed studies, to support the facts within our articles. Read our &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="/verywell-editorial-process-4777042"&gt;editorial process&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; to learn more about how we fact-check and keep our content accurate, reliable, and trustworthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-article-sources__citation-sources_1-0" class="comp mntl-article-sources__citation-sources mntl-citation-sources mntl-sources" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;ol class="mntl-sources__content"&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aviram M, Rosenblat M. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.5041/RMMJ.10113" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Pomegranate for your cardiovascular health&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;RMMJ&lt;/em&gt;. 2013;4(2):e0013. doi:10.5041/RMMJ.10113&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roelofs EJ, Smith‐Ryan AE, Trexler ET, Hirsch KR, Mock MG. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/17461391.2016.1230892" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Effects of pomegranate extract on blood flow and vessel diameter after high‐intensity exercise in young, healthy adult&lt;/a&gt;s. &lt;em&gt;European Journal of Sport Science&lt;/em&gt;. 2017;17(3):317-325. doi:10.1080/17461391.2016.1230892&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-3"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saeed E, Javed F, Rana Z, et al. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/efd2.70075" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Bioactive compounds, their mechanisms of action, and cardioprotective effects of pomegranate (&lt;em&gt;punica granatum&lt;/em&gt;): a comprehensive review&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;eFood&lt;/em&gt;. 2025;6(4):e70075. doi:10.1002/efd2.70075&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-4"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aviram M, Rosenblat M, Gaitini D, et al. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.clnu.2003.10.002" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Pomegranate juice consumption for 3 years by patients with carotid artery stenosis reduces common carotid intima-media thickness, blood pressure and LDL oxidation&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Clinical Nutrition&lt;/em&gt;. 2004;23(3):423-433. doi:10.1016/j.clnu.2003.10.002&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="author-bio_1-0" class="comp author-bio"&gt;

&lt;p class="author-bio__bio-text"&gt;
&lt;span class="author-bio__bio-title"&gt;By &lt;a href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/mira-miller-5202407"&gt;Mira Miller&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Miller is a journalist specializing in mental health, women's health, and culture. Her work is published in outlets ranging from Vice to Healthnews.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="trust-ribbon_1-0" class="comp trust-ribbon trust-ribbon-expandable-block"&gt; 
&lt;div class="loc expandable-content"&gt;&lt;div id="trust-ribbon__feedback-block_1-0" class="comp trust-ribbon__feedback-block article-feedback mntl-article-feedback"&gt; 
&lt;div class="article-feedback__success-section js-success-section is-hidden"&gt;
&lt;p class="article-feedback__heading"&gt;Thanks for your feedback!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="article-feedback__feedback-section js-feedback-section is-hidden"&gt;
&lt;p class="article-feedback__heading"&gt;What is your feedback?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;button id="helpful-button_1-0" class="comp helpful-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Helpful
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;button id="report-error-button_1-0" class="comp report-error-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Report an Error
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;button id="other-button_1-0" class="comp other-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Other
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-x close-button"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-x" href="#icon-x"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Verywell Health</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:56:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxPMzhlYk54ZVN3dzJ2MndqMUNXTkMyQS1HQW5Kem5BTEFvTnhhLVVHcnI5ZlNOVlJKQVdjTkRfZ3BadUQzcW92SW5yY01tQUNjOUpvNlRDUzZWaDZ5bkppMTY3ZFJJbUdFcWlqNnpXVll2QXNaNy1OOHVXdEJSVUhRRWt3</guid></item><item><title>Ocala医生获得缓刑，对导致患者心脏病发作的处方进行罚款- Ocala-News.com</title><link>https://www.ocala-news.com/2025/12/26/ocala-doctor-gets-probation-fine-over-prescriptions-that-caused-patients-heart-attack/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;

		
		
&lt;p&gt;An Ocala physician has been fined $7,500 and placed on probation by state health officials following a medical malpractice complaint that he prescribed unnecessary thyroid medication to a patient who then suffered a heart attack as a result. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Dr. Steven Charles Tieche, who practices at the Recharge Clinic on SW 17th Street in Ocala, appeared before the Florida Board of Medicine on December 5, in Dania Beach. The Board issued its final order on Monday, December 22, placing Tieche’s license on probation for one year.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;According to the administrative complaint adopted by the Board, a patient presented to Tieche at Recharge Clinic in June 2023 to discuss hormone replacement therapy. Following an evaluation, Tieche interpreted the patient’s lab results as indicating low thyroid levels. As a result, he prescribed compound thyroid supplements LT3 and LT4.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In early July, Tieche increased the patient’s dosage. By mid-August, the patient returned with severe symptoms, including anxiety, tremors, irregular heart rate, and vomiting, leading Tieche to discontinue the supplements.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Days later, on August 21, 2023, the patient was admitted to the UF Health Leesburg Emergency Department with chest pain and diagnosed with a myocardial infarction, commonly known as a heart attack.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A subsequent review by an endocrinologist revealed that the patient’s original lab results from June showed normal thyroid levels. The specialist diagnosed the patient with thyrotoxicosis, a condition caused by abnormally high levels of thyroid hormone.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;State investigators determined that Tieche failed to meet the prevailing professional standard of care by prescribing the supplements in the absence of a confirmed diagnosis of hypothyroidism. The Department of Health charged Tieche with medical malpractice under Florida Statutes.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;At the December hearing, Tieche was present and represented by counsel, but the facts of the case were not in dispute. Under the terms of the final order, the Ocala doctor must pay an administrative fine of $7,500 and case costs of $2,847.21 within 30 days. He is also required to complete five hours of continuing medical education (CME), specifically in the area of Thyroid Disorders, within one year.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;During his one-year probation, Tieche is prohibited from practicing medicine without indirect supervision from a board-certified family practice or internal medicine physician. This monitoring physician must review 100 percent of Tieche’s endocrine patient records and 25 percent of his active patient records once every quarter.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Tieche must also appear before the board’s probation committee at the beginning and end of his probationary period.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Tieche, who co-founded Recharge Clinic with his wife, is a board certified physician in anesthesiology and holds multiple other certifications. &lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p id="jp-relatedposts" class="jp-relatedposts"&gt;
	&lt;h3 class="jp-relatedposts-headline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Related&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;	&lt;/div&gt;

	

	
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ocala-News.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:55:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxNN2NidEl6S1AySWxuMEdCSXpZS0Jrbk9WZ3RvQjJhS1B5OEx4aWJ4V09ESWZnSGFiMVE3U0lMSF9meG8zRS11VXg2aXVRa3phdEVhdjExMFNNUHlTMEhiN01Bekt4NHF5SWFFclB5azVsZWlhOGZDM0NhQ1hWbW5Ya2xzV0ktLXloazFIWHpxWkFzLWRvQUNDOFQycjd4Rmc1V0M1MW5EYnN2SVZsdkdkNWxCTkZlSkRfZVNVWk5WTWlZUQ</guid></item><item><title>Ozempic时代的婚姻和性：更新-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/26/podcasts/the-daily/sex-ozempic-update.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:52:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNNFpPWkVZQWZZVWpCYk9OMWZMYkpwWFh2UXNEVlBmMHNadVQ1Z3ZUcnFkOFRsZDZDM096a1BFWkFob3djbWhnT3pZQmlXMVdQZW4yUGltR2VLWmdyMDRKb2w1NHdya3hkbnNYR21Tc1N4Zmxlbi1Oc3BRQVYzTDhTMUZ3MA</guid></item><item><title>科学家通过恢复代谢平衡实现小鼠阿尔茨海默氏症的完全神经系统恢复- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/scientists-achieve-full-neurological-recovery-from-alzheimers-in-mice-by-restoring-metabolic-balance/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers have discovered that Alzheimer’s disease may be reversible in animal models through a treatment that restores the brain’s metabolic balance. This study, published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.xcrm.2025.102535" target="_blank"&gt;Cell Reports Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, demonstrates that restoring levels of a specific energy molecule allows the brain to repair damage and recover cognitive function even in advanced stages of the illness. The results suggest that the cognitive decline associated with the condition is not an inevitable permanent state but rather a result of a loss of brain resilience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more than a century, people have considered Alzheimer’s disease an irreversible illness. Consequently, research has focused on preventing or slowing it, rather than recovery. Despite billions of dollars spent on decades of research, there has never been a clinical trial of any drug to reverse and recover from the condition. This new research challenges that long held dogma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was led by Kalyani Chaubey, a researcher at the Case Western Reserve University School of Medicine. She worked alongside senior author Andrew A. Pieper, who is a professor at Case Western Reserve and director of the Brain Health Medicines Center at Harrington Discovery Institute. The team included scientists from University Hospitals and the Louis Stokes Cleveland VA Medical Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers focused on a molecule called nicotinamide adenine dinucleotide, known as NAD+. This molecule is essential for cellular energy and repair across the entire body. Scientists have observed that NAD+ levels decline naturally as people age, but this loss is much more pronounced in those with neurodegenerative conditions. Without proper levels of this metabolic currency, cells become unable to execute the processes required for proper functioning and survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous research has established a foundation for this approach. A 2018 study in the &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences&lt;/em&gt; showed that supplementing with NAD+ precursors &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.1718819115" target="_blank"&gt;could normalize neuroinflammation and DNA damage&lt;/a&gt; in mice. That earlier work suggested that a depletion of this molecule sits upstream of many other symptoms like tau protein buildup and synaptic dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2021, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.2011226118" target="_blank"&gt;another study&lt;/a&gt; published in the same journal found that restoring this energy balance could reduce cell senescence, which is a state where cells stop dividing but do not die. This process is linked to the chronic inflammation seen in aging brains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, an international team led by researchers at the University of Oslo recently &lt;a href="https://www.psypost.org/boosting-nad-reverses-alzheimers-like-deficits-in-animal-models/" target="_blank"&gt;identified a mechanism where NAD+ helps correct errors in how brain cells process genetic information&lt;/a&gt;. That study, published in &lt;em&gt;Science Advances&lt;/em&gt;, identified a specific protein called EVA1C as a central player in helping the brain manage damaged proteins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these promising leads, many existing supplements can push NAD+ to supraphysiologic levels. High levels that exceed what is natural for the body have been linked to an increased risk of cancer in some animal models. The Case Western Reserve team wanted to find a way to restore balance without overshooting the natural range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They utilized a compound called P7C3-A20, which was originally developed in the Pieper laboratory. This compound is a neuroprotective agent that helps cells maintain their proper balance of NAD+ under conditions of overwhelming stress. It does not elevate the molecule to levels that are unnaturally high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To test the potential for reversal, the researchers used two distinct mouse models. The first, known as 5xFAD, is designed to develop heavy amyloid plaque buildup and human like tau changes. The second model, PS19, carries a human mutation in the tau protein that causes toxic tangles and the death of neurons. These models allow scientists to study the major biological hallmarks of the human disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers first confirmed that brain energy balance deteriorates as the disease progresses. In mice that were two months old and pre-symptomatic, NAD+ levels were normal. By six months, when the mice showed clear signs of cognitive trouble, their levels had dropped by 30 percent. By twelve months, when the disease was very advanced, the deficit reached 45 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The core of the study involved a group of mice designated as the advanced disease stage cohort. These animals did not begin treatment until they were six months old. At this point, they already possessed established brain pathology and measurable cognitive decline. They received daily injections of the treatment until they reached one year of age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results showed a comprehensive recovery of function. In memory tests like the Morris water maze, where mice must remember the location of a submerged platform, the treated animals performed as well as healthy controls. Their spatial learning and memory were restored to normal levels despite their genetic mutations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mice also showed improvements in physical coordination. On a rotating rod test, which measures motor learning, the advanced stage mice regained their ability to balance and stay on the device. Their performance was not statistically different from healthy mice by the end of the treatment period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The biological changes inside the brain were equally notable. The treatment repaired the blood brain barrier, which is the protective seal around the brain’s blood vessels. In Alzheimer’s disease, this barrier often develops leaks that allow harmful substances into the brain tissue. Electronic microscope images showed that the treatment had sealed these gaps and restored the health of supporting cells called pericytes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also tracked a specific marker called p-tau217. This is a form of the tau protein that is now used as a standard clinical biomarker in human patients. The team found that levels of this marker in the blood were reduced by the treatment. This finding provides an objective way to confirm that the disease was being reversed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking about the discovery, Pieper noted the importance of the results for future medicine. “We were very excited and encouraged by our results,” he said. “Restoring the brain’s energy balance achieved pathological and functional recovery in both lines of mice with advanced Alzheimer’s. Seeing this effect in two very different animal models, each driven by different genetic causes, strengthens the new idea that recovery from advanced disease might be possible in people with AD when the brain’s NAD+ balance is restored.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team also performed a proteomic analysis, which is a massive screen of all the proteins in the brain. They identified 46 specific proteins that are altered in the same way in both human patients and the sick mice. These proteins are involved in tasks like waste management, protein folding, and mitochondrial function. The treatment successfully returned these protein levels to their healthy state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To ensure the mouse findings were relevant to humans, the scientists studied a unique group of people. These individuals are known as nondemented with Alzheimer’s neuropathology. Their brains are full of amyloid plaques, yet they remained cognitively healthy throughout their lives. The researchers found that these resilient individuals naturally possessed higher levels of the enzymes that produce NAD+.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This human data suggests that the brain has an intrinsic ability to resist damage if its energy balance remains intact. The treatment appears to mimic this natural resilience. “The damaged brain can, under some conditions, repair itself and regain function,” Pieper explained. He emphasized that the takeaway from this work is a message of hope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also included tests on human brain microvascular endothelial cells. These are the cells that make up the blood brain barrier in people. When these cells were exposed to oxidative stress in the laboratory, the treatment protected them from damage. It helped their mitochondria continue to produce energy and prevented the cells from dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the results are promising, there are some limitations to the study. The researchers relied on genetic mouse models, which represent the rare inherited forms of the disease. Most people suffer from the sporadic form of the condition, which may have more varied causes. Additionally, human brain samples used for comparison represent a single moment in time, which makes it difficult to establish a clear cause and effect relationship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research will focus on moving this approach into human clinical trials. The scientists want to determine if the efficacy seen in mice will translate to human patients. They also hope to identify which specific aspects of the brain’s energy balance are the most important for starting the recovery process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The technology is currently being commercialized by a company called Glengary Brain Health. The goal is to develop a therapy that could one day be used to treat patients who already show signs of cognitive loss. As Chaubey noted, “Through our study, we demonstrated one drug-based way to accomplish this in animal models, and also identified candidate proteins in the human AD brain that may relate to the ability to reverse AD.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.xcrm.2025.102535" target="_blank"&gt;Pharmacologic reversal of advanced Alzheimer’s disease in mice and identification of potential therapeutic nodes in human brain&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Kalyani Chaubey, Edwin Vázquez-Rosa, Sunil Jamuna Tripathi, Min-Kyoo Shin, Youngmin Yu, Matasha Dhar, Suwarna Chakraborty, Mai Yamakawa, Xinming Wang, Preethy S. Sridharan, Emiko Miller, Zea Bud, Sofia G. Corella, Sarah Barker, Salvatore G. Caradonna, Yeojung Koh, Kathryn Franke, Coral J. Cintrón-Pérez, Sophia Rose, Hua Fang, Adrian A. Cintrón-Pérez, Taylor Tomco, Xiongwei Zhu, Hisashi Fujioka, Tamar Gefen, Margaret E. Flanagan, Noelle S. Williams, Brigid M. Wilson, Lawrence Chen, Lijun Dou, Feixiong Cheng, Jessica E. Rexach, Jung-A Woo, David E. Kang, Bindu D. Paul, and Andrew A. Pieper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:08:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxOY1lkb0VPV0g4SzhVSVJIdDZjRFR0VkZsZUZpRXVZbHVqMWFWY3RGWWk3TzNpV1ppenBJTDNULWpZWW1QdWs2TDVGWFZSbmpkNVRyQ21oeUxKcVR6WU5IRFc3QV9fdG5yQ1VLQkp2bUJnbzdOSEMzZFAtbWF1YzdHbk9MZVR2SDdLeVlyemloUTkxcndzc29XamQxLXFzYWgtQ1JNbUFMTWRPdEVWTnNaU2dJUlNGZUEwczlGRnZnaVBvNmM</guid></item><item><title>骑自行车会导致勃起功能障碍吗？一位泌尿科医生解释说- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/26/health/cycling-prostate-erectile-dysfunction-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmj3h9jsn000e3b6povrpcc29@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note_elevate inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    Dr. Jamin Brahmbhatt is a urologist and robotic surgeon with Orlando Health and an assistant professor at the University of Central Florida’s College of Medicine.
&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj3h58vf001z29oyhrfcbbw0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            During the pandemic, I did what many other people did: I bought a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/17/health/biking-workout-exercise-routine-benefits-wellness"&gt;stationary bike&lt;/a&gt;. I joined the group rides, pushed through the resistance and pedaled my way to better health. A few weeks in, I started noticing something I didn’t expect — a subtle, intermittent pressure near my prostate that lingered throughout the day.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00023b6p8fpa1smu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As a urologist, knowing what those sensations can sometimes signal only made me more anxious.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00033b6pni52f9yl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Was the bike irritating something important? Was this the start of chronic prostate pain or even trouble in the bedroom? The worry built up enough that I stopped riding and eventually sold the bike. That fear is something I hear from patients all the time: Is biking causing my prostate issues or erection problems? The science-based answer is that it probably does not.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00043b6pugzn6mc9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In my case — and in many others — the problem wasn’t &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2Fcnn-underscored%2Fhealth-fitness%2Fcycling-essentials-for-beginners%3Futm_source%3Dinternal%26utm_medium%3Dmainsite%26utm_id%3Dfeatures&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C2e857a36a8ae4a64130808de3cea8f07%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C639015175304342729%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=4l4VcSXKk%2FRssVnOkxYJA4%2FjRB5K0vncvjOJBNiCwxw%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;the bike or the exercise&lt;/a&gt;. It was my form and my mind.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00053b6ph6iw5t94@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The prostate sits just below the bladder and wraps around the urethra. It is located deep in the pelvis, directly above the perineum (the soft area between the scrotum and anus). Anything that irritates that region, including pressure, tight muscles or prolonged sitting, can create sensations that men interpret as “prostate pain.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00063b6pk3wkh40z@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Cycling concentrates your body weight on the perineum, where the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/body/22000-pudendal-nerve" target="_blank"&gt;pudendal nerve&lt;/a&gt;, key blood vessels and the pelvic floor muscles all travel. The major nerves that support erections also run along the outer surface of the prostate, which is why irritation in the surrounding tissues can feel like a prostate or sexual function problem, even when the gland itself is normal.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00073b6p8epdpqic@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A narrow or traditional bike saddle can press on these sensitive areas for long periods, creating burning, pressure or a bruised feeling. That discomfort is real, but it isn’t the prostate or surrounding nerves themselves being damaged. Cycling affects the tissues around the gland — not the gland itself. This mirrors what the latest &lt;a href="https://www.auanet.org/guidelines-and-quality/guidelines/male-chronic-pelvic-pain" target="_blank"&gt;American Urological Association guidelines&lt;/a&gt; note: Perineal pressure and prolonged sitting are known triggers for pelvic and scrotal pain, not true prostate injury.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00083b6paw4uyvss@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/prostatitis/symptoms-causes/syc-20355766" target="_blank"&gt;Prostatitis&lt;/a&gt; is one of the most commonly misunderstood diagnoses in my field. The severe bacterial form — the one that causes fever, chills and intense urinary symptoms — is rare. Much more often, men are told they have prostatitis, even though there is no infection. Their symptoms come from irritated or tight pelvic floor muscles, nerve hypersensitivity, stress or prolonged sitting — problems that don’t show up on urine tests or cultures. Tenderness in these muscles is found in a significant number of men with pelvic pain, which helps explain why the symptoms can feel so similar to prostate inflammation.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00093b6pmcktud1t@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Cycling can aggravate these muscles for some riders, especially if they stay seated the entire ride or are new to the activity. The discomfort that follows can feel identical to true prostate inflammation, even though the prostate itself is normal.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000a3b6p2vfq0key@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The fear of erectile dysfunction often appears the moment men feel pressure or numbness in the pelvic region after a ride. Older research studies raised concerns that cycling might reduce blood flow to the penis. Those early studies made headlines, and many men still assume there is a direct link between biking and erectile dysfunction — but that’s not necessarily true.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000b3b6pojc8o0lc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29031767/" target="_blank"&gt;More recent research&lt;/a&gt; shows that regular cycling does not increase the long-term risk of erectile dysfunction. In fact, many cyclists report better sexual function than those who don’t ride, mainly because cycling or any exercise can improve heart and vascular health. Temporary numbness or tingling after a long or intense ride can happen, but it typically resolves quickly once pressure is relieved.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000c3b6pvo7hmjpl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Erections depend on healthy blood vessels, well-functioning nerves and balanced hormones working together with psychological factors such as stress and arousal. Chronic conditions such as diabetes, high blood pressure, high cholesterol and heart disease are among the most common contributors to erectile dysfunction because they reduce blood flow to the penis. Smoking, inactivity, obesity, stress and certain medications also play major roles in the quality of erections.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000d3b6pv2fewvdk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Testosterone affects libido and energy but is rarely the sole cause of erectile dysfunction. The latter is usually a whole-body issue, not a cycling problem. And as mentioned earlier, the cardiovascular benefits of cycling often help erectile function rather than harm it.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000e3b6p8yw7c1n6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Even if cycling doesn’t cause permanent harm, it can still leave riders with temporary sensations during or after a ride. These feelings come from how your body meets the saddle — the amount of time you stay seated, your posture and how conditioned your pelvic muscles are for supporting pressure in that position.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000f3b6piph5xxxk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            How you ride also matters. Stationary bikes often keep you in one position for extended periods, especially during high-resistance climbs, which can increase pelvic pressure. That’s different than outdoor cycling, which naturally shifts your weight — you stand to pedal, adjust during climbs and descents, and move more freely — giving the pelvic muscles brief breaks. Electric bikes assist during harder efforts and may limit how far forward you lean, but they still depend on proper saddle fit and posture.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000g3b6phztuwa67@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Factors such as saddle shape, handlebar height and uninterrupted time in the seat determine how much pressure the pelvis absorbs. New riders tend to notice these sensations more simply because their bodies haven’t yet adapted to longer periods in the saddle.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000h3b6pljpk88ya@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Some men may notice pelvic symptoms more than others. Riders with a history of lower back problems, hip tightness, chronic stress, anxiety or previous pelvic pain often have more sensitive pelvic floor muscles to begin with. Men with desk jobs who sit for long hours may also feel saddle pressure more intensely when they first start cycling. These symptoms don’t mean harm is being done — but they do mean your body may need more attention to bike fit, posture and gradual mileage.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000i3b6pbcs7ggp3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Most cycling-related discomfort improves with adjustments rather than stopping the activity. Saddles with center cutouts or split designs reduce pressure on sensitive areas, and small changes in seat height, tilt or handlebar position can shift weight away from the perineum.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjjblzeg00043b6p3ymick11@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Briefly standing every 10 to 15 minutes, wearing padded shorts and building mileage gradually can also help.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000j3b6pr48su20c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            If symptoms persist, pelvic floor physical therapy is one of the strongest evidence-backed treatments available. The goal isn’t to stop cycling — it’s to ride in a way that supports comfort, protects the surrounding tissues and allows your body to adapt safely over time.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000k3b6p4uqnp7ij@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Persistent numbness, discomfort lasting hours or days after cycling, painful erections or new urinary changes should be evaluated. These symptoms are usually treatable and do not imply permanent injury.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjjbmb1200063b6pfe8n1mq0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Equipment adjustments, a short break from riding or targeted therapy often resolve the issue.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjjbmjis00083b6ptv8ylt8r@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Persistent symptoms shouldn’t be ignored, but they also shouldn’t trigger panic. Most riders improve with straightforward changes.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000l3b6pyj842rfi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Cycling did not damage my prostate or affect my sexual health — but the sensations I felt were real, and the fear is something I hear from men every week. Understanding how saddle pressure interacts with the pelvic floor and nerves can help you ride more comfortably and interpret new sensations without assuming the worst.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000m3b6pkmrdev2h@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Looking back, I probably didn’t need to sell my bike. What I needed was a better seat, a few adjustments and a reminder not to panic the moment something in my pelvis felt different.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000n3b6ptxfoopda@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            I know many men react the same way I did — with fear first, facts later. You don’t have to. With the right setup and a little awareness, cycling can stay part of your routine without putting your prostate or sexual health at risk.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000o3b6pok17pib2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            And this isn’t just about cycling. Any new exercise will come with an adjustment period, and it’s normal to feel unfamiliar aches as your body adapts. A little preparation, good form and asking for help when you need it can keep you moving safely.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmj3hq4sq00173b6p3s4u3cmn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note_elevate inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    Get inspired by a weekly roundup on living well, made simple. Sign up for &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/newsletters/life-but-better?source=nl-acq_article"&gt;CNN’s Life, But Better newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for information and tools designed to improve your well-being.
&lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:00:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQOWFXTUI0ek9waThYUGcwMzlxQjNkNU43bExCRXJHcnN0TVJYMDBfeERIYnBZTnZKMFpWbDhEdHh6LTdtLXNDQ1IydEU3b2JHTGpzb1RReWx5bVF2aXNIcmNBV2Y2Q0YtYlNPR2FKS1p3eS1PcmpBWjhzQV9wd3lUUjdHVnV5S1AzeWVncg</guid></item><item><title>昨晚吃了太多糖？以下是营养师今天建议您做的事情- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/what-to-do-if-you-ate-too-much-sugar-last-night-11863856</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Don’t restrict or cleanse—just return to your usual balanced meals and routine.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Start the next day with a protein- and fiber-rich breakfast to steady blood sugar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hydrate, move your body and practice self-kindness to break the binge-restrict cycle.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; So you ate an entire pint of ice cream while streaming Netflix. Or maybe you ate more dessert than felt comfortable at a family gathering. We’ve all been there. But then the inevitable happens. You wake up the next morning feeling not so great and maybe a little anxious and guilty. And you’re wondering what to do next.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While you may have the overwhelming urge to restrict calories, cut out carbs or resort to an expensive cleanse, dietitians recommend you let it go and get back into your regular routine. There is no need to take any extreme measures.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-first-thing-you-should-do"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; The First Thing You Should Do &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; You might think the best way to recover from a sugar-filled night is to double down on rigid food rules. But with that approach, you can really get caught in a vicious cycle. Instead, let it go and get back to your regularly scheduled programming!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Resist the urge to “undo” the sugar with more restriction, says &lt;a href="https://revvhealth.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Marissa Beck, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;. “Get back into a routine with ample self-care, tune into hunger and fullness cues, and aim for regular meals and snacks that include all macronutrients,” she says.&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;If you focus on balance and nourishing your body, you can get on with the show in a way that supports your physical and mental health. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; What’s the first step you should take? Start your day with a nourishing protein- and fiber-rich breakfast to set the tone. While you might think &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-happens-to-your-body-when-you-skip-breakfast-8417958" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;skipping breakfast&lt;/a&gt; is a good way to make up for the sugar you ate the night before, the opposite is true. Eating a nutrient-dense breakfast that’s rich in protein and fiber supports &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/simple-ways-to-keep-blood-sugar-in-check-11791785" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;balanced blood sugar&lt;/a&gt; and will keep you feeling energized and ready to take on the day. It can also prevent cravings and overeating later in the day so you don’t repeat the same cycle. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Then, aim to eat balanced meals and snacks for the rest of the day. Skipping meals in an attempt to compensate for overeating can backfire. When you deprive your body of the nutrition it needs, it may respond by ramping up hunger hormones, which may lead to eating more later in the day. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To stay consistent, Beck suggests a midmorning snack of strained strained (Greek-style) yogurt with berries, nuts and chia seeds. Lunch could be a fiber-filled grain bowl like this 10-minute &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/263359/buffalo-chicken-grain-bowl/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Buffalo Chicken Grain Bowl&lt;/a&gt;. If you’re hungry between lunch and dinner, have an afternoon snack like our satisfying &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7913705/chickpea-snack-salad/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Chickpea Snack Salad&lt;/a&gt;. Dinner could be our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7946192/creamy-spinach-artichoke-salmon/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;Creamy Spinach-Artichoke Salmon&lt;/a&gt;, a side of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7965900/air-fryer-baby-potatoes/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;Air-Fryer Baby Potatoes&lt;/a&gt; and a fresh salad.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-why-getting-back-to-your-routine-is-key"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Why Getting Back to Your Routine Is Key &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; No diets, cleanses or &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7898359/why-i-dont-believe-in-calorie-counting-according-to-a-dietitian/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;restricting calories&lt;/a&gt; here! Restriction leads to bingeing, and bingeing leads to restricting. Give yourself some grace, eat a balanced meal and put a stop to the binge-restrict cycle before it starts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “I often tie this back into the broader picture of developing a healthy relationship with food,” says &lt;a href="https://www.lextalknutrition.com/philosophy" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Alexis Silver, M.P.H., RDN&lt;/a&gt;. “At some points in your life, you’re going to eat more sugar, sodium or fat. But your overall habits and lifestyle choices are what really determine your health. We’re all human!”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-tips--strategies"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Tips &amp;amp; Strategies &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In addition to nourishing your body and eating regular meals and snacks, there are other things you can do to alleviate any unpleasant physical or emotional symptoms. These strategies can help you get back on track and move on.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Go for a walk.&lt;/strong&gt; “It will help lower your blood sugar and clear your head,” says &lt;a href="https://www.soundbitesnutrition.com/about-lisa" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Lisa Andrews, M.Ed., RD, LD&lt;/a&gt;. “One night of overindulgence won't destroy your health, but moving your body may improve your mood if you feel crappy after too much sugar.” &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stay hydrated. &lt;/strong&gt;While there’s nothing magical about drinking water, and it doesn’t negate sugar, it is important for digestion and overall health. You might be feeling &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7921422/why-bloating-can-be-normal-healthy-according-to-a-dietitian/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;bloated&lt;/a&gt; or sluggish. “Oftentimes this sluggish feeling is due to dehydration and less an effect of the sugar consumption,” says &lt;a href="https://www.arugalyssa.com/about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="nofollow"&gt;Alyssa Smolen, M.S., RDN, CDN&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be kind to yourself and get curious. &lt;/strong&gt;It's important to remember that no foods are good or bad, and that you don't need to feel shame about what or how much you eat. Eating isn't a moral or shameful act. This will help you learn from your experience. What was going on that caused you to eat that much sugar? Were you having a rough day? Were you bored? Was the ice cream just tasting too good? Answering these questions creates self-awareness and prepares you to make a different choice the next time you’re in a similar situation. It may be helpful to talk to a healthcare provider if you consistently have binge-eating episodes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Eating too much sugar happens to all of us. But there’s no need to panic or punish yourself the next day. Skip the restrictive diets and cleanses. Instead, focus on getting back to your regular routine with balanced meals, staying hydrated and moving your body. Acknowledge the moment with kindness, reflect on what happened and let it go. Your health is determined by your overall habits, not one sugary night.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNYk02ZkRVNzJnRURRZHJiZjZXY1dPS1JOSDlRLXhZUW5GeGtSaWNER0FHZXhhWU51QUk3QWhxQXNPTTdrZUVuWVR2M2ZFOUZCRE1KMkhUazNsSGEwV3JUNDRINXp5d0M1RlFjWVplcmI4VjExcHVvX1ptWTRtTnh2YzVuYWlRdFZCUVU0</guid></item><item><title>科学家确定了可能改变游戏规则的阿尔茨海默病治疗方法，可以像高胆固醇一样控制它-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/northwestern-university-possible-alzheimers</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;Scientists at Northwestern University used a novel compound to arrest early stages of Alzheimer’s disease in mice — setting the stage, if all goes well, for a groundbreaking treatment in which the debilitating condition can be controlled like high cholesterol. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The researchers discovered an unknown subtype of a protein in the brain which can lead to Alzheimer’s disease, according to a &lt;a href="https://alz-journals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/alz.70968" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;new paper&lt;/a&gt; the team published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Alzheimer’s &amp;amp; Dementia: The Journal of the Alzheimer’s Association&lt;/em&gt;, and they demonstrated that their new novel compound, dubbed NU-9, can attack this brain protein and stop the disease from taking hold — in mice, at least.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Most people are used to monitoring their cholesterol levels,” said Richard Silverman, a chemistry professor at Northwestern who coauthored the paper and invented NU-9, in a &lt;a href="https://news.northwestern.edu/stories/2025/12/nu-9-halts-alzheimers-disease-in-animal-model-before-symptoms-begin" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;university statement&lt;/a&gt;. “If you have high cholesterol, it doesn’t mean that you will have a heart attack soon. But it’s time to take drugs to lower your cholesterol levels to prevent that heart attack from happening down the road. NU-9 could play a similar role. If someone has a biomarker signaling Alzheimer’s disease, then they could start taking NU-9 before symptoms appear.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;For this particular experiment, the team took lab mice that were predisposed to develop Alzheimer’s disease but hadn’t developed the condition yet, and started giving them an oral dose of NU-9 for 60 days. They were especially curious about how NU-9 would impact the protein amyloid beta oligomers, which accumulate in the brain hand in hand with signs of Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;After closely examining the mice brains, scientists observed that NU-9 essentially decreased the presence of a previously unknown subtype of amyloid beta oligomers that they dubbed ACU193+ AβOs. This specific type of protein was associated with brain inflammation that shows up before people are diagnosed with Alzheimer’s. When the team introduced NU-9 into these mice brains, they found that NU-9 tamped down the presence of this toxic protein and hence decreased inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“These results are stunning,” William Klein, a Northwestern neuroscience professor and the paper’s principal investigator, summed up in the university statement.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“There are a couple early diagnostic blood tests for Alzheimer’s disease in development,” he said. “The promise of better early diagnostics — combined with a drug that could stop the disease in its tracks — is the goal.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The next step now is to experiment and analyze the effectiveness of NU-9 in the later stages of Alzheimer’s disease, according to the scientists.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Silverman originally invented NU-9, a synthetic compound with the technical name of cyclohexane-1,3-dione, in an effort to identify chemicals that can tackle neurological diseases. Besides Alzheimer’s disease, the NU-9 has proved &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/02/210223110414.htm" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;effective against Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS)&lt;/a&gt; and possibly &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/frontotemporal-dementia/symptoms-causes/syc-20354737" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;frontotemporal degeneration&lt;/a&gt;, all &lt;a href="https://lesturnerals.org/national-institute-on-aging-invests-an-additional-7-3-million-into-nu-9/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;three of which involve&lt;/a&gt; the appearance of toxic protein in brains.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on Alzheimer’s disease:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://futurism.com/health-medicine/scientists-intrigued-alzheimers-drug-mice"&gt;Scientists Intrigued by Old Drug That Reverses Signs of Alzheimer’s in Mice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNQmNIQ2t4YmNDMjhjZ0d5dFhtLWF0Ny1CRVF0ZWpleW1lQ3dZeXNDM05Zc0lOSHhTT0x4MzZvVndBb1gtRUptdVhFWDFTaU9jd0c5UVdfblV2NC1IVlh3RTRxTU8tWnNGdnBDazE1Wng3NVB4aUsxRGo0UGNWN2lKWnFxRDZfUGc</guid></item><item><title>手术中扁平化后，我被从身体弹射到天堂。当我回来时，没有癌症的痕迹-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15378465/near-death-experience-heaven-cancer-cured.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rosemary Thornton had been praying for a miracle after the tragic death of her husband.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But, instead, she was dealt with the devastating health blow of her own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2018, two years after her husband died by suicide, the Midwestern author noticed unusual vaginal bleeding, which prompted her to rush to a gynecologist. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A biopsy in the following days revealed Thornton, 59 at the time, had stage two &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15321767/Vaccine-prevent-STDs-effective-preventing-cervical-cancer-new-breakthrough-research-shows.html"&gt;cervical cancer&lt;/a&gt;, which affects about 13,000 American women every year and kills 4,000. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Soon after diagnosis, Thornton underwent emergency surgery to assess the cancer and remove the tumor from her cervix. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While this operation is generally considered safe, Thornton began to bleed out on the operating table and her blood pressure plummeted. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As the monitors measuring her vital signs displayed an 'error' message, Thornton claims, she raised her arms toward the ceiling, with her fingers reaching up as though she was about to hold somebody’s hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When she flatlined seconds later, she was considered clinically dead and said she was 'catapulted out of her body.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Rosemary Thornton, pictured here, suffered a near-death experience while undergoing surgery to remove cervical cancer &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Thornton, now 66, said: 'It was the most extraordinary moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It wasn’t gentle. I was catapulted out of my body like a ping. The first thing I declared was that my heart had stopped beating. I then told the universe I was no longer dying, I had died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I didn’t feel any terror, though, only release. All the anxiety, regret and sadness was gone. What was left was me – every part of my personality, even my giggle - went with me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I realized we carry everything that really matters when we leave this world.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Thornton claimed she was floating through a 'velvety blackness' that was filled with peace. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rather than the afterlife being an empty void, it was calm. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'For someone who’s always struggled with anxiety, this place was surely Heaven itself,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Thornton is one of the one in 10 Americans who have had a near-death experience (NDE), a transformative event that occurs during a severe medical crisis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some feel themselves being propelled down into a black hole, blinded by a bright light or &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/sciencetech/article-15223139/near-death-experience-visions-revealed.html"&gt;wandering a Matrix-like grid&lt;/a&gt;. Many are met by an angel and taken to heaven for a visit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But not all NDEs are pleasant. A &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15191705/Scientists-reveal-really-happens-near-death-experience.html"&gt;recent study&lt;/a&gt; out of the University of Virginia found  that ‘a small percentage of NDEs experienced [are] distressing.' The team also suggested between 10 and 22 percent of these experiences are negative. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Thornton is pictured here two days after her near-death experience. She claims the experience was so peaceful that she begged angels not to end her back&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Thornton claims that as she floated through the darkness, she felt a 'presence' behind her that said: 'You are the image and the likeness. I am the Original.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She then entered a white room filled with 'radiant light and a swirling mist' that she compared to a 'spiritual car wash.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I was told I had been restored to wholeness and that it was time for me to push through,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She was then shown a vision of a nurse who had been caring for her sitting in a supply room sobbing uncontrollably, convinced she had failed her patient. Thornton absorbed the grief as if it were her own and claims she made the decision then to return to her body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said: 'I lowered my hand from death’s door and next thing I knew, I was in the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I felt disappointed. I even argued with the angels not to send me back.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Tests concluded Thornton had suffered a heart attack, which caused her to cross over to the other side. But she was more surprised that four days later, she had no evidence of cancer and that her blood work was 'textbook perfect.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The surgeon said my tissue was so pink and perfect she would have never believed I’d had cancer,' Thornton said. 'The cancer was gone, but more than that, my soul was made whole again.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Thornton (pictured here) said the experience strengthened her faith in God and taught her how to enjoy the small aspects of life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's unclear if the surgery she had was considered successful from a medical standpoint.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Thornton now claims she is visited by angels dressed in light who surround her and sing during moments of sadness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The experience also helped her strengthen her faith in God and has shown her how to appreciate the small aspects of her life, prompting her to move to the countryside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said: 'In the afterlife, I discovered God not only loves us, but really likes us, just as we are. It’s changed everything for me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'To anyone facing the end, I can promise you don’t need to be afraid. What’s waiting is peace, joy and more life than we can imagine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Death really is like waking up from a very intense dream. And this whole time on Earth is reduced to this tiny little grain of salt. It’s not a big deal.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:33:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxNbllQakNzS0swRDNnOE42cFVhdkNaYXV5ZFlpS25jQ1RuRUo1azNMVzd4eHdRWnF0Z3lkTzBoZFVOa0w5V2xzR3BhckdiY3ZGd1dZVVN0TGJLV3lJWVBEQ1YwTTRRSnJJTHVfaXA2Ry1uUzRMcHlqVmJENzlqcEVPRDN1WTBzRHFmYXNTOEtLUGdYb0FxbUpKUEFSS1VwOFnSAaQBQVVfeXFMTUpKeTJGRGVEM0FnV2dzNnJkYlRXaHpSNDdidVpqMnRESktyemlSX1c4UFZ6QkdDc1ZiN3lHUEx1LTk3eEdraVZPTHJMbUNkUTNtek1zaFI1NmJvVUp1aVJGMWdwazVMZWhpQjFPWDBBb1NHR3BSeFhianZSeTVXYlNMMzRHQkNYQTljemZWZkxKSGQwRzVfUnY5TXRyX3BNVE53Tjk</guid></item><item><title>新的研究揭示了咖啡和巧克力中发现的一种有益化合物--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/12/26/dark-chocolate-health-benefits/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4XQRGIXIIRHPRPKB3UKDBPUBH4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;If you enjoy dark chocolate or coffee, or both, you may be benefiting from a substance found in these products that is linked to a reduction in cellular aging&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3N7DIRITIRCTHF44BU2L4KNNJQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.aging-us.com/article/206344" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published this month in the journal Aging found that people with higher blood levels of an alkaloid called theobromine seemed to have slower cellular aging as measured by “epigenetic clocks,” models that estimate aging based on molecular biomarkers. Most abundant in cocoa, theobromine is also found in smaller amounts in coffee and tea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:31:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOektQdkU4eVoxTDZzTUZZNGNtWVhCWUxnQ0g5LTV4aDJFby1yWGtZSkpKckxKRXlQYjhTZ0VjNXZoVEVVc3JMc3RvQUQ4eWdxUXlCMk5DeHBNNUhycW9CNFVUOGwwZ1hSSXo5Y1MtUFpsUlMzOWNjUUdWN2tyU3g0VnhGS0d5Rnpaenc</guid></item><item><title>达菲并不是美国唯一推荐的流感治疗方法。这些是其他人。-CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/26/health/flu-treatment-tamiflu-xofluza-relenza-rapivab</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmhi9y00f526ozdpz4gv6s@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When the flu strikes, it can feel relentless: rising fever, hacking cough, stuffy nose and sore throat. For many people, relief can come in the form of Tamiflu, a prescription antiviral medication used to treat and even prevent the illness.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt700063b6pzfkdgx2t@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But some people may not realize that Tamiflu isn’t the only option.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt800073b6pms06fbrs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Other flu treatments are available in the United States. These alternatives sometimes fly under the radar, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/treatment/antiviral-drugs.html" target="_blank"&gt;in part because some are targeted for specific populations&lt;/a&gt;. But Xofluza, a one-dose pill, is approved for people 5 years and older – and can be a strong alternative for some people who may otherwise be prescribed Tamiflu.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000a3b6p9w6ekwly@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Antiviral medications tend to work best when started within two days after symptoms begin, so having easy access to treatment options is key for treating the flu most effectively.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000c3b6pykhjmbku@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            To treat flu this season, there are &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/treatment/antiviral-drugs.html" target="_blank"&gt;four antiviral drugs recommended&lt;/a&gt; by the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention: Tamiflu or oseltamivir, Xofluza or baloxavir, Relenza or zanamivir, and Rapivab or peramivir.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000d3b6pxarl68sy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Tamiflu is used to treat flu in people ages 2 weeks and older, and to &lt;a href="https://www.tamiflu.com/" target="_blank"&gt;reduce the chance of getting the flu&lt;/a&gt; in people 1 year and older. The medicine is administered in liquid form or capsules, and typically must be taken twice daily for five days when used for flu treatment. When used for prevention after exposure, it is typically taken once daily for 10 days. Available as a generic or under the trade name Tamiflu, it &lt;a href="https://www.goodrx.com/tamiflu?c" target="_blank"&gt;may cost about $50 or less&lt;/a&gt; without insurance. The most common side effects include nausea and vomiting.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000e3b6pzjm5v4l6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As another option, Xofluza is administered as a single-dose tablet and approved for ages 5 and older. It can be used to &lt;a href="https://www.xofluza.com/about-xofluza.html?c" target="_blank"&gt;treat or prevent&lt;/a&gt; the flu, and it &lt;a href="https://www.goodrx.com/xofluza?srsltid=AfmBOorpfTCHg0ZxUo26czQwzVfqtltq-qeYhS72mql5MTa4BrGHdob4" target="_blank"&gt;may cost nearly $200&lt;/a&gt; without insurance, but eligible patients can use &lt;a href="https://www.xofluza.com/save-on-xofluza/coupon.html" target="_blank"&gt;coupons&lt;/a&gt; to lessen costs. The most common side effects include diarrhea and vomiting.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000f3b6pfjqp9n2c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The most common complaint I hear about is vomiting from Tamiflu,” Dr. Ari Brown, a pediatrician based in Texas and author of the &lt;a href="https://www.draribrown.com/books/" target="_blank"&gt;Baby 411&lt;/a&gt; book series, said in an email. She referenced a &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fpmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov%2Farticles%2FPMC10569673%2F&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7Cjacqueline.howard%40cnn.com%7C49eceb51e5a94e5640df08de42fe93ba%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C639021858353662466%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=Nwf8pYiivUtl9SoH6lp8euGgW0v%2B8JQlw%2BIBC0XsbfI%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;2023 study&lt;/a&gt; that showed about 18% of people experience vomiting with Tamiflu versus 5% with Xofluza.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjlpj8iz00073b6pwv8icuej@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The study also found that about 5% of people get diarrhea with Xofluza compared with none taking Tamiflu. “I’ve also had a few pediatric patients experience moodiness with Tamiflu, which is reported in the literature,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000i3b6p52br2qf3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The “biggest difference” between Tamiflu and Xofluza is that Xofluza can stop viral shedding in one day while Tamiflu may take about three days, Brown said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000j3b6p5gghm7l4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            That means the rest of the household may have less exposure to the flu and fewer people may come down with it, but “both antivirals will help reduce the duration of the misery by a couple of days,” Brown said. For instance, with treatment, some people may experience five days of flu symptoms instead of seven.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000k3b6p9oq2wzg2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Rapivab is one of the other prescription medications approved to treat flu. The drug is approved for ages 6 months and older, &lt;a href="https://rapivab.com/" target="_blank"&gt;given once as an intravenous infusion&lt;/a&gt; by a health care provider. It &lt;a href="https://www.singlecare.com/prescription/rapivab" target="_blank"&gt;may cost up to about $1,000&lt;/a&gt; without insurance, and the most common adverse reaction in adults tends to be diarrhea.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000l3b6pox0s4b96@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Lastly, Relenza is the other recommended flu medication. It is &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/drugs/postmarket-drug-safety-information-patients-and-providers/relenza-zanamivir-information" target="_blank"&gt;inhaled in powder form&lt;/a&gt;, and typically administered using an inhaler device twice a day for five days. The prescription drug is approved to treat flu in ages 7 and older, and for preventive use in ages 5 and older. It &lt;a href="https://www.goodrx.com/relenza?c" target="_blank"&gt;may cost up to about $90&lt;/a&gt; without insurance. &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/druginfo/meds/a699021.html#side-effects" target="_blank"&gt;Side effects&lt;/a&gt; include allergic reaction, dizziness or irritation of the nose, and it is not recommended for people with breathing problems, such as asthma.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000n3b6pphv57pbn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Among the recommended flu treatments, Tamiflu tends to be the go-to flu medication for most patients. But Xofluza is becoming more widely used, Brown said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjlp0r6b00023b6p2nebd1uo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            However, it may not always be available in pharmacies, recommended by providers or covered by insurance.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjlp15kw00053b6pqjlsbgfx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I suspect it is region-dependent,” Brown said about access to treatment.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjlp2wip000b3b6ph4rqkaxy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “When one part of the country has surging flu cases, there is higher demand. We have not encountered this issue in Austin,” she said. For instance, this flu season, she has only had one Xofluza prescription that she needed to send to a different pharmacy because the first pharmacy was out of stock.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000o3b6pveuc4qm3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But overall, “Xofluza is rising in popularity over Tamiflu,” Brown said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjlpp3y700093b6pi69u022v@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “One dose. Fewer side effects. More insurances are covering the cost of it now and manufacturer coupon makes it less expensive than in previous years,” she said, adding that she prefers it for her patients. “But all of the factors above–cost, ability to swallow a pill, availability can impact that decision.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000q3b6pohxzb491@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Another factor that may impact decisions: There is a growing concern about the influenza virus developing resistance to Xofluza.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000r3b6pkphitr6b@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This is more in the minds of the practitioner – and I think it has been one of the reasons it hasn’t been used more frequently – the influenza virus can develop resistance to baloxavir, to Xofluza, during the course of treatment,” said Dr. William Schaffner, an infectious disease expert at Vanderbilt University Medical Center.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000s3b6pxk0oevts@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “That happens sometimes around 10% of the time, so it’s not trivial. And that’s why I think the longer-term Tamiflu continues to be favored – that and the side effect of diarrhea,” he said. “So, Tamiflu tends to be recommended more frequently, despite the fact that you do have to take it for five days.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000t3b6pbo5taj5e@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Xofluza resistance has appeared to occur even more frequently in younger children, Dr. Tim Uyeki, chief medical officer of the influenza division at the CDC’s National Center for Immunization and Respiratory Diseases, said during a call earlier this month of the CDC’s &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/coca/hcp/trainings/seasonal_influenza_2025-2026.html" target="_blank"&gt;Clinician Outreach and Communication Activity&lt;/a&gt; (COCA).
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000u3b6ph8a4jrje@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This emergence of baloxavir resistance is associated with a longer duration of symptoms,” Uyeki &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wN-6nVGBBc0" target="_blank"&gt;said during the call&lt;/a&gt;. “Fortunately, transmission of a baloxavir-resistant virus from person to person has been very, very limited. It’s been reported, but it appears to be very uncommon and there’s no circulation of baloxavir-resistant viruses or oseltamivir-resistant viruses in the general population.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000w3b6pj1aunv3c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            National influenza experts discussed on the COCA call that Tamiflu or oseltamivir is preferred for treating hospitalized patients and people with progressive illness.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000x3b6pqp8sfr94@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Xofluza is not recommended during pregnancy, while breastfeeding, for outpatients with complicated or progressive illness, severely immunosuppressed people or hospitalized patients, because of the lack of information on its use for these groups.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000y3b6pvmtinmow@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But there are situations for which Xofluza may be preferred.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000z3b6pacacjyik@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “For a patient with known or suspected influenza B, baloxavir has much greater efficacy against influenza B compared to oseltamivir,” Uyeki said during the call, adding that the medication is “generally well tolerated.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt800103b6p1gm4vlbs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “A single dose of baloxavir is not associated with many side effects and fewer side effects compared to oseltamivir,” he said. “For patients, I think every patient would prefer a single oral dose of baloxavir versus five days, twice-daily of oseltamivir treatment.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt800113b6p1kmgcbh6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            At the end of the call, Uyeki added that researchers should continue studying the potential benefits of treating flu patients with a combination of antiviral medications, especially those with severe disease.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt800123b6pcl5c15qe@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I think we need more data for treatment of influenza in hospitalized influenza patients, so severe influenza,” he said. “And for that we need more data for a combination antiviral treatment, for example oseltamivir-plus-baloxavir.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:10:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQWWdHdDFCOUF1MnBDVlV4aGEwaXlpdEdVOXVUSU51MnJQcDluR3hPWXhoQzc2ZUhTQmh2WElBdXRwa3FFY0gtZV90OXlwU3FHWWxNeVpRV0h3eWthTS10RjNKV1NYbVRvam83SWZpVndIaE54LUx0VkQtRlpNZnlPaU5OdXQ4V0MxN2lB</guid></item><item><title>这种常见血压药物可延长动物寿命并减缓衰老- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/this-common-blood-pressure-drug-boosts-lifespan-and-slows-aging-in-animals</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The hypertension drug &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rilmenidine"&gt;rilmenidine&lt;/a&gt; has been found to slow aging in worms – an effect that, if it translates to humans, could one day help us live longer and stay healthier in old age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rilmenidine appears to mimic the effects of caloric restriction on a cellular level, and reducing available energy while maintaining nutrition has been shown to extend lifespans &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-018-24146-z"&gt;in several animal models&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether this translates to human biology, or is a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/skipping-meals-could-be-much-worse-for-you-than-we-realized"&gt;potential risk to our health&lt;/a&gt;, is a topic of &lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/flash/2020/can-calorie-restriction-extend-your-lifespan/"&gt;ongoing debate&lt;/a&gt;. Finding ways to achieve the same benefits without the costs of extreme calorie cutting could lead to new ways to improve health in old age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/dick-van-dyke-credits-his-longevity-to-one-habit-and-its-backed-by-science"&gt;Dick Van Dyke Credits His Longevity to One Habit, And It's Backed by Science&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a study published in 2023, young and old &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Caenorhabditis_elegans"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Caenorhabditis elegans&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; worms treated with the drug – which is normally used to treat &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/us-has-new-guidelines-for-high-blood-pressure-heres-what-that-means"&gt;high blood pressure&lt;/a&gt; – lived longer and presented higher measures in a variety of health markers in the same way as restricting calories, as the scientists had hoped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below for a summary of the research:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"For the first time, we have been able to show in animals that rilmenidine can increase lifespan," &lt;a href="https://news.liverpool.ac.uk/2023/01/23/hypertension-drug-could-be-repurposed-to-delay-ageing-study-finds/"&gt;said molecular biogerontologist João Pedro Magalhães&lt;/a&gt;, from the University of Birmingham in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are now keen to explore if rilmenidine may have other clinical applications."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;C. elegans&lt;/em&gt; worm is a favorite for studies, because many of its genes have similarities to counterparts in our genome. Yet in spite of these similarities, it is still a rather distant relation to humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further tests showed that gene activity associated with caloric restriction could be seen in the kidney and liver tissues of mice treated with rilmenidine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, some of the changes that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/mice-that-eat-less-live-longer-and-we-may-finally-know-why"&gt;caloric restriction gives in animals&lt;/a&gt; and thought to confer certain health benefits also appear with a hypertension drug that many people already take.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_144581" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-144581" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/08/SizeAndMorphologyCElegansCellsComparedToHumanCells642.jpg" alt="Various cell types illustrated in shades of pink" class="size-full wp-image-144581" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/08/SizeAndMorphologyCElegansCellsComparedToHumanCells642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/08/SizeAndMorphologyCElegansCellsComparedToHumanCells642-600x334.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-144581" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Some human cell types and their nuclei on the left, compared to cells from &lt;em&gt;C. elegans &lt;/em&gt;on the right. (&lt;a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:C_elegans_cell_and_nucleus_sizes.svg"&gt;J.J.Froehlich/CC BY-SA 4.0/Wikimedia Commons&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another discovery was that a biological signaling receptor called nish-1 was crucial in the effectiveness of rilmenidine. This particular chemical structure could be targeted in future attempts to improve lifespan and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/making-one-diet-change-for-8-weeks-could-turn-back-the-clock-on-aging"&gt;slow down aging&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We found that the lifespan-extending effects of rilmenidine were abolished when nish-1 was deleted," the researchers explain in their &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/acel.13774"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Critically, rescuing the nish-1 receptor reinstated the increase in lifespan upon treatment with rilmenidine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Low-calorie diets are hard to follow and come with a variety of side effects, such as hair thinning, dizziness, and brittle bones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's early days still, but the thinking is that this hypertension drug could confer the same benefits as a low-calorie diet while being easier on the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-blood-pressure-guidelines-mean-you-may-now-have-hypertension"&gt;New Blood Pressure Guidelines Mean You May Now Have Hypertension&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This research presents a novel case for rilmenidine to be considered a potential calorie restriction mimetic through its prolongevity and health preserving effects," the authors &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/acel.13774"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What makes rilmenidine a promising candidate as an anti-aging drug is that it can be taken orally, it's already widely prescribed, and its side effects are rare and relatively mild (they include palpitations, insomnia, and drowsiness in a few cases).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_141684" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-141684" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/ManTakingBloodPressurereadingAtHome_R_U_642.jpg" alt="A man sitting on a couch taking his blood pressure" class="size-full wp-image-141684" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/ManTakingBloodPressurereadingAtHome_R_U_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/ManTakingBloodPressurereadingAtHome_R_U_642-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/ManTakingBloodPressurereadingAtHome_R_U_642-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-141684" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Rilmenidine is normally used to treat high blood pressure. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEwj7ICt3Y/"&gt;Prostock-studio/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-common-diabetes-drug-is-linked-to-exceptional-longevity-in-women"&gt;Recently, observational research&lt;/a&gt; hinted that the drug &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metformin"&gt;metformin&lt;/a&gt;, which is already used to manage type 2 &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="181787" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, may also give older women a better chance of living to the grand old age of 90.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists in the US and Germany analyzed data from a long-term US study of postmenopausal women. Records on 438 people were picked out – half of whom took metformin to treat  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="175539" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, and half who took a different &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-confirms-experimental-drug-breaks-record-for-weight-loss-in-clinical-trials"&gt;diabetes drug&lt;/a&gt;, called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sulfonylurea"&gt;sulfonylurea&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those in the metformin group were calculated to have a 30 percent lower risk of dying before the age of 90 than those in the sulfonylurea group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study can't demonstrate cause and effect like a randomized controlled trial (RCT), because the participants weren't randomly assigned to one treatment or the other – rather, they were following professional medical advice. What's more, there wasn't a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-a-placebo"&gt;placebo group&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key strength was the average follow-up period of 14 to 15 years, extending far beyond the length a standard RCT would be able to. That's important to understand how any intervention impacts lifespan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-critical-factor-predicts-longevity-better-than-diet-or-exercise-study-says"&gt;One Critical Factor Predicts Longevity Better Than Diet or Exercise, Study Says&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We'll need a lot more research to figure out if rilmenidine might also work as an anti-aging drug for humans, but the early signs in worms and mice are promising. Scientists now know more about what rilmenidine can do, and how it operates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"With a global aging population, the benefits of delaying aging, even if slightly, are immense," &lt;a href="https://news.liverpool.ac.uk/2023/01/23/hypertension-drug-could-be-repurposed-to-delay-ageing-study-finds/"&gt;said Magalhães&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Repurposing drugs capable of extending lifespan and healthspan has a huge untapped potential in translational geroscience."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/acel.13774"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Aging Cell&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in January 2023.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:02:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxOa2VMcDAycjM5dGJWbVF2Yzhfakt6VTRMcEVVeVA3S19IMk0yUWR5Y2hLc1pyUFctUjg5QXljamFNZUd6b19BSUdOdEJRN1dzaC1JZkRuQVdhZ21ycG44Q2lFZzNMUEVQa3BzNjFjaDdYMzFjdUQ2TTdJZ0Q4NmRySEJrNmc2M2EyVkxNMzV0S0hwSnZKcVRXRUQ5OGQ5UUc4VEJkckl3</guid></item><item><title>专家表示，猪器官移植有朝一日可能会优于人类器官移植</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/dec/26/pig-organ-transplants-could-one-day-be-superior-to-human-ones-says-expert</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A leading surgeon behind a clinical trial of transplanting pig kidneys into living humans has said they could one day be superior to those from human donors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Robert Montgomery, the director of NYU Langone’s Transplant Institute, said the first transplant &lt;a href="https://clinicaltrials.gov/study/NCT06878560?term=ukidney&amp;amp;rank=2" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;of the trial&lt;/a&gt; had already been carried out, with another expected to take place in January. Six patients are initially expected to receive the pig organs, which have been gene-edited in 10 places to reduce rejection by the human body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Should the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) give approval, the trial will be expanded to involve 44 further transplants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The approach, called xenotransplantation, is aimed at solving the shortage of human organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;According to the NHS Blood and Transplant, in the UK alone more than 12,000 people have died or been removed from the transplant waiting list over the past 10 years before receiving a new organ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Participants in the new trial are either ineligible for human kidney transplantation or on a waiting list for such an organ but thought to be more likely to die, or remain un-transplanted, within five years than receive it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“The truth is that there’s just never going to be enough human organs,” Montgomery told the Guardian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;He speaks from experience. He is not only a pioneering transplant surgeon and one of &lt;a href="https://time.com/collections/100-most-influential-people-2025/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Time Magazine’s most influential people of 2025&lt;/a&gt;, but he has inherited a heart condition called dilated cardiomyopathy, which killed his father and brother. After Montgomery experienced seven cardiac arrests – one of which resulted in a month-long coma – he &lt;a href="https://www.stlawu.edu/news/surgeon-survivor-humanitarian-laurentian" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;received a heart transplant himself&lt;/a&gt; in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“I think everybody really knows that we have a terrible problem in terms of rationing organs because there’s such a scarcity of supply. But unless you’ve walked in the shoes of somebody who’s waiting for a transplant, you don’t really fully understand how unlikely it is that you’re going to receive a transplant in time,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Montgomery has pioneered new approaches to increasing supply of human organs, including &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(06)69115-0/abstract" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;domino-paired kidney transplants&lt;/a&gt;. In this situation, a living donor whose kidney is incompatible with their expected recipient is matched with another patient, whose own incompatible donor is then matched to another patient and so on, creating a chain of donors and recipients that increases the availability of compatible organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Montgomery has also been a leader in the use of organs from donors with hepatitis C, treating recipients with medication to clear the resulting infection, and even accepted a hepatitis C–positive heart for his own heart transplant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But he said other approaches were needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Having spent a career trying to increase incrementally the number of human organs available, I realised that we just weren’t making that much progress, not in a meaningful way,” he said. “And any progress we made was kind of deleted by the ever-expanding number of people who are waiting for transplants. ”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While the idea of xenotransplantation has been around for decades, Montgomery said recent developments had proved pivotal – including the ability to create gene-edited pigs. “There were all these kind of jokes about xenotransplantation, like it’s just around the corner and it’s an awfully long corner,” he said. “But suddenly we’re in it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Montgomery carried out the world’s first gene-edited pig-to-human organ transplant in 2021. While the recipient of the kidney was a brain dead individual, Montgomery said it was an important step, showing the organs were not immediately rejected and providing crucial safety data that had opened the door for use in living people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Montgomery said it was even possible that pig organs could eventually become superior to human ones for transplants, with the possibility for further gene edits to make rejection less likely. “They could be superior at some point because we can constantly modify them to make them better, where you can’t do that with a human organ,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Studies by researchers &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/news/immune-reactions-found-behind-human-rejection-transplanted-pig-kidneys" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;including Montgomery&lt;/a&gt; have shown that transplanting the pig’s thymus – an organ involved in the development and selection of immune cells – along with the kidney can also improve tolerance, raising the possibility of eventually reducing or even eliminating the need for anti-rejection drugs. “We’re not there yet, but that’s why we’re doing those studies,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While the new clinical trial is a first to be carried out with xenotransplantation, pig organs have previously been transplanted into a handful of humans, most of whom were already severely ill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some of these patients subsequently had to have the organs removed and &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2023/nov/01/pig-heart-transplant-faucette-dies" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;others have died&lt;/a&gt;, albeit not necessarily from complications relating to the transplant. However, Montgomery said there were two living recipients of pig kidneys who still had the organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;He said kidneys and hearts were promising organs for xenotransplantation, while lungs were more complicated. “[And] the liver, it’s still a mystery of whether it’s going to work,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;He said he would not be adverse to receiving a pig heart himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Next time around, if I continue to be healthy and alive, I certainly would consider it,” he said. “I’ve got kids who have the same genetic disease that I have and I certainly think about them all the time, and want them to have more options than my dad had, or my brother or I had.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxOeVJka0ZBczlVNHpFNVpqZS14aG1ocEN0M3FLYWtjekZGQXlfLVpLanY2b3NYenFLd2NrUmp2aHZuWEdjT2wxMTdfV3JqWmthQVlTbExmd1l1WmVEX1NHcGxZeURfSnR3cEFPOGhaLXhnRlVHTE5nVzNPNnpqbFFqdGxkUk8zeHV6dEpKOGdad2szR251MTZadkFfQTNBUXZSSXVxR2pmOWdHc3lnQ0hUQ1Y4RDlQZkVQU3ZsaV9n</guid></item><item><title>美国是否应该仿效丹麦的疫苗政策？专家说，我们没什么相似之处-美国国家公共广播电台</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/12/26/nx-s1-5656214/childhood-vaccination-denmark-rfk-policy</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-103674" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Guards march in the courtyard of Fredensborg Palace in Denmark. The northern European country of around 6 million people has been suggested as a model for U.S. childhood vaccination policy.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Scott Barbour/Getty Images Europe/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Scott Barbour/Getty Images Europe/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a long-time vaccine critic, has made it clear he thinks American children get too many vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Earlier this month, President Trump issued a &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/fact-sheets/2025/12/fact-sheet-president-donald-j-trump-begins-process-to-align-u-s-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/" target="_blank"&gt;memorandum&lt;/a&gt; directing Kennedy and the acting director of the CDC to align the U.S. with best practices on childhood vaccine recommendations from peer nations, and it specifically mentioned Denmark. That could mean fewer shots against fewer diseases.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But critics say you can't simply adopt another country's vaccine schedule in the U.S., which has a very different population and different health risks.&lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;"It's like fitting a square peg in a round hole when our goal is to prevent disease," says &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/person/josh-michaud/" target="_blank"&gt;Josh Michaud&lt;/a&gt;, associate director for global and public health policy at KFF.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Denmark recommends routinely vaccinating all children against just 10 diseases. In the U.S., the immunization schedule calls for routine universal vaccination against 16 diseases. It was 17 diseases until last week, when the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention officially dropped the recommendation to vaccinate all newborns against hepatitis B.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But Denmark has created its immunization schedule in a very different context than that of the U.S., notes &lt;a href="https://medschool.cuanschutz.edu/accords/about/accords-faculty-directory/O-Leary-Sean-UCD11631" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Sean O'Leary&lt;/a&gt;, chair of the Committee on Infectious Diseases for the American Academy of Pediatrics.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's like comparing a cruise ship to a kayak," says O'Leary, a professor of pediatrics and infectious diseases at the University of Colorado School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Different populations, different health systems&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;For starters, Denmark's population is about 6 million people – roughly that of Wisconsin – compared to &lt;a href="https://www.census.gov/popclock/#:~:text=select%20date,Learn%20More%20%7C%20Download%20and%20Share" target="_blank"&gt;more than 343 million people&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. Denmark also lacks the racial and ethnic diversity and wide income disparities that are prevalent in the U.S. Denmark also has a highly unified health system, with a national health registry that basically tracks everyone from birth to death, Michaud says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"And so if there are outbreaks or if there are cases of these diseases, they can easily identify them," Michaud says. "They can treat them, get them into care, and also track down contacts, if that's needed for the particular disease we're talking about."&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;What's more, Danish families get about a year of paid parental leave — between the two parents — so they can stay home with their babies, who potentially aren't exposed to as many diseases. Plus, Denmark has free, universal health care. So for example, if an infant is hospitalized with RSV – a disease which Denmark does not routinely vaccinate against but the U.S. does – then the system will absorb the cost, so it's not a barrier to getting care.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That's very different from the U.S., where many people struggle to access health care, says &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/profiles/jake-scott" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Jake Scott&lt;/a&gt;, an infectious disease specialist at Stanford University School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We have fragmented insurance, we've got millions uninsured, we don't have a national health registry and we've got enormous gaps in the continuity of care," Scott says. "And we use broader vaccine recommendations because our system can't reliably identify and follow up with every person at risk."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The U.S. also has higher rates of childhood obesity and asthma than Denmark, Scott notes, which puts those kids at higher risk of some diseases.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;"What diseases do they want to bring back?"&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;All of these complex differences have led the U.S. to create a different immunization schedule than Denmark's – one that puts a greater emphasis on disease prevention rather than management, says &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/faculty/497/william-john-moss" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. William Moss&lt;/a&gt;, an epidemiology professor at the Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health and director of the school's International Vaccine Access Center.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The reason why countries, particularly in Europe, have different vaccination schedules is not because they consider the vaccines not to be safe or that the vaccines don't work," Moss says. And I think it's very important that people understand that."&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Scaling back America's vaccine schedule to model Denmark's in this very different context puts America's children at real risk, O'Leary says. "It's like, what diseases do they want to bring back to the U.S.? Which diseases do they want kids to be hospitalized for that they're not protected from? I simply don't get it."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Which country is the outlier?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In his presidential memo, Trump called the U.S. "a high outlier in the number of vaccinations recommended for all children" compared to peer countries.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But when you look at the 30 countries that are part of the European Center for Disease Prevention and Control, the U.S. is very much in line with them, says Michaud of KFF.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"In fact, it is Denmark that seems to be the outlier here in terms of recommending very few vaccines," he says. "In the case of Germany, France and Italy, we might be talking about 15 or more vaccines."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Even compared to other Nordic countries with similar health systems, Denmark is "unusually minimalist," says Scott of Stanford. "Sweden, Norway, Finland – they all cover more diseases."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;It's unclear what Kennedy might do next. The Health and Human Services Department notified the press last Thursday that it was going to make "an announcement regarding children's health" with the CDC the next day. But HHS canceled the press conference hours later. &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/18/health/hhs-childhood-vaccine-changes" target="_blank"&gt;Media reports&lt;/a&gt; suggest the administration had planned to announce an overhaul of the childhood vaccination schedule. HHS spokesperson Andrew Nixon declined to discuss the matter.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In an email to media, the HHS said the announcement had been postponed until after the first of the new year.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Experts say it's legally murky whether the health secretary could overhaul vaccine policy by simply announcing it in a press conference, without going through the usual process for deliberating such changes.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Kennedy technically has broad authority in setting vaccine policy, says &lt;a href="https://www.uclawsf.edu/people/dorit-reiss/" target="_blank"&gt;Dorit Reiss&lt;/a&gt;, a law professor at the University of California, San Francisco whose research focuses on legal and policy issues related to vaccines. But simply announcing such a major change via press conference — rather than going through the CDC's Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices — could open up the Trump administration to legal challenges, she says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The process makes them very vulnerable to legal challenges," Reiss says.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxPYXNhNTEySVdkeHJna3QtTXhGNjNrNzN2Mk9BSURfTkltS0FqQlFncElPZXdoWDBBd0c3ZEFXNDRSSmp2ZHd1UThkVkZkRFFWUFB0MGdFdGhVS0hwSjFJMVBrYjkwQ2pqUkhwS2NxMWZvdm9vRlFjeXk1eWdjUlR3Uk5PTUtoaDNxVDNzb2ln</guid></item><item><title>为什么女性在晚年会爱上女性-《每日电讯报》</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/wellbeing/sex/why-women-fall-in-love-with-women-in-later-life/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;p&gt;After putting their daughter to bed one November evening in 2022, David* fetched two glasses and uncorked a bottle of red, anticipating what had become an increasingly rare night at home with his wife. There had been tensions between the 50-year-old and his second wife Eva, 45, for several weeks. Time alone, David hoped, would get them back on track.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, that night three years ago saw &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/wellbeing/sex/bring-back-intimacy-broken-marriage/"&gt;their marriage spectacularly implode&lt;/a&gt;, as civil servant Eva announced she was gay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The couple had been planning to relocate to Bristol, but that summer Eva’s mood seemed different. She’d suddenly decided against the move, which led to rows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Her swift change of heart totally confused me and things were strained at home – I hoped we’d talk and reconcile. But when I went to put my arm around her on the sofa that night she assumed I was instigating sex and angrily jumped up and blurted out ‘I’m gay and I’m in love with someone’.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I sat there in stunned silence as it all poured out. Eva had been having an affair with a married lesbian at work, and when that woman’s wife had discovered some steamy email exchanges… well, the s--- hit the fan, frankly.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bombshell left David blind-sided. “It was an incredibly dark time which left me questioning everything – my own masculinity, my abilities in bed, whether my wife’s aversion to full sex was actually psychosomatic, was she repulsed by me?” he admits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After their child, now 12, was born their sex life changed. Penetrative sex became problematic, often &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/wellbeing/sex/everything-you-need-to-know-about-urinary-track-infections/"&gt;leading to UTIs&lt;/a&gt; for Eva. “It made me sad but we just adapted the way we were intimate, and I’d definitely describe the relationship as happy – healthy even,” says David, an east London lecturer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the revelation, “I took &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/wellbeing/mental-health/what-antidepressants-do-to-your-brain-body/"&gt;antidepressants&lt;/a&gt; for a year and found a support group specifically for ‘straight spouses’ like me. I just needed to speak to someone about it as Eva didn’t want her sexuality made public, so I’d agreed to keep the details of our split secret.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What I learnt in that group was that for the person ‘coming out’, it’s a process of self-discovery over months, perhaps years, whereas for the person left – me – it wasn’t a &lt;em&gt;process&lt;/em&gt;, but an &lt;em&gt;event&lt;/em&gt; that upended my whole life,” says David.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’ve always thought I was emotionally intelligent, but the stigma and feelings of shame I felt were overwhelming.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Anecdotally, it’s likely many of us will know of couples who’ve been in this situation” says Dr Justin Lehmiller, a senior research fellow at the Kinsey Institute and host of the &lt;em&gt;Sex and Psychology&lt;/em&gt; podcast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Personally I know several people, men and women, who didn’t come out until midlife and most of these individuals had previously been in long-term heterosexual relationships,” says Dr Lehmiller. “The phenomenon is real but it’s an under-researched area.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;The role of sexual fluidity&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sexual attraction and behaviour don’t necessarily stay the same for everyone over the course of their lives, says Dr Lehmiller. “While most people’s sexuality remains pretty stable over time, some people experience one or more shifts in their attractions, and women are more likely to experience these than men, which may explain why there seem to be more later-in-life lesbians than gay men,” he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This sexual fluidity is significant and something “most women have to some degree” says Dr Ruth L. Schwartz, author of &lt;em&gt;Conscious Lesbian Dating &amp;amp; Love&lt;/em&gt;. Dr Schwartz founded the Conscious Girlfriend Academy, an online school for lesbian relationship education in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“About 50 per cent of the women in our academy were married or in long-term partnerships with men at some point. We have women who are just coming out in their 50s, 60s and 70s, and it’s often a process fraught with self-doubt and inner turmoil,” says Dr Schwartz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Some who come out later in life realise they were never really sexually attracted to their husbands and always ‘endured’ sex. But, others felt fine about having sex with men – they just feel more drawn to being sexual with women. It’s also common for women to feel sexually bisexual, but emotionally lesbian, i.e. they fall more deeply in love with women even though sex can work well enough for them with either gender.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While your wife “coming out” is understandably a shock for any husband, there’s even more emotional turmoil for the woman herself, which can have endured for decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lisa Madsen, 56, a licenced clinical social worker, only came out at the age of 50. “There wasn’t a single moment when I knew I was gay, but certainly the intimacy between my husband and I ebbed away after about eight years of marriage,” she admits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I spent the first half of my life trying to be the woman everyone else needed me to be – a good daughter, a devoted wife, a mother who held everything together.”&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxQNkZkek16dXV1a0h4SjZIakM1Y0k4X2VlOEFySkx6UXVBVmMwZkZRZDFiUUtVcUp3ZWFJYk5BZkkwTGpIVkIxY3BrYVhncEhkTWlTRVNONDJaMzBjb1B4Ymd1SlZsQVhCczRlN0FGcURLbThobDVWdnR3ZjNycVFEMFNnWnBJQ2FNek5fZkdvbU9XOGdkd3BFS3hIM1pGdElxMGVFUGlXWmU</guid></item><item><title>“许多自闭症”的新科学及其对疾病起源的揭示--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/26/autism-research-diagnosis-subtypes/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="X4GBVQ4E3BBNJIJPIG7Q5NNSQI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;When Marc and Cristina Easton’s son was diagnosed with autism at 20 months, the Baltimore couple left the doctor’s appointment in confusion. Their toddler — who was very social — didn’t resemble the picture of the condition they thought they knew. And the specialists could offer little clarity about why or what lay ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:23:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQdjZjWWVtMUpka3ZhTmZVRUFYVUo5aWJkWWFzS21ZQTVWZkx3RUdfdHpvcmZGVVFhb2M5aDdRc2xpYmFRcE1WV2dic3pRQVpTdzhYLV9BUnZWM2h1Q0xmVXpGR0o5RG9IbVI0blR6MTRuZ1RxeFBMc0d6SUdsNl9NeDZLRXhNdHZCTGE1UQ</guid></item><item><title>当你的妻子服用睾丸激素是什么感觉-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/26/magazine/what-its-like-when-your-wife-goes-on-testosterone.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:02:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxQRS1lSmlaNkJ5QlZRSW9kbkRUeU1pTlVKdElGSnE0N3JlN0g3Uk0tTl8yXzE3QzZxVzdyT2dQMDJXMFNaV2sxeDZRU3pNSWp4NXB6OGpaTUdLM0JRTW5VYTNIbmJQb2c0eHN0NWQyX2pDV3JmT3IwY2ZZd1F6SW1OXzRnSGJvdGxlRV9wcnhvcVNRbk81Q083LUk2YXJFakE</guid></item><item><title>疫苗中的铝盐可能是卫生官员的目标- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/aluminum-salts-vaccines-kennedy-rcna248055</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-43885e" class="body-graf"&gt;With further changes to the U.S.’ recommended vaccine schedule likely in the year ahead under Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr.’s leadership, his agency’s recent scrutiny of one vaccine additive in particular — aluminum salts — may offer a clue about what’s to come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a1d86d" class="body-graf"&gt;Earlier this month, members of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention’s vaccine advisory committee — &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/rfk-jr-cdc-acip-vaccine-panel-eight-new-members-rcna212477" target="_blank"&gt;whom Kennedy selected&lt;/a&gt; after firing the previous group — suggested digging into concerns about aluminum salts, though large studies have found them to be safe. Andrew Nixon, a spokesperson for the Department of Health and Human Services, told NBC News that the committee is “reviewing the body of science related to aluminum and other possible contaminants in childhood vaccine[s].” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1bff07" class="body-graf"&gt;Similarly, a statement that &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccine-safety/about/autism.html" target="_blank"&gt;appeared on the CDC website&lt;/a&gt; last month said that HHS is investigating whether aluminum in vaccines could be linked to autism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d70731" class="body-graf"&gt;Aluminum salts are not a “contaminant” in vaccines: The compound is added as an adjuvant, an ingredient that boosts the body’s immune response to a vaccine, allowing for a smaller dose to be used. Nearly a century of evidence has found it to be safe for this purpose. Aluminum salts are naturally present in soil and water, and the amount children are exposed to from vaccines is minuscule compared with cumulative daily exposures from food. (&lt;a href="https://www.chop.edu/vaccine-education-center/vaccine-safety/vaccine-ingredients/aluminum" target="_blank"&gt;Exposure from infant formula or breastmilk&lt;/a&gt; is higher than exposure from vaccines in the first six months of life, as well.) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7dc770" class="body-graf"&gt;“This is not the thing that you wrap your food in at the barbecue. … The purpose of them is to just help the immune system respond a little more robustly to that vaccine,” said Dr. Michelle Fiscus, chief medical officer at the Association of Immunization Managers, a nonprofit that supports public vaccination programs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-dd8694" class="body-graf"&gt;“Aluminum adjuvants have made vaccines very, very effective and have helped us significantly reduce suffering and sickness and death,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-fa2c4d" class="body-graf"&gt;Skeptical or negative statements about aluminum have cropped up repeatedly during federal health announcements and meetings in recent months. President Donald Trump in September said aluminum was being “taken out of the vaccines” during a news conference in which &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/trump-acetaminophen-fda-pregnancy-autism-cause-rcna232909" target="_blank"&gt;he and Kennedy warned that Tylenol use in pregnancy&lt;/a&gt; may be linked to autism. (The bulk of scientific research has not identified such a link.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0f08bb" class="body-graf"&gt;“Who the hell wants that pumped into a body?” Trump said of aluminum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-32d4e7" class="body-graf"&gt;Then, during the CDC’s vaccine advisory panel meeting, Dr. Tracy Beth Høeg, acting director of the Food and Drug Administration’s Center for Drug Evaluation and Research, argued for adopting the vaccine schedule that Denmark uses, which is sparser than in the U.S., in part because doing so would reduce aluminum exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="styles_inlineImage__FvnTh styles_medium__MEKii" id="anchor-29011f"&gt;&lt;picture class="styles_image__i32F7" data-testid="picture" data-flavor="fit" data-original-height="1667" data-original-width="2500"&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 1000px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-12/251224-cdc-vaccine-meeting-gk-85edb4.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251224-cdc-vaccine-meeting-gk-85edb4.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 320px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-12/251224-cdc-vaccine-meeting-gk-85edb4.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251224-cdc-vaccine-meeting-gk-85edb4.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251224-cdc-vaccine-meeting-gk-85edb4.jpg" alt="Image: Advisory Committee On Immunization Practices Holds Meeting At CDC Headquarters"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption styles_caption__TCewG" data-testid="caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption__container" data-testid="caption__container"&gt;Retsef Levi listens during a meeting of the CDC Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices on Dec. 5 in Atlanta.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="caption__source" data-testid="caption__source"&gt;Elijah Nouvelage / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-887baa" class="body-graf"&gt;“I do not feel like we have the data to show that there is an established safe amount [of aluminum] that children can receive before the age of 2, before the age of 18,” Høeg said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0eead9" class="body-graf"&gt;Some public health experts worry that the investigation into aluminum is part of a broader push to restrict access to or approval of some childhood shots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-16e24b" class="body-graf"&gt;Last week, HHS postponed a planned announcement about children’s health to the new year. The details are not yet known — &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/18/health/hhs-childhood-vaccine-changes" target="_blank"&gt;CNN reported&lt;/a&gt; that the Trump administration was considering decreasing the number of recommended childhood vaccines to align more closely with Denmark’s, citing an unnamed source “familiar with the plans.” Several other outlets subsequently reported the same, though NBC News has not confirmed that plan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3c1574" class="body-graf"&gt;Already, the CDC’s vaccine advisory committee voted to &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/cdc-panel-vote-hepatitis-b-vaccine-babies-rfk-jr-rcna247482" target="_blank"&gt;stop recommending the hepatitis B vaccine&lt;/a&gt; for all newborns, and as a result, the &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/cdc-stops-recommending-hepatitis-b-vaccines-newborns-rcna248035" target="_blank"&gt;CDC now advises women&lt;/a&gt; who test negative for the virus to decide about the shot with their medical providers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-301bce" class="body-graf"&gt;Changing vaccine recommendations based on concerns about aluminum salts would be a flimsy justification, several public health experts said. Even in Denmark, many recommended vaccines contain aluminum salts, including those for human papillomavirus (HPV), pneumococcal disease, tetanus and whooping cough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e1eb1b" class="body-graf"&gt;Of the pediatric vaccines on the CDC’s schedule that are &lt;a href="https://vaccine-schedule.ecdc.europa.eu/Scheduler/ByCountry?SelectedCountryId=58&amp;amp;IncludeChildAgeGroup=true&amp;amp;IncludeChildAgeGroup=false&amp;amp;IncludeAdultAgeGroup=true&amp;amp;IncludeAdultAgeGroup=false" target="_blank"&gt;missing from Denmark’s universal recommendations&lt;/a&gt;, just three — for hepatitis A, hepatitis B and meningococcal vaccines — contain aluminum salts. The others — for respiratory syncytial virus (RSV), rotavirus, flu and chickenpox — do not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="styles_inlineImage__FvnTh styles_medium__MEKii" id="anchor-af3293"&gt;&lt;picture class="styles_image__i32F7" data-testid="picture" data-flavor="fit" data-original-height="1667" data-original-width="2500"&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 1000px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-12/251224-chickpox-vaccine-gk-94f5b2.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251224-chickpox-vaccine-gk-94f5b2.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 320px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-12/251224-chickpox-vaccine-gk-94f5b2.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251224-chickpox-vaccine-gk-94f5b2.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251224-chickpox-vaccine-gk-94f5b2.jpg" alt="A person holds a vial for the Varivax vaccine"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption styles_caption__TCewG" data-testid="caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption__container" data-testid="caption__container"&gt;A person holds a vial of the Varivax vaccine, which protects against chickenpox, in Los Angeles on Oct. 24.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="caption__source" data-testid="caption__source"&gt;Patrick T. Fallon  / AFP via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5e9a20" class="body-graf"&gt;The shot that anti-vaccine activists most frequently and erroneously associate with autism — the combination measles, mumps and rubella vaccine — also does not contain aluminum salts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b0f480" class="body-graf"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/ANNALS-25-00997" target="_blank"&gt;study of more than 1.2 million children in Denmark&lt;/a&gt;, published in July in the journal Annals of Internal Medicine, found no link between aluminum salts from vaccines and neurodevelopmental disorders, including autism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-42985a" class="body-graf"&gt;But Kennedy — who has made unsubstantiated claims that aluminum in vaccines is linked to rising rates of allergies and autism in children — demanded the paper be retracted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-cd7b67" class="body-graf"&gt;“A closer look reveals a study so deeply flawed it functions not as science but as a deceitful propaganda stunt by the pharmaceutical industry,” he &lt;a href="https://www.trialsitenews.com/a/flawed-science-bought-conclusions-the-aluminum-vaccine-study-the-media-wont-question-aaec2793" target="_blank"&gt;wrote in an editorial on the website TrialSite News&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-52e796" class="body-graf"&gt;Kennedy argued that the paper excluded some children who may have been at risk and did not include a control group. However, Annals of Internal Medicine stood by the study and said there was &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/medical-journal-rejects-kennedys-call-for-retraction-vaccine-study-2025-08-11/" target="_blank"&gt;no reason to retract it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-072ba4" class="body-graf"&gt;Kennedy, a longtime critic of vaccines, had been involved in lawsuits against the pharmaceutical company Merck over allegations related to its HPV vaccine (which contains aluminum salts), but since taking office, he has said any fees earned would go to one of his sons. His focus on aluminum dates back to his time as chairman and chief litigation counsel at &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/rfk-jr-childrens-health-defense-tax-revenue-loss-rcna179934" target="_blank"&gt;the anti-vaccine group Children’s Health Defense&lt;/a&gt;. The group has claimed for years that thimerosal — a mercury-based preservative — is linked to autism, and Kennedy said in &lt;a href="https://annlouise.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/RFK-Interview-July-2020.pdf?utm_source=chatgpt.com" target="_blank"&gt;a podcast appearance in 2020&lt;/a&gt; that aluminum had replaced thimerosal in some vaccines, causing them to remain toxic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-6cb8cc" class="body-graf"&gt;In reality, the ingredients serve different purposes and aluminum salts have been used in vaccines for nearly a century. Thimerosal, meanwhile, was largely phased out of childhood vaccines in 2001, and under Kennedy’s leadership, HHS in July &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/thimerosal-mercury-removed-from-us-flu-vaccines-acip.html" target="_blank"&gt;pulled the ingredient from the roughly 5% of flu vaccines&lt;/a&gt; that still had it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-11b6f7" class="body-graf"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/11-12-2025-who-expert-group-s-new-analysis-reaffirms-there-is-no-link-between-vaccines-and-autism" target="_blank"&gt;recent analysis&lt;/a&gt; from the World Health Organization found no link between autism and vaccines containing thimerosal or aluminum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bac3e2" class="body-graf"&gt;“There’s this constant movement of the goal post to try to implicate vaccines in the development of these diseases, and there’s just not science to back those claims,” Fiscus said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e823d7" class="body-graf"&gt;In 2021, Kennedy &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lkKOt4SYYiY" target="_blank"&gt;told food blogger Mikhaila Peterson&lt;/a&gt; that all aluminum-containing vaccines had “negative risk profiles” and that the brains of children with autism were “loaded with aluminum.” He suggested, too, that kids develop food allergies because “we’ve been inducing allergies by pumping them full of aluminum.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9ca85f" class="body-graf"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/21412506/" target="_blank"&gt;large German study&lt;/a&gt; in 2011, however, did not find an increased risk of allergies in vaccinated children and even identified a decrease in hay fever among the group. In 2023, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/36180331/" target="_blank"&gt;a study found&lt;/a&gt; a positive association between vaccine-related aluminum exposure and persistent asthma, but the results couldn’t be replicated and scientists said the research didn’t properly control for confounding variables.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5e1559" class="body-graf"&gt;In response to mounting hesitancy about aluminum salts in vaccines, Dr. Seth Ari Sim-Son Hoffman, a physician-scientist at Stanford Medicine, decided to reanalyze the existing data with some of his colleagues. The team’s findings, &lt;a href="https://publications.aap.org/pediatrics/article/doi/10.1542/peds.2025-074874/205757/The-Role-and-Safety-of-Aluminum-Adjuvants-in?autologincheck=redirected" target="_blank"&gt;published this month&lt;/a&gt; in the journal Pediatrics, found no major safety concerns with aluminum-containing vaccines. Side effects were mostly limited to redness and swelling at the injection site. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b1b912" class="body-graf"&gt;“When you see the same ‘no’ finding or ‘no’ association across multiple countries, multiple study designs and over a million children, that’s really, really clear and reassuring,” Hoffman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c80692" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;The current childhood vaccine schedule in the U.S., he added, “is backed by powerful evidence in terms of safety and effectiveness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQVDdjMVlYQ3NYUnYwUjhsam9raVZtVmNpQzBMZmltRW1FUkhxN3dYWEN2Vm1fNk5Rdno3X0NXUGNHSF9oYlNoNXJrVnFTZzJCRDhzZ0xMb0ZLM2FyNDJlZG9EN3U4dnEtNktJVlFlUmdFVUhrN3pleFNJaEVxM0FKQ2p6d1g4QS00c1c2MFdn0gFWQVVfeXFMTzJUVjFZNHRGY19BQklHSERiRTZMc016bm9wekR6ZEozWmNpRkpDZlMyR0xMRGlRNFJ0ZlhGVkpCRlJQZWZadmc2bjk5ZDN5blNWUl93SHc</guid></item><item><title>吉尔德兰/奥尔巴尼边境附近停电后恢复供电- WRGB</title><link>https://cbs6albany.com/news/local/power-outage-affecting-2000-customers-near-guilderland-albany-border-mckownville</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h2 class="StoryPage_headline__AP3j8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Power restored after outage near Guilderland/Albany border&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="ByLineContainer_storyBylineContainer__0JNT7" id="js-Story-Byline-0"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="ByLine_storyByLineText__cze7l"&gt;by WRGB Staff&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="ByLineContainer_storyDatelineText__yS9e8"&gt;Thu, December 25, 2025 at 10:48 AM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="ByLineContainer_storyDatelineText__yS9e8"&gt;&lt;span class="ByLineContainer_updatedText__0D6FY"&gt;Updated &lt;/span&gt;Thu, December 25, 2025 at 4:25 PM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="UserWayButton_userWayButton__h8S9a ByLineContainer_userWayButton___vCFL"&gt;&lt;img alt="UserWay icon for accessibility widget" src="/resources/defaults/news_3.0/icons/accessibility/userway-transparent.svg"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WRGB</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:08:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxNOGg0RHMwZHJuVWwxU1J0UU1YWlpocXNFa0VvczZMM2l5UnpNX3hjZEw5ckVNd2p5YktMaTg1TTlKR2tKaFRKX1l2bmp3VEhVRVYxVmdHZ1V0b2Q0dXJDTS12cFNINFowMkNVSmJKN2hzQzRCdUNwbTVxWjVUUW82NnB6aVhqMThpaDVVb2pGZXZicFFyZlpnU3YtY1dxYjJ5dnJqbWtDYlBGQ09mWnpKcnRKbzM</guid></item><item><title>这种常见的食物成分可以塑造儿童的生命健康- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251225080732.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Researchers from the Institut Pasteur and Inserm have found that when mother mice consume dietary emulsifiers, it can negatively affect the gut microbiota of their offspring. These early changes in gut bacteria are linked to a higher risk of chronic inflammatory bowel conditions and obesity later in life. The findings point to possible health effects that extend across generations and underscore the need for human studies, particularly to understand how early-life exposure to emulsifiers may influence long-term health. The study was published in &lt;em&gt;Nature Communications&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emulsifiers are additives widely used in processed foods to improve texture and extend shelf life. They are common in products such as dairy items, baked goods, ice cream, and some powdered baby formulas. Despite their widespread use, scientists still know relatively little about how these substances affect human health, especially their impact on the gut microbiota.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How the Study Was Conducted&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research was led by Benoit Chassaing, Inserm Research Director and Head of the Microbiome-Host Interactions laboratory (an Inserm unit at the Institut Pasteur). In the study, female mice were given two commonly used emulsifiers, carboxymethyl cellulose (E466) and polysorbate 80 (E433), starting ten weeks before pregnancy and continuing through pregnancy and breastfeeding. The researchers then examined the gut microbiota of the offspring, which had never directly consumed these emulsifiers themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results showed that the young mice experienced noticeable changes in their gut bacteria within the first weeks of life. This period is especially important because mothers naturally pass part of their microbiota to their offspring through close contact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disrupted Gut-Immune Communication&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The altered microbiota included higher levels of flagellated bacteria, which are known to activate the immune system and promote inflammation. The researchers also observed that more bacteria were coming into close contact with the gut lining. This process, described as bacterial "encroachment," caused certain gut pathways to close earlier than normal. These pathways usually allow small bacterial fragments to cross the gut lining so the immune system can recognize them and learn to tolerate the body's own microbiota.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When these pathways closed too soon in the offspring of emulsifier-exposed mothers, communication between the gut microbiota and the immune system was disrupted. As the animals reached adulthood, this disruption led to an overactive immune response and chronic inflammation, significantly increasing the risk of inflammatory gut diseases and obesity. The study links early-life microbiota changes in mice, even without direct emulsifier consumption, to a higher likelihood of developing these chronic conditions later on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Implications for Human Health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It is crucial for us to develop a better understanding of how what we eat can influence future generations' health. These findings highlight how important it is to regulate the use of food additives, especially in powdered baby formulas, which often contain such additives and are consumed at a critical moment for microbiota establishment. We want to continue this research with clinical trials to study mother-to-infant microbiota transmission, both in cases of maternal nutrition with or without food additives and in cases of infants directly exposed to these substances in baby formula," comments Benoit Chassaing, last author of the study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This work was funded by a Starting Grant and a Consolidator Grant from the European Research Council (ERC).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:01:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE1rTVViSUpycXZrdUlZTV91MzNBNFJpalVnZ1ZSY01Ja1BhM1NrZ0hIYkducXBOUTRFOGRsMGdFRGdPbjh2VDFkUk96T042WGY0Mmd2OUM2YWs5aVFET3pIUG4wQ1N0TzE4V0h6bUVnQQ</guid></item><item><title>十年来纽约市流感病例攀升至最高水平-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/26/nyregion/nyc-flu-cases.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:00:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE92eGtIZzhwZ3BteUQ4bmpLeHFkd2FIY0dCdUxzcWxJYnhJMy1TSEd1NGFrTnJ4bFBsa0V1M1lEUURhWGg1WTVKdWVpNmpoQ082UVlwU1FESlJpdjlESVptYjZTcnJpbk1OQkg1bU1wQQ</guid></item><item><title>为什么科学家们用无人机捕捉鲸鱼的呼吸：短波- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/12/26/nx-s1-5655233/whale-health-breath-blow-virus-drone</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resnx-s1-img-5863252" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                A humpback whale exhales out of its blowhole. Scientists are now using drones to study these exhalations and identify when whales are sick.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Dr. Mridula Srinivasan/NOAA
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Dr. Mridula Srinivasan/NOAA
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Scientists in the Arctic are catching the exhaled breaths of whales to better understand their health. How? Drones.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Drones have really revolutionized our ability to get a biological sample from a wild whale," says &lt;a href="https://www2.whoi.edu/site/amy-apprill/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Amy Apprill&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a marine microbial ecologist from Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Typically, scientists collect samples from wild whales by getting close to them in a boat, and then shooting a dart gun to snag a small skin sample. Otherwise Apprill, who was not involved in the current study looking at whale microbial infections, says most samples come from whales that are dead.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;To collect the breaths, researchers flew a drone over surfacing whales, which they operated from a nearby boat. Whales breathe through their blowholes, which are the equivalent of nostrils on their heads. Using live camera footage, the scientists hovered the drone over a whale that looked like it was about to blow. They captured the exhales on petri dishes attached to the drone.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Lead author of the study, &lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Helena-Costa-6" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Helena Costa&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; says collecting the samples is both stressful and fun. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Of course, in the moment it's like a lot of people just screaming 'Fly lower' or 'Go right' and 'The whale is coming.' So it's a lot of chaos on the boat. But of course, once you look back and you see the results and you see how well the method works, that's a lot of fun."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;By studying respiratory whale microbes, scientists hope to piece together how deadly diseases spread in whale populations. And although there aren't protocols to treat a sick whale, managers can help the large mammals by reducing their stress during illness by, for example, temporarily altering shipping lanes to avoid them. Or, if a whale is carrying a disease that can spread to humans, governments can limit whale-people interactions.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Based on blow samples collected from 2022 to 2025 in the Arctic waters around Norway and Iceland, the team detected cetacean morbillivirus in a couple groups of whales. This virus can cause immunosuppression and severe disease in cetaceans–whales, dolphins and porpoises–and has caused several mass die-offs in these animals. The researchers also detected herpes virus, which is often asymptomatic but can cause severe or fatal disease in immunocompromised animals.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The team didn't detect avian influenza virus or the bacteria brucella, which can both infect humans.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Costa says she's most interested in what the long term data will reveal, "because obviously four years of data is interesting, but if we have 30 years of data we can understand better the dynamics of the circulation of these pathogens…how some stressors, for example, pollutants or climate change, are affecting these dynamics of these diseases."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2024/05/20/1198910024/ai-sperm-whales-communication-language" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Listen to how scientists are decoding whale clicks with AI here&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1186/s12917-025-05152-6" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Read the full research article here&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Interested in more science on charismatic megafauna? Email us your question at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:shortwave@npr.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;shortwave@npr.org&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Listen to every episode of Short Wave sponsor-free and support our work at NPR by signing up for Short Wave+ at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://plus.npr.org/shortwave" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;plus.npr.org/shortwave&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Listen to Short Wave on &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://n.pr/3HOQKeK" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Spotify&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://n.pr/3WA9vqh" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This episode was produced by Rachel Carlson and Kai McNamee. It was edited by Patrick Jarenwattananon. Tyler Jones checked the facts. The audio engineers were Maggie Luthar and Peter Ellena.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxPTDBRTUhDSHZLOTFFSXVxMnVGckU2dTV6emRob2VoWmZLdzNSc2pCak5sRDZUWkVVcEQxREZxVkVYeHJPLXhIVnpTMEllVlQwa2JQaDhqU2thQTl6UzRiOHVwZEtDQjVWYTBfWm5Zc2dpNXFNcVVpSzRTY0x3ZW1vc3RnblR3YWRJ</guid></item><item><title>6个高蛋白冬季sabzi ，值得在餐盘上占有一席之地-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/6-high-protein-winter-sabzi-thatdeservea-regular-place-on-the-plate/photostory/126184671.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Winter eating changes instincts. Meals slow down, portions grow warmer, and sabzi moves from side dish to centre stage. This is also the season when protein quietly matters more, not for muscle talk but for warmth, satiety, and steady energy through shorter days. For context, an average adult needs about 0.8 grams of protein per kilogram of body weight per day. That works out to roughly 45–55 grams daily for most women and 55-65 grams for most men, depending on build and activity. Vegetables will not meet this number alone, but winter sabzi can meaningfully support it, especially in vegetarian households where protein has to be built thoughtfully across the plate. Scroll down for six winter sabzi do exactly that, without turning food into a calculation...&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4wFBVV95cUxQVzk3N3VIc2NtWFdOdDktdWd4NkJTTGhha3V4T1FJMmE3OVRGVW8yTHdMNVpXWUpxTEQ1N1V0NWM5UHM0Rll3U1JpMVJkbHFOQno0SHVBYmRfOHE3dDE0VzVaS0lFQ1hqR3RaUHFmTVc3MjNiU0R5RnJVdU9nVlE1M0lWLWlVamhZLW93X3ptaVZaVlplblU3eEZHaGJFZ19DUnJzNjFhcnF6MDJ4WkhIMndQOXIyQUc5NFRuOUVpNy1ZRHZEbW5FYjFTdjM5M20yMFZKcnB5dzR5Tks0LUFaalBfZw</guid></item></channel></rss>