<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>如何接种2019冠状病毒病(COVID-19)疫苗，并确保该疫苗在您的保险范围内-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-vaccine-access-drugstores-acip-300170f72c4f864656788695dd0ff23f</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;Drugstores are ready to deliver updated COVID-19 vaccines this fall and insurers plan to pay for them, even though the shots no longer come recommended by an important government committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Friday, &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/cdc-advisers-vaccines-hepatitis-b-covid19-a1fb61ef7e29d93d2828618d890cceb3"&gt;vaccine advisers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; picked by Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. declined to specifically recommend the shots but said people could make individual decisions on whether to get them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recommendations from the advisers to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention require sign-off by the agency’s director, but they are almost always adopted. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those recommendations normally trigger several layers of insurance coverage and allow drugstores in many states to deliver the shots. But insurers and government officials have said coverage will continue, and several states have allowed for vaccine access through pharmacies, the most common place to get shots. &lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Many people start seeking vaccinations in the late summer or early fall to get protection against any winter surges in cases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s a closer look at the issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Will insurers cover these shots?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many are expected to do so, but you still may want to check with yours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Department of Health and Human Services said Friday that the committee vote “provides for immunization coverage through all payment mechanisms.” An HHS spokesperson said that includes Medicaid, the Children’s Health Insurance Program, commercial coverage sold through health insurance marketplaces and the federal Vaccines for Children program, which pays for roughly half of childhood vaccinations in the U.S. each year.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The VFC program normally automatically covers any vaccines recommended by the CDC committee.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;The trade group America’s Health Insurance Plans said earlier this week that its members will continue to cover the shots at no cost to patients through 2026. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That group includes every major insurer except UnitedHealthcare. And that insurer has said it will continue covering the vaccine at no cost for its standard commercial coverage, which includes plans offered for individuals and through small businesses. &lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;One caveat: Large employers that offer coverage will make their own decisions on the vaccines. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They may be motivated to continue coverage: The vaccines can help ward off expensive hospital bills from people who develop a bad case of COVID-19. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Where people can get vaccinations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;About two-thirds of adults get COVID-19 shots at pharmacies, and around 30% receive them at doctors’ offices, according to CDC data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Access to the shots has grown after &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/covid-vaccine-access-limitations-645d64cee13664840fc9a39ff2d309c0"&gt;a clunky start&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to vaccine season that saw some people travel to nearby states when they couldn’t make appointments at pharmacies closer to home. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drugstore chains like CVS say their locations are stocked with the latest vaccines, and they now are able to deliver vaccinations in all 50 states and Washington, D.C. Prescriptions are required in D.C. and a handful of states, including Florida and Georgia, CVS Health spokeswoman Amy Thibault said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walgreens also requires prescriptions in a few states, a company spokesperson said. &lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Who can get the shot&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until now, the U.S. has recommended yearly COVID-19 shots for everyone age 6 months and older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Food and Drug Administration &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/vaccines-covid-shots-fda-kennedy-pfizer-children-9ce19908ae7afb354732aa162fd28532"&gt;recently approved&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; the shots for all people age 65 and older, and for younger adults and children with conditions that put them at high risk for catching a bad case of COVID-19.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC maintains &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.cdc.gov/covid/risk-factors/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;a long list&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; of conditions that would put someone at high risk, including asthma, cancer, heart or lung problems, obesity, depression and a history of smoking. It also includes those who are physically inactive, and the agency notes that this list is not conclusive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients can consult with their doctor or care provider to decide whether they are high risk if they don’t have a condition on that list. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both CVS and Walgreens representatives say their companies will ask patients under age 65 if they have any of these factors. They won’t require proof. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In simplest terms, if a patient says they’re eligible, they will get the vaccine,” said Thibault, the CVS Health spokeswoman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Science and Educational Media Group. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 13:27:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxOWFRYRHZYN3dtVm11RkpzQWZaNW55SHVxaUdHMDlhVVlJTkM2bkI0aVpuQ29USWwxaHd1UC1DazYzRThSSm1wWmFnQ3dDbmN3cW1sLVRJSTItOTJGNXdrREloaGxZRlRvazZNYXIxYmRyS0RsV3FvZnRGeE5mZlhVTlpBN2dIdXFBYUZydUNGbTdMRWJmU1dJS2JGMlc</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr.解雇的威斯康星大学医生谈论新型冠状病毒疫苗指南-《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/uw-doctor-fired-by-rfk-jr-speaks-on-new-covid-vaccine-guidance/</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisgFBVV95cUxPd0pkZmJsYTd4Qm54MHdNamIzLTNwQk1qTWVBTm01eTNVZkVoOXhlQ2hqSXh2d1A1QmJ6QXRJbkpvaFlubFhBaS1IX1RXaFdfeFdLZEJwdWxtMjBpRldndGpydnF6TnQ5M3dwVUxxU25RdDVWcWdqMW1WcGdaRDN2UUNpa0J0aEN3WGhkTjFwdVhkcXhtTGV2anNOdG4xdkdSU2VGQ19WdG4xRnU0YWRpX1B3?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;UW doctor fired by RFK Jr. speaks on new COVID vaccine guidance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirwFBVV95cUxQU0ZMaGNwYlVnWVlQd2FKYTVGN2p1eHU4YXpXRnhzTmlwZDFTb1VBWmtQTHd3SGdHWThTczVuejM4RkxnZlZ4R1praVZ0UE4wLVg2NXdQRElIZVowU0wtY2l0UldJb0VpQUhHM0NUZkszeVRBV2xZa3JNWnViSHdXdUtVQXNFUUFpSGRjYldfeGJNTHJTZUdRNGtSazBuOWtzYmtQMjd5N01XOWRfbHk0?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;CDC vaccine panel adds new rules for getting the COVID vaccine in a tense meeting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;NPR&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigAFBVV95cUxQMEoyQl9IeUVNOGxqLXk2Z3dsb3FWcWlDakVrd1NWekszS0tJVnBmTjh3bm5wMUhpaEw2RFFEMUxXNHRXbDNJclZVQ2pad0J0V2lMR2xkT1NTUGwwRUZXM2JIZ0x1cXRRLU5LUUQybXBlTGJsb3paYW03bnBPY1EtTg?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;CDC advisers vote that patients must consult a health care provider for Covid-19 vaccination, but no prescription required&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogFBVV95cUxQbnJRN3BXaGdPSlJqWms0SkJqel8ySmloZHBQUW1uUkl5VDhYQk9PTjJqVkdhUUhYYWRXZEt0M0RIaGRZNVBZTWx0RXJjb3dsQmc4T3JmLWt4c01PUENpcl8xdFdtSEJmVXRWX0QxTFhGU0hpTFhla1hGY3Z1aXVOVW51UWRXV0czZ3gzS1RfdzVWLTIzUHJvY1FXWlMwalNQRHc?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Kennedy’s advisory panel recommends new restrictions on MMRV vaccines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;AP News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitAFBVV95cUxOSk1zYkJXRjJ2SHNxZXZPdlRmTXRHck4ydWw4cXo0eUQwU3dyYjFEQWFZR24zX095czBTb1JvWW5fYjM4RDV2cEdwb2Jadlp3NXZqSDFvaVgxNnBhZmtDLWJMZGNRMzdkeExuUnA5OHZLMVV2eHZ0Y0I5MVRHSV9yNUJrWTRYTzF1R2xiVWFuZVBFOEJFTjJKbVNneWZiNThGdVZqYTJZblRwc0N2c0tsc09yOHI?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;RFK Jr. Panel Sparks Chaos, Muddies Long-Set Vaccine Schedule&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Bloomberg.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxPd0pkZmJsYTd4Qm54MHdNamIzLTNwQk1qTWVBTm01eTNVZkVoOXhlQ2hqSXh2d1A1QmJ6QXRJbkpvaFlubFhBaS1IX1RXaFdfeFdLZEJwdWxtMjBpRldndGpydnF6TnQ5M3dwVUxxU25RdDVWcWdqMW1WcGdaRDN2UUNpa0J0aEN3WGhkTjFwdVhkcXhtTGV2anNOdG4xdkdSU2VGQ19WdG4xRnU0YWRpX1B3</guid></item><item><title>一位退休祖父的胃灼热是一种罕见疾病的警告信号-哥伦比亚广播公司新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/mesenteric-ischemia-chronic-northwestern-university-health/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;For retired grandfather Ed Langevin, life was good. He spent plenty of time with his grandkids. He went to church regularly. And he loved the simple things, like a bowl of pasta or a sub from his favorite deli. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in February 2024, everything changed. Every meal left Langevin with heartburn. He could barely eat, and even a little bit of food made him feel full. While he used to regularly eat a whole sub, now a quarter of the sandwich left him feeling full and kept him from eating for days. He was often nauseous, and he became afraid of eating because of the pain food caused him. He lost 20 pounds in three months. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I didn't think I was going to make it, to be honest," Langevin told CBS News. "I just wasn't feeling good at all. I'd be laying out in the sunroom on the couch most of the day." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Langevin struggled to learn what was wrong with him. His general doctor "did all sorts of tests," Langevin said, including checking his liver and pancreas. Finally, in May 2024, a stomach scan revealed that he had an &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/danielle-perea-intestinal-transplant-mesenteric-ischemia/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;unusual condition called mesenteric ischemia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. His doctor said he'd only seen it once before. Langevin had never heard of it and researching the condition filled him with fear. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I made the bad decision of going on Google and checking this out, and oh my gosh, I thought I had only a few years left by the way those articles were," he said.&lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The specialist that his primary care physician sent him to see set him straight. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He said, 'Don't ever look at that stuff, just don't,'" Langevin said. "He said, 'We're going to get you through it.'" &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is mesenteric ischemia? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mesenteric ischemia occurs when narrowed or blocked arteries restrict blood flow to the small intestine, &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/mesenteric-ischemia/symptoms-causes/syc-20374989" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;according to the Mayo Clinic's website&lt;/a&gt;. There are two forms of mesenteric ischemia: Acute and chronic. Acute mesenteric ischemia occurs suddenly and is often caused by a blood clot, according to the Mayo Clinic. Chronic mesenteric ischemia builds up over time and usually occurs when fatty deposits build up in the arteries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A chronic case of the condition can become acute if left untreated, the Mayo Clinic said. The condition can cause pain, malnutrition and potentially fatal complications, including intestinal damage and organ failure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/18/659652b7-a702-48bf-b77e-09751fd5cc2f/thumbnail/620x619/014dd724a9f074d5844993dfc2003496/langevin-scan-1-1.png#" alt="langevin-scan-1-1.png " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/18/659652b7-a702-48bf-b77e-09751fd5cc2f/thumbnail/620x619/014dd724a9f074d5844993dfc2003496/langevin-scan-1-1.png 1x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;An abdominal scan shows the blockage in Ed Langevin's superior mesenteric artery. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Bluhm Cardiovascular Institute at Northwestern Medicine Palos Hospital

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Langevin had the latter form of the disease, said Dr. Gabriel Wallace, the director of vascular surgery at the Bluhm Cardiovascular Institute at Northwestern Medicine Palos Hospital. Langevin's condition was "pretty extreme," Wallace said. Patients like Langevin tend to be miserable by the time they are diagnosed, Wallace said.  &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"They can't eat, they lose weight, they start becoming malnourished, and there's a real psychiatric or psychologic detriment," Wallace said. "The psychological toll of not being able to eat, the disruption of your normal life, the pain, the fear of eating, it totally wrecks people." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Treating mesenteric ischemia &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While mesenteric ischemia is dangerous and unpleasant, it's not difficult to treat, Wallace said. He performed a minimally invasive procedure on Langevin in June 2024, placing a stent in the superior mesenteric artery. The stent holds the artery open and allows blood to flow normally. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The surgery took less than an hour, Wallace said. Langevin was sent home the same day. He was also placed on antiplatelet medication, Wallace said. Langevin said that when he returned for his two-week check-up, he was able to eat an entire sub sandwich without any discomfort first. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/18/2d24aa2b-3885-46d4-8359-82baeba5e666/thumbnail/620x899/a5e06684d6945e5b626b802eb66c4eda/langevin-scan-3-stent-1.png#" alt="langevin-scan-3-stent-1.png " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/18/2d24aa2b-3885-46d4-8359-82baeba5e666/thumbnail/620x899/a5e06684d6945e5b626b802eb66c4eda/langevin-scan-3-stent-1.png 1x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;The stent placed in Ed Langevin's superior mesenteric artery. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Bluhm Cardiovascular Institute at Northwestern Medicine Palos Hospital

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For about a year, everything went well. In March 2025, Langevin began feeling bloating and discomfort after eating again. He returned to Wallace. A scan found that some scarring from the first surgery was compressing the stent. Wallace said it was not an uncommon complication and he performed a second procedure that extended the stent. Langevin will continue to receive regular follow-up care to ensure that the condition is correctly managed.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Getting back to normal  &lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, about six months out from his follow-up surgery, Langevin is back to his old self. Steaks, pasta and sandwiches are back on the menu. He has gained back most of the weight he lost and is back to spending plenty of time with his grandkids. He and his wife are planning to travel to Rome in November as part of a pilgrimage with his local church.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm doing really good. I'm feeling normal," Langevin said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/18/77d5d6cd-cee9-4ee7-b452-67334af9ef2a/thumbnail/620x465/3b7d20ea92643f57605de688a027f637/img-1116-ed-langevin-1.jpg#" alt="img-1116-ed-langevin-1.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/18/77d5d6cd-cee9-4ee7-b452-67334af9ef2a/thumbnail/620x465/3b7d20ea92643f57605de688a027f637/img-1116-ed-langevin-1.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/18/77d5d6cd-cee9-4ee7-b452-67334af9ef2a/thumbnail/1240x930/b1074774180b498ffbf5b6ab59ff486a/img-1116-ed-langevin-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Ed Langevin and his wife at an area restaurant.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Ed Langevin

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Langevin told CBS News that he hopes his story reminds others of the importance of advocating for themselves in a healthcare setting. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Just don't give up," Langevin said. If you find a doctor that's given up on you, find another one, but just don't give up." &lt;/p&gt;

      

                    
        
      
                  
    
    



    
      
    
  

          
  
        
      &lt;div class="content-author"&gt;
      &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/team/kerry-breen/" class="content-author__name" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Kerry  Breen&lt;/a&gt;

      &lt;div class="content-author__bio"&gt;
        &lt;div class="content-author__full-information"&gt;
          &lt;p class="content-author__text"&gt;Kerry Breen is a news editor at CBSNews.com. A graduate of New York University's Arthur L. Carter School of Journalism, she previously worked at NBC News' TODAY Digital. She covers current events, breaking news and issues including substance use.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/section&gt;

  
  

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxOTTdCLWwtazloTEtPM2ltTHZCYVVOZzlEMDZ1VzU1YXJTNkNQb1dEZUU2dWJYc3pLOS05MEtQX3AybXBUdFZoYmF6ZWp3RlcxWVlqRThoYXBqZzN6ZEpOZjRRU0w2RndMb3pvTm5HY0g4LTdzOHRpdnlWN3RCdGNUMmJWZFVrR3pBb2VvVm1QaWJaZ9IBlwFBVV95cUxQRFdUUHFPclh5Mm5nYmhkZUdZR19EekdIUUM0TzlsUXlwZFJPV0s3SnZOZjBGRjdNSVg3T1k2bGM3bmFYMlFvZXRLNlQwOWhwaW50MUJDT0pqWXRCeWJDblNBeEFQUUJ5b29Hc1BYNzB6ZlZqUURIQkhHQ3lYZDY5Z3JDbDVSZTBlVjVfdXBFdEhqa1Y5U3dV</guid></item><item><title>疫苗专家组的紧张局势暴露了RFK Jr.领导下的科学更广泛的冲突。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/09/20/acip-vaccine-cdc-criticism-rfk/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AXAY47Q7H13V1D9VNT1268CTD0" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The chair of a new panel of federal immunization advisers selected by Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. said Friday that the group’s “enormous depth and knowledge about vaccines, about science” should be obvious to anyone listening to them work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 10:17:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQanZ0UjlmMkI3VnNQZVVVVnBkN296X3ZqaTF4aGd6emhNQ1NuZVhHNzFvU3dPLThxNDZmZFlidVU1bVh3TVFuMTJ5ZnVvN3NVWDc4aFdLeFV1YWFZTU82OXU3Mi1EaFNsUFRUeEpNMUlfRVA0ZlpaM1Y2RDczX2V6U0kxZ0RlWUU</guid></item><item><title>几乎没有人使用这种令人惊讶的简单治疗高血压的方法- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250919085237.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Few people with high blood pressure were using salt substitutes, even though they are a simple and effective way to lower sodium intake and manage blood pressure, according to preliminary research presented at the American Heart Association's Hypertension Scientific Sessions 2025. The meeting is the premier scientific exchange focused on recent advances in basic and clinical research on high blood pressure and its relationship to cardiac and kidney disease, stroke, obesity and genetics.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;High blood pressure occurs when the force of blood flowing through the blood vessels is consistently too high. High blood pressure can lead to other serious events such as heart attack and stroke. Using data from 2017 to 2020, 122.4 million (46.7%) adults in the U.S. had high blood pressure and it contributed to more than 130,000 deaths. Too much sodium and too little potassium in the diet are risk factors for high blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Overall, less than 6% of all U.S. adults use salt substitutes, even though they are inexpensive and can be an effective strategy to help people control blood pressure, especially people with difficult-to-treat high blood pressure," said lead study author Yinying Wei, M.C.N., R.D.N., L.D., and Ph.D. candidate in the departments of applied clinical research and hypertension section, cardiology division, at UT Southwestern Medical Center in Dallas. "Health care professionals can raise awareness about the safe use of salt substitutes by having conversations with their patients who have persistent or hard-to-manage high blood pressure."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Salt substitutes are products that replace some or all of the sodium with potassium. Potassium salt tastes similar to regular salt, except when heated it can have a bitter aftertaste. Many foods contain some sodium in their natural state, however, the largest amount of sodium comes from processed and packaged foods and meals prepared at restaurants. The American Heart Association recommends consuming no more than 2,300 mg of sodium a day, with an ideal limit of less than 1,500 mg per day for most adults, especially for those with high blood pressure. For most people, cutting back by 1,000 mg a day can improve blood pressure and heart health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This study is the first to examine long-term trends in salt substitute use among a nationally representative sample of U.S. adults. Using data from the National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (NHANES) from 2003 to 2020, researchers analyzed the use of products that replace salt with potassium-enriched or other alternative salts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The investigation focused on people with high blood pressure, and an additional analysis was conducted among adults eligible to use salt substitutes, including people with normal kidney function and those not taking medications or supplements that affect blood potassium levels. Some salt substitutes contain potassium, and they can raise blood potassium to dangerous levels in people with kidney disease or those taking certain medications or potassium supplements. Excessive potassium can lead to irregular heart rhythms. People with high blood pressure who are thinking about switching from regular salt to a salt substitute should first consult with a health care professional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The analysis found:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Overall, salt substitute use among all U.S. adults remained low, peaking at 5.4% in 2013-2014 before falling to 2.5% by 2017-March 2020. Data collection for 2020 stopped before March because of the pandemic.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Among adults eligible to use salt substitutes, only 2.3% to 5.1% did so.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Usage was highest in people with high blood pressure whose BP was controlled with medications (3.6%-10.5%), followed by those with high blood pressure whose BP was not controlled despite medications (3.7%-7.4%).&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Salt substitute use remained consistently less than 5.6% among people with untreated high blood pressure and for people with normal blood pressure.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Adults who ate at restaurants three or more times a week appeared less likely to use salt substitutes compared to those who ate out less often, but this difference was no longer statistically significant after accounting for age, race/ethnicity, education level and insurance status.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Salt substitute use remained uncommon over the last two decades including among people with high blood pressure," Wei said. "Even among individuals with treated and poorly managed or untreated high blood pressure, most continued to use regular salt."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This study highlights an important and easy missed opportunity to improve blood pressure in the U.S. -- the use of salt substitutes," said Amit Khera, M.D., M.Sc., FAHA, an American Heart Association volunteer expert. "The fact that use of salt substitutes remains so low and has not improved in two decades is eye-opening and reminds patients and health care professionals to discuss the use of these substitutes, particularly in visits focused on high blood pressure." Khera, who was not involved in this study, is a professor of medicine, clinical chief of cardiology and director of preventive cardiology at UT Southwestern Medical Center in Dallas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study has several limitations. First, information about salt substitute use was self-reported, so there may have been underreporting or misclassification. In addition, all types of salt substitutes were included in the analysis, therefore, the analysis could not specifically separate potassium-enriched salt from other types of salt substitutes. Finally, the survey data did not capture how much salt substitute the participants used.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Future research should explore why salt substitute-use remains low by investigating potential barriers, such as taste acceptance, cost and limited awareness among both patients and clinicians," said Wei. "These insights may help guide more targeted interventions."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Study details, background and design:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;    &lt;li&gt;The analysis included 37,080 adults, ages 18 and older (37.9% were aged 18-39, 36.9% were aged 40-59 years, and 25.2% were aged 60 and older). 50.6% of participants were women, 10.7% of participants self-reported their race as non-Hispanic Black, and 89.3% self-reported they were from other racial and ethnic groups.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Participants were categorized into four subgroups based on presence or absence of high blood pressure (≥130/80 mm Hg) and whether they were using blood pressure lowering medication: 1) high blood pressure that was treated and controlled; 2) high blood pressure that was treated and not controlled; 3) untreated high blood pressure; and 4) those with normal blood pressure.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Salt types were classified as ordinary salt (iodized salt, sea salt, kosher salt), salt substitute (potassium-enriched or other salt substitute) and no salt use.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;An additional analysis was conducted on a subgroup of individuals eligible to use salt substitutes -- those with healthy kidney function (estimated glomerular filtration rate ≥ 60) and not taking medications or supplements that affect blood potassium levels.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;The frequency of eating at restaurants to assess its influence on salt substitute use was also evaluated.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;All analyses incorporated NHANES sampling weights and complex survey design.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Despite their effectiveness in lowering sodium intake and managing blood pressure, salt substitutes were rarely used by people with high blood pressure, according to a review of almost 20 years of U.S. health survey data.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Researchers recommend increasing awareness of salt substitutes as a strategy to help effectively treat blood pressure, especially for individuals with difficult-to-treat or treatment-resistant high blood pressure.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;The study is supported by a grant from the National Institutes of Health.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: The study featured in this news release is a research abstract.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Abstracts presented at American Heart Association&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;'&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;s scientific meetings are not peer-reviewed, and the findings are considered preliminary until published as a full manuscript in a peer-reviewed scientific journal.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 07:57:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE9Tc1RCdjZnNVJCSnM1UDRseFBjVHVkeEtfcnliR01xT2VZN0lzSHc5M3ZGblJ2TjBMaUk2Mk93Sm1kcml2RjFocjVqSHBySlk3eWJjSzllMV9WNjF1cGpBRDdzbW0xemRoT01MekJHYw</guid></item><item><title>阳光对健康的好处可能大于患皮肤癌的风险-黑客新闻</title><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45298034</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hacker News</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 06:03:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWEFVX3lxTE1tR0pQUG1WeFhfdTVIczRJV01VNUJpZEJ5UTdUc0JCOW94SzRkN2lGc1NfZDFkR1hYbmJHcWxxTzZZQXRPRDFycFJZek9oVkdFVkpfNHFoQlU</guid></item><item><title>我无法治愈的病情是一种潜在的Ozempic副作用。相信我—减肥不值得。- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/laurieyarnell/ozempic-side-effect-gastroparesis-stomach-paralysis</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-1
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="skincare" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139329371" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;In case you’ve been living under a rock and missed the hype, Ozempic is an injectable diabetes drug that’s become popular as an off-label medication for weight loss. It mimics GLP-1, a naturally occurring hormone, to suppress appetite and delay the passage of food in the stomach, making many feel fuller after eating less.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if I wanted to, I couldn’t take drugs like Ozempic because I have a stomach condition called gastroparesis, also known as paralysis of the stomach. Recently, media outlets have reported that in rare instances, taking &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/07/25/health/weight-loss-diabetes-drugs-gastroparesis/index.html" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7941202" data-affiliate="true"&gt;these drugs might be linked&lt;/a&gt; to the development of gastroparesis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unless you’re related to me, you’ve probably never heard of the condition, but gastroparesis is thought to affect about &lt;a href="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/digestive-diseases/gastroparesis/definition-facts#:~:text=symptoms%20and%20complications.-,How%20common%20is%20gastroparesis%3F,the%20United%20States2%2C%203." target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7941202" data-affiliate="true"&gt;10 men and 40 women&lt;/a&gt; out of 100,000 people. In addition to nausea and vomiting, the condition also causes gas, acid reflux, distension and other equally fun symptoms. As my gastroenterologist explained it to me, the muscles in the stomach react too slowly in people with gastroparesis, causing food to sit there until it starts to ferment. The resulting symptoms, particularly the severe nausea and vomiting, mean that eating will be the last thing on your mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But no matter how much weight you may lose, you do not want gastroparesis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My condition is officially listed as idiopathic — that is, it has no known cause. In the spring of 2015, I started to feel nauseous all the time. After months of morning sickness-like nausea and vomiting, followed by a misdiagnosis and an unnecessary surgery to remove my gallbladder, my gastroenterologist mentioned an unusual medical condition that could only be diagnosed with a special test at the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the radioisotope gastric-emptying test, I had to ingest egg salad containing a small amount of tasteless radioactive material that allowed a mini camera to follow the food through my digestive system. Scans of my stomach were then taken over several hours. Afterward, it was official: I was diagnosed with gastroparesis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another reason why you don’t want gastroparesis? There is no cure. Ondansetron, the drug of choice for the nausea, does nothing for me. The preferred drug for delayed stomach emptying, domperidone, was available in the U.S. when I first developed the condition but I now have to get it from Canada. And the cost of domperidone, about $1,000 annually, is not picked up by insurance. I also have to take pantoprazole and sucralfate, twice a day each, to prevent painful acid reflux and ulcers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are surgical treatments like one I had last year at a gastroparesis clinic in Ohio to help manage symptoms, but again, they are not a cure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though some cases of gastroparesis do go away on their own, the longer you’ve had the condition, the greater the likelihood that it won’t. Gastroparesis is not life-threatening, but it has definitely been life-altering for me, as any chronic medical condition can be. It literally affects every aspect of my life; I never know when I will wake up feeling nauseous, so having to cancel plans is an unfortunate side effect of gastroparesis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best way for me to manage the condition is by being hypervigilant about what I eat and drastically limiting fiber and fats. No meat, no more fresh veggies or most fruits, no lettuce, and no oil or fried foods that slow down digestion. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I eat lots of small, bland meals and I am constantly monitoring my symptoms. If I don’t eat enough, I get nauseous. If I eat too much, I get nauseous. If I eat something that actually tastes good, I will probably get nauseous. I am afraid to try a dish when when I don’t know exactly what’s in it, since accidentally eating a food that’s isn’t “safe” can lead to extreme nausea that has me curled up in the fetal position for days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I often bring my own food when I travel, even for a day, and I am always thinking ahead about my meal options. I always carry my meds, as well as snacks that don’t require refrigeration, like oyster crackers, saltines and mints. Big events like weddings can be particularly challenging; I’ve had to sneak away to eat my yogurt or plain turkey wrap, which I bring in an insulated lunch bag. I carry a plastic bowl in my car, just like I did when I was pregnant, in case I have to vomit. In short, I am never not thinking about gastroparesis or worrying about its potential symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 03:16:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxPa2lKVTRKYnpuX0dmSWlkMjF4T2FHbThZb3FrMVJhNmg1U0k3aVBIaktVSHQxc3pDTVBQUDRpMXBYYUhWOXpUbHB0anV0MFhscmxqYUVBTTFNUUMzUFJtSmh6MVlQV2VVWGJ0V3JTWmVoMTNobFpvMUlJcFNFVkJaNHYwVDRRRjBJdWtPWXVzQlcyWk1a</guid></item><item><title>我无法治愈的病情是一种潜在的Ozempic副作用。相信我—减肥不值得。- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/laurieyarnell/ozempic-side-effect-gastroparesis-stomach-paralysis?origin=hfspl</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-1
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="skincare" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139329371" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;In case you’ve been living under a rock and missed the hype, Ozempic is an injectable diabetes drug that’s become popular as an off-label medication for weight loss. It mimics GLP-1, a naturally occurring hormone, to suppress appetite and delay the passage of food in the stomach, making many feel fuller after eating less.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if I wanted to, I couldn’t take drugs like Ozempic because I have a stomach condition called gastroparesis, also known as paralysis of the stomach. Recently, media outlets have reported that in rare instances, taking &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/07/25/health/weight-loss-diabetes-drugs-gastroparesis/index.html" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7941202" data-affiliate="true"&gt;these drugs might be linked&lt;/a&gt; to the development of gastroparesis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unless you’re related to me, you’ve probably never heard of the condition, but gastroparesis is thought to affect about &lt;a href="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/digestive-diseases/gastroparesis/definition-facts#:~:text=symptoms%20and%20complications.-,How%20common%20is%20gastroparesis%3F,the%20United%20States2%2C%203." target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7941202" data-affiliate="true"&gt;10 men and 40 women&lt;/a&gt; out of 100,000 people. In addition to nausea and vomiting, the condition also causes gas, acid reflux, distension and other equally fun symptoms. As my gastroenterologist explained it to me, the muscles in the stomach react too slowly in people with gastroparesis, causing food to sit there until it starts to ferment. The resulting symptoms, particularly the severe nausea and vomiting, mean that eating will be the last thing on your mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But no matter how much weight you may lose, you do not want gastroparesis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My condition is officially listed as idiopathic — that is, it has no known cause. In the spring of 2015, I started to feel nauseous all the time. After months of morning sickness-like nausea and vomiting, followed by a misdiagnosis and an unnecessary surgery to remove my gallbladder, my gastroenterologist mentioned an unusual medical condition that could only be diagnosed with a special test at the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the radioisotope gastric-emptying test, I had to ingest egg salad containing a small amount of tasteless radioactive material that allowed a mini camera to follow the food through my digestive system. Scans of my stomach were then taken over several hours. Afterward, it was official: I was diagnosed with gastroparesis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another reason why you don’t want gastroparesis? There is no cure. Ondansetron, the drug of choice for the nausea, does nothing for me. The preferred drug for delayed stomach emptying, domperidone, was available in the U.S. when I first developed the condition but I now have to get it from Canada. And the cost of domperidone, about $1,000 annually, is not picked up by insurance. I also have to take pantoprazole and sucralfate, twice a day each, to prevent painful acid reflux and ulcers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are surgical treatments like one I had last year at a gastroparesis clinic in Ohio to help manage symptoms, but again, they are not a cure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though some cases of gastroparesis do go away on their own, the longer you’ve had the condition, the greater the likelihood that it won’t. Gastroparesis is not life-threatening, but it has definitely been life-altering for me, as any chronic medical condition can be. It literally affects every aspect of my life; I never know when I will wake up feeling nauseous, so having to cancel plans is an unfortunate side effect of gastroparesis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best way for me to manage the condition is by being hypervigilant about what I eat and drastically limiting fiber and fats. No meat, no more fresh veggies or most fruits, no lettuce, and no oil or fried foods that slow down digestion. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I eat lots of small, bland meals and I am constantly monitoring my symptoms. If I don’t eat enough, I get nauseous. If I eat too much, I get nauseous. If I eat something that actually tastes good, I will probably get nauseous. I am afraid to try a dish when when I don’t know exactly what’s in it, since accidentally eating a food that’s isn’t “safe” can lead to extreme nausea that has me curled up in the fetal position for days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I often bring my own food when I travel, even for a day, and I am always thinking ahead about my meal options. I always carry my meds, as well as snacks that don’t require refrigeration, like oyster crackers, saltines and mints. Big events like weddings can be particularly challenging; I’ve had to sneak away to eat my yogurt or plain turkey wrap, which I bring in an insulated lunch bag. I carry a plastic bowl in my car, just like I did when I was pregnant, in case I have to vomit. In short, I am never not thinking about gastroparesis or worrying about its potential symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 03:16:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxQT3lVQzkyMFZLekpGLTZXRTRKX3VJX3d4ekpHNWNuRWw1MWJMNWdNNlhhMHJaejVGMVpNWEpMVUQ3ZXg4eGJmMmFjUEdJNS1oT0l4T0Y2Vkt4ZTJvQzJ6SWZtQk1vY29FZ25xamxqbWswb2x6RkRCVU81cl9wWm13cVY4d0Zub1NRLTZrMnBLMTRSVS1SdjhTQTNMUnpBQk53R2hPbDZ3</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr.的疫苗顾问为接种新冠疫苗增加了障碍-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/09/19/cdc-covid-vaccine-vote-acip/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="U2LVQKJXEZGQDACAVFNY3C7L44" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;ATLANTA — A federal vaccine advisory panel unanimously voted Friday on a more restrictive approach to coronavirus vaccines by recommending that everyone consult a clinician before getting a shot. The shift creates a complication for Americans who for years were able to get a free shot without having to justify it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 01:49:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNeERZUlRfenhZWjVfMW9nX1ZTb0IwNXBTcm91QXhudWNLUHg5S3VSejNxY0JHckhvRXg3WVBQWkVRRE1kVVdEbFNsblVMZ194Ti1GUFkyLU5FYzNNUW1LbjBtMnJETDEyNmpBeVdVWWpsRUk1bVozT2JzcG16U2FMNWhYTQ</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr.精心挑选的CDC咨询小组如何对新冠疫苗等进行投票- PBS</title><link>https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/how-rfk-jr-s-hand-picked-cdc-advisory-panel-voted-on-covid-vaccines-and-more</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-text"&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kennedy made what he called &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/hhs-restore-public-trust-vaccines-acip.html"&gt;“a clean sweep”&lt;/a&gt; in June when he fired the entire committee and replaced them with his handpicked selections. These new members included &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/anti-science/rfk-announces-new-acip-members-including-vaccine-critics"&gt;noted vaccine skeptics and conspiracy theorists&lt;/a&gt;. Some members &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/hhs-cdc-announce-new-acip-members-sept-2025.html"&gt;joined the committee as recently as this week&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The advisory committee’s performance appeared “sloppy” and highlighted how “medicine is an art and a science,” said Dr. Georges Benjamin, executive director for the American Public Health Association. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You have a committee, and you bring one new person in, that changes the whole dynamics,” Benjamin said. “A lot of these folks are on a very steep learning curve because they’re not vaccine specialists – most of them.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are four takeaways from the meeting and how the panel’s decisions will affect health policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The committee tried to fight its image&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Committee chair Martin Kulldorff opened the meeting by rejecting criticism that panel members were anti-vaccine and challenging previous directors of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention to a debate about vaccine science. Other committee members pushed back at the characterizations they have faced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Joseph Hibbeln, a psychiatrist and Omega-3 fatty acid researcher who serves on the committee, said the members did not enter the conversation with “pre-determined attitudes or pre-determined opinions,” but instead were respectful of others, even during disagreements: “We are not, as a committee, anti-vaxxers.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the manner in which the ACIP was reshaped in recent months, and Kennedy’s statements and actions on vaccines, has worked to undermine public health workers and institutions, said Jennifer Nuzzo, an epidemiologist who directs the Pandemic Center at the Brown University School of Public Health. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nuzzo specifically pointed out how many of the committee members had criticized research about infectious diseases, including COVID-19, at the meeting and demanded more research. During the proceedings, their arguments often relied upon personal stories, such as their own experiences getting vaccine information at their local pharmacy, rather than data and evidence. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Water cooler conversations [do] not amount to epidemiology,” Nuzzo said. “There’s a lot of reasons why anecdotes may be misleading. Sometimes, they do suggest something else is going on, but you have to do rigorous studies to figure it out.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;COVID-19&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Much of Friday’s discussion was consumed with a technical review of COVID-19 infection rates, and deliberations grew tense. During public comments, health experts said the committee’s proposed recommendations for COVID-19 vaccines created more confusion and erected more barriers at a time when people are losing health care coverage and communities are experiencing worsening health outcomes on multiple fronts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Retsef Levi, a professor at the MIT Sloan School of Management, chaired the committee’s COVID-19 working group. According to his presentation of the group’s findings, assessed levels of protection from COVID-19 vaccines against hospitalization, death and long COVID “are based on very low-quality data and analyses,” he said. “That is a major uncertainty we all have to acknowledge.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We feel the vaccines should be prescribed,” he said, adding that the group recommended that state and local authorities should require prescriptions for COVID-19 vaccines. The outcome for that measure was up in the air through the vote itself on Friday, which resulted in a 6-6 tie. Kulldorff cast the deciding “no” vote as the committee’s chair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dozens of medical societies, including the American Medical Association, the American Academy of Pediatrics and the American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists, have touted the safety and efficacy of COVID-19 vaccines and have &lt;a href="https://www.ama-assn.org/public-health/prevention-wellness/open-letter-american-public-respiratory-virus-vaccines"&gt;recommended their use&lt;/a&gt; to prevent severe health outcomes and death linked to the disease. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trade association AHIP, formerly known as America’s Health Insurance Plans, which represents health insurance companies, &lt;a href="https://www.ahip.org/news/press-releases/ahip-statement-on-vaccine-coverage"&gt;issued a statement Tuesday&lt;/a&gt; saying that companies planned to cover vaccines based on recommendations that already were in place as of Sept. 1 until the end of 2026. They did not wait for this week’s ACIP meeting before deciding to extend coverage. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“While health plans continue to operate in an environment shaped by federal and state laws, as well as program and customer requirements, the evidence-based approach to coverage of immunizations will remain consistent,” the group said. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Tom Frieden, former CDC director during the Obama administration, &lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/show/cdc-panel-overhauled-by-rfk-jr-changes-childhood-vaccine-recommendations"&gt;told PBS News Hour’s Ali Rogin&lt;/a&gt; that the insurer association’s decision marked “a huge vote of no confidence” in the vaccine advisory panel’s process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And that’s unfortunate,” Frieden said. “I think, stepping back, you have to look at what this administration, and particularly Secretary Kennedy, is doing, rather than what he is saying. He’s saying he wants to restore trust. He just destroyed trust of the insurers.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even as vaccine uptake rates decline nationwide, physicians and public health experts urged the committee to protect access to vaccines for people who still wanted to acquire that level of protection for themselves and their families. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Low uptake should not limit access to those who want to be vaccinated and reduce their risk for severe outcomes,” said Dr. Robert Hopkins, Jr., medical director of the National Foundation for Infectious Diseases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What actually happens in reality is “hard to say,” said Dr. Sean O’Leary, an American Academy of Pediatrics fellow, who pointed out during a call with reporters that Kennedy’s committee has “sown confusion.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Hepatitis B&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, after hours of deliberation, the committee attempted to vote, then postponed and ultimately tabled a vote that would have delayed dosage of the hepatitis B vaccine for newborns until a month after they are born. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hepatitis B, an infectious disease that weakens the liver and is transmitted through blood and bodily fluids. It often takes months for symptoms to become obvious, heightening the risk of subsequent transmission to others. People who engage in intravenous drug use with shared needles are at higher risk of contracting the disease. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As few as &lt;a href="https://www.hepb.org/what-is-hepatitis-b/what-is-hepb/facts-and-figures/"&gt;1 in 4 people in the U.S.&lt;/a&gt; who are estimated to be sick with hepatitis B are diagnosed, meaning many people are unaware they have been infected. Testing is possible, but stigma often inhibits people from asking for the test or having more candid conversations with their health care providers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because the disease can be passed from a pregnant person to their fetus,  the vaccine for hepatitis B has been available and administered in the United States to newborns within their first hours of life, a practice that has been in place since 1991. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The vote to change the timing of when infants receive the vaccine began to unravel as presentations began. Leading up to the committee’s decision to ultimately table the vote, a feeling of uncertainty persisted among ACIP members who seemed increasingly unconvinced that their vote on hepatitis B vaccines was necessary at this time, given its benefits. The vaccine has been deemed safe and effective in controlling the disease’s spread. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The optimal approach seems to be to have a standard recommendation,” said Dr. Cody Meissner, a committee member. “It’s very hard to identify people who are most likely to be exposed and infected to hep b, such as IV-drug users, sex workers, homeless people. You can’t find them. It’s hard to get them vaccinated.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parents and families “don’t understand the discussion of the subtleties that we’re going through,” said Hibbeln. “If we make a major change in what has been a successful vaccine campaign, we have to have a darn good reason.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Multiple experts asked why the committee was pushing this vote at all and given the vaccine’s  long-running track record of safety and effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I would urge the committee to follow the methodical process of an evidence-based science,” said Dr. Amy Middleman, a professor of pediatrics at the University of Oklahoma’s College of Medicine. “Please, please do that for public confidence and in order to make sure the science is adequately and appropriately vetted.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Experts later praised the decision to table the hepatitis B vote as being the correct choice because of the implications of delaying its administration on newborns, families and public health. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Measles, mumps, rubella and varicella&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also on Thursday, ACIP members voted to remove the option for a combined vaccine that boosts protection against measles, mumps, rubella and varicella (MMRV) for kids under age 4. Instead, the committee voted 8-3 to recommend that toddlers up to age 3 receive an MMR vaccine with a separate dose to protect against varicella, also known as chickenpox. This option already exists and some physicians already recommend it to caregivers.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/watch-live-rfk-jr-s-hand-picked-vaccine-panel-meets-to-consider-covid-shots-and-more"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WATCH:&lt;/strong&gt; RFK Jr.’s hand-picked vaccine panel recommends new restrictions on MMRV vaccines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“HHS will examine all insurance coverage implications following today’s ACIP recommendation, prior to a final decision on adoption” by CDC Acting Director Jim O’Neill, according to a statement issued by HHS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During their discussion, committee members expressed concern about a slightly increased risk of febrile seizures in young children who receive the MMRV vaccine. But O’Leary said these cases are rare and “benign.” He said health care providers had preferred to deliver the combination vaccine “because it’s less pokes for children.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The American Academy of Pediatrics stands by its recommendation to “offer parents the choice,” O’Leary. “Now, what they’ve done is take away the choice for parents” of children under age 4, he said. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The AMA is concerned that this change not only reduces parental choice, but also reflects ACIP’s reliance on selective data in forming its guidance,” said Dr. Sandra Fryhofer with the American Medical Association. &lt;/p&gt;

                                            &lt;div class="inline-invite inline-invite-type__funding inline-invite-style__default"&gt;
        
                    &lt;div class="inline-invite-funding__box"&gt;
                &lt;figure class="invite__logo"&gt;
                    &lt;svg class="svg"&gt;&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#pbs-newshour-horiz-refresh"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
                &lt;/figure&gt;
                &lt;p class="invite_heading"&gt;
                    We're not going anywhere.
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p class="invite_body"&gt;
                    Stand up for truly independent, trusted news that you can count on!
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://give.newshour.org/page/85597/donate/1?ea.tracking.id=nh_july_2025_rescission_article&amp;amp;supporter.appealCode=N2507QW07000AA" class="donation-link ga-click-funding ga-click-ender-funding"&gt;
                    &lt;button class="donate-button"&gt;Donate now&lt;/button&gt;
                    &lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="#000000" class="bi bi-arrow-right-short" version="1.1" id="svg1" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:svg="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;
                    &lt;defs id="defs1"&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;
                    &lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" d="M4 8a.5.5 0 0 1 .5-.5h5.793L8.146 5.354a.5.5 0 1 1 .708-.708l3 3a.5.5 0 0 1 0 .708l-3 3a.5.5 0 0 1-.708-.708L10.293 8.5H4.5A.5.5 0 0 1 4 8z" id="path1"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
                    &lt;/svg&gt;
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;


                                    &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PBS</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:08:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxOZEFNOVB0ZUlOcmlXRndJeDJQQ0pZRkFoSUUyYmRKdTZTaDNkNXBYTUNxOHhUWDRjdWRrSGZJREkzRC1iX0VkLXVITy1MY05FRlFwVXJyVzdEZmdRQml6Wlc0MnRmUjZ1SjFDWjRJb2s4VERLbkZJWDRpcnJjOFhpdG1FekJhZU9RUm5Db0lhV2lxbmo4X2RkRDFzVDRueEtEblZoeTRlRHpjTWwzdGhoUS130gG3AUFVX3lxTE9rVkoxQjNhUmhQZ1J3dnBMUEdXeEFQME5PcWVja0hxRGxFeE4wZndhNHpwZV9FeFBsdFk3Wl9GSTZuaG9YaU9lU2F3aExKUXl6aEZjaTRZU1MxSXdsRjFVaGVOcEVvS3otajYzSjFkbHhfYjZfeG1YMEdKcEU5d2MzQXJkQ2toZk9Pc2ZRMGhaS25MMGg1UWFZMXZVWEtZVEdJX285dWs3QmRoekZ6dzA4dHVCb2szaw</guid></item><item><title>研究：阿司匹林将结直肠癌复发率减半- NewsNation</title><link>https://www.newsnationnow.com/health/aspirin-colorectal-cancer/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>NewsNation</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 23:41:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTFB5UFlyX0JUSzl2eWYyTG9zeC1IOWZCNzhjMFM5d2hnYkEtM3V4R1dyUzVWOVIycXU1ZzZzWlM0MnZtZFlnelhJaXN1bndabTUxSlh2S180RU5fa0pNaENEZFF0N0FPMFc4SU8wckZwV0bSAXZBVV95cUxPdjlwQ3I4M1BwdEtiWXg1Yzl4alI0Y01UZkx2SEM3eFlEZXIwdUowMHJCR0hBV2NubGVwR1l6elRoZEl3R3NpNXdPaUI3eUZRcEhNclhJMjhkM2IyVDNHZVl6WWxyeEhaQS01SnFpR0ZObTRqRnBn</guid></item><item><title>CDC疫苗小组在混乱中推迟了一次投票并推翻了另一次投票-纽约时报</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/19/health/cdc-vaccines-mmrv-hepatitis-b.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 22:15:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxNb1FXYXhpWHR1RkNCMVVJelUyNXd3LVhJTF9idDFDa2VNMkI0VjBSQW1YMU1fdmVXa3lyNlJzcHhrdm5mdE1yMGRLT1VzU2dzUndualMwdWZ3c0ZralRuUF9fYlZHMXE4VjJPa21IS0hpUVd5N1poVlJ0TWpKV2tKczZn</guid></item><item><title>孕妇不应该使用大麻，新的医疗指南说-纽约时报</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/19/health/pregnancy-cannabis-marijuana-guidelines.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 20:15:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxQRlJWTVRhWlY4TEoxMmVRQUhoV2xyTUJKMG1yTTZpNU5hUEhNb0VzSzBPN1liYnVQSEtHcGJ3akhmSVRLNDNwQldrd0U4WWlPbERzaFhrbl9DUkFnSlRvbGFLY3ViNkgxaGNzVEhHTGR2ODhpYURlQXIzODFWMVMwbnd0cXJyUFd5dGZyenpXMA</guid></item><item><title>美国疾病控制与预防中心（ CDC ）顾问投票决定增加新的新冠疫苗规则，以阻止疫苗接种- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/09/19/nx-s1-5545946/cdc-covid-vaccine-acip-recommendations</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-89631" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                ACIP member Retsef Levi points to a slide while speaking during a meeting of the CDC's Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices on September 18, 2025 in Atlanta, Georgia. The federal vaccine advisory group, recently appointed by Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., made recommendations Friday on the COVID vaccine.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Elijah Nouvelage/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Elijah Nouvelage/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;A panel of vaccine advisers to the federal government debated several changes to COVID-19 vaccine access in a chaotic meeting Friday, marked by confusion over processes, technical difficulties and passionate disagreement among members and other experts in attendance.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Ultimately, the committee backed away from its most controversial proposal that called for states to require those who want a COVID-19 vaccine to get a prescription.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The committee voted to recommend vaccination for adults 65 and older and younger people subject to a process called shared decision making. Their recommendations would not prohibit anyone over six months from getting the shot, but they do call for patients to speak with a clinician about the risks and benefits.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;For people 64 and younger the conversation should emphasize that benefits are greatest for people with the most risk of serious disease and lowest for people without increased risk.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The advisers also voted that the CDC should add information about the possible risks and uncertainties related to COVID vaccine effectiveness to information sheets about the shots. Many of the risks were speculative or already known to be unfounded.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;While the CDC generally adopts the recommendations of the panel, the votes are not final until acting CDC director Jim O'Neill signs off on them.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The gathering underscored the turbulent and highly politicized nature of vaccine policy under the leadership of Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., which is now at odds with positions held by major medical organizations.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Over the course of the meeting, many clinicians in attendance raised concerns about how ACIP had sidelined expert input, elevated questionable or preliminary data, and broken from the established process for developing these recommendations, which influence insurance coverage.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's troubling to see the erosion of the committee's integrity," said Dr. Sandra Fryhofer, who spoke on behalf of the American Medical Association on Friday, "We're concerned about how vaccine recommendations are being developed by this new panel, data is being selectively used to justify specific conclusions&lt;em&gt;." &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;The recommendations on COVID-19 come on the heels of Thursday's vote to restrict access to the MMRV vaccine in children under 4, and represent the latest push in Kennedy's ongoing campaign to reshape vaccine policy in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;However, some proposals that would have more dramatically reshaped the vaccine schedule did not make it through. A vote to remove the recommendations that infants get the hepatitis B vaccine at birth failed to pass on Friday morning.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;And the recommendation that a prescription be required for anyone to get a COVID vaccine – which could have been a new hurdle in many places, if states adopted the recommendation – ended in a tie. ACIP chairman Martin Kulldorff voted no, breaking the tie. The motion failed.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;This was the second meeting of the vaccine panel since Kennedy fired &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/06/09/nx-s1-5428533/rfk-jr-vaccine-advisory-committee-acip" target="_blank"&gt;the existing roster&lt;/a&gt;, chosen during the Biden administration, and installed his own choices. Some on the panel have a history of criticizing vaccines, particularly the COVID-19 shots which have been an animating force for many of Kennedy's supporters.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;One member, Retsef Levi, an MIT professor of operations management, drove much of the discussion leading up the votes on COVID-19, which were not shared publicly until Levi presented them at the end of the meeting. Several outside medical groups in attendance requested that the voting topics be shared to have transparency.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In his comments, Levi emphasized safety concerns about the vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"I don't think that the public currently believes the narrative of safe and effective," he told the panel.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There has been considerable confusion around the availability of COVID-19 shots since late August when the Food and Drug Administration only &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/08/27/nx-s1-5515503/fda-covid-vaccines-restricted" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;approved&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the fall boosters for people who are 65 and up, or have high risk medical conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 20:05:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxQU0ZMaGNwYlVnWVlQd2FKYTVGN2p1eHU4YXpXRnhzTmlwZDFTb1VBWmtQTHd3SGdHWThTczVuejM4RkxnZlZ4R1praVZ0UE4wLVg2NXdQRElIZVowU0wtY2l0UldJb0VpQUhHM0NUZkszeVRBV2xZa3JNWnViSHdXdUtVQXNFUUFpSGRjYldfeGJNTHJTZUdRNGtSazBuOWtzYmtQMjd5N01XOWRfbHk0</guid></item><item><title>地图显示，如果疫苗接种继续下降，美国将面临致命的疫情爆发-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15114917/Maps-reveal-deadly-outbreak-hit-US-measles-vaccinations-decline.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The deadly measles outbreak that plagued &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/texas/index.html" id="mol-6ec1c950-9588-11f0-b934-b39a01c64dab"&gt;Texas&lt;/a&gt; this year could have been drastically less severe, a new study claims, but only if more people were vaccinated.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers from at the University of Texas, in Austin, found there would have been about half as many measles cases in the state if just five percent more people had received the MMR vaccine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And hospitalizations would have also dropped by about half. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The outbreak &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14473199/texas-measles-outbreak-doctor-cases.html"&gt;ripped through &lt;/a&gt;Texas and surrounding states earlier this year, sickening 762 people and hospitalizing 99, mostly children. Two young girls died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The state's measles vaccination rate had slipped to 94.3 percent of kindergarteners, down from 98.5 percent in 2013. In Gaines County, the epicenter of the outbreak, coverage was even lower at 82 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But now researchers have modeled how the crisis might have unfolded under different immunization rates. The projections did not provide death data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Based on the current measles vaccine uptake, the model said that in Gaines County alone, about 400 people would have been infected and approximately 80 would have been hospitalized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In one scenario, which looked at measles cases and hospitalizations if vaccine rates were five percent lower, the study estimated there would have been approximately 500 cases in Gaines County, about 100 more than under the current levels of vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It also estimated there would have been nearly 100 hospitalizations, compared to the 80 estimated under current rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured above is Peter Hildebrand with his wife Eva and two of his children. They met with RFK Jr, health secretary, after the death of their daughter from the measles &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above graphs from the model show estimates for the total number of cases and hospitalizations from measles that would be recorded in Gaines County under different vaccination rates&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But, if vaccine rates were five percent higher in the county, the model estimated that cases would have dropped to 200 and hospitalizations to 40.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Across Texas, the model estimated that at current vaccination levels the outbreak would have caused six counties to record an infection rate above 12 measles cases per 1,000 people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But, if the vaccination rate was five percent higher, estimates suggested that no county would have recorded an infection rate above this. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt; Writing in their study, the scientists warned: '&lt;span&gt;Findings of this study highlight the critical role of improving MMR vaccination coverage to prevent large-scale measles outbreaks, particularly in regions with declining immunization rates.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The [outbreak] underscores the challenges in maintaining community immunity in the setting of vaccine hesitancy and disruption of routine vaccination programs.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The study comes &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15114545/vaccine-rfk-panel-recommends-mmrv-measles.html"&gt;amid proposals&lt;/a&gt; from Robert F Kennedy's team to tweak recommendations for the measles vaccine in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;An estimated 92.5 percent of kindergarteners are now vaccinated against measles nationwide, data suggests, compared to the peak of 95.2 percent in 2019 to 2020. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The CDC recommends 95 percent vaccination for herd immunity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For the study, published as a &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama-health-forum/fullarticle/2838809?utm_campaign=articlePDF&amp;amp;utm_medium=articlePDFlink&amp;amp;utm_source=articlePDF&amp;amp;utm_content=jamahealthforum.2025.3992"&gt;letter in JAMA&lt;/a&gt;, researchers constructed a computer model of Texas and then tracked how a measles outbreak might unfold under different vaccination rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They tracked three scenarios: One with measles vaccination rates matching current levels, a second with a five percent higher vaccination rate, and a third with a five percent lower vaccination rate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In each scenario, the first measles case was detected in Gaines County on January 20, 2025, in line with the recent outbreak. The simulation was run until June 10, 2025, about two months before the official end of the outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above map shows the model's estimate for measles cases and hospitalizations across Texas under current vaccination levels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above shows its estimates if five percent fewer people were vaccinated than current levels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;And this map shows the estimates for measles cases and hospitalizations if vaccination rates rose by five percent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Overall estimates were not provided for the total number of cases or hospitalizations detected in the entire state of Texas, or for deaths in either Texas or Gaines County.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Vaccination rates are dropping nationwide amid growing distrust of public health recommendations, with a recent KFF Poll finding that fewer than half of Americans now say they have confidence in the FDA and CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Vaccination rates are particularly low in Gaines County in part because it is home to a large religious community of Mennonite Christians.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Measles used to be a major scourge in the US, with 3 to 4million people infected every year, while 48,000 were hospitalized and 400 to 500 died from the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But amid the rollout of the vaccination, the disease almost disappeared, with the US achieving measles elimination status in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A sign reading 'measles testing' is seen in Gaines County, Texas, that was the epicenter of a major measles outbreak this year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But amid falling vaccination rates, it now appears to be returning, with the 1,491 measles cases recorded this year being the most since the disease was declared eradicated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Measles is the most infectious disease in the world, and is spread via droplets expelled when someone sneezes, coughs or exhales. One patient is likely to infect nine out of ten unvaccinated people they come into contact with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Early warning signs of the disease include a fever, cough, runny nose and red, watery eyes, that appear within a few days of infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But within a week patients can break out in a nasty reddish-brown rash that covers the face and then spreads downward over the body, including the limbs and feet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Measles is particularly dangerous to older adults, young children and pregnant women because they have weakened immune systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About one in five unvaccinated people infected with the disease are hospitalized, while one in 20 unvaccinated children infected develop pneumonia and one in 1,000 suffer from encephalitis, or swelling on the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The CDC estimates that nearly one to three out of every 1,000 unvaccinated children who are infected with the disease will die from respiratory or neurological complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 19:34:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxOemxxaDBxR3dmN0dUNnM0OUVPWGs0NUl5ZkplWUVLTGRBcGJ0dDdyUnk3T0IwdzRoRGhadVA5dzZBbzM4OTczOHIxUGU0SDMzNmxMRFRKMXd4eGF6TjRfaHlzckNkYXF4SHhXOEV2akN1d3BzUjMxVl9FZzlKbHRsUnprZDg5M2plM2hremU5Qk0xM3JTanpkN3dZQlZJYk9IdDFjZnozRkpjVERmcDg4TENpYXF4RXJOdnc5QdIBwgFBVV95cUxNeEJyYjFtRmZDckpqSDFMcjc1Y2dCWVZCMkV2V1dVdEVnaWI5SFFtTVN1WDdhcndqOUc2RVY1NTlhOTRSQUlWcVExank3dUZoZk93cUZsdFItbXl0dUJHaXFYa0pwN0xrZDdWU3NqUzRHT2NEU19lb2EtaTBvV1BXazNsQjUyTHVCcE9RVTBjRnFaMGE0Z3lBcVpVWjF1Sl95dTBqNWVZQmRWN0tSMkRNSXNLaDR6ZjlFbVphZkh4TUJJdw</guid></item><item><title>科学家找到纹身-癌症链接-但这不是您所期望的- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-find-a-tattoo-cancer-link-but-its-not-what-youd-expect-2000661419</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-lg lg:leading-[29px] font-serif max-w-none "&gt;
              
              
              &lt;p&gt;You may have heard lately that tattoos can potentially raise your risk of skin cancer. Recent research might complicate that narrative, however, suggesting that tattoos aren’t as harmful to our skin as assumed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Scientists at the University of Utah led the study, &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/jnci/advance-article/doi/10.1093/jnci/djaf235/8239343?login=false"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; last month in the Journal of the National Cancer Institute. Contrary to their expectations, they found that people who had multiple tattoos actually had a lower associated risk of melanoma. That said, the findings don’t provide conclusive proof that tattoos can prevent skin cancer, the researchers caution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-4 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Further investigation is warranted to clarify these relationships,” they wrote.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;An unexpected finding&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Several recent studies have indicated that tattoos could pose a unique cancer risk. Just this March, for instance, a study of twins living in Denmark &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/tattoos-could-be-a-hidden-cancer-risk-study-of-twins-finds-2000578684"&gt;found&lt;/a&gt; that people with a tattoo had greater odds of being diagnosed with skin cancer (and lymphoma) than their non-inked siblings.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tattoo ink can contain &lt;a href="https://tattoo.iarc.who.int/background/"&gt;potential carcinogens&lt;/a&gt;, such as certain metals, and some researchers have speculated that the ink can agitate our body’s cells in harmful ways, causing inflammation or other changes that fuel cancer formation. By that logic, people with large or multiple tattoos should have a greater risk of skin cancer. And indeed, the Danish study did find that people with a larger tattoo had a higher risk than others.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;With the help of cancer registry data, the researchers behind the new study attempted to survey as many Utah residents as possible who had been diagnosed with melanoma between January 2020 and June 2021, conducting the surveys by phone. All told, they obtained responses from 1,167 melanoma cases. They then compared these cases to controls matched in age, ethnicity, and other factors (this data was collected from a representative survey of Utah residents regularly conducted by the state health department).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As with the earlier Danish study, the researchers expected that the more tattoos someone had, the greater their odds of having skin cancer would be. But to their great surprise, they found otherwise.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;People with two or more tattoos had a lower associated risk of both invasive and localized (also called &lt;em&gt;in situ&lt;/em&gt;) melanoma, the results showed. The most apparent lower risk was seen in people who had four or more tattoos and in people with three or more large tattoos.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;What to think about your tattoos&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The researchers certainly aren’t ready to declare that tattoos will keep people safe from skin cancer just yet.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In their paper, they argue the lower observed risk in people with multiple tattoos is likely a sign of “unmeasured confounding”—meaning they might have failed to control for other important risk factors that could differ between people who get tattooed a lot compared to people who don’t. People who get multiple tattoos may be more vigilant about their skin care in general, for instance, and opt to wear sunscreen or stay out of the sun more often.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The researchers also point out that they still observed a small increased risk of skin cancer associated with only having one tattoo, further muddying the implications of their work.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="s1"&gt;“This isn’t a black and white case of ‘get more tattoos, and you could lower your risk of melanoma,’” said lead study author &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="s1 s3"&gt;Rachel McCarty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="s1"&gt;, a former doctoral student at the University of Utah’s Huntsman Cancer Institute, in a &lt;a href="https://healthcare.utah.edu/huntsmancancerinstitute/press-releases/2025/09/study-finds-melanoma-less-common-individuals-several-tattoos"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; from the institute. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="s1"&gt;“Instead, we need to do more research to understand what we are seeing and if this decreased risk is simply due to behavioral or physical factors, or if there could be beneficial immune responses associated with tattooing which lower melanoma risk.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting at least one other recent study &lt;a href="https://aacrjournals.org/cebp/article-abstract/29/10/2093/124436/Tattoos-and-Hematologic-Malignancies-in-British?redirectedFrom=fulltext"&gt;failed&lt;/a&gt; to find a link between potentially relevant cancers like lymphoma and tattooing. So at least for the time being, the jury is still out on whether people should be concerned about their tattoos and to what extent.&lt;/p&gt;
              
                          &lt;/div&gt;

            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 19:25:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxOanFkSmRrY21OSUZ4NFVYdldrVTdfSzBYSUllZER5ajFiUUtjRVBsb2FHdFJMMWtSc3BpUmRvRGNqWHJLclM5cDJYN2xTRDNnMUJrOGdpWXlCdWRxSUIxMnV2OTNHX2s5NVhuSVJpM2pkcU45RXJFM1ppVW53U1hkM2JfT0FyVFNaa01hZ1lpdkkwWjViNTE5QlFiZHI</guid></item><item><title>路易斯安那州报告在沿海水域发现五例食肉细菌死亡-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/sep/19/louisiana-flesh-eating-bacteria-deaths</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Five people in &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/louisiana" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Louisiana&lt;/a&gt; have died in 2025 from a flesh-eating bacterium found in warm coastal waters, substantially exceeding the annual average on such deaths, state officials have said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Those who had died from contracting Vibrio vulnificus as of Wednesday were among at least 26 to be infected with the bacterium, with each case resulting in hospitalization, according to &lt;a href="https://ldh.la.gov/news/vibrio-seafood-safety" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Louisiana’s department of health&lt;/a&gt;. Most of those cases – 85% – involved wounds being exposed to seawater, and 92% of the infected had one underlying health condition, the health department said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Over the previous decade, &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/louisiana" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Louisiana&lt;/a&gt; has registered an average of 10 Vibrio infections and a single death, state health department officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The higher numbers in Louisiana come after scientific researchers have &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-023-28247-2" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;warned&lt;/a&gt; of evidence that Vibrio infections are becoming more common amid rising sea surface temperatures associated with the climate crisis – which has primarily been spurred by human emissions of greenhouse gases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Vibrio bacteria flourish in warm coastal waters and proliferate between May and October. Infections can result from exposing an open wound to seawater or from consuming seafood that is either raw or undercooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;About one in five people who contract Vibrio vulnificus in particular die – occasionally within two days of feeling sick from the infection. Those who do survive such an infection on occasion require limb amputation or intensive care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The story of one man who grew up in New Orleans, and died after contracting Vibrio vulnificus in July in nearby Bay St Louis, Mississippi, vividly illustrated the dangers of the bacterium to the public in the region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Basil Kennedy, 77, evidently contracted the bacterium after scraping his leg on a boat trailer, his daughter told the Louisiana news station &lt;a href="https://www.fox8live.com/2025/08/12/mississippi-man-with-new-orleans-ties-dead-flesh-eating-bacteria/?fbclid=IwY2xjawMIJmBleHRuA2FlbQIxMABicmlkETFiWHRIU0s4a3JKSzlEVnF4AR4JF8LK9Y54BiehiI1D2POkhtUW-W1YaB6A7tX7tTSHMpz-UqfKNzquUUcBFA_aem_Jlk9wK-fDHfZz4cxZ-24MA" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;WVUE&lt;/a&gt;. Kennedy reportedly cleaned and bandaged the wound, and he avoided getting into the water, thinking nothing more of it. But in about three days, his health sharply declined, and he died, his daughter said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Kay Kennedy Regimbal told the station “there doesn’t need to be fear of the water” despite her father’s death – but she added that “there really needs to be an education and an understanding of how to be prepared for a situation where you may be exposed or there is a potential risk”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Symptoms of Vibrio infection can include gastrointestinal illness, an unusually severe wound or – as associated with bloodstream infection – fever, blistering and dangerously low blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The US usually reports about 150 to 200 cases of Vibrio vulnificus a year. About half of those cases occur in Texas, Louisiana, Mississippi, Alabama and Florida. Louisiana officials said the most cases and deaths have been in their state and Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOOGJoRUk3N0lPam9lUDV4NXdUWEduN0F4ODVuMVc4dGhoak9qeW9Yb1JxN0tjUjBIS2VsLTB2eGZESkJuZUpCUjk0VE1IcVJNWGRFdFNoV3B4SEw2UWhHQTNqSG9haVI3WVViV2RwbERmemF5Tm8yX0VrbkREYzIxOW1BTlhJaWVtVkxhYVRVOA</guid></item><item><title>密歇根州的顶级文档提供新冠肺炎疫苗资格说明- MLive.com</title><link>https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/09/michigans-top-doc-offers-covid-19-vaccine-eligibility-clarification.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GXOI6EIDS5BT3KYL6SAIX2KI2A"&gt;Michigan’s chief medical executive has issued guidance to clear up confusion for vaccine providers and residents alike regarding this year’s COVID-19 booster. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="M4NZWKAIHVH7VLA4X6RGZH5F5Y"&gt;Anyone older than 6 months and without contraindication, who has not yet received the 2025-2026 vaccine, can be considered to have an underlying condition that makes them eligible to be vaccinated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4UH2R5A3J5HB3NGXTRDDAFL76I"&gt;Not being vaccinated in and of itself is an underlying condition, explained Dr. Natasha Bagdasarian, citing studies that found last year’s booster reduced risk of severe illness leading to emergency room visits by 33% and hospitalization risk by 45%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QWRZQJBCZVH43OWFBPCW4ZSIW4"&gt;“National medical organizations and scientific experts continue to recommend routine COVID-19 vaccination for those at high risk, but also recommend vaccines be made available for all those who want them, ages six months and older,” Bagdasarian said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VDCNOUFZ2VHR7AKXIL6HQALKMI"&gt;“As the state’s chief medical executive, it is my duty to protect and promote public health, and everyone deserves the opportunity to access COVID-19 vaccine if they desire one.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="H64CD5XN4RBXZOUMNW2WCZFFQU"&gt;Bagdasarian issued a “&lt;a href="https://links-1.govdelivery.com/CL0/https:%2F%2Fwww.michigan.gov%2Fmdhhs%2F-%2Fmedia%2FProject%2FWebsites%2Fmdhhs%2FCME-Standing-Recommendation-Regarding-2025-COVID-19-Vaccines-FINAL-436pm_09182025.pdf%3Futm_campaign=%26utm_medium=email%26utm_source=govdelivery/1/0100019962494de1-47cbff9c-7d68-4ef1-96f2-f947163035e4-000000/mLX4bn_G0H3VQAxu2OE4ZINzsfAerHgwn9hFw9a5PnY=423" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://nam10.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Flinks-1.govdelivery.com%2FCL0%2Fhttps%3A%252F%252Fwww.michigan.gov%252Fmdhhs%252F-%252Fmedia%252FProject%252FWebsites%252Fmdhhs%252FCME-Standing-Recommendation-Regarding-2025-COVID-19-Vaccines-FINAL-436pm_09182025.pdf%253Futm_campaign%3D%2526utm_medium%3Demail%2526utm_source%3Dgovdelivery%2F1%2F0100019962494de1-47cbff9c-7d68-4ef1-96f2-f947163035e4-000000%2FmLX4bn_G0H3VQAxu2OE4ZINzsfAerHgwn9hFw9a5PnY%3D423&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7Cjhicks3%40mlive.com%7C42522d753d4c45f3731108ddf78547de%7C1fe6294574e64203848fb9b82929f9d4%7C0%7C0%7C638938874327223509%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=VfgYs%2Fnl4aw1jfyHz%2Bqt6im%2BvquOOP44Zh6VoUc71M8%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0"&gt;standing recommendation&lt;/a&gt;” on the vaccine Friday, Sept. 19. It was not a mandate to anyone. Rather, it was meant to offer clarity and support. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YER4LE5CWVBCFJL6LMUAFR5WLE"&gt;“This gives (providers) support to interpret the FDA label and say ‘Yes, you’re at higher risk and we feel comfortable because this is best practice in Michigan as outlined by this standing recommendation,’” she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QF6S6325P5CS3L7GGZYKT7CDWE"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/08/2025-covid-vaccine-eligibility-what-michigan-residents-need-to-know.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/08/2025-covid-vaccine-eligibility-what-michigan-residents-need-to-know.html"&gt;&lt;b&gt;2025 COVID vaccine eligibility: What Michigan residents need to know&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UIT26ASVYZA5NMCSZ4MRLEOWRU"&gt;U.S. Health Secretary Robert Kennedy Jr. said vaccines will remain available for “all patients who choose them after consulting with their doctors.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UPHFZKAAGJHWNBQFZUD6GCIUCY"&gt;However, in late August federal regulators imposed new eligibility restrictions when they approved the latest round of COVID vaccines. They limited shots to people 65 and older or who have health conditions that increase their risk of severe illness from coronavirus infection. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WGYOYRD5NJDWNPJZWBHYDRSEVQ"&gt;Regulators didn’t provide a complete list of underlying conditions and referred to a list from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) which was also not exhaustive. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="N7FDNN6SY5D4ZIPDVKQLIGSREA"&gt;The conflicting federal messages and ambiguous eligibility guidelines created confusion among vaccine providers and those who want to get a booster this fall. That confusion sparked Bagdasarian’s official recommendation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HXEAZPBQGNDUNCNDHHXHDUTDNI"&gt;The Michigan Department of Health and Human Services (MDHHS) continues to support COVID booster shots for anyone older than 6 months, with exceptions for those with a vaccine allergy or condition that prevents them from being vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3HC3TZLZRFGJ5DH2NVOF3VGUOQ"&gt;State guidance aligns with the American Academy of Pediatrics (AAP) and the American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UGD4FJODC5ETLJYSB2NHVGXIEY"&gt;“As we enter respiratory virus season, any barrier to COVID-19 vaccination creates a dangerous vulnerability for children and their families,” said AAP President Dr. Susan Kressly in a statement. “Respiratory illnesses can be especially risky for infants and toddlers, whose airways and lungs are small and still developing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RGGSHZLCTJB5TJRSHGWHW6ROC4"&gt;On Wednesday, Gov. Gretchen Whitmer &lt;a href="https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/09/gov-whitmer-instructs-agencies-to-remove-barriers-to-covid-vaccine-access.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/09/gov-whitmer-instructs-agencies-to-remove-barriers-to-covid-vaccine-access.html"&gt;ordered state agencies to remove barriers&lt;/a&gt; to vaccine access for any resident who wants a shot. That included ensuring all health insurance plans under state regulatory authority cover vaccines, to the extent possible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ITJ5K52HNFH5VCQSQSYJ3DMVPI"&gt;For more information about COVID vaccines, including access, contact your primary care physician or visit &lt;a href="https://www.michigan.gov/coronavirus/resources/covid-19-vaccine" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.michigan.gov/coronavirus/resources/covid-19-vaccine"&gt;Michigan.gov/coronavirus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:YD3VSZSNJFBK5JCBXBEHYRZ3UY" data-fusion-component="YD3VSZSNJFBK5JCBXBEHYRZ3UY"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:YD3VSZSNJFBK5JCBXBEHYRZ3UY" data-fusion-component="YD3VSZSNJFBK5JCBXBEHYRZ3UY"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>MLive.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxNSjZYTnJnWEh0bEVRMlIwZy1OOFZ1UExXN2dxd3FveGJ4QmZGbFVHUDQxX2FPZzhUNEltaThVSlNXakRnZjVNakE5LWpvODVEc0NWY2FuU3J4RWxDLUdiMkpINkFSbG9MczN2V2tTZGFsWWpFU0dkZlNkRUVDQWpRS3h1V3lPU3hVVGdvRW5PT3hUNDIwOURiSlRDNWRJRXpOOTBCb0JUNFJkOWfSAb8BQVVfeXFMTlN1Rjd5X0MxYURSS0FPTTVMc3ZBeVVVdEEtS1ZDMEgzMkVBeEVjazdOQmxpbkRfdi1uWExsWUM1NGYta0ZKbzBVMndrMnBZZk1qQ01uVDhqWTlOZTJiNUVzLXhoaGtMUlNtWjdvZHdkVVlQa3piT0lmUmFqQ1lWYWhsVHJ6RkxpM1k3OFN1dnZCNUNFdEtWT1owZ2JJenYyaGo1SDBpR0xTSjJvdnp3LVQ2X1AyS1lHeU83SVBvZnM</guid></item><item><title>纽约数十人住院治疗的致命肺部疾病现已在1000英里以外的州被发现-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15114971/lung-disease-legionnaires-Iowa-deadly-pneumonia.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A bacterial infection that plagued &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/new_york/index.html" id="mol-7aa01310-9562-11f0-93eb-5da462fdacf7"&gt;New York City&lt;/a&gt; for weeks has traveled nearly 1,000 miles to two more states. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rates of Legionnaires’ disease cases in Marshall County, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/iowa/index.html" id="mol-7a9f28b0-9562-11f0-93eb-5da462fdacf7" class=""&gt;Iowa&lt;/a&gt;, have doubled in about a week, reaching a total tally of 68 cases since a cluster was first announced on Thursday, Sept 4.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Iowa Department of Health officials still do not know the source of the declared outbreak in the county, home to around 40,000 people, and have launched an investigation into its origins. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They are urgently focused on testing 12 cooling towers, large air conditioning units for big buildings, in the north-central part of town, believing these to be the most likely origin of the &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14972215/outbreak-deadly-lung-disease-legionnaires-new-york-city.html"&gt;contaminated aerosolized&lt;/a&gt; water droplets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Legionnaires’ disease is spread &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15039397/new-york-deadly-lung-legionnaires-disease-spread.html"&gt;through aerosolized droplets&lt;/a&gt; containing the bacterium Legionella. Legionella can survive in airborne water droplets for several hours, although this timespan is highly dependent on factors such as relative humidity and the specific bacterial strain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The disease causes &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/pneumonia/index.html" id="mol-7a9abbe0-9562-11f0-93eb-5da462fdacf7"&gt;pneumonia&lt;/a&gt;, a severe lung infection that often begins with a high fever that can rocket past 104 degrees Fahrenheit (40 degrees Celsius). A relentless, dry cough and profound shortness of breath quickly follow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The illness wages a full-body attack, bringing muscle aches, headache and a confused mental state as well as severe gastrointestinal symptoms like nausea, diarrhea, and abdominal pain. In some of the most severe cases, the infection can even lead to coughing up blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sydney Grewell, the county's health department director, said the scale of the outbreak is unlike anything the community or the state has experienced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The recent outbreaks mirror a major incident in Manhattan, where tainted cooling towers sickened 114 people and resulted in seven fatalities throughout Harlem and Morningside Heights&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Earlier this month, it was announced that a deadly outbreak of Legionnaires' disease, which first tore through New York City neighborhoods, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14954791/Legionnaires-disease-death-Michigan-cases.html"&gt;has now spread&lt;/a&gt; to the city's northern suburbs, claiming new lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Health officials in Westchester County announced two fatalities, one in White Plains and another in New Rochelle, and confirmed 35 additional cases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The outbreak echoes a recent crisis in Manhattan, where 114 people were sickened across Harlem and Morningside Heights, leading to seven deaths traced to contaminated cooling towers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the source of the Westchester cluster remains under investigation, Health Commissioner Dr Sherlita Amler pointed to the summer's prolonged stretch of 90-degree days as a key factor, creating the warm, stagnant water conditions in which the lethal Legionella bacteria thrive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Meanwhile, in Michigan, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14954791/Legionnaires-disease-death-Michigan-cases.html"&gt;a deadly outbreak&lt;/a&gt; of Legionnaires' disease at a retirement community claimed the lives of two residents this summer, prompting an urgent investigation by health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The deceased, both residents of Allegria Village in Dearborn, contracted bacterial pneumonia in June and July. While their identities have not been released, officials confirmed they had recently moved into separate units within the continuing care facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Wayne County Health, Human and Veterans Services department is leading the investigation, which is still in its early stages, to determine the source of the contamination and ensure the safety of other residents and staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Up to 18,000 people are hospitalized with Legionnaires’ disease each year in the US, and about one in 10 die. It’s more common between June and October, in part because air conditioners run more than any other time of year and cooling towers are typically the cause of outbreaks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The number of Legionnaires' disease cases in Marshall County, Iowa, has surged to 68, doubling the total in just over a week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Despite launching an investigation, health officials in Iowa have not yet identified the source of the outbreak in the county, which has a population of approximately 40,000 people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Legionella bacteria thrive in warm water. Summer weather creates ideal conditions for it to multiply to dangerous levels in human-made water systems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Iowa health officials have not said how many of the 68 patients in that state have been hospitalized. In Marshall County, one death has been recorded: Father Bernard ‘Bernie’ Charles Grady, 82.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The retired Catholic priest, described by his brother Peter as a ‘remarkable’ and ‘incredible’ man, became the outbreak's first and, so far, only fatality according to &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.siouxlandproud.com/news/iowa-news/legionnaires-cases-in-iowa-community-grow-as-one-family-grieves/"&gt;SiouxLand Proud&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Specialized testing confirmed he had been infected by the bacteria. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;His illness began suddenly with dizziness during dinner on August 22nd. A week later, after suffering from congestive heart failure, he passed away in a Waterloo hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The extremely high fevers associated with Legionnaires' disease drastically increase the body's metabolic rate. This means the heart has to work much harder and faster to deliver oxygen and nutrients to fight the infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Infections are more likely to be severe in seniors, who have weaker immune systems than younger populations.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In severe cases, the bacterial infection can spread to the bloodstream, leading to sepsis, which in turn can cause a dramatic drop in blood pressure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;in Michigan, a deadly outbreak of Legionnaires' disease at a retirement community has claimed the lives of two residents this summer, prompting an urgent investigation by health officials&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To compensate, the heart must pump even more vigorously, which can overwhelm a heart that is already weakened or has pre-existing conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the US, an estimated 250 to 800 people die from Legionnaires' disease each year, based on reported case data, which represents only a fraction of actual cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The symptoms of Legionnaires' disease are indistinguishable from those of many other types of pneumonia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Without a specific reason to suspect Legionella, a doctor will often diagnose and treat it as community-acquired pneumonia, without ever identifying the exact cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Health department director Grewell said: ‘This is something I’ve never experienced. I don’t think this is something that Marshall County has experienced, and I don’t think this is something the state has experienced as well, especially of this magnitude.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘We have seen some trends in the patients that we are seeing, which is why we narrowed the focus to northcentral Marshalltown. Those people have visited the area, traveled to the area, and that’s where our cooling towers are primarily located.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:31:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxOd1FDbHZ5T2d0azFNamJBRkkzZVBOYVhnRjlzby1nYWd3UldRR0pxWlVIRTFpMXpPUXU0VHRNQUFqSDVOZnB6M3p0OEl0c05PbzdaVWxZaktXdmVZdVFETVpOanRpOXUyRl8wRXBLYXBhU3FsQnkzTVczOGJsOGF1dGt5clpEOTB6X0NwbVBoUzRpNm9IZzRWVDh3Rll6a0pEWXBpRkNNUdIBrAFBVV95cUxNWGp6OWxyRmNwWjZLRng5aHBMQjB5YzBYLWhDOVk4LXR5czlVdHVnTndOdDRVU3dHUHJMYTRMS1ducUxVV3VfRjdzRmhyRGw3d09jMHI0bHF0N3hCdmlYT3ZEa2RER3FmdTRrMTdTMXJ0dGxVWkRqbE41R2hTajBnZ1U4RmRtQkdnbVZzUUR1TTZlX1hwQmwzRHV6S0tGaVhscEt6azF1WTg2ZURU</guid></item><item><title>每年对数百万人进行的“过度使用”医学检查使癌症风险增加三倍-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15115371/overused-medical-test-triples-children-cancer-risk-ct-scan.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Radiation exposure from 'overused' medical scans may triple the risk of cancer in children, a government-funded study suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Every year, about 18 percent of Americans, 61million, undergo imaging tests like CT scans, which use radiation to create detailed pictures from inside the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the tests are crucial for detecting injuries, chronic diseases and cancer, repeated scans can cause &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14482065/Over-used-medical-test-given-millions-year-causing-explosion-tumors.html"&gt;small amounts of radiation&lt;/a&gt;, a known carcinogen, to accumulate in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With these risks in mind, researchers in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/california/index.html" id="mol-250d97a0-9577-11f0-a15e-b9099f259218"&gt;California&lt;/a&gt; examined data from nearly four million children in the US and Canada to examine radiation's effect on cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They found about one in 10, adding up to 3,000, cases of blood cancers such as leukemia and lymphoma in children could be attributed to radiation exposure from tests like CT scans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In fact, getting just one or two head CT scans was linked to nearly twice the risk of developing cancer. But as children got more scans over time, they were over three times more likely to be diagnosed than children who didn't have the tests. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers suggest about one in 10 blood cancers in children and teens could be prevented entirely by cutting out unnecessary imaging tests and lowering radiation doses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Using other methods like ultrasound or MRI, they said, could provide a feasible alternative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A new study from researchers in California found regular scans using radiation could increase a child's risk of cancer by 3.5 times (stock image) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Rebecca Smith-Bindman, first study author and radiologist at the University of California San Francisco, said: 'Children are particularly vulnerable to radiation-induced cancer due to their heightened radiosensitivity and longer life expectancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'While medical imaging can be lifesaving, our findings underscore the critical need to carefully evaluate and minimize radiation exposure during pediatric imaging to safeguard children’s long-term health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This involves ensuring that imaging is performed only when it provides essential information for the child’s care and, in cases such as CT scans, using the lowest possible radiation doses.'  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 15,000 children in the US are diagnosed with cancer every year, with the most common form being leukemia, accounting for around 30 percent of US diagnoses per year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Roughly 1,600 American children die of cancer each year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Recent research also shows childhood cancers have &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14267083/doctors-warning-toxic-chemicals-cause-childhood-cancers.html"&gt;increased by about 35 percent&lt;/a&gt; over the last half-century, which experts have suggested could be due not only to better diagnostic tools but also increased environmental exposures like radiation and pollution. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The new study, published Wednesday in the &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2502098"&gt;New England Journal of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, followed a cohort of 3.7million children born between 1996 and 2016 across six US healthcare systems and Ontario, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/canada/index.html" id="mol-151c01a0-9573-11f0-a15e-b9099f259218"&gt;Canada&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The participants were followed from birth until they either: were diagnosed with &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-151990a0-9573-11f0-a15e-b9099f259218"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; or a benign tumor, ended healthcare coverage, turned 21 or until the study's end date of December 31, 2017. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above shows the relative risks for blood cancers in children according to cumulative radiation exposure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Half of the participants were male, and the largest group (43 percent) were born between 1996 and 2004, and 4,916 (0.1 percent) died before the end of the study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Of the participants, 2,961 were diagnosed with blood cancer during the study period. Eight in 10 cases were lymphoma, while leukemia and bone marrow cancer accounted for 15.5 percent. The remainder were rare cancers of the white blood and immune cells. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 58 percent of cancer patients were males, and just over half the cancers were diagnosed in children under five years old.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers found for children who underwent a head CT, about 25 percent of their cancers could be attributed to radiation exposure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Additionally, getting one or two CT scans of the head was associated with a 1.8-fold increased risk of blood cancer, and receiving repeated scans increased the risk 3.5 times. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers wrote: 'In our cohort of children and adolescents, we estimated that medical imaging was associated with 10.1 percent of hematologic cancers.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The risk comes from the unregulated radiation exposure that varies widely machine-to-machine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;CT scans can be life-saving tests, catching disease or bleeding early enough to be treated. They also used to diagnose and monitor diseases like cancer and bone injuries, as well as to assist in surgeries and evaluate efficacy of certain treatments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, experts say they are sometimes overprescribed and performed unnecessarily, potentially because of the money-making opportunities for the hospitals, as the tests are very expensive, or out of doctors' fears of missing a diagnosis and being sued. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above shows the risk of blood cancers after exposure to radiation &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Radiation is a known carcinogen found to damage the DNA molecules within cells, causing them to multiple out of control and form cancer cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It also generates free radicals, toxic molecules that attack DNA and other compounds within cells, and induces inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Radiation from tests like CT scans is easily absorbed by the bones, where it travels to bone marrow and increases the risk of blood and bone marrow cancers.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers urgently urged clinicians to only use scans with radiations when necessary instead for an MRI or ultrasound, neither of which use radiation.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Diana Miglioretti, study author and professor at UC Davis Health and chief of the Division of Biostatistics, said: 'This study provides robust, directly observed evidence of a clear dose-response relationship between radiation from medical imaging and hematologic malignancy risk in children and adolescents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Our findings align with international research highlighting that children are especially radiosensitive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It’s crucial for clinicians to weigh the immediate benefits of imaging against potential long-term health risks and to optimize imaging protocols to minimize radiation exposure.'  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The research was funded by the National Cancer Institute (NCI) and grants from the Ontario Ministry of Health and Long-Term Care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Previous research from Dr Smith-Bindman estimated that more than 100,000 new cancers will have been caused by CT scans from exams done in 2023 alone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The research, published in April, estimated 'CT-associated cancer could eventually account for five percent of all new cancer diagnoses annually.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:22:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxNWE0xay1iVGZoN2xEMnlUQWJ6M3pzcndoNWUzak50cU5xal9jQmtPX3I1Z2RDSk14dUh3eVN4QTR2TGpsbExHTDhuVElPWjdSTTg0ZjhmSHZONExpbXltMmZSMjg2TEs5TVNrZkRNTk1aN3BpS0FheXpPTS0yMmh5elI4OWtadmlEUUZGbkZEYmJQYzRQTEJKaXhHMmZXenJZR0M1RkV3bnpCMmUyZUhoOG5qWnVWZ9IBuwFBVV95cUxNYUUxdHQ4dUtoQlhkWlJIS0EtWEdPaFNueEdCRFpKeXRQVmMtNk9VSnNfSHFXVXdHNFl1cDdnWGpoRXJVRXpVNU45S25rLVlZdE5GOFlXWTVHQjNOYkQ2U0xpNEoySUM2RV95YkN6Zlc2dG9pT2JVRHBBQ29hNDVZZ2NuUktkM0dtWHFNd2hNUnNMX1l3eGg2Mk1RY1hMRDdNVnRCMFNmSmJQeXlPakVRWmJiN2N1V0p4OTlz</guid></item><item><title>新的研究表明，这种夜间习惯可能会增加您的痴呆风险- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/dementia-risk-habit-study-11813296</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new study in &lt;em&gt;Neurology&lt;/em&gt; links chronic insomnia with a 40% higher risk of later cognitive impairment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;People with insomnia who also slept less than usual, were more likely to have markers tied to memory problems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Starting a nightly routine and advice from a health care professional can help with quality sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Sleepless nights aren’t just exhausting—they may carry implications for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/worst-habits-for-brain-health-11773249" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;long-term brain health&lt;/a&gt;. While many of us experience occasional rough patches, chronic insomnia has been increasingly connected to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/everyday-habits-hurting-your-memory-11804198" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;memory and thinking changes&lt;/a&gt; as we age. Now, new research published in &lt;em&gt;Neurology&lt;/em&gt;, the medical journal of the American Academy of Neurology, adds weight to that concern: older adults with chronic insomnia had a 40% higher risk of developing cognitive impairment (a category that includes MCI and dementia) during follow-up.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; What’s especially notable is that the investigators also looked inside the brain. Among people with insomnia who reported sleeping less than usual, imaging at baseline revealed more white matter changes (often a sign of small blood-vessel stress in the brain) and higher amyloid burden (a protein that can accumulate in Alzheimer’s disease). Together, the clinical and imaging findings help explain why &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/exercise-sleep-insomnia-risk-new-study-8628457" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;persistent sleep problems&lt;/a&gt; might track with later cognitive issues.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-was-this-study-conducted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Was This Study Conducted? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Researchers drew on data from the long-running Mayo Clinic Study of Aging, which follows older adults over time. They compared participants with and without chronic insomnia and tracked annual cognitive testing alongside brain imaging. Cognitive outcomes included global cognitive scores and diagnostic status (normal, MCI or dementia). 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Imaging focused on white matter hyperintensities (WMH) on MRI. White matter hyperintensities are bright spots linked with small-vessel changes. The imaging also included amyloid-PET, which visualizes amyloid accumulation. The team used established statistical models to estimate both the risk of developing cognitive impairment and how cognition and imaging markers changed over time, while adjusting for many health and lifestyle factors.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-did-the-study-find"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What Did the Study Find? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In this study, chronic insomnia was linked to a 40% higher risk of developing cognitive impairment over the study period. Second, among those with insomnia who also slept less than their usual amount, baseline testing and scans painted a less favorable brain-health picture—poorer cognitive performance, more WMH and higher amyloid at the outset. Importantly, insomnia was not tied to faster accumulation of WMH or amyloid across follow-up. In plain terms: having insomnia, particularly with less sleep, was linked to greater risk. It wasn’t linked to a faster pace of brain damage later on.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To help interpret the magnitude, the authors note this elevated risk is meaningful—large enough to deserve attention—yet still observational. The study cannot prove that treating insomnia would prevent cognitive impairment; other factors may contribute despite careful adjustments.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This study has some notable limitations. Insomnia was identified from medical records rather than overnight sleep studies. Changes in sleep duration were self-reported and not always measured at the same time as the insomnia diagnosis. And because participants are from a single region, the results might not be generalizable to everyone.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-does-this-apply-to-real-life"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Does This Apply to Real Life? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re wrestling with ongoing sleep trouble, there’s a lot you can do, starting tonight. Anchor a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/i-tried-a-doctor-recommended-sleep-routine-for-2-weeks-8763725" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;consistent wake-up time&lt;/a&gt; every day (weekends included) to steady your body clock. Build a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/things-women-over-50-should-do-before-bed-11757559" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;wind-down routine&lt;/a&gt; 30 to 60 minutes before bed: dim the lights, step away from email and doomscrolling and switch to quiet, low-stimulation activities. Get bright outdoor light soon after waking and keep evening light low to reinforce your natural rhythm.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Protect your sleep by reserving the bed for sleep and sex. If you're awake and frustrated for about 20 minutes, get up and do something calm in dim light until you feel sleepy again. Cut off caffeine by early afternoon, and avoid alcohol for three to four hours before bed. Daily movement, like walking, helps build healthy sleep pressure and brief stress-management practices (slow breathing, progressive muscle relaxation, a short mindfulness session) can reduce nighttime arousal.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For chronic insomnia, ask a health care provider about cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia. If you snore, wake up gasping or feel excessively sleepy in the day, consider getting screened for obstructive sleep apnea. Talk to a health care professional if your sleep problems persist for three months or more, if you routinely sleep less than six or seven hours despite your best efforts or if sleepiness makes driving unsafe.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A large study in &lt;em&gt;Neurology&lt;/em&gt; reports that chronic insomnia is associated with a 40% higher risk of developing cognitive impairment, and that people with insomnia who also slept less than usual showed more white matter changes and higher amyloid at baseline. While the research doesn’t prove causation, it’s a clear nudge to take &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/habits-that-can-disturb-your-sleep-8551851" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;persistent sleep problems seriously&lt;/a&gt;. Prioritize a consistent routine, smart light exposure, movement and talk with a health care professional if insomnia sticks around.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:14:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibkFVX3lxTE5ubWY2OGhPcncwbnRwTTV5VWc3Q1VRaE80Yk9RV0Zqcnh4ZXMwVUFDaHA2ck1LaVdFbDBlUXFXUzMteDkyd1BZMm9LRjQ0NTM2alBlNTJHMko1S0ZpLUFvWDlqbUMzMnpYRlJIZnpB</guid></item><item><title>您需要了解的关于美国“接吻虫”病的所有信息- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/19/health/video/gupta-kissing-bug-chagas-endemic-us-digvid</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="video-resource__details--leaf"&gt;
                    &lt;p data-editable="headline" class="video-resource__headline inline-placeholder"&gt;Everything you need to know about ‘kissing bug’ disease in the US
                &lt;/p&gt;
                        &lt;p class="video-resource__showlink"&gt;
                              
                        &lt;/p&gt;
                              

                        
                        &lt;div data-editable="description" class="video-resource__description inline-placeholder"&gt;&lt;p&gt; Experts say “Kissing bugs” are now endemic in the US and spreading Chagas. CNN’s Dr. Sanjay Gupta walks us through how the disease is diagnosed and treated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                    
                &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:29:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOSWpGRnNEdm1SZjNzRlM3V3l5bThFTnduajlVcjFCbEV3OUhZSTdEckdZcGtHVDhSR3VXdHYxYmFUQ3NDXzJqc3BCSE9UdDg0d2ZOZ0czblpGZ2N3cS1CUVFYNTIxRHVQTFIzTjN2SDhiV2ZjV0czLUl3RHhqazFrRDJ2QkZfQ1g2d1N3eXEzbw</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心疫苗顾问决定不推迟婴儿乙型肝炎疫苗注射的更改- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/rfk-jr-cdc-vaccine-panel-hep-b-babies-data-rcna232394</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f65185" class="body-graf"&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is not expected to change recommendations for hepatitis B vaccines in newborns, after its panel of advisers tabled Friday a much-awaited vote on the issue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-386654" class="body-graf"&gt;The panel had been expected to recommend delaying the use of the vaccine in babies, currently administered shortly after birth, but some members expressed frustration over a lack of evidence about side effects and said more discussion was needed. One member also said the voting language wasn’t clear and could lead to confusing guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0e1c88" class="body-graf"&gt;The unorthodox decision follows a chaotic, unconventional voting process for the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP), whose 12 members were all appointed under Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. in the last few months. Many have expressed skepticism about the safety and efficacy of vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-db5bab" class="body-graf"&gt;The members were due to vote Friday on whether to delay the first dose of the hepatitis B vaccine until a child is at least 1 month old, provided the mother tests negative for the virus. Currently, the first dose is given within 24 hours of birth because hepatitis B — an incurable infection that can lead to liver disease, cancer and death — can be transmitted from mother to child during delivery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-258047" class="body-graf"&gt;The hepatitis B vaccine has become a target of Republican legislators, including Rand Paul of Kentucky, who question the medical necessity of protecting newborns if their mothers have tested negative for the virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bccfe3" class="body-graf"&gt;ACIP member Dr. Robert Malone said Thursday that the committee took up the subject because “a significant population” in the U.S. has concerns about vaccine policy, including giving the hepatitis B vaccine at birth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5d513e" class="body-graf"&gt;However, many public health experts questioned the need for a vote without new data to analyze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-27e0cd" class="body-graf"&gt;Minutes before tabling the subject, the ACIP voted unanimously to recommend testing all pregnant women for hepatitis B. A spokesperson for the Department of Health and Human Services said the test is covered across insurance programs and the goal of the vote was to encourage providers and health systems to increase testing rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-776e8d" class="body-graf"&gt;At the meeting on Thursday, CDC staffers &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://www.cdc.gov/acip/downloads/slides-2025-09-18-19/02-langer-hep-b-508.pdf__;!!PIZeeW5wscynRQ!oU4Q9e_38wyod3qsCKl_7D82SjN7OstS2ldBmu3EqyV-o31SM2XBkZiE0YK48MAU2QrYje_19WDXlAWPDKUJwPrXjHrd$" target="_blank"&gt;summarized the results of 17 studies&lt;/a&gt;, which found that the hepatitis B vaccine is overwhelmingly safe and has helped to virtually eliminate hepatitis B infections among newborns. The agency also noted that many pregnant women aren’t screened for hepatitis B in the U.S., making it hard to rely on testing to decide which children to vaccinate. According to the CDC, 12-16% of pregnant women in the U.S. are never tested for hepatitis B during pregnancy — and even if they are, some cases can be missed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3cafe7" class="body-graf"&gt;Several ACIP members pushed back on what they said were omissions in the CDC’s presentations, pointing to individual studies and anecdotes that they said raised questions about neuro-developmental side effects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e064ba" class="body-graf"&gt;Two committee members, Malone and Vicky Pebsworth — both of whom have a history of sharing misinformation about vaccines — said the CDC presentations omitted a &lt;a href="https://nap.nationalacademies.org/read/13164/chapter/10" target="_blank"&gt;2012 report from the Institute of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;. The report said it couldn’t determine whether hepatitis B vaccines were associated with brain inflammation because no studies had properly looked at that research question. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c60234" class="body-graf"&gt;“The absence of data that statistically proves lack of safety does not mean that the product is safe,” Malone said on Friday morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7afc72" class="body-graf"&gt;Pebsworth also raised concerns about CDC data showing irritability or fussiness in some infants who received the hepatitis B vaccine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f59d79" class="body-graf"&gt;“These are not trivial reactions,” Pebsworth said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-cd9b05" class="body-graf"&gt;However, such symptoms are hard to attribute to vaccines because infants can be irritable or fussy regardless of vaccination. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f1ec3e" class="body-graf"&gt;Dr. Cody Meissner, a pediatrician and the only current ACIP member who has previously served on the committee, pushed back on Pebsworth’s concern, noting that irritability or restlessness “are certainly not objective parameters that should be used to assess safety.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f81574" class="body-graf"&gt;He added that no vaccine is 100% safe or effective, but that the committee was meant to decide whether protection from vaccines outweighs any possible risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a2cb0b" class="body-graf"&gt;“When you apply that to a newborn hepatitis B vaccine, I don’t think there’s any question whatsoever that the benefit far outweighs any adverse side effect,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4e4e0a" class="body-graf"&gt;Cases of acute hepatitis B infections among children plummeted after the CDC &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/preview/mmwrhtml/mm5730a3.htm" target="_blank"&gt;began recommending a universal dose&lt;/a&gt; at birth in 1991. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-896a09" class="body-graf"&gt;It's unclear whether ACIP will revisit the subject in the future. If they do, liaisons from the National Foundation for Infectious Diseases, the American College of Physicians and the Society for Adolescent Health and Medicine called on the committee to return to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/media/pdfs/2024/09/ACIP-Evidence-to-Recommendations-Framework-cdc.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;a framework for vaccine recommendations&lt;/a&gt; that has long guided the advisory panel's decisions. The framework considers a vaccine's risk and benefits, whether a recommendation is feasible and how it would impact health equity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3bbc2a" class="body-graf"&gt;Dr. Amy Middleman, a liaison for the Society for Adolescent Health and Medicine, said it's easy to be distracted by conflicting studies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-86845c" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“I would urge the committee to use the methodical, scientific method to weigh the risks and benefits appropriately,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:06:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxQN2J1QU1MSGIzX0o2TWRjQWFFcnBETE9FQ2k0ZmZsWHppeFhPM1J4OUdPTTRBV3YtcWh4akxfNThpM2J2Z3RSZG84a0M5RHRBRzl2Wl9feFByX2M2djhZZUQ1cnRqelhFYjJLNEpGNkRqX1Nzd0lDSm5QMjlfSHFUd2RrYmVQMVljNVhOSjZWdHVYU05RZmVQX0FOcUXSAVZBVV95cUxQNnpaeGFKeFhxLW5aNjd1Q3JHUnA4V0hoM1RFeEU5NTE0dm95dEV4UVJVdUk5QVRDUTRTWHpwYlhDWXRwX05EQzk0Njlsc3Z3Q0QtOEZpZw</guid></item><item><title>观看直播：疾控中心咨询小组讨论COVID-19疫苗风险，与外部专家就流程进行争论- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/cdc-vaccine-advisory-panel-covid-19-hepatitis-b-vaccines/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-update__bodytext"&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;After the tabled hep B vote, some liaison members from top medical organizations shared their agreement for holding off on making changes to the current recommendations. Some also urged more transparency in how decisions will be made on future potential recommendation changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I would urge the committee to use the methodical scientific method to weigh the risks and benefits appropriately," said Dr. Amy Middleman, a liaison for the Society for Adolescent Health and Medicine. She added, "This is important for all vaccine decisions, and this is what I think some of us are really concerned about in terms of the absence of it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ACIP member Retsef Levi said he appreciated the desire to keep scientific methods but took issue with the liaison member's comments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have to say that one thing that puzzles me is that many of the speakers that push for the scientific approach are speaking very confidently in the absence of the gold standard evidence of robust long-term clinical trials against placebo," Levi added, who has been pushing for more research beyond what the CDC has presented during the meetings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When ACIP chair Kulldorff began to move on from the hep B discussion, Dr. Jason Goldman, president of the American College of Physicians, chimed in asking for more explanation and to call out the committee for muting him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That is disrespectful. You want debate and discussion, but you're muting people and silencing them," Goldman said. "Please provide to the public so they can have trust, faith and confidence in vaccination as to what process we are going to be using to properly vet and discuss all future vaccines. … Tell the public how you are going to be analyzing all of these vaccine decisions so we can have confidence in this committee."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kulldorff responded that he previously responded to that comment already before moving on to the next agenda matter.&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/div&gt;
            
            

          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:23:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxQREsycTlXTG5mU0VGcmc3cHE5cjhldDFQTXlaTUFKMExBSl8tb1lDVmVYSnRXa0VoRF96WDRqbVp2ZEFCOXI3TFkxOFdTOThMYXE3WGl1Q0tERkxYckZMTXhfSHBreU1lSTNLb0RlY3F0ZjZfdnNYSE9lX0lYcUl0TXhYQ0o3VmcwTTlOLTVmT1VXbmlTMldXWHRB0gGfAUFVX3lxTE1mWjNOZ3I4MTFjdGFVSzF4dFl2QUx5ZW05NEd2RGEzUjJOQXVCMktJYnVUbW92N09sUGFUMzNWWWtaNDBUUWRjVXM1V3J5N01pd294QnpSNWVRRmt6MWc4ZDl3VGR6Q1EwRHRXQzRHbXE4UEQyVWw4MWRJcE56a3VJbUtXMzEwdjFrcUdOU1JhV0RHb0hxX1padkZJSGR4aw</guid></item><item><title>一家长寿创业公司的创始人表示，在他父亲被诊断患有阿尔茨海默氏症后，他遵循了5个习惯来遏制大脑衰老-商业内幕</title><link>https://www.businessinsider.com/longevity-startup-founder-habits-to-protect-brain-aging-alzheimers-2025-9</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="post-body-content post-story-body-content" data-component-type="post-body-content" data-load-strategy="exclude" data-track-content="" data-post-type="story" data-track-marfeel="post-body-content"&gt;
            
                &lt;p&gt;In his 20s, Dugal Bain-Kim was all about getting swole: lifting big weights, doing long gym sessions, and trying every supplement he could get his hands on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now at 41, he has different priorities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When I was younger, I had more time to take a spray-and-pray approach to my health and wellness," Bain-Kim, CEO and cofounder of the longevity startup Lifeforce,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;told Business Insider. "There's enough going on in life to have to be really efficient and really clear about what my most important goals are."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, Bain-Kim had a stark reality check about his health when his father was diagnosed with &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/facing-early-onset-alzheimers-how-family-copes-with-genetic-fate-2025-2" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Alzheimer's disease&lt;/a&gt;. His condition deteriorated quickly, and he recently died at age 70.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowing his genetic risk, Bain-Kim said he is making some major changes to his routine to protect his brain as much as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's this common misperception that Alzheimer's and dementia are like getting struck by lightning, it's just bad luck and there's nothing to do about it," Bain-Kim said. "Having that information can lead someone to think differently about their life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From microdosing GLP-1 medication to switching up his workouts, here's what he's doing differently that he hopes will move the needle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="feaba09e-864e-405f-9c7e-0f2c25432531" data-toc-id="feaba09e-864e-405f-9c7e-0f2c25432531"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taking creatine: a rising star supplement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="feaba09e-864e-405f-9c7e-0f2c25432531"&gt;While many trendy supplements promise better longevity and brain health, Bain-Kim isn't convinced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In general, people are taking too many supplements," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he believes&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;one standout exception is &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/creatine-demand-soars-muscle-fat-loss-and-brain-power-benefits-2025-6" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;creatine&lt;/a&gt;, a fitness supplement originally sold for muscle-building that may also protect our brains.&lt;/p&gt;
              
              
              &lt;section class="dad-related-posts-component at-inline related-posts" data-component-type="dad-related-posts" data-delay-third-party-scripts="true" data-size="2" data-min-size="2" data-container-index="in_content_recirc_1" data-included-verticals="health" data-placement="inline" data-track-marfeel="dad-related-posts-inline" data-excluded-verticals="bi-video" data-root-margin="250px 0px" data-track-view='{"event":"module_in_view","element_name":"in_content_recirc","subscription_experience":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"in_content_recirc_1"}'&gt;
                  &lt;p class="content-recommendations-title-container"&gt;
                    &lt;h2 class="content-recommendations-title display-xs ignore-typography"&gt;
                      Related stories
                    &lt;/h2&gt;
                  &lt;/p&gt;
            
                &lt;div class="dad-related-posts-container" data-track-click-shared='{"element_name":"in_content_recirc","product_field":"in_content_recirc_1","click_text":"Read next","event":"tout_click"}'&gt;
                    &lt;div class="related-posts-container"&gt;
                      
                      
                      
                      &lt;article data-component-type="tout" data-load-strategy="exclude" class="tout style-loading as-horizontal as-placeholder with-ungrouped-text" data-post-id="post"&gt;
                       
                          
                            &lt;span class="tout-image"&gt;        &lt;/span&gt;
                        
                      
                      
                          &lt;h3 class="tout-title font-weight-garnett-500"&gt;
                            &lt;span class="tout-title-link"&gt;Business Insider tells the innovative stories you want to know&lt;/span&gt;
                          &lt;/h3&gt;
                      
                      
                      
                      &lt;/article&gt;          
                      
                      
                      &lt;article data-component-type="tout" data-load-strategy="exclude" class="tout style-loading as-horizontal as-placeholder with-ungrouped-text" data-post-id="post"&gt;
                       
                          
                            &lt;span class="tout-image"&gt;        &lt;/span&gt;
                        
                      
                      
                          &lt;h3 class="tout-title font-weight-garnett-500"&gt;
                            &lt;span class="tout-title-link"&gt;Business Insider tells the innovative stories you want to know&lt;/span&gt;
                          &lt;/h3&gt;
                      
                      
                      
                      &lt;/article&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
              &lt;/section&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Creatine is a combination of amino acids that our bodies naturally produce to provide energy to tissues like muscle. For years, athletes have used it as a supplement to top up their body's energy&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;reserves to fuel &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/creatine-most-effective-fitness-supplement-science-burn-fat-build-muscle-2024-8" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;muscle growth&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emerging research suggests that creatine could have a similar effect on the brain, giving our brain cells extra resources to fend off cognitive decline and stressors like sleep deprivation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bain-Kim said he takes&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;creatine daily, alongside protein powder and glutamine (for healthy joints).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="70edb653-17d6-4845-aeab-33ac7b6786b7" data-toc-id="70edb653-17d6-4845-aeab-33ac7b6786b7"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microdosing GLP-1 medication&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="70edb653-17d6-4845-aeab-33ac7b6786b7"&gt;Blockbuster drugs like semaglutide (sold as Ozempic and Wegovy) and tirzepatide (Mounjaro, Zepbound) are&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/weight-loss-glp-1-drugs-ozempic-wegovy-mounjaro-effects-future-2023-12" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt; known as GLP-1s&lt;/a&gt;. They work on hormone receptors to manage appetite and metabolism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="70edb653-17d6-4845-aeab-33ac7b6786b7"&gt;But growing research suggests that they could have even further-reaching benefits for the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="70edb653-17d6-4845-aeab-33ac7b6786b7"&gt;Bain-Kim said he was intrigued by new research that the medications could help stave off cognitive decline. Recent studies have shown GLP-1s like semaglutide and liraglutide are linked to a lower risk of dementia and may slow down the process of brain shrinkage and related thinking problems as we age. More clinical trials are ongoing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="70edb653-17d6-4845-aeab-33ac7b6786b7"&gt;That has inspired Bain-Kim to explore microdosing a GLP-1 himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="136c64db-e800-41d4-90d1-16f8ff24fda9" data-toc-id="136c64db-e800-41d4-90d1-16f8ff24fda9"&gt;Doing more Zone 2 cardio&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The evidence is clear: building a strong body can help protect your brain, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bain-Kim still lifts weights but decided to double down on cardio. A healthy heart and blood flow are essential to keeping the brain functioning well over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In particular, exercise like jogging or biking at a lower heart rate (known as &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/what-is-zone-2-cardio-exercise-training-benefits-2023-10" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Zone 2&lt;/a&gt;) can help build a stronger, healthier heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bain-Kim said he's added two sessions a week of light cardio exercise to his routine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To round out his weekly exercise, he also plays a match of competitive pickleball regularly, as higher-intensity activity helps to boost &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/vo2-max-explained-what-is-good-how-improve-2024-3" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;VO2 max for better fitness and longevity&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="cda4a1f1-7076-4cfd-bfdb-ea0e498fb5ac" data-toc-id="cda4a1f1-7076-4cfd-bfdb-ea0e498fb5ac"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Switching to a MIND diet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bain-Kim said he's optimizing his diet for cognitive health, tweaking his already-healthy &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/mediterranean-diet-best-healthy-eating-longevity-rankings-2025-1" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt; with even more emphasis on brain-protecting foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His new routine is based on the &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/mind-diet-longevity-brain-health-ways-to-follow-2024-2" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;MIND diet&lt;/a&gt;, which Harvard researchers developed to help prevent cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It emphasizes nutrients like fiber and healthy fats such as omega-3s that support the brain, through a weekly goal of:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;6 (or more) servings of leafy greens&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5 servings of nuts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;4 servings of beans&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 servings of berries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1+ serving of fatty fish like salmon, mackerel, or sardines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Olive oil as your primary cooking oil&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 id="e0b8de74-6ada-4cd3-abf3-24c30c21376f" data-toc-id="e0b8de74-6ada-4cd3-abf3-24c30c21376f"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Making sleep a priority&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may not be flashy, but a good night's sleep is the cornerstone of Bain-Kim's daily routine to protect his brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said his personal sweet spot for peak health and performance is about seven hours and 45 minutes of quality sleep, not just time in bed. Neuroscientists recommend between &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/guides/health/how-much-sleep-do-you-need" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;seven and nine hours of sleep&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Everyone appreciates a good night's sleep, but for me that's now core to my strategy because of the brain protection benefits of getting enough sleep," Bain-Kim said. "It's become the non-negotiable for me."&lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            &lt;/section&gt;
            
            
            
            
              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Business Insider</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:08:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxNdFJVSkVKYzZUOW0xQkJiVGVwUnVyQWFGcW5sT2tqR2Rxd0lCS3gyS2VVdUd0Q3dCUFFKd2hwVXBldVFQckFfQXB3Ulp1WDQtdXZZRkhIODRnc2lteFp3RURaRE9jX1U4MVRWVUFYd2dtS2c2bTdfZUtnMkNvXzExNVhxc1NDM0lDQ05SVzlpdmtwQU5jeVBxQ2oyMmpzaERhTDN5S1lDWW0</guid></item></channel></rss>