<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>每周玩游戏超过10小时？你一定会喜欢阅读这篇文章- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/gaming-more-than-10-hours-a-week-youll-want-to-read-this-2000711944</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl prose-science dark:prose-science"&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;We’ve got great news for everyone who’s ever been kept awake until the wee hours of the morning by a family member or housemate screaming obscenities at their monitor while playing video games. Your lectures about how playing video games for so long isn’t healthy now have new scientific justification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0899900725003685?via%3Dihub"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt; published earlier this month in the journal Nutrition found an association between gaming more than 10 hours a week and poor diet quality, higher body mass, and lower sleep quality. The research suggests that playing video games isn’t the main problem, but overdoing the amount of time dedicated to it, according to Mario Siervo, a co-author of the study from the Curtin School of Population Health.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;Hardcore gaming might impact health&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;“What stood out was students gaming up to 10 hours a week all looked very similar in terms of diet, sleep and body weight,” he said in a Curtin University &lt;a href="https://www.curtin.edu.au/news/media-release/study-reveals-how-many-hours-of-video-games-per-week-might-be-too-many/"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt;. “The real differences emerged in those gaming more than 10 hours a week, who showed clear divergence from the rest of the sample.”&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Siervo and his coworkers worked with over 300 students from Australian universities who self-reported how much time they spent gaming per week. Based on this information, the team organized them into three categories—low gamers (0 to 5 hours of gaming per week), moderate gamers (5 to 10 hours per week), and high gamers (more than 10 hours per week).&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Low and moderate gamers described similar health statuses, which were significantly worse for high gamers. For example, the researchers noted lower diet quality for high gamers. Heavy gamers were more likely to be obese, with a median BMI of 26.3. By comparison, low and moderate gamers had healthier averages of 22.2 and 22.8, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“Each additional hour of gaming per week was linked to a decline in diet quality, even after accounting for stress, physical activity and other lifestyle factors,” Siervo explained.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Poor sleep quality&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you’re trying to argue against your household gamer logging 10 hours a week, sleep quality might be your strongest case. In the study, all three categories reported poor sleep quality overall, though moderate and high gamers had lower scores than low gamers. The study found an important association between gaming hours and sleep disruption.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“This study doesn’t prove gaming causes these issues, but it shows a clear pattern that excessive gaming may be linked to an increase in health risk factors,” Siervo clarified. “Our data suggests low and moderate gaming is generally fine, but excessive gaming may crowd out healthy habits such as eating a balanced diet, sleeping properly and staying active.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To which he added: “Because university habits often follow people into adulthood, healthier routines such as taking breaks from gaming, avoiding playing games late at night and choosing healthier snacks may help improve their overall wellbeing.”&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:35:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxQdVYwbE1wbjdQVERYTHJrU2lHWXJCeW50ajk4cHpwZWlUZ1JneTQ3UFFtV1EwRzI0U2d0TnBJWXlMek1NbklFY2Jjek5IN3FhRUlnb2JneUtSa2x4WU1abEZHalJxLTRyaEZtZkEzUEJKU2l3TGJMNHQyWW5WSm1kVkttaUxxYlNiaXZfZzkwLXU</guid></item><item><title>美国麻疹疫情创纪录的一年。这可能是致命卷土重来的开始- KSL新闻</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51435585/us-had-record-breaking-year-for-measles-it-may-be-the-start-of-a-deadly-comeback</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;DALLAS — Tuesday marks one year since a measles outbreak started in west Texas, and there have been new cases in the United States each week since.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Texas reported more than 760 cases — and the deaths of two children – before declaring the outbreak over in August. It was the largest outbreak the US had seen in decades, and since then, other large outbreaks — one in the upstate region of South Carolina and another on the border of Utah and Arizona — have amassed hundreds of cases each and continue to expand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first two weeks of 2026 have been some of the worst yet, with exposures reported at schools, churches, restaurants, shops, airports and more. The continuous spread of measles over the past year leaves the US at risk of losing elimination status, which the country has held since 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is startling, because just a few years ago, measles was very rare in the United States," said Dr. Caitlin Rivers, ​an epidemiologist and director of the Center for Outbreak Response Innovation at the Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Now we're seeing in a single week what we might have seen in an average year," she said. "There's been a real shift in the presence of this preventable disease in our life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether that balance can shift back depends on how quickly the US can improve vaccination coverage, experts say – which, in many ways, has become an uphill battle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US reported more than 2,200 confirmed measles cases in 2025 — significantly more than there have been in any year since measles was declared eliminated in the US in 2000. At least ​171 measles cases have been reported in the first two weeks of 2026, which is nearly as many as the average annual total in those 25 years since elimination in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The vast majority of cases — more than 95% — have been in people who had not been vaccinated with the recommended two doses of the measles-mumps-rubella (MMR) vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts fear that the situation may have to get much worse before it gets better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's particularly devastating, they say, because the illnesses and deaths they foresee are almost entirely preventable with the help of vaccines — but lagging coverage has left many vulnerable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's not clear yet whether the US will maintain its measles elimination status. In April, the Pan American Health Organization, part of the World Health Organization, will formally make the determination. The decision will require a detailed review of epidemiological and laboratory evidence to understand patterns of measles spread over the past year — including whether more recent outbreaks are linked to the Texas outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But experts say that formally losing measles elimination status would be a symptom of more deeply rooted issues, particularly challenges with vaccination that have been building for many years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's face it, whether we lose elimination status or not in spring, is our public health system actually doing well?" said Dr. Demetre Daskalakis, former director of the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention's National Center for Immunization and Respiratory Diseases, who resigned in protest last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Measles elimination is a vital sign of our public health system. That public health system is blue in the ICU," he said. "I don't need to check its pulse to know [it's not doing well]. I know the answer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A record share of U.S. kindergartners had an exemption for a required vaccination last school year, according to data from the CDC, marking the fifth year in a row that coverage with the MMR vaccine was below the federal target of 95%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC says that the increase in vaccine exemptions may be "due to an increase in vaccine hesitancy." A recent &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/schoolvaxview/pubs-resources/parental-attitudes-toward-vaccination-requirements.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;survey&lt;/a&gt; of parents conducted by the agency found that most supported vaccine requirements to attend school. But among those seeking an exemption, the most commonly reported reason – cited more than a third of the time – was a philosophical or personal belief objection to vaccination. Difficulty meeting school requirements by the deadline was also reported as a reason for exemption by about 23% of parents. Medical reasons were cited by more than a quarter of parents, but the CDC said that might include parents who consider concerns about vaccine safety or side effects as a "medical" reason to request an exemption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Vaccines are a victim of their own success. It's not just that we eliminated measles. I think we eliminated the memory of measles," said Dr. Paul Offit, director of the Vaccine Education Center at the Children's Hospital of Philadelphia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Offit remembers speaking with &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC557162/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Maurice Hilleman&lt;/a&gt;, a microbiologist who developed the MMR vaccine and dozens of others, just months before Hilleman's death in 2005. Measles cases had reached a record low in 2004 but were starting to trend up again, just a few years after the US had achieved elimination following a long and hard-fought battle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I asked him, 'Do you think that we can educate people about the importance of the vaccine, about the serious nature of this disease, or does the virus have to come back?" Offit said. He said there was a tear in his eye when he replied that the virus was going to have to come back to teach that lesson.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That was an enormous defeat for him," Offit said. "It's an enormous defeat for us to once again see children be exposed to something that could kill them — and did kill them – in this country, when that was completely unnecessary."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it seems more and more that the virus isn't necessarily doing that, educating either, Offit said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were three deaths from measles last year — as many as there had been over the past 25 years combined — yet it's been a struggle to increase vaccination rates, even in communities that experienced outbreaks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The South Carolina health department has offered a mobile vaccination clinic since the early weeks of the outbreak in the upstate region of the state, but state epidemiologist Dr. Linda Bell has said that uptake has been "disappointing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles outbreaks tend to occur in under-vaccinated pockets of the U.S., often in tight-knit communities, such as those with certain religious beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL News</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:25:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxNYzgxRTVlbzVNOWlUaTBxZm5yN0NCMjZPcnM5RDF6Y1ZPVEN1NmMwMEd0dlMxNzBvNE1xNmljaFZqVl9HbnAxUDY4VjhIeDZ2UkNYWTd6X0RDOFZCX2NpelU2U0pOR3hVUkxiZWEzekZZQUF5V19YOXhqN2gyZXJfUW9XRlBOZFdCZ2hJRFdVNUFYSWFSY1FVNmtyYUNLYmEzWVROVV9TREdHYWpESkEwLWtVandkMTd5</guid></item><item><title>肠道检查：家庭微生物组测试是“破坏健康”的方法还是简单的浪费？ |抗病毒-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2026/jan/20/at-home-microbiome-gut-tests-health</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;F&lt;/span&gt;or a few hundred dollars you can put your poo in an envelope and post it off to a laboratory. In return you’ll get a report (sometimes generated by AI) outlining your food sensitivities, metabolic fitness, and what pathogens or fungi you’re harbouring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;These at-home gut microbiome tests or “GI mapping” kits are frequently promoted by influencers as a way to “hack your health” and “take control” through analysing some of the trillions of organisms that live in your digestive tract.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But how much can an at-home gut test really tell you, and are they actually worth doing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="even-experts-struggle-to-interpret-at-home-microbiome-tests" class="dcr-12pc8kk"&gt;Even experts struggle to interpret at-home microbiome tests&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Rupert Leong, a gastroenterologist and microbiome researcher based at Macquarie university hospital, is increasingly seeing patients alarmed by gut microbiome reports they don’t understand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Leong said depending on what is being analysed, gut microbiome testing can be “very powerful and accurate” in detecting microbial markers. But interpreting what those markers mean for an individual remains a major challenge, and different labs vary in their methodology, leading to differing results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We are still in the infancy of understanding how to interpret them,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="bc737553-b5e0-4164-bf4f-bcdaf3c83cde" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":7,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Crunch time: are freeze-dried fruit and veg actually healthy to eat or just chips in a different form? | Antiviral","elementId":"bc737553-b5e0-4164-bf4f-bcdaf3c83cde","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2025/dec/24/freeze-dried-fruit-veg-healthy-food-nutrition-benefits"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":8,"display":0,"theme":1},"isInStarRatingVariant":false}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If a gut microbiome test is ordered by a specialist doctor or accredited dietitian with a clear clinical reason, sent to a reputable lab, and interpreted by someone trained to make sense of the results, it can be genuinely helpful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Leong recently saw a patient with inflammatory bowel disease and rectal bleeding who had already undergone standard medical tests. The microbiome results, in that case, helped confirm dietary issues and guide further treatment once simple and important issues had been ruled out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But these cases are the exception, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A healthy mix of organisms in one person could be problematic in another; “The same organism has different species and acts differently in different individuals,” Leong said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It means for the vast majority of people who order these tests online, and who may be curious about their gut health or wondering about their symptoms or foods to avoid, “there are no translatable benefits” to ordering a test, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Temporary dietary changes, medications or illness could all affect the results, and what those results actually mean for an individual’s health outcomes isn’t well understood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="false-alarms-can-cause-distress" class="dcr-12pc8kk"&gt;False alarms can cause distress&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;One of Leong’s patients who took a commercial home test came to him panicking about bowel cancer after the report suggested she had certain inflammatory markers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Leong said a colonoscopy remains the definitive test to investigate bowel polyps and cancers. The free home bowel screening test issued by the Australian government, which looks for hidden blood in stool, is an evidence-based way to detect early warning signs of bowel cancer and may prompt follow-up testing, including a colonoscopy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;And while some home gut microbiome tests claim to offer insights into metabolism or inflammation, “very few experts can use these results appropriately at present,” Leong said, including gastroenterologists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;This is because clinicians aren’t trained to interpret the complex outputs the tests generate, the science is still developing, and there aren’t clear guidelines on what to do with the information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="the-illusion-of-control" class="dcr-12pc8kk"&gt;The illusion of control&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;At-home microbiome tests are spruiked by online influencers as a way of empowering people who want more insights into their health. But Dr Erica Zurawski, an assistant professor in environmental studies, said this encourages consumers to internalise health responsibility while giving their personal data to large for-profit companies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="0e4c8499-0dfd-4816-88f0-4e4e42cec81b" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":21,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"More kissing, less kimchi: seven surprising ways to boost your gut health","elementId":"0e4c8499-0dfd-4816-88f0-4e4e42cec81b","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2025/sep/19/kimchi-kissing-seven-surprising-ways-boost-gut-health"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":8,"display":0,"theme":1},"isInStarRatingVariant":false}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Her research &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41157986/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;has examined how&lt;/a&gt; direct‑to‑consumer microbiomeare often pitched “as a wholesale solution to myriad health issues when, in fact, they oversimplify the complexity of the inner workings of the gut, its malleability, and the impact external factors have on it,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It makes people feel they are doing something wrong, “while the underlying issues that cause poor gut health,” including the influence of harmful industries and government policies, are “side-stepped,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41599-025-06260-2" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;complexity gets smoothed over and ignored&lt;/a&gt; … testing kits fail to account for things such as stress, pollution, or access to meaningful health care to address adjacent health issues.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="back-to-basics" class="dcr-12pc8kk"&gt;Back to basics&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;So how can you actually support gut health?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Leong says: “A diverse diet, high in fibre” is a sensible place to start.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Zurawski adds that governments have a responsibility to address the broader social and environmental conditions that influence gut health, including poverty, housing, pollution, and access to affordable, nutritious food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If you are experiencing gut symptoms or concerns, Leong recommends seeing a qualified dietitian or GP before jumping to expensive, at-home testing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="448e717d-2246-4ec6-8079-29236eb96724" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.CalloutBlockElementV2" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="CalloutBlockComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"callout":{"description":"&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What health trend&amp;amp;nbsp;do you want examined?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;","prompt":"Share your experience","displayOnSensitive":true,"elementId":"448e717d-2246-4ec6-8079-29236eb96724","title":"Share your experience","isNonCollapsible":false,"formFields":[{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.CalloutFormFieldBase","name":"what_is_your_namepseudonym","id":"172730135","hideLabel":false,"label":"What is your name/pseudonym?","hidden":false,"type":"text","required":false},{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.CalloutFormFieldBase","name":"what_news_story_or_health_information_being_shared_on_social_media_have_you_seen_that_youd_like_us_to_examine","id":"172730137","hideLabel":false,"label":"What news story or health information being shared on social media have you seen that you’d like us to examine","hidden":false,"type":"textarea","required":true},{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.CalloutFormFieldBase","name":"do_you_have_a_link_to_an_example_you_can_share","id":"173258657","hideLabel":false,"label":"Do you have a link to an example you can share?","hidden":false,"type":"text","required":false},{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.CalloutFormFieldRadio","name":"can_we_publish_your_response","options":[{"label":"Yes, entirely","value":"Yes, entirely"},{"label":"Yes, but contact me first","value":"Yes, but contact me first"},{"label":"Yes, but please keep me anonymous","value":"Yes, but please keep me anonymous"},{"label":"No, this is information only","value":"No, this is information only"}],"id":"172730143","hideLabel":false,"label":"Can we publish your response?","hidden":false,"type":"radio","required":true},{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.CalloutFormFieldBase","name":"email_address","description":"Your contact details are helpful so we can contact you for more information. They will only be seen by the Guardian.","id":"172730145","hideLabel":false,"label":"Email address","hidden":false,"type":"text","required":false},{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.CalloutFormFieldBase","name":"phone_number","description":"Your contact details are helpful so we can contact you for more information. They will only be seen by the Guardian.","id":"173258668","hideLabel":false,"label":"Phone number","hidden":false,"type":"text","required":false}],"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.CalloutBlockElementV2","tagName":"aus-callout-antiviral","activeFrom":1725148800000,"id":"bb8fc08d-d44b-4ccf-9d6c-c259975cf0a5","calloutsUrl":"https://callouts.guardianapis.com/formstack-campaign/submit","formId":5915696},"pageId":"commentisfree/2026/jan/20/at-home-microbiome-gut-tests-health"}'&gt;&lt;div data-gu-name="callout"&gt;&lt;aside&gt;&lt;div id="expander-5915696 form" class="dcr-16jslbg"&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" class="expander__checkbox dcr-1acea34" id="expander-checkbox-5915696 form" aria-label="Expand 5915696 form"&gt;&lt;div class="expander__collapsible-body dcr-7fyrb" id="expander-5915696 form__collapsible-body" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;div id="5915696"&gt;&lt;div class="dcr-sdk583"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-qc5pzg"&gt;Share your experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 class="dcr-1qoquav"&gt;Share your experience&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;div class="dcr-1r3uzz1"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;What health trend do you want examined?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div role="tabpanel" id="form-tab" aria-labelledby="form" class="dcr-1m8xpey"&gt;&lt;div class="dcr-1af7plv"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your responses, which can be anonymous, are secure as the form is encrypted and only the Guardian has access to your contributions. We will only use the data you provide us for the purpose of the feature and we will delete any personal data when we no longer require it for this purpose. For alternative ways to get in touch securely please see our &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://www.theguardian.com/tips"&gt;tips guide&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-171s16m"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-191xdls"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;label aria-hidden="true" for="expander-checkbox-5915696 form" class="dcr-1oxs02n"&gt;&lt;span id="svgplus" class="dcr-12dqv06"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="-3 -3 30 30" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" focusable="false" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="m10.8 13.2.425 9.8h1.525l.45-9.8 9.8-.45v-1.525l-9.8-.425-.45-9.8h-1.525l-.425 9.8-9.8.425v1.525z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Show more&lt;/label&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxPcE9NWXRYNUoySFViaktqQmNJZWJNSjM2Q2xIc3Fjdzl3NWY0Y2NkMXVma1A0WjluN2d6RHYzcU9IajBpby04bFVvcXFFT21GbFRWaHBrOGktZmhsb3ViMmJ1NlhtWnZSTTU1RHdFVnI3eG9DdHlONUdSVW1ZbEJXSW5oWWxEZm5JOVB6WWx4NG1SVnM</guid></item><item><title>晒伤的主要原因终于揭晓，这不是我们一直相信的原因-银河日报</title><link>https://dailygalaxy.com/2026/01/sunburn-cause-finally-discovered-rna-damage-not-dna/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content dynamic-entry-content" itemprop="text"&gt;
			
&lt;p&gt;Scientific consensus on the biological mechanisms underpinning &lt;strong&gt;sunburn&lt;/strong&gt; has remained largely unchanged for decades. The prevailing view posited that &lt;strong&gt;ultraviolet (UV) radiation&lt;/strong&gt; induces DNA mutations in skin cells, triggering inflammatory responses and initiating cell death to prevent carcinogenesis. This framework has shaped dermatological education, cancer research funding priorities, and public health messaging across high-UV index regions.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers from the &lt;a href="https://www.ku.dk/en" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;University of Copenhagen&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.ntu.edu.sg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nanyang Technological University (NTU Singapore)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; identified a different primary trigger. Through controlled experiments involving both murine and human epidermal models, the study demonstrated that the &lt;strong&gt;initial cellular response to UVB exposure is governed by RNA damage&lt;/strong&gt;, not DNA lesions. This distinction alters the molecular understanding of &lt;strong&gt;cutaneous inflammation&lt;/strong&gt; and raises new questions about the mechanisms of UV-induced cell signaling.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/New-research-shows-that-UV-B-exposure-damages-RNA-not-DNA.jpg.webp" alt="Close Up,of,a,sunburn,marks,on,a,woman's,back" class="wp-image-117966" srcset="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/New-research-shows-that-UV-B-exposure-damages-RNA-not-DNA.jpg.webp 1000w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/New-research-shows-that-UV-B-exposure-damages-RNA-not-DNA-420x280.jpg.webp 420w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/New-research-shows-that-UV-B-exposure-damages-RNA-not-DNA-520x347.jpg.webp 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;New research shows that UV-B exposure damages RNA, not DNA, triggering an early skin inflammation response via ZAKα and ribosomal stress pathways. Credit: Shutterstock&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The findings, published in &lt;a href="https://linkinghub.elsevier.com/retrieve/pii/S1097276524008840" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Molecular Cell&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, have attracted growing attention from &lt;strong&gt;biomedical regulatory agencies&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;skin disease researchers&lt;/strong&gt; exploring alternative models of &lt;strong&gt;UV damage signaling&lt;/strong&gt;. In mouse models lacking the ZAK alpha kinase gene, a key regulator in ribosomal stress detection, typical UV-induced responses such as keratinocyte death and epidermal swelling were suppressed. This suggests that ZAK alpha’s activation by &lt;strong&gt;damaged messenger RNA (mRNA)&lt;/strong&gt; precedes and may override DNA-dependent pathways.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;RNA Damage as the Signal Origin&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The core mechanism centers on what researchers described as the &lt;strong&gt;ribotoxic stress response (RSR)&lt;/strong&gt;. Upon UVB exposure, damaged mRNA triggers ZAK alpha to initiate inflammatory signaling and programmed cell death. “We found that the first thing the cells respond to after being exposed to UV radiation is damage to the RNA,” said Simon Bekker-Jensen, professor of molecular medicine at the University of Copenhagen, “and that this is what triggers cell death and inflammation of the skin.”&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/ZAK-knockout-mice-1200x1200.jpeg.webp" alt="Zak Knockout Mice" class="wp-image-117964" srcset="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/ZAK-knockout-mice-scaled.jpeg.webp 1200w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/ZAK-knockout-mice-420x420.jpeg.webp 420w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/ZAK-knockout-mice-160x160.jpeg.webp 160w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/ZAK-knockout-mice-520x520.jpeg.webp 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;RNA damage from UV-B activates ZAKα, triggering a stress response in skin cells. The pathway leads to cytokine production, cell death (via JNK and p38), and inflammation. In mouse models, wild-type mice showed typical sunburn responses—immune cell infiltration and epidermal thickening—while ZAKα knockout mice did not, confirming ZAKα’s key role in mediating UV-induced skin inflammation. Credit: Molecular Cell Journal&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;In knockout mice lacking the &lt;strong&gt;ZAK gene&lt;/strong&gt;, those acute inflammatory markers were notably absent. In vitro tests using cultured human keratinocytes revealed the same pathway activation: &lt;strong&gt;RNA damage&lt;/strong&gt; activated pyroptotic and apoptotic death via the &lt;strong&gt;p38&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;JNK&lt;/strong&gt; signaling routes, respectively. This dual-pathway activation reinforces the premise that ZAK alpha governs &lt;strong&gt;early UV stress responses&lt;/strong&gt; through cytoplasmic signals rather than nuclear genome surveillance.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Friction Point: Diagnostic, Therapeutic, and Textbook Realignment&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The immediate friction point is conceptual and infrastructural. &lt;strong&gt;Sunscreen formulations&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;UV protection protocols&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;dermatological interventions&lt;/strong&gt; have historically been modeled around DNA-centric assumptions. The shift toward RNA-first mechanisms compels a reevaluation of &lt;strong&gt;photoimmunology models&lt;/strong&gt;, particularly for inflammatory conditions such as &lt;strong&gt;polymorphic light eruption&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;UV-aggravated eczema&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, ZAK alpha’s role as a molecular sentinel introduces both &lt;strong&gt;therapeutic targets&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;diagnostic markers&lt;/strong&gt;. Potential pharmaceutical interventions that modulate the RSR pathway may offer new methods for &lt;strong&gt;controlling UV-induced skin inflammation&lt;/strong&gt;, independent of mutagenic &lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2025/08/chernobyls-dogs-are-transforming-at-record-speed-what-radiation-is-really-doing-to-their-dna/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="97247" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;DNA repair processes&lt;/a&gt;. However, these applications remain theoretical; as of January 2026, no ZAK alpha inhibitors have entered clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/The-discovery-challenges-long-standing-DNA-focused-models-of-sunburn.jpg.webp" alt="Woman's,back,skin,hurt,from,sun,burn.,burn,from,the" class="wp-image-117968" srcset="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/The-discovery-challenges-long-standing-DNA-focused-models-of-sunburn.jpg.webp 1000w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/The-discovery-challenges-long-standing-DNA-focused-models-of-sunburn-420x280.jpg.webp 420w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/The-discovery-challenges-long-standing-DNA-focused-models-of-sunburn-520x347.jpg.webp 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The discovery challenges long-standing DNA-focused models of sunburn, with implications for dermatology education, drug development, and clinical treatment of UV-related inflammation. Credit: Shutterstock&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The research, conducted by faculty at the &lt;a href="https://researchprofiles.ku.dk/en/organisations/institut-for-cellul%C3%A6r-og-molekyl%C3%A6r-medicin" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Department of Cellular and Molecular Medicine&lt;/a&gt; at the University of Copenhagen, in collaboration with NTU’s &lt;em&gt;Lee Kong Chian School of Medicine&lt;/em&gt;, indicates a broader need for academic and medical reassessment. Assistant Professor Anna Constance Vind, a co-author of the study, noted, “This new knowledge turns things upside down. I think most people associate sunburn with DNA damage; it is established knowledge.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Educational and clinical materials reliant on DNA-centric inflammation models will likely need revision to include the role of RNA and ribosomal stress pathways. Key areas of impact include:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Medical curricula&lt;/strong&gt; covering dermatology, cell signaling, and photobiology&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Textbooks and training programs&lt;/strong&gt; for dermatologists and general practitioners&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clinical diagnostics&lt;/strong&gt; involving inflammatory skin responses to UV&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drug discovery pipelines&lt;/strong&gt; targeting early UV damage detection and response&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Whether this RNA-centric model applies uniformly across skin types, UV spectrum ranges, and environmental exposure durations remains under investigation. The interaction between &lt;strong&gt;long-term DNA mutations&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;acute RNA signaling&lt;/strong&gt; is also unresolved; they may operate on separate timelines, with independent but complementary biological effects.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Daily Galaxy</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxOZnR5OEthX3lWLUVRMDZoTXloelZ3ejM5cS1ETHZmTDVBaURNZjlWel9iZXdpdnNENzFBSzV6RV9NNnNCNERPS2pBM2x3aThhOHhSajB4QWtUNHYyenhqQVVtVlFkaDRkTWRoNVp0bEtMU0ZUYWlJcWxqRHRvWjBNZWI1dGhqY2xfMzQzeg</guid></item><item><title>怀孕期间加州野火烟雾暴露与儿童自闭症风险有关- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/california-wildfire-smoke-pregnancy-autism-risk-children-rcna254429</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-aee60a" class="body-graf"&gt;Pregnant women's exposure to wildfire smoke — particularly in the third trimester — may increase the risk of autism in their children, according to new research, which looked at hundreds of thousands of births in Southern California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b226b7" class="body-graf"&gt;The study, published Tuesday in the journal Environmental Science &amp;amp; Technology, is the first to examine a potential link between prenatal wildfire smoke exposure and autism. &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/autism-air-pollution-new-study-bolsters-suspected-link-n270331" target="_blank"&gt;Earlier research&lt;/a&gt; has suggested that pregnant women's exposure to air pollution more broadly, including smog spewed by vehicles, smoke stacks and lead, may be linked to the developmental disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-88c12b" class="body-graf"&gt;The new research focused on exposures to PM 2.5, tiny particles in wildfire smoke that can lodge deep in the lungs and enter the bloodstream, which has raised major health concerns. To estimate smoke exposure, researchers used a model to estimate levels of PM 2.5 at each individual’s home address during their pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a650f6" class="body-graf"&gt;“This paper supports other scientific research that links prenatal exposure to air pollution, particularly PM 2.5 to autism,” said Alycia Halladay, chief science officer at the nonprofit Autism Science Foundation, who was not involved in the study. “The size of the risk is not huge, but it is consistent with other research and adds to a body of scientific literature linking air pollution and autism.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-44f120" class="body-graf"&gt;“Both autism and wildfires are on the rise, and this study is just the beginning of investigating links between the two,” said senior study author Mostafijur Rahman, an assistant professor of environmental health sciences at Tulane University’s Celia Scott Weatherhead School of Public Health and Tropical Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-50e48b" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How big is the risk?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-31960f" class="body-graf"&gt;The study analyzed health records of more than 200,000 births in Southern California from 2006 through 2014. California, the researchers said, leads the country in both yearly acres burned by wildfire and rates of childhood autism diagnoses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-dc4040" class="body-graf"&gt;The increased risk was strongest when mothers were exposed to wildfire smoke during the third trimester (the last three months of pregnancy), especially during stretches of multiple smoky days, rather than from overall average pollution levels alone, the study found. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b56af5" class="body-graf"&gt;The risk of autism diagnosis was about 10% higher for children whose mothers experienced 1 to 5 smokey days in the third trimester, 12% higher with 6 to 10 days and 23% higher with more than 10 days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-afa41f" class="body-graf"&gt;The association was clearest among women who didn’t change residences during pregnancy, suggesting that sustained exposure in the same location — not just occasional smoke — may play an important role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8b0fed" class="body-graf"&gt;The study, however, doesn’t explain why wildfire smoke may increase autism risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1226a9" class="body-graf"&gt;Rahman said wildfire smoke is quite different from other pollutants, such as traffic pollutants, that people are exposed to on an almost everyday basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a687f2" class="body-graf"&gt;“Wildfire smoke has a unique chemical composition,” he said, “including higher levels of carbon compounds, metal, toxic byproducts, and it tends to occur in intense and short term spikes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1ec2e6" class="body-graf"&gt;The third trimester is a critical period in a fetus’s development, said lead study author David Luglio, a post-doctoral fellow with the Celia Scott Weatherhead School.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e932f4" class="body-graf"&gt;“In terms of the brain, and the late trimester, this is when the brain really grows in size and develops its main centers,” he said. He added that the findings shouldn’t cause alarm, noting that autism isn’t limited to environmental factors, but is also believed to have a strong genetic component.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b698aa" class="body-graf"&gt;Halladay said exposure to high levels of PM 2.5 have already been linked to lower birthweight, higher levels of preterm births, asthma and obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-581c97" class="body-graf"&gt;“So close monitoring, as well as mitigation of air pollution, should be a priority for regulatory agencies going forward,” she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-3c3570" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More research is needed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0b1b46" class="body-graf"&gt;Autism spectrum disorder — characterized by challenges with social and communication skills and by repetitive behaviors — affects 1 in 31 school-aged children in the United States, according to &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/autism-rates-up-cdc-report-2025-rfk-jr-rcna201305" target="_blank"&gt;the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-2cb9dd" class="body-graf"&gt;The disorder is believed to be “multifactorial,” said Dr. Akhgar Ghassabian, an associate professor of pediatrics and population health at the NYU Grossman School of Medicine, with several environmental factors “shown to be involved, particularly if these environmental exposures happen during early life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b37db5" class="body-graf"&gt;Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., with the backing of President Donald Trump, has made autism a high-profile research priority, saying that health officials want to better understand the condition’s “root causes,” including potential environmental causes, such as air pollution, chemicals and medicine. Kennedy has also promoted unproven treatments, &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/trump-touted-drug-leucovorin-autism-families-already-tried-rcna233291" target="_blank"&gt;including leucovorin&lt;/a&gt;, a synthetic form of vitamin B9 or folate, which the body needs to make healthy blood cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9953b7" class="body-graf"&gt;In September, Trump claimed without new evidence that acetaminophen — the active ingredient in the pain reliever Tylenol — was a cause of autism, a statement that drew intense pushback from OB-GYNs, autism advocacy groups and international health organizations, like the World Health Organization. A large new analysis found &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/tylenol-pregnancy-safe-no-link-autism-trump-kennedy-rcna253662" target="_blank"&gt;no link between acetaminophen and autism&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-cc643c" class="body-graf"&gt;David Mandell, a psychiatry professor at the University of Pennsylvania, said the idea that wildfire smoke exposure could raise autism risk is broadly consistent with previous research linking air pollution exposure during the mother's pregnancy to poorer neurodevelopmental outcomes in children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d5490c" class="body-graf"&gt;But he said that he was cautious about how the study’s findings were interpreted, noting that the observed effects were small and that the highest exposure group did not show a clear increase in risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8f8a9e" class="body-graf"&gt;“They do see a more elevated risk at the second-highest exposure level in the third trimester among nonmovers, but not at the highest exposure level,” Mandell said. “This lack of a dose response makes me skeptical about the findings. I’d definitely want to see a replication before I put a lot of stock in it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-ce563b" class="body-graf"&gt;The authors note the study has limitations: Exposure estimates were based on outdoor air, and researchers don’t know how much smoke people were exposed to indoors, or whether they used air filters, wore masks or altered their behavior during a wildfire event. Rahman said further studies are still needed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e4babe" class="body-graf"&gt;The findings, he said, “reinforce the importance of minimizing smoke exposure during a wildfire event when possible and following the public health guidance.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-413477" class="body-graf"&gt;Mandell said that he hopes an administration "truly interested in improving child outcomes would strengthen" the Environmental Protection Agency and strengthen the Federal Emergency Management Agency "to reduce pollution and help families cope.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9d2c20" class="body-graf"&gt;“This administration seems to be going in the absolute opposite direction,” he said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-06a458" class="body-graf"&gt;Rahman said he is also curious whether prevention — such as masks or air purifiers — may reduce the risk seen in the study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-98c81a" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“Wildfire smoke is a potentially preventable environmental exposure,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:00:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxNWi1pUkV5ZEI2WUtsR0tFYTJ2V2dtekZWd3dNb0tiaTJFbHl6N2FINHZFbWR6MDhRc2psTEE1XzJJcVBuemxKODhrcWlSblFnc2F6ZUVKMnlCc25nTzh3eVFVYS1URFZNV01tRnBkNFZTc2c5cnJteS00YldJdTR3Q0JtaEJQQl9yRjhrUG16bG5kT1g2RmN4c2lMVUkzczFWY3gycmpvTzlHNDNURXhF</guid></item><item><title>美国在麻疹方面创下了破纪录的一年。这可能是致命卷土重来的开始- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/20/health/us-measles-outbreak-one-year</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljntw200003b6sk8birl15@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Tuesday marks one year since a measles outbreak started in West Texas, and there have been new cases in the United States each week since.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmklkveu400063b6s3rznp2io@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Texas reported more than 760 cases — and the deaths of two children – before declaring the &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/18/health/texas-measles-outbreak-declared-over"&gt;outbreak over&lt;/a&gt; in August. It was the largest outbreak the US had seen in decades, and since then, other large outbreaks — one in the upstate region of &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/08/health/south-carolina-measles-outbreak-challenges"&gt;South Carolina&lt;/a&gt; and another on the border of Utah and Arizona — have amassed hundreds of cases each and continue to expand.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmklmnmms00003b6p6514ffko@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The first two weeks of 2026 have been some of the worst yet, with &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/15/health/measles-exposure-what-to-do-wellness"&gt;exposures&lt;/a&gt; reported at schools, churches, restaurants, shops, airports and more. The continuous spread of measles over the past year leaves the US at &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/09/health/measles-elimination-investigation"&gt;risk of losing elimination status&lt;/a&gt;, which the country has held since 2000.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmklleh3k00023b6se27yx7ym@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It is startling, because just a few years ago measles was very rare in the United States,” said Dr. Caitlin Rivers, ​an epidemiologist and director of the Center for Outbreak Response Innovation at the Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkllgjel00053b6s9l2ll65n@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Now we’re seeing in a single week what we might have seen in an average year,” she said. “There’s been a real shift in the presence of this preventable disease in our life.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmklni3my00063b6puk4qsw4z@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Whether that balance can shift back depends on how quickly the US can improve vaccination coverage, experts say – which, in many ways, has become an uphill battle.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkllgsy000083b6s3na67xuy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The US reported more than 2,200 confirmed measles cases in 2025 — significantly more than there have been in any year since measles was declared eliminated in the US in 2000. At least ​171 measles cases have been reported in the first two weeks of 2026, which is nearly as many as the average annual total in those 25 years since elimination in the US.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmklllcmx000c3b6sx5ue5xi5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The vast majority of cases — more than 95% — have been in people who had not been vaccinated with the recommended two doses of the measles-mumps-rubella (MMR) vaccine.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljkbef006p27nxb77a4ckg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Experts fear that the situation may have to get much worse before it gets better.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmklk0u0500013b6su7fizaud@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It’s particularly devastating, they say, because the illnesses and deaths they foresee are almost entirely preventable with the help of vaccines — but &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/14/health/vaccine-exemptions-county-risk-measles-vis"&gt;lagging coverage&lt;/a&gt; has left many vulnerable.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f00083b6ptxalh4rr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It’s not clear yet whether the US will maintain its measles elimination status. In April, the Pan American Health Organization, part of the World Health Organization, will formally make the &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/11/10/health/canada-measles-elimination-status-removed"&gt;determination&lt;/a&gt;. The decision will require detailed review of epidemiological and laboratory evidence to understand patterns of measles spread over the past year — including whether more recent outbreaks are linked to the Texas outbreak.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f00093b6p7h6jwvnp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But experts say that formally losing measles elimination status would be a symptom of more deeply rooted issues, particularly challenges with vaccination that have been building for many years.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000a3b6pdd3p39mp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Let’s face it, whether we lose elimination status or not in spring, is our public health system actually doing well?” said Dr. Demetre Daskalakis, former director of the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention’s National Center for Immunization and Respiratory Diseases, who resigned in protest last year.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000b3b6pzhoqg2r4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Measles elimination is a vital sign of our public health system. That public health system is blue in the ICU,” he said. “I don’t need to check its pulse to know [it’s not doing well]. I know the answer.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000c3b6pu6zooffj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/31/health/vaccination-school-requirements-cdc"&gt;record share&lt;/a&gt; of US kindergartners had an exemption for a required vaccination last school year, according to data from the CDC, marking the fifth year in a row that coverage with the MMR vaccine was been below the federal target of 95%.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmklwh4q900003b6s3bxua13a@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The CDC says that the increase in vaccine exemptions may be “due to an increase in vaccine hesitancy.” A recent &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/schoolvaxview/pubs-resources/parental-attitudes-toward-vaccination-requirements.html" target="_blank"&gt;survey&lt;/a&gt; of parents conducted by the agency found that most supported vaccine requirements to attend school. But among those seeking an exemption, the most commonly reported reason – cited more than a third of the time – was a philosophical or personal belief objection to vaccination. Difficulty meeting school requirements by the deadline was also reported as a reason for exemption by about 23% of parents. Medical reasons were cited by more than a quarter of parents, but the CDC said that might include parents who consider concerns about vaccine safety or side effects as a “medical” reason to request an exemption.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000d3b6ph96jf0tr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Vaccines are a victim of their own success. It’s not just that we eliminated measles. I think we eliminated the memory of measles,” said Dr. Paul Offit, director of the Vaccine Education Center at the Children’s Hospital of Philadelphia.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000e3b6pvk9mmrj1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Offit remembers speaking with&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC557162/" target="_blank"&gt; Dr. Maurice Hilleman&lt;/a&gt;, a microbiologist who developed the MMR vaccine and dozens of others, just months before Hilleman’s death in 2005. Measles cases had reached a record low in 2004 but were starting to trend up again, just a few years after the US had achieved elimination following a long and hard-fought battle.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000f3b6p2rdjhwku@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I asked him, ‘Do you think that we can educate people about the importance of the vaccine, about the serious nature of this disease, or does the virus have to come back?” Offit said. He said there was a tear in his eye when he replied that virus was going to have to come back to teach that lesson.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000g3b6p6ebs73pf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “That was an enormous defeat for him,” Offit said. “It’s an enormous defeat for us to once again see children be exposed to something that could kill them — and did kill them – in this country, when that was completely unnecessary.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000h3b6pd2rpeowp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But it seems more and more that the virus isn’t necessarily doing that educating either, Offit said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000i3b6pytcripbb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There were three deaths from measles last year — as many as there had been over the past 25 years combined — yet it’s been a struggle to increase vaccination rates, even in communities that experienced outbreaks.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000j3b6pha5k9q6u@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The South Carolina health department has offered a mobile vaccination clinic since the early weeks of the outbreak in the upstate region of the state, but state epidemiologist Dr. Linda Bell has said that uptake has been “disappointing.”
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000k3b6pb555xjf2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Measles outbreaks tend to occur in &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/14/health/vaccine-exemptions-county-risk-measles-vis"&gt;under vaccinated pockets&lt;/a&gt; of the US, often in tight-knit communities, such as those with certain religious beliefs.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000l3b6p4eyp37nw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Daskalakis says that there’s a new type of tight-knit community in the US – one that’s less geographically connected, but created and held together by the spread of anti-vaccine messaging, including by US Department of Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. and others at the extremes of the &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/16/politics/rfk-vaccines-covid-maha-cassidy-explainer"&gt;MAHA movement&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000m3b6pdxgtetxu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The mission since the dawn of the vaccination program in America is that if we can prevent a disease with a vaccine that has an extremely favorable risk-to-benefit profile, that we do it,” Daskalakis said. “It seems as if the value of that strategy has been minimized for some populations. Not for everybody, but enough where I expect that measles is going to be a part of our future, at least in the medium-, if not long-term.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmklo8k24000d3b6pazd5mo7b@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            HHS says that Kennedy has been “clear and consistent” in his messaging that vaccination remains the most effective way to prevent measles, but the agency also says that &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/03/02/health/measles-rfk-vaccines"&gt;individuals should consult with their health care provider&lt;/a&gt; about what is best for them and their family.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkltbwue00003b6sj3aaqcvh@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            HHS recently made sweeping changes to the childhood vaccine schedule, now recommending fewer vaccines for most American children in a move Kennedy &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/media/releases/2026/2026-cdc-acts-on-presidential-memorandum-to-update-childhood-immunization-schedule.html" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; “protects children, respects families, and rebuilds trust in public health.” MMR vaccine recommendations were not changed, but experts worry it could contribute to &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/05/health/childhood-vaccine-schedule-overhaul"&gt;broader doubts about vaccines&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000n3b6p0byetz29@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It’s unclear what will change individual minds about vaccination, experts say — perhaps a recalibration of public health messaging and more families fearing measles reaching their doorstep — but the risk for increasingly large outbreaks mean there will be many preventable illnesses and deaths ahead.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000o3b6pjoiltlou@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There have already been more than 550 measles cases in the South Carolina outbreak, and at least one out of every 1,000 people with measles may die.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmklkk5au00003b6ph4mwsxpp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It’s a matter of numbers. The more cases there are, the more opportunities there are for severe illness,” said Rivers, whose organization developed a &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/ivac/resources/us-measles-tracker" target="_blank"&gt;measles case tracker&lt;/a&gt; and worked with health departments from across the country to help them learn from their experiences responding to measles.
    &lt;/p&gt;





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000p3b6pne8cr3ac@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Raising vaccination rates is the best way to keep cases to a minimum and prevent those tragic outcomes, experts say.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000q3b6pvl8ubq7v@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            That could happen in a matter of months, Rivers said. It’s how other large outbreaks have been &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/03/10/health/measles-outbreak-new-york-2019-lessons-learned"&gt;brought to a halt&lt;/a&gt;. But the potential for change may depend on whether people are perceiving these outbreaks as threats to their own lives, she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000r3b6p46oonp2j@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “With sufficient attention, motivation and policy changes like strengthening school entry requirements, we can get those coverage levels up very quickly,” she said. “We have all the pieces in place. We just need families to understand how important it is, and that piece could take years.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000s3b6pj46i7ide@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The increase in the frequency and size of measles outbreaks will certainly put additional strain on public health, Daskalakis says. Continuing to build relationships and lean on trusted partners within local communities can help reinforce critical messaging about the importance of vaccines.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000t3b6p53r8uc7p@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Still, optimism persists.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkljko1f000u3b6p1efdssim@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This is what public health does,” Daskalakis said. “Public health is never static. There’s always a new challenge, there’s always new misinformation and, frankly, also new information that moves you in a different direction.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:30:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTE1HdWtlTHFmVVR3ODZVY051TDg3dDJabmNEQkxTelZwOHBfWnVtT1BCMjdxT2NjOWhwTEYwMm5xSFNrQldKTkliV1pYdDZhVXNwTzE2RVRhSUN5SDAyeFRsQkl5SEZVSm8zejd2S1V3ekZSLXNT</guid></item><item><title>还需要说吗？不，您不需要“清除寄生虫” --《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2026/jan/20/parasite-cleanse-worms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Last August, supermodel Heidi Klum revealed that she and her husband, Tom Kaulitz, were planning a worm and parasite cleanse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Everything on my Instagram feed at the moment is about worms and parasites,” she told the &lt;a href="https://www.wsj.com/style/heidi-klum-project-runway-return-routine-d0292c92" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Wall Street Journal&lt;/a&gt;, ominously adding: “I don’t know what the heck is going to come out.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Maybe &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; social media feeds aren’t full of posts about worms and parasites, in which case, congratulations. But type “parasite cleanse” into TikTok or Instagram and you’ll be inundated with so-called experts peddling expensive herbal supplements that promise to detox the body and rid it of harmful worms and parasites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;One TikTok user, whose credentials are “holistic mama”, suggests people should do deworming cleanses if they experience “sleep issues, gut issues, weight loss issues, mood swings, skin issues”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It would be nearly impossible to find a single human not dealing with at least one of these issues. Does that mean everyone should be on a parasite cleanse?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“NO,” Caroline Susie, spokesperson for the Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics wrote in all caps over email. She emphasized that there was no solid clinical evidence behind them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Ideally, all-caps discouragement from a medical professional would be enough reason to steer clear of something. But if you’re still unconvinced, here’s what to know about parasite cleanses, and why you probably don’t need to do one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-are-parasites" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are parasites?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Parasites are organisms that live in, on or with another organism and get their food “from or at the expense of its host”, per the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/parasites/about/index.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. For example: tapeworms, fleas or me when I lived at my parents’ house after college.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Humans contract parasites in several ways, says Beth Czerwony, outpatient dietitian for Cleveland Clinic’s Center for Human Nutrition. These include ingestion of contaminated food or water and direct contact with infected feces, she explains. Some parasites, like hookworm, can also penetrate the skin when a person walks barefoot on contaminated soil, and others can be transmitted person to person in unhygienic environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the US and UK, the most common intestinal parasites are giardiasis and cryptosporidiosis, says Dr William A Petri, professor of infectious diseases at the University of Virginia. Both are transmitted through the ingestion of fecally contaminated food or water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Parasitic infections are extremely common. According to a 2023 World Health Organization (WHO) &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/soil-transmitted-helminth-infections" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt;, almost 25% of the global population has an infection related to parasitic worms like roundworms, whipworms and hookworms. These infections tend to be concentrated in “the poorest and most deprived communities” where people lack access to clean water and sanitation, per the WHO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Having intestinal parasites is less common in places with good sanitation,” says Czerwony.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-are-the-symptoms-of-a-parasitic-infection" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the symptoms of a parasitic infection?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Symptoms vary based on the type of parasite and the health of the host, says Czerwony. Often, symptoms include conditions like diarrhea, nausea and/or vomiting, stomach pain, loss of appetite or increase in hunger, unexplained weight loss, skin irritation, visible worms or eggs in one’s stool, and itching around the anus or genitals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-is-a-parasite-cleanse" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is a ‘parasite cleanse’?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Klum said of her own cleanse that it had “all these herbs”. Most of those so-called remedies peddled on social media &lt;a href="https://health.clevelandclinic.org/parasite-cleanse" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;involve&lt;/a&gt; taking herbal supplements (like anise, clove, grapeseed, wormwood and goldenseal), dietary changes (like eliminating processed foods or cutting out gluten) or some combination of the two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="does-it-work" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does it work?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;No.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“There is no evidence that these parasite cleanses are either effective or needed,” says Petri. And if someone feels better after one of these cleanses, it’s probably not the result of parasites, says Susie – it might simply be that they’re eating more nutrient-dense food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;At-home cleanses are also not without risks. &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2026/jan/08/supplements-vitamins-safety-dosage-limit-guide" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Supplements are not regulated&lt;/a&gt;, Susie notes. Additionally, she says, some herbs can interact with other medications and be toxic at high doses. Restrictive diets can also lead to nutrient deficiencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="how-do-you-treat-a-parasitic-infection" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you treat a parasitic infection?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“If you think you may have a parasite, it is important to contact a medical professional and not treat it yourself,” says Czerwony.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Infections can be diagnosed with stool samples or blood tests and, in some cases, with imaging tests like endoscopies or colonoscopies, she explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If a patient does have a parasitic infection, treatment depends on the type of parasite and the severity of the infection. Often, doctors will prescribe antiparasitic or antibiotic medications, and/or rehydration and nutrition support if severe weight loss has occurred, Czerwony says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="did-the-parasite-cleanse-work-for-heidi-klum" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did the parasite cleanse work for Heidi Klum?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure id="fc789204-afae-4504-9260-710036d6f7fa" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Heidi Klum’s worm costume.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Stephen Lovekin/Rex/Shutterstock&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Unclear, but probably not. Klum – who once dressed as a worm for Halloween – told &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/soil-transmitted-helminth-infections" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;People&lt;/a&gt; magazine in November: “I don’t even know if anything happened!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE55d3ZrajFiZlFzdGtwdWg2UjF6UFN4cUdrZVdhc0l5dFJ4TmdMOFdNTjFkMDFucERKSG10bkkzMC05UjlGLW82RC1NSU8tdGM2T2Z4XzJNX1BxOVRrQjZNMnJwYmRTM2FrNmRndW9LbzJHQUJiT05Hd3B0TQ</guid></item><item><title>《精神病学圣经》会增加产后精神病诊断吗？ -《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/20/health/postpartum-psychosis-dsm-diagnosis.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:52:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQQ0NXdDdVX3ZzbGczUWxGNnBCcnR6WEVhODh4U1k3QkVXUlc3REFKdW45RlpEaXBtbW9BQm9BZjQxR002N2FJeDRwaHVHQUF5YzNmcHZmclAzbEFENF94WWlYaHgybDMwTFJDTGEzMllSa3NoYkhSaUxPcjdUNnpQQVdfRnBfd0It</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr.正在对女性发动战争-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/technology/2026/01/rfk-jr-maha-women-moms-science.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="21" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkheilp60026357bhcreqc5h@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://slate.com/theslatest?utm_source=slate&amp;amp;utm_medium=article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=article_plain_text_topper&amp;amp;sailthru_source=Article-TopperText-CTA"&gt;Sign up for the Slatest&lt;/a&gt; to get the most insightful analysis, criticism, and advice out there, delivered to your inbox daily.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="91" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkhegg2y00gnzskwiwzo9dtm@published"&gt;Let’s get this out of the way first: Robert F. Kennedy Jr. is not going to be successful at his stated MAHA goal. You can’t make America healthier—I refuse to even say “again” when &lt;a href="https://slate.com/technology/2013/09/life-expectancy-history-public-health-and-medical-advances-that-lead-to-long-lives.html"&gt;we weren’t healthy before&lt;/a&gt;—while you are simultaneously so &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/house-democrats-slam-rfk-jr-research-funding-cuts-vaccine-policy"&gt;drastically slashing&lt;/a&gt; budgets for scientific research. You also can’t make America healthier while ignoring any expert who is not a crackpot—and so very much data—on &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/im-a-physician-who-has-looked-at-hundreds-of-studies-of-vaccine-safety-and-heres-some-of-what-rfk-jr-gets-wrong-259659"&gt;the basics of vaccines&lt;/a&gt;. More minimally, you can’t make America healthier while claiming that, say, seed oils are the devil (&lt;a href="https://slate.com/technology/2025/01/sweetgreen-menu-salad-nutrition-seed-oil.html"&gt;seed oils are innocent&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="55" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkheh3px000o357bj3dyz1q3@published"&gt;So the question isn’t whether RFK Jr. will make America healthier. On balance, he will only be a disaster for American health. (Sure, he will occasionally get things right—this fact brings to mind the saying about &lt;a href="https://en.wiktionary.org/wiki/a_stopped_clock_is_right_twice_a_day"&gt;broken clocks&lt;/a&gt;, and the one &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Infinite_monkey_theorem"&gt;about a monkey at a typewriter and &lt;em&gt;Hamlet&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.) But what will he actually do?&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="51" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkheh3sm000p357bigw43aqz@published"&gt;Well, to be sure, he will make life worse—&lt;a href="https://slate.com/technology/2025/08/rfk-jr-vaccines-mrna-dangerous-diseases-deaths.html"&gt;and shorter&lt;/a&gt;—for &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/04/30/rfk-jr-hhs-job-cuts-minority-health-offices.html"&gt;lots of groups of people&lt;/a&gt;. But as a person who recently gave birth to a baby and spent months watching and reading the news from maternity leave, my answer to that question is: RFK Jr. is waging a war on women.&lt;/p&gt;

    


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="107" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkheh3w0000q357blqahgqf8@published"&gt;Let’s go through some of the ways. Kennedy is encouraging women to breastfeed, to provide their babies with, &lt;a href="https://www.c-span.org/clip/news-conference/user-clip-rfk-jr-on-breastfeeding-and-infant-formula/5183687"&gt;as he puts it&lt;/a&gt;, “the infant formula that God made, the infant formula in a mother’s breast.” (Would that not be the infant formula that the &lt;em&gt;woman&lt;/em&gt; made, with her own body? I digress.) While increasing breastfeeding rates is a goal shared by many legitimate public health experts (see: broken clock), the biological advantages of breastfeeding are &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/jun/20/is-breast-really-best-i-looked-at-all-the-data-to-find-out"&gt;somewhat limited&lt;/a&gt;, making this a strange enterprise for a government official. But more to the point, the costs of breastfeeding, particularly exclusively breastfeeding with no supplement from formula, are huge. For women.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="129" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkheh3z0000r357bpln4o8pa@published"&gt;Namely, breastfeeding is very time-consuming, even in the best of circumstances. (In the worst, it can involve women working on the project of feeding their infant at &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2024/jan/10/traded-sanity-for-milk-breastfed-despite-the-pain"&gt;great expense to their own well-being&lt;/a&gt;.) Formula—real, store-bought formula—is, except in &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/response-broader-fda-investigation-byheart-initiates-voluntary-recall-two-batches-infant-formula"&gt;freak cases&lt;/a&gt; of contamination, a perfectly safe and good option for getting babies fed, right now. Nonetheless, Kennedy has, along with his weird breastfeeding comments, simultaneously &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DHd6XoDvp9O/"&gt;widely publicized&lt;/a&gt; a project “to make sure infant formula products are safe and wholesome.” What Kennedy really stands to do here is scare women away from a method of nourishing their babies that is perfectly acceptable, that is healthy, and that stands to make life easier—and in some cases, simply livable—for us by introducing his classic fearmongering tactics to matters that have already been settled.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="215" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkheh41x000s357buj4x7i2n@published"&gt;Then there’s the Tylenol fiasco. Kennedy has called on women to restrict the use of Tylenol during pregnancy to cases where it is “absolutely necessary.” For the unaware, Tylenol is somewhat notoriously a medicine that is deemed safe during pregnancy—the American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists &lt;a href="https://www.acog.org/news/news-releases/2025/09/acog-affirms-safety-benefits-acetaminophen-pregnancy"&gt;released a statement&lt;/a&gt; saying that Tylenol is “one of the few options available to pregnant patients to treat pain and fever.” There are all kinds of very sensible recommendations against taking certain substances during pregnancy, if at all possible, and Tylenol is not one of them. So where is Kennedy getting this? It’s another fear campaign. The evidence regarding Tylenol use while with child, &lt;a href="https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/5582061-kennedy-trump-tylenol-autism/"&gt;he notes&lt;/a&gt;, “is not sufficient to say it definitely caused autism, but it is very suggestive.” These comments came on the heels of Donald Trump’s even stronger warning: “Don’t take Tylenol. Don’t take it. Fight like hell not to take it.” Science, of course, always &lt;em&gt;could&lt;/em&gt; find a link &lt;a href="https://slate.com/technology/2026/01/microplastics-brain-research-not-bad.html"&gt;between any given thing and anything else&lt;/a&gt;, but it is telling that the studies done so far on Tylenol and autism &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/22/health/kennedy-autism-tylenol-trump.html"&gt;have, taken together, not found anything conclusive&lt;/a&gt;. And still, Kennedy is &lt;a href="https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/5518478-tylenol-acetaminophen-pregnancy-risks/"&gt;trying&lt;/a&gt; to knock the bottle from our hands during what is, for some women, one of the most physically unpleasant times of our lives.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="87" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkheh44o000t357b7yrk0xj3@published"&gt;The war on women shows up less obviously, but perhaps with even more wide-reaching consequences, in other RFK Jr. projects. Take his stance on vaccines. He recently oversaw the removal of several from the recommended childhood immunization schedule. Who, by and large in America, will be taking care of the kids who have to stay home from school when they get sick? Who will take them to the emergency room? Who will &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/AmerAcadPeds/posts/an-infant-born-prematurely-and-infected-with-measles-has-died-in-canada-the-infa/1132893888872170/"&gt;bear the blame&lt;/a&gt; when what happens is even worse than an ER visit? Disproportionately, women.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="92" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkheh473000u357b0mtcy6tg@published"&gt;Then take his stance against ultraprocessed foods, which he has &lt;a href="https://time.com/7211678/rfk-jr-ultra-processed-foods-ban/"&gt;called&lt;/a&gt; a “mass poison”—and the fact that in his new food guidance, he advises that children should avoid sugar through age 10. Who will be ensuring that a Lunchable never so much as touches a child’s lips? (Lunchables: They are not healthy, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/technology/2024/04/lead-lunchables-consumer-reports-california-regulations-unhealthy.html"&gt;but they are safe&lt;/a&gt;!) Who will be convincing 9-year-olds to forgo birthday cake, or figuring out what to present as a birthday treat if it is not cake? Probably the group of people who mostly take care of children: women.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="91" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkheh49u000v357b0ebhj9vo@published"&gt;For the record, ultraprocessed foods are not even inherently bad. The fact is that they are a tool (like formula, like Tylenol) that can make life easier, more manageable, and even—by extension—&lt;a href="https://slate.com/life/2025/01/ultraprocessed-foods-healthy-energy-fear-trader-joes.html"&gt;literally healthier&lt;/a&gt;. These tools also allow women tasked with gestating children, caring for infants, and doing housework to not be completely consumed by it. Consider: Who even has time to prepare food entirely from scratch? To breastfeed exclusively? To lie there pregnant and in pain, just for the sake of it? A woman who does not work outside the home.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="152" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkheh4d9000w357bogvkdvev@published"&gt;Yes, women could always&lt;em&gt; just not &lt;/em&gt;follow Kennedy’s advice. Just use formula. Just take Tylenol! Just make &lt;a href="https://slate.com/technology/2017/07/dont-panic-over-the-chemicals-in-your-mac-and-cheese.html"&gt;the mac and cheese&lt;/a&gt; for dinner. Just vaccinate your children. I am personally &lt;a href="https://slate.com/culture/2020/09/anne-helen-petersen-burnout-book-reviewed.html"&gt;a huge fan of &lt;em&gt;just exercising your own agency&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. But there are two issues here: One is the incredible swirl of half-realized health information that women &lt;em&gt;already&lt;/em&gt; have to navigate, both when it comes to finding answers through official channels (doctors, often, simply have no answer for &lt;a href="https://slate.com/technology/2021/08/pain-sex-vestibulodynia-physical-therapy-hormones.html"&gt;even basic inquiries into our pain&lt;/a&gt;) and when it comes to logging onto any social media site for any reason. There are just so many autoplaying videos of influencers out there issuing dire warnings about one thing or another that we already have to navigate, even though most of it has to do with the danger of not buying this or that gadget, or course, or coaching session that they so happen to be selling.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="114" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkheh4g9000x357b1i0hblsp@published"&gt;The other is that Kennedy is shaping not just the present state of our health &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/17/rfk-jr-reshaping-healthcare-hhs-trump-support/"&gt;but the future of health care writ large&lt;/a&gt;. He helps decide who staffs agencies, what gets funded, which direction the country points in when it comes to research. He has overseen cuts to offices in the Department of Health and Human Services that &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/04/30/rfk-jr-hhs-job-cuts-minority-health-offices.html"&gt;work to improve minority health&lt;/a&gt;. He has done a “&lt;a href="https://www.wsj.com/opinion/rfk-jr-hhs-moves-to-restore-public-trust-in-vaccines-45495112"&gt;clean sweep&lt;/a&gt;” of the panel that advises the Centers for Disease Control on vaccines in order to appoint his own people. He has, in his first year at HHS, “significantly thinned out the sprawling $1.7 trillion department,” &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/rfk-jr-kennedy-trump-health-hhs-maha-5e1e9e3208c42b6a185facad26e3b457"&gt;as an evenhanded report from the Associated Press put it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="61" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkheh4ja000y357bjj8bf0t8@published"&gt;When it comes to women’s health specifically, he may not have (yet) shown the specific laser-focus in cutting that he has in other areas. But he has already shown a willingness &lt;a href="https://www.whi.org/md/news/whi-funding-announcement"&gt;to snatch away and dangle&lt;/a&gt; funding for research into women’s health. Last spring in a typically-chaotic MAGA move, he cut—then, following public outcry, restored—support for &lt;a href="https://www.ajmc.com/view/hhs-cuts-funding-for-nih-based-women-s-health-initiative-threatening-decades-long-study"&gt;the sprawling Women’s Health Initiative&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="139" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkheh4lx000z357bkc5eqrm4@published"&gt;Consider Kennedy, then, a health influencer who has not just access to a national podium, but also a say in what happens with a hulking budget. We might be able to individually ignore his advice, even as it becomes a more and more tiring process to sort out what is true and what is not, as iterations of Kennedy’s views are repeated everywhere from the social media accounts of other influencers to the CDC’s &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/11/20/nx-s1-5615040/cdc-rfk-childhood-vaccines-autism"&gt;own website&lt;/a&gt;. But we will, as the consequences of his agenda come to bear on who is hired by the government and what work they are able to do, increasingly simply be living in Kennedy’s world. The lesson for this second year of his tenure is clear: However exhausting it is, we have to pay attention. Pop a Tylenol and get ready to fight &lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;back.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="The Slatest" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmkhegg2y00gqzskwbs2zyph3@published"&gt;


    &lt;div class="newsletter-signup__intro newsletter-signup__intro--centered"&gt;
          &lt;img alt="" class="newsletter-signup__img" hidden data-src-light="https://dot.cdnslate.com/static/media/components/newsletter-signup/the-slatest.49f353b.png" data-src-dark="https://dot.cdnslate.com/static/media/components/newsletter-signup/the-slatest-dark.ca73d21.png"&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Get the best of news and politics&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Sign up for Slate's evening newsletter.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 10:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTFBRWTE3cUZhR1hmc005SlU2eko2SXJqWnk5U2NvZW55TTdKa3RlNVZ0X0VES0pYWl9zZ01GNS0tWTQ0bUdmSEFJWnpuU1czbTNFdVpKUzlaNFgwNkZlWGdxaGcxcl9kQldETTFneUtfMGpsRlRUa2loZFdNU3A</guid></item><item><title>已映射：最活跃（和最不活跃）的状态- Axios</title><link>https://www.axios.com/2026/01/20/most-least-active-states</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 10:36:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiaEFVX3lxTE5SX0xHbHprTG9rRGpIOU5OVmJ0VkRsZVRkZUV2VWpMTnB5bklVWXU5cVdOVHI1OHdOOFZxUkJUcHBtVWN5VVAwalNzY1BqcUFDM2Z2V28yOVFSSXVtUFhkYTgxTkJYb29N</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现人类精子中隐藏的RNA “衰老时钟” - Phys.org</title><link>https://phys.org/news/2026-01-scientists-hidden-rna-aging-clock.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 10:10:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE5rdmZiU0w3SHF2RlE1V3paYk9CU3NhZnhPY2ZsRXd6OXgzUF9RTUVWLV9XTG9MSzJwUFd0VGx5TzZ3dTg1Q0xLb0VPSkh6eG9YTGpaTzFNNWhZb09FUWkxYk1HT0dQZWMyaERUOTlHdnprdjVZYW40</guid></item><item><title>想睡得更好吗？按照专家的建议，通过这五种简单的生活方式改变来改善您的肠道健康- Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://www.fitandwell.com/wellness/sleep/want-to-sleep-better-improve-your-gut-health-with-these-five-easy-lifestyle-changes-as-recommended-by-an-expert</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;

&lt;p id="8d56c591-083e-45d7-a261-a9daa8c5ef77"&gt;Can’t sleep? Or do you find yourself constantly waking up at night? The answer to getting a good night’s sleep could actually be linked to what’s going on in your digestive system. Gut health and sleep are bedfellows—and if you can improve one, the other will follow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s because gut microbes don’t just digest the food we eat, explains Dr Manal Mohammed, a senior lecturer in Medical Microbiology at the University of Westminster in London: “A healthy gut microbiome supports better sleep by producing sleep-regulating neurotransmitters like serotonin and melatonin, reducing inflammation and modulating stress hormones,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="8d56c591-083e-45d7-a261-a9daa8c5ef77-2"&gt;“When the gut is happy, this also promotes the production of calming chemicals in the body like GABA, and helps maintain circadian rhythms [the body’s internal clock]. Together, these effects contribute to deeper, more restorative and consistent sleep.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, how can you improve your gut health? Mohammed has a five-step guide. Here’s what she recommends to ultimately help you towards a better night’s sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-1-keep-consistent-meal-times" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-1-keep-consistent-meal-times"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Keep consistent meal times&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="b182ba1f-cb5a-4404-87ef-0c855a912aeb"&gt;Like the body’s circadian rhythm, the digestive system has its own internal clock that helps the gut maintain a steady daily flow. Studies have found that &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40488812/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40488812/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;erratic meal-times&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.fitandwell.com/nutrition/eating-too-late-could-wreck-your-sleep-muscle-recovery-and-impact-weight-gain-why-this-expert-recommends-an-early-dinner" target="_blank" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.fitandwell.com/nutrition/eating-too-late-could-wreck-your-sleep-muscle-recovery-and-impact-weight-gain-why-this-expert-recommends-an-early-dinner"&gt;eating too close to bedtime&lt;/a&gt; plays havoc with microbes because it interferes with nutrient absorption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By contrast, Mohammed explains that “predictable eating patterns reduce inflammation, stabilize blood sugar and enhance the production of SCFAs [&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9498509/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9498509/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;short-chain fatty acids&lt;/a&gt;], which are important for strengthening the gut lining and supporting the gut-brain axis. Overall, regular meal timing helps maintain a balanced, diverse and healthy gut microbiome.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-2-eat-foods-rich-in-prebiotics-and-probiotics" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-2-eat-foods-rich-in-prebiotics-and-probiotics"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Eat foods rich in prebiotics and probiotics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="b11e42cd-7113-4d39-9586-a2a7d263ccef"&gt;Prebiotics are widely available in fiber-rich foods, while probiotics can be found in some fermented foods, or for larger quantities through supplementation. The two work together to keep the gut happy and this can have the knock on effect of better sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-4iNbA9mpegH8HAi3PBoSMR" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-4iNbA9mpegH8HAi3PBoSMR slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Probiotics provide beneficial live bacteria for the gut: found in foods such as kefir, kimchi, sauerkraut and miso,” Mohammed tells &lt;em&gt;Fit&amp;amp;Well.&lt;/em&gt; “Prebiotics, on the other hand, are non-digestible fibers that serve as food for these beneficial bacteria and they are found in foods like garlic, onions, leeks, bananas, oats, asparagus and chicory root.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Probiotics help introduce and support healthy gut microbes, while prebiotics help them survive, grow and thrive. They support a healthy gut microbiome by working together to promote beneficial bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This synergy enhances microbial diversity and boosts SCFA production such as butyrate, which strengthens the gut barrier and supports digestion, immunity and gut–brain communication.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-3-cut-back-on-sugar-and-ultra-processed-foods-upfs" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-3-cut-back-on-sugar-and-ultra-processed-foods-upfs"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Cut back on sugar and ultra-processed foods (UPFs) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="865f111b-5fb9-475b-b3e0-45692561772f"&gt;Sugary and UPFs—such as sodas, cereals and ready meals—are highly inflammatory, they irritate and weaken the gut lining by reducing microbial diversity and spiking blood sugar levels. UPFs are often low in fiber and high in additives, like emulsifiers and artificial sweeteners, which suppress fiber-fermenting bacteria—negatively impacting gut health, and therefore sleep quality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mohammed explains that when you cut back on these nutrient-deficient foods it “allows beneficial microbes such as &lt;em&gt;Lactobacillus&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Bifidobacterium&lt;/em&gt; to thrive, while stabilizing blood sugar and inflammation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She recommends swapping sugary products and UPFs for whole foods, including vegetables, fruits, whole grains, legumes, nuts and seeds. “This will increase the amount of prebiotic fiber in the body, boosting the production of SCFAs to strengthen the gut barrier, regulate immune function, support gut–brain communication and reduce inflammation—creating an environment where a healthy and diverse gut microbiome can flourish,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-4-try-to-reduce-stress" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-4-try-to-reduce-stress"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4. Try to reduce stress &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="58aeec68-eb4a-40cc-93d9-4bc396fb8334"&gt;This one might be easier said than done, but stress levels can really play havoc with the gut and sleep. Stress floods the body with the hormone cortisol, leading to an increase in inflammation in the body and a weaker gut lining. When you are less stressed, your digestion can work more efficiently and this helps to maintain a “balanced and resilient gut ecosystem”, says Mohammed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reducing stress levels can be tricky but breathwork and exercise can help, as can taking time away from social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-5-stay-well-hydrated" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-5-stay-well-hydrated"&gt;&lt;span&gt;5. Stay well hydrated&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="b06cd1bc-0f95-4a94-aaaa-11af4c1da4b6"&gt;There are so many ways in which drinking a healthy amount of water is beneficial for your gut. Water supports the breakdown of food, absorption of nutrients and helps lubricate the digestive tract to help with the removal of waste—promoting regular bowel movements. It also supports a healthy gut microbiome and immune function. A happy, more stable gut environment means you are more likely to have a deeper and restorative sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:05:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6AFBVV95cUxPX2haLVRnYVFQX1hzbmVRMFpkdHZVNzNPcDZwRXhmcklmNXdVa3BrMld6Sk5yUE9FMk0xQjJOMHNYNTZBNzF6bkxEN2k4b2cyZkRWNndWZEYtd0s3UGs5OVplcjAwelhkenl1RWdCRzRUOWhGcHhheWZ5WEFxRE0xZ1pvQlltVXp1Y1VCZy1jU1ctZHlVTnNrRVc4MFR2TjNXVURMODJkU1FmeENlMnp0Q1VldWRwZ0t6YTRmVEFvVTNsX1RzQXRwcGx1UlMycG5SeFlDZnplaGFiMldndEZjZnF3YldETWlF</guid></item><item><title>迈克尔·莫里茨（ Michael Moritz ）的《澳大利亚人》（ Ausländer ） —一个与当下相呼应的大屠杀故事-《金融</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9da42c47-429b-49e0-87ea-42d08e052fd8</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="o-grid-row details-section o3-type-body-base css-pmzbjb"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Delivery Monday - Saturday, including FT Weekend and FT Digital Edition: all the content of the FT newspaper on any device. Savings based on annual price.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Financial Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:00:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE9KSDdPbmdxNXB2bmR4VmJKcjl2NWp6a284Wk9tTFV1dlB1d3RiVjZkclZEdlk2UEk5SWZhc3hrMmhKMUxiNlFERXl3c3RWUXVtVmx6RzczdzRNZ2hjM0ZCN3FhdFVJSnA0OXlQUk5jbUk</guid></item><item><title>关于健康贴片的真相：它们真的可以治疗压力、斑点和性欲丧失吗？ -《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2026/jan/20/truth-about-health-patches-can-they-treat-stress-spots-and-lost-libido</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;his morning, I woke up feeling a little groggy. My go-to remedy is usually a coffee and cold-water face plunge, followed by a compulsive phone scroll. But today called for something more, so I unpeeled a small, yellow “energy” patch the size of a walnut, popped it on to my upper arm and hoped for the best.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The patch (£12 for 30) contains – so the packaging says – vitamins B5, B3 and a “microdose” of caffeine. It is made by Kind Patches, which is one brand in an increasingly crowded market of wellness stickers that claim to treat everything from lack of sleep to period pains to pimples. They are coin-sized, and often come in TikTok-friendly shades of sunflower yellow and peachy orange: you may have seen a teenager sporting a star-shaped one on their face to treat spots, or influencers patting blue magnesium ones on their wrists before bed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;These patches are designed to deliver various substances into the bloodstream through the skin – to ward off some of the most common symptoms of everyday life. Feeling tired? Patches. Feeling stressed? Patches. Feeling anxious? Patches. From libido boosters to immunity enhancers, there’s a patch for every condition if you look hard enough. The wearable patch market – which also includes disease monitoring and drug delivery – was estimated at &lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/5ebdee6d-eee0-4ed9-a7e2-7547bd1f03c9" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;$9.95bn in 2024&lt;/a&gt; (approx £7.45bn) and is predicted to grow significantly in the next five years, according to the Financial Times. Forget eating your feelings; pop a sticker on them instead.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="89c65e0d-f726-4cb8-ad45-cf40b21e432f" data-spacefinder-role="supporting" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-a2pvoh"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Star patches for acne and pimples are the accessory of choice for gen Z.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Karen Stanley/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But do they work? Or are they yet more snake oil in the &lt;a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-11-05/global-wellness-industry-is-now-worth-6-3-trillion" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;$6tn global wellness industry&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;designed to exploit our weaknesses, on the basis that those most human of conditions – how well you sleep, how happy you are – are there to be corrected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;John Tregoning, professor of vaccine immunology at Imperial College London and author of the book &lt;a href="https://guardianbookshop.com/live-forever-9780861549382/?utm_source=editoriallink&amp;amp;utm_medium=merch&amp;amp;utm_campaign=article" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Live Forever?&lt;/a&gt;, says it is impossible to know. “It’s not like a vaccine where you did or didn’t get the virus. It is: do you feel better?” For example, the energy patch I’m wearing now may make me feel better. “But my take on energy might be different to yours,” Tregoning points out. If nothing else, he says, patches like the ones I am sampling “are an example of drifting placebo. Simply by putting it on, it might get you out of a slump”. It’s also nigh-on impossible to prove which ones don’t work if you can’t prove which ones do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;You cannot feel these patches , and they slide off easily in the bath. But you can certainly see them, which for some users is half the point. Depending on where you place the patch – guidance varies, but most suggest the neck and chest areas to see which makes a difference – they are often as visible as you need them to be. Some claim to work the same day, while others suggest using them for up to a month. The effects of the energy patch I am wearing are supposed to be instant. I can’t say I feel anything that morning, but by the time I peel it off in the bath, I do believe I feel fresher. The idea is neat. But is it the patch? I also did some yoga, and had steak for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;I try another energy patch by The What Supp Co (£18 for 15 patches), which it says is for “fatigue, fed-up feelings and focus”. It contains ashwagandha (which it &lt;a href="https://thewhatsupp.com/products/protect-your-energy-vitamin-patches" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;claims&lt;/a&gt; “helps your body adapt to stress”) and caffeine among a list of other ingredients. I pop the red W-shaped patch on my wrist, as shown in the instruction video. I don’t know if it is doing anything, but I do struggle to get to sleep that night, which is debatably down to the caffeine (luckily I have a patch for sleep too).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Acupuncturist Ross J Barr also makes a &lt;a href="https://www.rossbarr.com/collections/patch/products/focus-patches?variant=55856746627452" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;patch&lt;/a&gt; that promises to support “focus, clarity and mental performance” (£15 for 10). Less visible than most, it smells herbal, a little festive, which is the point – it apparently offers a “deeply relaxing olfactive experience”&lt;em&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;I could also feel it when I put the patch on – a gentle tingling, not unlike a Tens machine, which did at least make me believe it was doing something. I also try Barr’s &lt;a href="https://www.rossbarr.com/collections/patch/products/period-patches?variant=44601291374756" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Period Patches&lt;/a&gt; for cramps, aches and pains (£15 for seven), which were developed with gynaecological staff at Miss Claire Mellon &amp;amp; Associates private practice. Like Barr’s other patch, it smells strongly of essential oils – somewhere between a meadow and tobacco – which is also the point. The sticker is stickier, and even after six hours it’s hard to remove. It is also designed to fit very specifically at the base of the spine. I don’t know how much this played into what happened next – but something did. My cramps seemed to mellow. Whether this was better than taking a painkiller, I couldn’t say. But the patches certainly cost more than over-the-counter painkillers – a factor that Dr Deborah Cohen, author of the new book Bad Influence: How the Internet Hijacked Our Health, thinks might influence how well they work. “The more expensive something is, the more you expect it to work,” she says. Cohen thinks women’s health has been neglected for too long, but&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;these patches expose broader problems in the healthcare system too. “One of the reasons we go to social media to solve our problems is because doctors can’t give that level of holistic care,” she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="60e35233-9643-491c-b91b-78c873e8cea5" data-spacefinder-role="supporting" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-a2pvoh"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Ross J Barr Focus Patches.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Ross J Barr&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Eleven days into my patch journey, I have tried one for sleep and one for dreaming (Ross J Barr, £14.99 for 10, and&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Kind, £12 for 30); two for focus (Kind, £12 for 30, and Ross J Barr, £15 for 10), one for energy (Kind, £12 for 30), one for chilling out (The What Supp Co, £18 for 15), and another for menstrual cramps (Ross J Barr, £14.99 for seven). I’d love to say their collective effect was seismic, but aside from feeling a little buzzy after wearing those containing caffeine and the aforementioned effects of Barr’s cramp patches, I can’t be sure that I felt &lt;em&gt;anything&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;That’s not to say they didn’t work. The science behind patches is at best nebulous and at worse absent, but as you can’t control the variables, it’s impossible to know if it’s the patch – or something else. “Reducing something to, say, one hormone is a very reductionist way of looking at our health,” says Cohen. “We need to be more holistic and look at the whole person before we work out how to treat something.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Inevitably some of these patches have taken a more sinister turn towards diet culture. Berberine, a plant-derived compound, is believed to suppress appetite. I try Kind’s berberine patches (which curiously changed their name from Weightless); they need to be worn every day to see a difference. When I go out for a walk, I have to turn back as I start feeling light-headed. I quickly take it off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;Ultimately, if patches are as good as they say they are, why isn’t everything on one?&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;I’m struck that only one of the patches I try comes with the caveat that they are not the only solution to a problem. Alongside using Barr’s sleep patches, for example, it is recommended that other basic sleep hygiene practices are brought in – read a book, turn off your phone, etc. While there may not be anything specifically wrong with putting on a patch if you can afford it, they are not a panacea. As Tregoning points out, it’s probably best to see them “like an expensive herbal tea”. Drink it if you like it and think it helps, but it’s not a cure-all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But then this is the problem with a lot of the products in the wellness space – everyone is looking for a hack, a quick fix. It is easier to put a sleep patch on than contemplate that poor sleep may be a logical response to the modern world; that a lack of energy may be due to an overwhelming life; that a lack of focus may mean you are dealing with bigger problems than the day-to-day of going to work. In an age in which we have learned to manipulate the aesthetics of our bodies through surgery or fillers, it seems highly appropriate that we might also now wear our supplements. As Cohen writes in her book, “the body is now a dashboard to be monitored and gamified”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="ec98b8d3-2cd1-4d0d-8d35-87523ca15e67" data-spacefinder-role="supporting" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-a2pvoh"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Karen Stanley/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;And of course, this is performative health. When I failed to give up smoking, my nicotine patch was proof to the outside world that I was at least trying. Lisa Payne, head of beauty at trend forecaster company Stylus, calls it&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;“handbag health” – the idea that you can carry around patches and pop them on when you need a lift. “These patches cost money, so it literally shows you have invested in your health.” Forget eating your feelings; pop a plaster on them instead. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 The use of patches in medicine is nothing new, says Pupinder Ghatora, a pharmacist and co-founder of a collagen supplement brand. “In pharmaceuticals, we’ve used patches for pain relief, anti-sickness medications, certain heart treatments and nicotine-replacement therapy. These medicines are clinically proven as the molecule is suitable for skin absorption and the formulation is designed with this in mind.” However, the evidence on wellness patches for other purposes is less clear. “Transdermal delivery can absolutely be effective but only when the science supports it. The skin barrier is incredibly sophisticated and not every ingredient can pass through it,” Ghatora says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The problem, adds Cohen, isn’t just the way these substances are delivered – it’s the substances themselves. “Before you get to the ‘route’, the first thing to ask is whether the compound they’re promoting is going to do anything.” Take something like dopamine, she says, for which patches do exist. This needs to go into your brain to work. How does that even happen?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“HRT patches and nicotine patches [which have been around for a while] require robust clinical trials to prove they have an effect. But if you can spin something into a wellness supplement, you don’t need regulators,” she says. “Ultimately, if patches are as good as they say they are, why isn’t everything on one?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Perhaps the most ubiquitous patches are Star patches. If you have a teenager – or watched last year’s Big Brother – there is every chance you’ve come across them. Designed to protect spots from bacteria and prevent picking, while also containing various ingredients which may or may not treat the spot, they have become such a mainstay of modern culture that the V&amp;amp;A recently acquired some in its &lt;a href="https://www.vam.ac.uk/collections/rapid-response-collecting?srsltid=AfmBOoqFisrHBGVBj0Q5Zwa6ZkuqzU81v9_Y_vLnMhq1-Dt0TWJ0UKHl" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Rapid Response Collecting&lt;/a&gt; as an example of gen Z lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="b04ec8d4-65f9-4d3f-aef7-ea12d840ae31" data-spacefinder-role="supporting" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-a2pvoh"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Kind’s Berberine metabolic balance patch.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Kind Patches&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Advertising that you have a pimple is a million miles away from how millennials like me and Payne grew up. “Our generation saw beauty as something that solves the problem you want to fix,” she says. If you had a spot, you’d buy concealer to hide it, not a neon sticker to broadcast it as a shared experience. But for some of gen Z, Payne says, a visible treatment for an internal feeling is as much about identity as anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It used to be easy to be good. All you had to do was combine a decent diet, exercise, time outside and connection with friends. Now, says Cohen, “daily life is subjected to medical interpretation and diagnosis, with normal variations reframed as conditions requiring intervention”. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 I spent three weeks patched up, on and off. And some people I know swear by Barr’s sleep patches. But it was also deep, dark December, a time when my moods and sleep shift like sand, and as a newish millennial parent, it was ever thus. Patches are an example of the way influencer culture has scrambled how we look at ourselves. But if you’re tired and there’s no other underlying problem causing it, the likelihood is you probably need to rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxQZ0QzX0RELUZCc2lrOW8zMVp6R0k2S1NJRG1uaVJnbVUtanQ4X1pPdWp1TWFCOUZ3clJOUTRSbE55RzNxUFFMRERQOWZQb1FPSHRac3F0SzNpTzNLZkZSLUpRbHpKV2xPdDJ1ZnNEaDVZa0FmaTRHMGdDUmc2ZzRwajZydWllaHdfOFV5RkpmRHdQcXlVNG5SX1g5aTVkd3pDMXhQUklZWkU3aWY3NGZBRlpLaVlJM2l5X2NmQm9YdVo</guid></item><item><title>医生说， “每天只需几分钟”就可以改善平衡并降低跌倒的风险- Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://www.fitandwell.com/exercise/bodyweight-exercises/a-doctor-says-all-it-takes-is-a-few-intentional-minutes-a-day-to-improve-balance-and-reduce-your-risk-of-falls</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;

&lt;p id="c7c34f02-07d5-4e2f-b4fc-42f0d007c3b0"&gt;Improving balance is one of the biggest concerns for many of my older personal training clients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During recent icy weather, one of my senior clients came to her session wearing a pair of &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://target.georiot.com/Proxy.ashx?tsid=110083&amp;amp;GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Famazon.com%2FYaktrax-Traction-Cleats-Walking-Medium%2Fdp%2FB0094GO9DA%2F%3Ftag%3Dhawk-future-20%26ascsubtag%3Dfitandwell-gb-1178288354270693491-20" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.amazon.com/Yaktrax-Traction-Cleats-Walking-Medium/dp/B0094GO9DA/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="hawklinks" data-google-interstitial="false" data-placeholder-url="https://target.georiot.com/Proxy.ashx?tsid=110083&amp;amp;GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Famazon.com%2FYaktrax-Traction-Cleats-Walking-Medium%2Fdp%2FB0094GO9DA%2F%3Ftag%3Dhawk-future-20%26ascsubtag%3Dhawk-custom-tracking-20" data-merchant-name="Amazon US" data-merchant-id="1471" data-merchant-network="Amazonus" data-merchant-url="amazon.com" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;YakTrax&lt;/a&gt;—ice grips that fit over your regular shoes, like snow chains you put around car tyres in winter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="c7c34f02-07d5-4e2f-b4fc-42f0d007c3b0-2"&gt;They’re worries are understandable. “Falls are one of the leading causes of injury worldwide, especially as we age,” internal medicine physician &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.instagram.com/seizethedaywithdrday/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.instagram.com/seizethedaywithdrday/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;Dr Cristina Sciavolino-Day&lt;/a&gt; tells &lt;em&gt;Fit&amp;amp;Well&lt;/em&gt;. “They can lead to fractures, hospitalizations, loss of independence and fear of movement afterward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What’s important to emphasize is that many falls are preventable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As a physician, I always remind my patients that balance is not something we either have or don’t have—it’s a skill, just like strength, and it can be trained at any age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The biggest mistake people make is thinking balance training has to be time-consuming or intimidating. It doesn’t. A few intentional minutes a day can really help to improve confidence, reduce fall risk and strengthen muscles. It just takes consistency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It becomes easier if you add these drills to things you are already doing like boiling water, brushing teeth, making coffee or microwaving leftovers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-ej2JKf3Gq7BYqwfaymviMa" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-ej2JKf3Gq7BYqwfaymviMa slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These little moments of exercise add up in a big way.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how Sciavolino-Day suggests &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.fitandwell.com/wellness/ive-been-using-the-habit-stacking-technique-for-over-a-year-and-i-think-its-the-easiest-way-to-improve-your-health-without-even-trying" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.fitandwell.com/wellness/ive-been-using-the-habit-stacking-technique-for-over-a-year-and-i-think-its-the-easiest-way-to-improve-your-health-without-even-trying"&gt;habit-stacking&lt;/a&gt; these balance drills with daily tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-1-calf-raises-while-the-kettle-boils" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-1-calf-raises-while-the-kettle-boils"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Calf raises while the kettle boils&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="looped-video" id="d360aaeb-aa07-4492-bd71-6c85b6c95f4b"&gt;&lt;video class="lazyload-in-view lazyloading" data-src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/HvP65e5XxqTBJ9643eSYk9/calf-raise-202601191631.mp4" autoplay loop muted playsinline src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/HvP65e5XxqTBJ9643eSYk9/calf-raise-202601191631.mp4"&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="8b457e89-d771-4529-ab47-4527331a2f6d"&gt;“This exercise wakes up your calves and ankles, which are some of the most important and overlooked muscles for balance,” says Sciavolino-Day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to do it:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="194e8f2e-a305-4629-bd8f-346d09ab2dc3"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stand by your kitchen counter for support, with your feet hip-width apart.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly lift your heels as high as you can, coming onto your toes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pause at the top, then lower your heels with control.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Let go of the counter as you get stronger and more comfortable.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;a id="elk-2-single-leg-balance-while-brushing-your-teeth" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-2-single-leg-balance-while-brushing-your-teeth"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Single-leg balance while brushing your teeth&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="looped-video" id="62e7eff8-e2b4-4d1b-a9ea-5f4e2d6b12f8"&gt;&lt;video class="lazyload-in-view lazyloading" data-src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/9ianPm7qiKQC5HHTzSsFBJ/balance-drill-stand-on-one-leg-202601191618.mp4" autoplay loop muted playsinline src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/9ianPm7qiKQC5HHTzSsFBJ/balance-drill-stand-on-one-leg-202601191618.mp4"&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="f3e08ef6-332a-428c-b84e-08d0b9fe8721"&gt;“Balancing on one leg strengthens your deep stabilizing muscles around your hips, knees and ankles, which are the same ones that keep you from wobbling when you trip, turn, or step off a curb,” says Sciavolino-Day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to do it:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="81dad43f-915d-44f3-a1f7-4e3342fa6b32"&gt;&lt;li&gt;From standing, carefully shift your weight onto one foot.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lift the other a few inches off the floor and hold this position.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep your core engaged and chest upright.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To progress this move once steady, raise and lower your knee to perform slow and controlled pulses.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Switch sides about halfway through brushing your teeth.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;a id="elk-3-standing-knee-lift-and-leg-extension-while-the-microwave-runs" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-3-standing-knee-lift-and-leg-extension-while-the-microwave-runs"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Standing knee lift and leg extension while the microwave runs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="looped-video" id="986f0290-8916-4d65-b0bf-25d9c9f9517c"&gt;&lt;video class="lazyload-in-view lazyloading" data-src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/v39UA8wc6icyrmEmmx2JUM/knee-raise-leg-extension-202601191618.mp4" autoplay loop muted playsinline src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/v39UA8wc6icyrmEmmx2JUM/knee-raise-leg-extension-202601191618.mp4"&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="9f85e3ad-e610-43c3-9931-e5efc265eace"&gt;“This exercise works on strength, stability and control. The slow, forward leg extension wakes up your hips and thighs, which are key for steadiness when stepping over things or recovering your balance after a stumble,” says Sciavolino-Day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to do it:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="9e0e73f3-b17d-44a6-a78f-960212aefbb3"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stand by your kitchen counter for support, with your feet together.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bend and raise your right knee in front of you to hip height.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lift your right foot in front of you, moving from your hip, keeping your leg straight.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Return to the start with control.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continue, alternating movements until you have completed your desired number of reps, then repeat on the other side.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Let go of the counter as you get stronger and more comfortable.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-wFBVV95cUxOVms0QkkxcUdMSnV6NGsxMmYyX2Fob1ZZa0dQaDlHX2I5enR6Z0c3b1Y5X0MwWm5HQmZVQjBMUXRYdnZobHh0dDZ0bGJoLUFQMHAwR2ItbkIxd25KaFN1Unpqcm1nV29DTVl1azlPUS1mdFZ2eW10dUpzeVYwTGpOcjRIMlhZMmdONFJIYkxFcF9VM1Vza19WV0loSHN3MndvSkFRZk9jUVRpVFUxMl9UMzdMQzlTRGFteklhRXBwYU1ha2V5STlvT1owZ3hqR1FHMWtRb0laR0pQN0NNLVRKazBheGxCMlBrNDh4ZUs5b1dGcmRhamFEblJ0dw</guid></item><item><title>诉讼对RFK Jr.的儿童新疫苗指南提出异议-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/19/rfk-childhood-vaccines-lawsuit/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="R2PWJT2UXBDEZKUR4FVKV2WU7A" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Several public health groups are suing to reverse a decision from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention that narrows the list of vaccines recommended for children, arguing that Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. and other leaders failed to consider how the new policy would endanger families and burden the health care system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 03:02:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxOMUVOZHVjMk5ua1pFRHZ0VGowOGltcFZCSXFLNkh5Z0M2Y21ETzNvWm4xYWctN2VKX2J0dXNTc2hMTnlkb20ycThGa0dlenduaVNxMnBtZmFXekFXbmpjNlBQYTV3XzBXWUlUZW9EQjhvUDB0WDBaWUcxaERkTjFOaExzVWVrSnM</guid></item><item><title>Triple H权衡儿童肥胖问题的增加- 411Mania</title><link>https://411mania.com/wrestling/triple-h-on-increase-childhood-obesity-inverting-food-triangle/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>411Mania</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 02:11:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNTzFtd0wwM29UTEx3WHg4QmY0aUlNemR1Wkc5Zy1NQ0o0MGloR0FaWU91UXZfV0xiNXEwdU9KTTJsRzQxM211WU1IQ3lqZE1oUWt2cTFQTlA3dWZHUHFhMnc0ckRhNUJ6SDJGaXdFa2JDWWJpZE5fV3llZUQwb3UtRzZWR2RzUHhXWWtTVmVXREh2WmJocTNpVEtn</guid></item><item><title>单个分子可以解释大脑中的血流如何触发痴呆症- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/a-single-molecule-may-explain-how-blood-flow-in-the-brain-triggers-dementia</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Reduced blood flow to the brain is thought to be a key factor in many forms of dementia, including  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="187972" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;, and scientists have just identified a new mechanism regulating this flow, which may also help explain how it goes wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A fat molecule helps maintain the system's balance, researchers at the University of Vermont discovered, and in mouse models of Alzheimer's disease, disruption of this balance led to problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixing the imbalance restored more normal blood flow, offering a hopeful new target for understanding and treating dementia-related brain changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This discovery is a huge step forward in our efforts to prevent dementia and neurovascular diseases," &lt;a href="https://www.uvm.edu/larnermed/medcommunications/news/r1-larner-spotlight-new-evidence-larner-researchers-points"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; pharmacologist Osama Harraz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/an-early-warning-sign-of-dementia-risk-may-be-keeping-you-up-at-night"&gt;An Early Warning Sign of Dementia Risk May Be Keeping You Up at Night&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Building on &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/bs.ctm.2020.01.005"&gt;previous studies&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Endothelium"&gt;endothelial cells&lt;/a&gt;, which line the inside of blood vessels, the team looked specifically at the protein Piezo1 – a pressure 'sensor' in the cells. When this sensor is overactivated, it can disrupt the brain's blood flow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By analyzing brain activity in mice, they determined that a fat molecule called PIP2 acts as a brake on Piezo1. When &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/neurons-in-the-brain-appear-to-follow-a-distinct-mathematical-pattern"&gt;brain cells are active&lt;/a&gt;, PIP2 levels are low, and Piezo1 is activated, increasing blood flow to where it is needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_187975" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-187975" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/BrainAnalysis.jpg" alt="Brain analysis" class="wp-image-187975 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/BrainAnalysis.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/BrainAnalysis-600x333.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-187975" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Researcher Osama Harraz at work analyzing brain vasculature. (David Seaver)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-may-be-tied-to-vascular-dementia-cases-review-finds"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;In mouse models of Alzheimer's, PIP2 was found to be abnormally low. This led to Piezo1 overactivating, boosting blood flow to areas where it wasn't required and disrupting overall circulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crucially, when the researchers restored PIP2 levels in these mice, normal blood flow patterns were largely recovered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's still early days in understanding exactly how this mechanism works – this was a short-term study that only looked at mice – but it's another promising area to explore when it comes to investigating the underlying &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/major-study-links-15-factors-to-early-dementia-risk"&gt;drivers of dementia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-may-be-tied-to-vascular-dementia-cases-review-finds"&gt;Vascular dementia&lt;/a&gt;, in which impaired blood flow to the brain is a key contributor, is one of the most common forms of dementia, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/17474930251404243"&gt;affecting millions&lt;/a&gt; worldwide. Blood flow problems are also thought to play a role in Alzheimer's disease, although the damaging buildup of toxic proteins is likely more significant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As blood flow controls the delivery of oxygen and nutrients &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/just-one-high-fat-meal-can-disrupt-blood-flow-to-your-brain-study-finds"&gt;to the brain&lt;/a&gt;, the implications extend beyond dementia. Maintaining the right balance is essential for keeping the brain functioning properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These findings establish the foundation for a therapeutic approach for improving cerebral blood flow in conditions where Piezo1 activity is altered and could have impacts beyond brain blood flow control," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.2522750122"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/castingcall?utm_source=SA_website&amp;amp;utm_medium=article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=casting_call"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg" alt="Audition now for ScienceAlert's Casting Call" class="alignnone wp-image-189354 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-1200x509.jpg 1200w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1.jpg 1266w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While our understanding of dementia is &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/an-early-warning-sign-of-dementia-risk-may-be-keeping-you-up-at-night"&gt;steadily improving&lt;/a&gt;, there's still a lot we don't know about how these diseases begin or why some people are more vulnerable than others. Even with vascular dementia, it's not clear what all of the contributing factors to blood flow might be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies like this help fill in those gaps by identifying the molecular players involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, the researchers plan to look at precisely how PIP2 interacts with Piezo1. Understanding that interaction will be crucial for controlling this system and potentially restoring healthy blood flow – and perhaps &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/promising-new-drug-reverses-mental-decline-in-mice-with-advanced-alzheimers" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;cognitive function&lt;/a&gt; too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are uncovering the complex mechanisms of these devastating conditions, and now we can begin to think about how to translate this biology into therapies," &lt;a href="https://www.uvm.edu/larnermed/medcommunications/news/r1-larner-spotlight-new-evidence-larner-researchers-points"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Harraz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.2522750122"&gt;&lt;em&gt;PNAS&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:24:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxQVER6ekxGaUwwQ21FOHRXQmdYYkFLSWVveUpHS0NQWTVlcVdYZW1rUlVrU1IzS3JEUzhyMFNKd2xkb3ZRVmJ3NjVsZTc4d0dsZnlmbTVjNFhTV19OUFBHS181dGlVVTNaUGd6MnFLYjdGQ1NCMy1xd2JFMEh5ZnBaclFoZ2RISXplWmQxbWpWbjRTdl9PVjd6WG5jYjA4cXZLTi1ZblBubw</guid></item><item><title>乐高教育在家学习套装正式宣布-砖扇</title><link>https://www.thebrickfan.com/lego-education-learning-at-home-sets-officially-announced/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content entry-content"&gt;
	
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=LNtsWdwRzsQ&amp;amp;mid=13923&amp;amp;murl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.lego.com%2fen-us%2fproduct%2fmars-mission-science-kit-45202" target="blank"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.thebrickfan.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/LEGO-Education-Mars-Mission-Science-Kit-45202.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LEGO has officially revealed a new line of LEGO Education sets called Learning at Home which should be available tomorrow. The sets are designed for kids to learn at home by doing various science experiments. One thing to note is that the Space sets have some new printing for the astronaut minifigures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=LNtsWdwRzsQ&amp;amp;mid=13923&amp;amp;murl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.lego.com%2fen-us%2fproduct%2fmoon-mission-science-kit-45200" target="blank"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.thebrickfan.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/LEGO-Education-Moon-Mission-Science-Kit-45200.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=LNtsWdwRzsQ&amp;amp;mid=13923&amp;amp;murl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.lego.com%2fen-us%2fproduct%2fmoon-mission-science-kit-45200" target="blank"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.thebrickfan.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/LEGO-Education-Moon-Mission-Science-Kit-45200-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=LNtsWdwRzsQ&amp;amp;mid=13923&amp;amp;murl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.lego.com%2fen-us%2fproduct%2fmoon-mission-science-kit-45200" target="blank"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.thebrickfan.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/LEGO-Education-Moon-Mission-Science-Kit-45200-3.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ignite a love of science and lunar travel in kids aged 8 plus with this Moon Mission Science Kit (45200), part of the LEGO® Education building-set collection. Target their passion for space with an educational toy they can build and play with repeatedly. Launch kids’ critical thinking skills with a spaceship toy, Earth-to-moon launchpad, habitat, greenhouses, 2 astronaut minifigures and more. Inspire STEM learning, exploration and independent play with the included physical science experiments for kids, which encourage them to find solutions and invent new ways of achieving their goals through fun. It’s great that adults can boost kids’ learning with a cool space toy that sparks ingenuity. This STEM gift for kids is ideal for holidays, Christmas or birthdays, encouraging them to jump in and get started. Girls and boys of all ages can develop their problem-solving and other STEM skills while enjoying a set that offers fun ways to learn more about their passion. Set contains 519 pieces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=LNtsWdwRzsQ&amp;amp;mid=13923&amp;amp;murl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.lego.com%2fen-us%2fproduct%2fantarctic-animals-science-kit-45201" target="blank"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.thebrickfan.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/LEGO-Education-Antarctic-Animals-Science-Kit-45201.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=LNtsWdwRzsQ&amp;amp;mid=13923&amp;amp;murl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.lego.com%2fen-us%2fproduct%2fantarctic-animals-science-kit-45201" target="blank"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.thebrickfan.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/LEGO-Education-Antarctic-Animals-Science-Kit-45201-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=LNtsWdwRzsQ&amp;amp;mid=13923&amp;amp;murl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.lego.com%2fen-us%2fproduct%2fantarctic-animals-science-kit-45201" target="blank"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.thebrickfan.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/LEGO-Education-Antarctic-Animals-Science-Kit-45201-3.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spark a love of science and nature in kids aged 7 years old and over with this Antarctic Animals Science Kit (45201), part of a series of LEGO® Education sets. Target their passion for animals with an educational toy they can build and play with repeatedly. Encourage kids’ critical thinking skills with an ‘icy’ slope, 2 toy penguin figures, an articulated whale figure, 2 scientist minifigures and more. Inspire STEM learning, nature exploration and independent play with the included life science experiments, which encourage them to find solutions and invent whole new ways of achieving their goals through fun. This STEM gift for kids is ideal for holidays, Christmas or birthdays, encouraging them to jump in and get started. It’s designed so that adults can boost kids’ learning with a cool animal toy that inspires ingenuity. Girls and boys can develop their problem-solving and other STEM skills while enjoying a set that offers fun ways to explore and learn more about their passion. Set contains 461 pieces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=LNtsWdwRzsQ&amp;amp;mid=13923&amp;amp;murl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.lego.com%2fen-us%2fproduct%2fmars-mission-science-kit-45202" target="blank"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.thebrickfan.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/LEGO-Education-Mars-Mission-Science-Kit-45202.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=LNtsWdwRzsQ&amp;amp;mid=13923&amp;amp;murl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.lego.com%2fen-us%2fproduct%2fmars-mission-science-kit-45202" target="blank"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.thebrickfan.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/LEGO-Education-Mars-Mission-Science-Kit-45202-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=LNtsWdwRzsQ&amp;amp;mid=13923&amp;amp;murl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.lego.com%2fen-us%2fproduct%2fmars-mission-science-kit-45202" target="blank"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.thebrickfan.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/LEGO-Education-Mars-Mission-Science-Kit-45202-3.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-1"&gt;

&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0069905765356104" data-ad-slot="8537706582"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ignite kids’ curiosity and love of science and space travel with this Mars Mission Science Kit (45202), part of the LEGO® Education building series. Target their passion for space with an educational toy they can build and play with repeatedly. Launch kids’ critical thinking skills with a drop-tower experiment, drop pod, Mars rover, Mars base, 4 astronaut minifigures and more. Inspire STEM learning, exploration and independent play with the 4 physical science experiments for kids, which encourage them to find solutions and invent new ways of achieving their goals through fun. This STEM gift for kids is ideal for holidays, Christmas or birthdays, encouraging them to jump in and get started. Boost kids’ learning with a cool, interplanetary space toy that sparks their creativity. Girls and boys aged 9 and over can develop problem-solving and other STEM skills while enjoying a set that offers fun ways to explore and learn more about their passion. Set contains 933 pieces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=LNtsWdwRzsQ&amp;amp;mid=13923&amp;amp;murl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.lego.com%2fen-us%2fproduct%2farctic-animals-science-kit-45203" target="blank"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.thebrickfan.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/LEGO-Education-Arctic-Animals-Science-Kit-45203.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=LNtsWdwRzsQ&amp;amp;mid=13923&amp;amp;murl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.lego.com%2fen-us%2fproduct%2farctic-animals-science-kit-45203" target="blank"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.thebrickfan.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/LEGO-Education-Arctic-Animals-Science-Kit-45203-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=LNtsWdwRzsQ&amp;amp;mid=13923&amp;amp;murl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.lego.com%2fen-us%2fproduct%2farctic-animals-science-kit-45203" target="blank"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.thebrickfan.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/LEGO-Education-Arctic-Animals-Science-Kit-45203-3.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Science and nature adventures await kids aged 9 years old and over with this Arctic Animals Science Kit (45203) LEGO® Education set. Target their passion for animals with an educational toy they can build and play with repeatedly. Encourage critical thinking skills with a brick-built Arctic camp cabin, big and little polar bear, walrus and reindeer figures, 4 scientist minifigures and more. Inspire STEM learning, nature exploration and independent play with the 4 life science experiments, which encourage them to find solutions and invent whole new ways of achieving their goals through fun. This animal lovers’ gift for kids is ideal for holidays, Christmas or birthdays, encouraging them to jump in and get started. It’s made so adults can boost kids’ learning with a cool animal toy that inspires ingenuity. Girls and boys can develop their problem-solving and other STEM skills while enjoying a set that offers fun ways to explore and learn more about their passion. Set contains 1,134 pieces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;div class="saboxplugin-wrap" itemtype="http://schema.org/Person" itemscope itemprop="author"&gt;&lt;div class="saboxplugin-tab"&gt;&lt;div class="saboxplugin-desc"&gt;&lt;div itemprop="description"&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you make a purchase or, sometimes, carry out some other action as direct result of clicking on a link at The Brick Fan, we will receive a small commission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Brick Fan is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com. As an Amazon Associate I earn from qualifying purchases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We partner with Rakuten Advertising, who may collect personal information when you interact with our site. The collection and use of this information is subject to the privacy policy located here: https://rakutenadvertising.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy/&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="clearfix"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;

&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0069905765356104" data-ad-slot="8537706582"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

							
	&lt;/div&gt;
				
		
		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Brick Fan</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:02:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxQYnNzQ2JDR2lqM2hzcmxFUDIydm1sbEVCNTlHczkwMlZ1TkJiYVhsbk5Ic2o2Vkp5Q3dtRFRyYTduT3NpRGp3WGxUQjYxTW5pbVphRkc0OVcxaEE3YjdMQVBmMzN2ME1wNzN5Ry1DczJBeVZMWnNzREctWExXZU83Q3Uyajg3VkRvWkwwdnRRZw</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，前列腺癌是英国最常被诊断出的癌症-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2026/jan/20/prostate-cancer-is-most-commonly-diagnosed-cancer-across-uk-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prostate cancer is now the most commonly diagnosed form of cancer across the UK, surpassing breast cancer, according to a leading charity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There were 64,425 diagnoses of prostate cancer in 2022, an analysis of NHS figures by Prostate &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/cancer" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Cancer&lt;/a&gt; UK found, and 61,640 new cases of breast cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The analysis found there to be a discrepancy at which stage men with prostate cancer were diagnosed, with 31% of men in Scotland diagnosed with prostate cancer at stage 4, compared with 21% of men in England.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;About one in eight men across the UK will be affected by prostate cancer in their lifetimes, with approximately 12,200 deaths each year caused by the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;One in four black men will be diagnosed with prostate cancer in their lifetimes. They also have a higher risk of a late-stage diagnosis compared with their white counterparts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prostate Cancer UK highlighted the apparent “postcode lottery” with regard to testing and diagnoses of the disease. It found that rates of prostate specific antigen (PSA) testing were highest in the south-east of England and lowest in the north-west.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Men living in areas of higher deprivation were 29% more likely to be diagnosed with cancer that had spread than those living in more affluent areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Chiara De Biase, the director of health services, equity and improvement at Prostate Cancer UK, said risk awareness campaigns had played a big part in the overall increase, which had led to “more men than ever being diagnosed and treated”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Prostate cancer is now the most common cancer in the UK, but despite this, men are facing deeply unfair inequities across the country, and their experiences vary hugely based on where they live,” De Biase said. “We urgently need an early detection programme that will address these regional inequities.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="470ecd2a-63ac-4586-b5ed-e0f666448292" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":9,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"NHS expands access to prostate cancer drug in England to save thousands of lives","elementId":"470ecd2a-63ac-4586-b5ed-e0f666448292","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/society/2026/jan/16/prostate-cancer-drug-abiraterone-nhs-england"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0},"isInStarRatingVariant":false}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;She added: “Mass risk-awareness campaigns have played a big part in causing this increase, such as how in February 2022, we launched a national campaign with the NHS to reach men across the UK to get them to check their risk of prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We also know that when celebrities like Bill Turnbull, Nick Owen and Colin McFarlane share their prostate cancer stories, men can be encouraged to ask about a test themselves.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Last year, prostate cancer became &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/jan/28/prostate-cancer-becomes-most-common-cancer-diagnosis-in-england" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the most common cancer in England&lt;/a&gt;, but new figures from Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland enabled the UK-wide analysis. In Scotland there were 5,608 prostate cancer diagnoses, an increase of 30% compared with previous figures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Ian Walker, the executive director of policy at Cancer Research UK, said that the figures could be affected by overdiagnosis of the disease, “where PSA tests in asymptomatic men could be spotting cancers that wouldn’t cause any harm”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A panel of expert government health advisers in November said prostate cancer screening &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/nov/28/prostate-cancer-screening-not-expected-to-be-made-widely-available-in-uk" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;should not be made available&lt;/a&gt; to the vast majority of men across the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The UK National Screening Committee instead recommended that there should be a targeted screening programme for men with a confirmed BRCA1 or BRCA2 faulty gene variant, which means they are more at risk of faster growing and aggressive cancers at an earlier age. Men in that category could be screened every two years between the ages of 45 and 61, they said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;This is despite campaigners and charities calling for men at higher risk of developing the disease, such as black men and those with a family history of the cancer, to have screening available to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A Department of &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/health" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; and Social Care spokesperson said: “We are determined to improve outcomes for men with prostate cancer, and we know that too many men in deprived communities are being diagnosed at a later stage when the disease is harder to treat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Last week the NHS expanded access to abiraterone – a treatment that can significantly improve survival rates and give patients precious extra years of life and we are also making progress on cutting cancer waiting times – in the last 12 months, 213,000 more patients received a diagnosis for suspected cancer on time.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxOUkM3bWR3RXlmMTd4aWtFYUw5NXFpT094NHVINXpDN0ZEZGp4MnJXREI3VXZCU2lYcWVoTFkyQ2tKMVZEX2F4WWVtRV9vbzE4WGh3aElZMTFVYlBzc3BhOXBpOFlYZGs1VlA1M1Q0YXVsbHdPX3JtMV9GTzJfNm51OTBtVXpmTXFhYTFvbm1WV0ZpN0NGSjhrLUt6SGE0RmgwYmFTUlh2Z29kcFhjYmttS2h4T0NXZllSTzA4</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现人体炎症的天然“关闭开关” - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/scientists-discover-the-bodys-natural-off-switch-for-inflammation/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:49:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPbXF6SGJnc3BtT0tXWGRxdS1FNWp1Z0lDXzRYbU5ZdmRBOWpMaFN5MWp6ME9nSmZmQWpZclg5Q2xPUE13SDQ1OUR4eHpnVkJZeUE2WXlJdHduNXlvR3UtWXZxbzBJdlViMzNWZ2VsUFRyTVZpTjdWTE1oSnhWNzZGWFJnMHQxOXJUM0hPSlpiN0NMem0tUGc</guid></item><item><title>Ozempic和其他GLP-1激动剂怀疑论者指南-怀疑论者</title><link>https://www.skeptic.com/article/skeptics-guide-ozempic-glp1-agonists/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="skp_content" class="gh-content gh-canvas skeptic_load_content"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card"&gt;&lt;img src="https://www.skeptic.com/content/images/2026/01/SKEPDOC-logo-2026-dark-light.webp" class="kg-image" alt="" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.skeptic.com/content/images/size/w600/2026/01/SKEPDOC-logo-2026-dark-light.webp 600w, https://www.skeptic.com/content/images/size/w1000/2026/01/SKEPDOC-logo-2026-dark-light.webp 1000w, https://www.skeptic.com/content/images/size/w1600/2026/01/SKEPDOC-logo-2026-dark-light.webp 1600w, https://www.skeptic.com/content/images/2026/01/SKEPDOC-logo-2026-dark-light.webp 2000w" sizes="(min-width: 720px) 720px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p class="note"&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;A new compass for the SKEPDOC column&lt;/strong&gt;. This column was founded by Harriet Hall, MD (1945–2023) who wrote it from 2006 to 2023. In 2026, we welcome William Meller, MD, to the helm. As an expert in evolutionary medicine, Dr. Meller will be our guide in navigating the deep biological history of our species to find the “True North” of human health. 
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;span class="dropCap"&gt;I&lt;/span&gt; have been practicing medicine for more than 40 years. During that time the management of obesity and Type 2 diabetes (T2DM)—the kind that usually is caused by being overweight—often felt like Sisyphus pushing a boulder up a hill, only to have it roll back down, often heavier than before. We faced a “diabesity” epidemic where the available tools were blunt instruments at best. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lifestyle interventions—meaning trying to get someone to change their behavior—was the most and least effective method we had. Most, because in the less than two percent of patients who were successful, it works very well. Least, because, well … 98 percent failed. And they failed because all of our evolutionary history (“See food? Eat it!”) was working against them. This is the mismatch theory: a mismatch between the environment of our evolutionary ancestry that designed our brains to seek foods that were at once rare and nutritious (sweets and fats) and the modern environment in which such foods are in such overabundance that we eat far beyond the saturation point. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pharmacological options were often disappointing: Sulfonylureas and insulin lower blood sugar but caused weight gain, exacerbating the underlying problem. Bariatric surgery works, but it is invasive and carries surgical as well as lifelong nutritional risks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote class="kg-blockquote-alt"&gt;When we look at the data for GLP receptor agonists, along with the innumerable before and after photos of successful weight loss transformations, we are forced to admit that we have moved from a realm of wishful thinking into one of potent pharmacology.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Into this therapeutic desert crawled the Gila Monster (above), a venomous lizard native to the American Southwest from which researchers derived GLP receptor agonists (Glucagon-like peptide-1 receptor agonists)—medications that mimic the natural GLP-1 hormone that lead to lower blood sugar, help control appetite, and promote weight loss by telling the pancreas to release more insulin when glucose is high, slowing the rate of stomach emptying, and signaling to the brain a sense of fullness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a skeptic, I am allergic to the word “miracle,” but when we look at the data for GLP receptor agonists, along with the innumerable before and after photos of successful weight loss transformations, we are forced to admit that we have moved from a realm of wishful thinking into one of potent pharmacology. But, as always in medicine, there is no free lunch. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="the-incretin-concept-from-gut-to-glory"&gt;The Incretin Concept: From Gut to Glory &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The story begins with the “incretin effect”—the observation that glucose taken by mouth triggers a much stronger insulin response by increasing the production of hormones in the pancreas, compared to when it is injected directly into a vein. The gut knows you are eating and tells the pancreas to get ready to pack away the extra calories as fat. In patients with Type 2 diabetes, this effect is blunted and the sugar floats around in the bloodstream much longer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists identified two main hormones responsible: Glucose-dependent Insulinotropic Polypeptide (GIP) and Glucagon-like Peptide (GLP-1). The problem is that GIP doesn’t work well in diabetics. GLP-1 works beautifully—stimulating insulin, suppressing glucagon, and slowing gastric emptying—but it has a fatal flaw: It is destroyed by the enzyme DPP-4 within minutes of entering the bloodstream. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This led to two distinct pharmaceutical strategies. The earlier version was DPP-4 Inhibitors. Drugs like the “Gliptins” block DPP-4, making GLP-1 last longer. They are well-tolerated but their ability to lower blood sugar is modest and they generally do not cause weight loss. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The newer strategy was to engineer versions of GLP to resist degradation. This is where the Gila monster strolled in. In the 1990s, while researching hormone-like drugs, Dr. John Eng noted a similarity between &lt;em&gt;exendin-4&lt;/em&gt; found in Gila venom to Glucagon-like peptide (GLP), and it was able to resist breakdown by DPP! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="the-evidence-efficacy-beyond-the-hype"&gt;The Evidence: Efficacy Beyond the Hype &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first GLP-1 agonist, exenatide (Byetta, approved in 2005), required twice-daily injections and produced modest weight loss. But the pharmacology evolved rapidly. We moved to once-daily liraglutide, and then to the once-weekly heavyweights: dulaglutide, semaglutide (Ozempic and Wegovy), and the dual GIP and GLP-1 agonist tirzepatide (Mounjaro and Zepbound). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The clinical trials, called LEAD, SUSTAIN, PIONEER, STEP, and SURPASS (you’ve got to just love the creative acronyms!) have generated data that are hard to dismiss: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glycemic Control&lt;/strong&gt;: These drugs consistently outperform most oral antidiabetics in lowering blood sugar by 10 to 20 percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weight Loss&lt;/strong&gt;: This is the game changer. While early drugs produced 2–4 kg of weight loss over six months, the newer agents are producing results previously only seen with surgery. In the STEP-1 trial, semaglutide 2.4 mg resulted in an approximately 15 percent body weight reduction. Tirzepatide pushed this further, achieving up to 22 percent weight loss in the SURMOUNT-1 trial. That is the effect of a 250-pound person losing 55 pounds! Who wouldn’t want some of that?! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cardiovascular Outcomes&lt;/strong&gt;: Perhaps most importantly, these drugs are not like some that just make numbers look better; they are saving lives. Liraglutide and semaglutide have demonstrated significant reductions in major adverse cardiovascular events (MACE), including heart attack and stroke, in high-risk populations. The SELECT trial recently showed semaglutide reduces MACE by 20 percent even in nondiabetic patients with cardiovascular disease. But don’t be fooled, it is not likely that these drugs have specific effects on the heart. It is probable that the fat loss alone is causing these benefits. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="some-skeptical-scrutiny-the-risks"&gt;Some Skeptical Scrutiny: The Risks &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a drug sounds too good to be true, we must look for the catch. GLP-1 agonists have plenty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The “Puke” Diet?&lt;/strong&gt; The most common side effects of GLP-1 agonists are gastrointestinal: nausea, vomiting, diarrhea, and bloating. In some trials, up to 45 percent of patients experienced nausea. While this usually subsides, it raises a valid question: Are people losing weight because their metabolism is optimized, or because they feel too sick to eat? The mechanism involves central appetite suppression in the hypothalamus, but the “gastric braking” effect is real and unpleasant for many. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Pancreas and Thyroid Scare&lt;/strong&gt;. Early observational data suggested a link between GLP-1 agonists and pancreatitis and pancreatic cancer. However, extensive reviews have not confirmed a causal link to pancreatic cancer, though a slight increase in pancreatitis persists in some data. This makes sense, as one of the major sites of GLP’s effects is on the pancreas. In the thyroid, these drugs cause C-cell tumors in rodents. Humans have far fewer GLP-1 receptors on their thyroid C-cells than rats, and so far no evidence of increased thyroid cancer has been confirmed in humans. Still, the Black Box warning remains: If you have a family history of endocrine tumors or medullary thyroid cancer, these drugs are not for you. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote class="kg-blockquote-alt"&gt;If we are simply shrinking patients without preserving their strength, we may be trading one set of problems for another.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vanishing Muscle&lt;/strong&gt;. Weight loss via GLP-1 agonists is not just fat loss, so overall body composition must be monitored. In the STEP-1 trial, DEXA scans showed that lean body mass (muscle and bone) accounted for nearly 40 percent of the weight lost. In older adults, this raises the specter of “sarcopenic obesity”—being frail and weak despite having excess fat. Losing muscle mass compromises physical function and metabolic health. If we are simply shrinking patients without preserving their strength, we may be trading one set of problems for another. Now, regular and increased exercise is part of the prescription for all patients taking GLP drugs, but studies on how well this works are still in progress. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Perioperative Peril&lt;/strong&gt;. Because GLP-1 agonists delay gastric emptying, there have been reports of patients aspirating (inhaling) gastric contents during anesthesia, even after standard fasting protocols. This is a new, practical safety concern that surgical societies are rushing to address. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mental Health&lt;/strong&gt;. Reports of suicidal ideation appeared in postmarketing monitoring of GLP-1 agonist users, prompting investigations by European regulators. However, recent large cohort studies have not supported an increased risk of suicidality compared to other diabetes medications. As with all centrally acting drugs, vigilance is required, but the current data are reassuring. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Lifetime Prescription?&lt;/strong&gt; The most significant caveat for GLP-1 agonists is durability. Obesity can be a chronic, relapsing disease. Trials show that when patients stop taking semaglutide, they regain two-thirds of the lost weight within a year, and cardiometabolic improvements revert toward baseline. This implies that these are not “cures” but lifelong therapies, much like blood pressure medication. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Financial Toxicity&lt;/strong&gt;. As I write this, these drugs are prohibitively expensive, creating a massive public health gap. We also saw shortages that left diabetic patients unable to fill prescriptions because the supply was diverted to off-label weight loss use. GLP-1 agonists are not expensive to produce, however, and the patent on Ozempic expired in January of 2026 in Canada and China (and lasts until 2030 in the U.S.), but I expect the market to bring the costs down dramatically over the next few years. As of this year, close to 12 percent of Americans have tried it at least once. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="needles-versus-pills"&gt;Needles Versus Pills &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If there is one thing that holds patients back from the current crop of injectable incretins it is the needle. Despite the efficacy of weekly injections, people prefer pills. The pharmaceutical industry, never one to leave money on the table, has been racing to develop an oral alternative that doesn’t require the strict fasting rituals of earlier attempts like oral semaglutide. Enter &lt;em&gt;orforglipron&lt;/em&gt;, the latest contender in the “nonpeptide small molecule” class, which promises the benefits of GLPs without the injection or the fuss. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike existing peptide predecessors that are digested by stomach acid unless armored with absorption enhancers, orforglipron is a chemical—a small molecule designed to survive the GI tract and activate the GLP-1 receptor directly. The data from the ATTAIN-1 trial, published in September 2025, look good. Patients on the 36 mg dose achieved an average weight loss of 11.2 percent over 72 weeks, compared to just 2.1 percent for placebo. No needles. And this pill does not require the “empty stomach, no water, wait 30 minutes” song-and-dance required by oral semaglutide; it can be taken with or without food. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote class="kg-blockquote-alt"&gt;These are serious medications with serious side effects, and they may require lifelong commitment.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, let’s look a little past the convenience. While an 11.2 percent average weight loss is clinically significant, it trails behind the 13.7 percent average reduction seen with semaglutide and 20.2 percent with tirzepatide. Furthermore, the biology of GLP-1 agonism remains the same regardless of delivery method: You cannot cheat physiology. In the ATTAIN-1 trial, adverse events led to treatment discontinuation in up to 10.3 percent of patients on the drug, compared to only 2.7 percent on placebo. The side effects are the usual suspects—gastrointestinal distress, nausea, and constipation—confirming that oral delivery does not bypass the “gastric braking” misery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We must also remain vigilant regarding safety. The development of a similar small molecule, lotiglipron, was unceremoniously halted due to liver toxicity concerns. While orforglipron has passed its Phase 3 hurdles without these specific signals so far, the history of pharmacology teaches us that rare, serious adverse events often lurk in the postmarketing shadows. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, while proponents argue that small molecules are cheaper to manufacture than biologics, whether those savings will be passed on to the patient or simply absorbed into the profit margins remains to be seen, with projected self-pay costs in some cases exceeding $1,000 per month. Orforglipron represents a technological leap, but it is not a magic wand; it is simply a more convenient way to induce the same physiological trade-offs we have seen over the last several years with the shots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="conclusion"&gt;Conclusion &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prior to the incretin era, our ability to manage the twin epidemics of diabetes and obesity was dishearteningly limited. GLP-1 receptor agonists represent a hard-earned pharmacological breakthrough, offering potent glucose control and unprecedented weight loss. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, skepticism is still warranted regarding their indiscriminate use. They are already being used in numerous off-label ways, like shedding a few pounds before a wedding, allegedly decreasing cravings for addictive drugs like alcohol and narcotics, and purportedly even for the treatment of Alzheimer’s and Parkinson’s disease. There are ongoing studies for these uses, but early data are weak and the risks are unknown. These are serious medications with serious side effects, and they may require lifelong commitment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Caveat emptor&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Skeptic</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:21:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE5OYlMxMzI4NzRVZm43eDJ5c0lSSWtyZ3h2SWprNDhxaWlqWU1CclZJUy0tb25fRmFWY01ZYnZicFZNWmhuRkxwZzlRT3AycUZPTmo2bjV6c1JmMF8zdWEwM0YtWmdpc2g4T0JsR1hpMjZlYkxWVjhIbA</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，减肥手术在收入水平上胜过GLP-1s治疗2型糖尿病- statnews.com</title><link>https://www.statnews.com/2026/01/19/diabetes-study-bariatric-surgery-better-than-glp-1s/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-constrained wp-block-post-content-is-layout-constrained"&gt;&lt;p&gt;When endocrinologist Mary Elizabeth Patti looks at a patient with type 2 diabetes who could benefit from weight loss, she sees more than body mass index and blood glucose levels. She also recognizes the challenges of social vulnerability, understanding how low income, food insecurity, and limited access to health care might matter in treatment choice. After all, those factors are strongly linked to developing type 2 diabetes and obesity in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For more than a dozen years, Patti has been a leader of long-running randomized clinical trials conducted in four U.S. cities that compared bariatric surgery to medication and lifestyle management for type 2 diabetes. &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2815401" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;In 2024&lt;/a&gt;, one of those trials demonstrated the superiority of bariatric surgery for patients, measured by lower blood glucose levels, higher weight loss (28% vs. 10%), less use of diabetes medications, remission of diabetes to the point of no longer needing to inject insulin, and reduced risk factors for cardiovascular disease. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In a new secondary analysis of the larger trial &lt;a href="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/ANNALS-24-01882" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;published Monday in the Annals of Internal Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, Patti and her colleagues asked how different social determinants of health affected outcomes after bariatric surgery compared to medical therapy for people with type 2 diabetes and obesity.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Bariatric surgery was better than medical therapy across all social backgrounds, they found, and not just in areas of higher deprivation. The ancillary study was smaller, and some of the participants randomized in earlier stages crossed over from medical to surgical treatment, and the reverse. The authors acknowledged and accounted for these limitations, along with the rapid development of more powerful obesity drugs not fully captured in the study. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Still, “Bariatric surgery remains an underutilized approach. Even in comparison to these really wonderful medications that we now have access to, it is still better,” Patti, an endocrinologist and director of the hypoglycemia clinic at Joslin Diabetes Center in Boston, told STAT. “I’m not a surgeon, but I think we need to keep in mind that surgery offers an approach which can be a durable therapy for type 2 diabetes and obesity.”&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;At the overall study’s start, carried out in Boston, Cleveland, Pittsburgh, and Seattle, 355 participants were randomly assigned to undergo medical therapy or one of three surgical approaches: gastric bypass, sleeve gastrectomy, or adjustable gastric lap banding. Medical and lifestyle interventions, based on the well-known Diabetes Prevention Program, included individualized nutrition counseling and instruction on exercise and how to monitor glucose. As time passed, fewer people chose lap band surgery, which has now fallen out of favor, and newer obesity drugs were increasingly available in the trials’ later stages. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Some people from the medication group later chose surgery, and some people who’d had surgery began taking obesity drugs. By year 12, more than a third of participants in the medical therapy groups and more than a quarter in the surgical groups were receiving incretin-based therapy, the class of drugs that includes older ones like liraglutide (sold as Saxenda) as well as newer GLP-1s like tirzepatide (sold as Mounjaro).&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The smaller study analyzed data from 258 adults with type 2 diabetes who began the larger trial having either undergone bariatric surgery or received medical and lifestyle therapy. They had been sorted by their ZIP codes to identify the Area Deprivation Index for where they lived. Their weight and hemoglobin A1c levels, which measure blood glucose, were tracked for seven&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;to 12 years.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While there was a trend toward better outcomes from surgery for people living in a high deprivation area, it was not statistically significant, Patti said. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Navigating diabetes care alone is hard, she said, particularly when combined with socioeconomic challenges. Patients are asked to modify their diets, perhaps in ways tough on family food budgets. Exercise is important, but not always feasible for people working two jobs to make ends meet. Then there’s the medical environment, where it’s difficult even for insured people to maintain access to medications and keep taking them consistently.  “If you don’t have an advocate in the health care system and you really don’t have a way to keep up with the need for approvals or prior authorizations, being an advocate for yourself — that’s really hard when you are having many social, financial and other stressors,” Patti said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Amid the enthusiasm for all things GLP-1, surgery may not be top of mind for these patients, whatever their socioeconomic circumstances. Neither approach is easy. One dividing line: If someone hopes to lose 100 pounds, that’s more likely with surgery than with medications. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“There’s so many more options now for people, which is great. And people might end up needing more than one modality,” Melanie Jay,  a professor of medicine and population health at New York University who is also director of the NYU Langone Comprehensive Program on Obesity Research, said in an interview. She was not involved in the study. “Obesity is a disease that often needs to be managed lifelong. We don’t have a cure yet, right?”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The biology behind the success of surgery or medical therapy is remarkably similar, something that may be lost in the rush to develop pills to replace injectable medications. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Surgery reduces appetite, too, changing the way nutrients interact with the intestine and resulting in increased secretion of — you guessed it — GLP-1 hormones after a meal. These hormones plus weight loss improve diabetes control. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“You’re not stopping medications because of side effects or because your insurance company is not paying for it anymore,” Patti said. “So it’s a sustained way to activate the same intestinally derived mechanisms that intersect with the brain to change appetite and metabolism.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Jason Samuels, a professor of surgery at Vanderbilt, argues that all therapies for obesity remain underused. Bariatric surgery, despite its track record for safety, effectiveness, and long-term durability, reaches a very small percentage of patients who qualify, he said, and medications don’t help all the people who could benefit. He was not involved in the study, which he called an important evaluation, even if outpaced by newer drugs. &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Looking ahead, next-generation incretin-based agents may narrow the gap for some patients, but real-world durability, tolerability, adherence, and — critically — affordability and access will determine how closely medications can match surgical outcomes across diverse populations,” he said via email about obesity drugs. “Ultimately, we need large, long-term, well-designed studies to clarify the best strategy for a given patient.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Patti wants surgery to still be in the discussion. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“We can look at epidemiology and large population studies, and they all show that bariatric surgery is more effective at improving diabetes control, improving diabetes remission, reducing complications, and prolonging survival,” she said. “But you know, when we’re talking to an individual patient, the question is, what’s the best choice for that particular patient?”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;STAT’s coverage of chronic health issues is supported by a grant from &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bloomberg.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bloomberg Philanthropies&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Our &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/supporters/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;financial supporters&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; are not involved in any decisions about our journalism.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:01:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPaThQYzN6Q0llMlJUaXhkWDJOM1VWcktYSDY0MFRtck1vV3RhaVpMaTRNVENXS01ZbTNiRFczcmxUSTAtaXVhb3VTQ3NDMmljamNOWVVIWXgtZmFHQTNJUGswSVc0ZTl5YWlRbmdlVU9salJxbjVwQkpHaDZRY1liSVhtN1VpV2padDFxQ1psY09vdw</guid></item><item><title>拥有“黄金之心”的21岁里格比男子在意外死亡后继续祝福他人-东爱达荷新闻</title><link>https://www.eastidahonews.com/2026/01/21-year-old-rigby-man-who-had-a-heart-of-gold-continues-to-bless-others-after-unexpected-death/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleText"&gt; &lt;p&gt;RIGBY — A Rigby man, remembered for the selfless life he lived, was able to bless others through organ donation. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Noel Rios, who went by the name Titus Freeman, died on the evening of Oct. 19, 2025, at the age of 21. He was riding his dirt bike — he’s been riding since he was three years old — when he was involved in a crash with a truck half a mile from his home in Rigby. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“He was most likely killed on impact,” Janice Bell, who is Freeman’s aunt, told EastIdahoNews.com. “He had a helmet and all his riding gear on, and it didn’t save him.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mediumRec1Mobile" class="mobile-ad medium-rectangle centered"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On Oct. 13, just days before the accident, Freeman turned 21. Bell said her nephew’s best friend, who is in his late 60s, told him he needed to get a “big boy license” since he was now 21. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“He took Friday off to go get his new drivers license … and he thought to himself (and told his mom), ‘I’m an adult now, I should be a donor.’ He wasn’t a donor before,” Bell explained. “When he went down there (to renew his license), he became a donor. That was Friday, and he was killed Sunday.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="smallTile1Mobile" class="mobile-ad small-tile centered"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;After the accident, Freeman was rushed to Eastern Idaho Regional Medical Center, where his family was told he wouldn’t survive. The hospital found out he was a donor, and he was taken to the Intensive Care Unit and put on life support. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A donor honor walk took place Oct. 22, where Freeman, who had been declared brain dead, was wheeled down to the operating room as family, friends, coworkers and hospital employees lined the hallways. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thanks to Freeman’s decision to become a donor, he helped save the lives of seven other people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mediumRec2Mobile" class="mobile-ad medium-rectangle centered"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“His heart went to another 21-year-old boy in Utah,” Bell, who said she hopes that person goes on to “do great things,” explained. “We don’t know much about his other ones (like) his kidneys and lungs.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure&gt;&lt;a href="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-Freeman-in-hospital.jpeg" class="fancybox"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-Freeman-in-hospital.jpeg" alt="Titus Freeman in hospital." class="alignnone size-full wp-image-804998" srcset="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-Freeman-in-hospital.jpeg 900w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-Freeman-in-hospital-300x167.jpeg 300w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-Freeman-in-hospital-768x427.jpeg 768w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-Freeman-in-hospital-860x478.jpeg 860w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-Freeman-in-hospital-600x333.jpeg 600w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Courtesy photo&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Freeman not only helped others as a donor but also by giving freely and serving those around him, which he did throughout his life. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Freeman worked for Knife River in Idaho Falls at the time of his death. Bell mentioned that he led a crew of men twice his age, and he’d get to work at 5 a.m. to start everybody’s machines so they’d be warm for them.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“He gave his whole crew lunch money (and gas money) all the time,” she said. “When he passed away, they all paid him back in his front loader (that) was his machine. It was full of money.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Freeman, who was born in Caldwell, has one older and one younger sister. Bell said Freeman had a challenging childhood, but he rose above it. At 19, he decided to buy a house in Rigby for his mom.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“She not only loved him — every parent has a favorite, I don’t care what they say. If they say they don’t, they lie — but Titus, the reason he was her favorite is he also loved her the most,” Bell said. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Freeman was a gifted baseball player who enjoyed playing disc golf and going fishing. When he was 12, he rebuilt a snowmobile, and most recently, he was rebuilding the engine in his truck. He got his truck running the day of his accident, but he never got a chance to drive it. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“He was such a good boy. Never in trouble in his life,” Bell recalled. “He didn’t go out drinking. He was in bed by 8 or 9. We call him the old man of the family. He was an anomaly.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mediumRec4Mobile" class="mobile-ad centered"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Bell said losing her nephew was “the worst thing possible,” but she is proud of the lives he was able to save. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“You don’t have to be religious, or you can be, but God — if there is a God — he did this. This must have been part of his plan … of some plan,” she said. “I guess he had a plan for my beautiful, sweet nephew.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Freeman will be honored in Utah this summer when his name is added to “The Celebration of Life Monument.” The &lt;a href="https://www.donorconnect.life/celebration-of-life-monument/"&gt;monument is a memorial and tribute&lt;/a&gt; to individuals both living and deceased that have donated organs, tissue, and eyes for either transplant or research in the intermountain area. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure&gt;&lt;a href="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-and-mom.jpeg" class="fancybox"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-and-mom.jpeg" alt="Titus freeman and mom" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-805001" srcset="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-and-mom.jpeg 900w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-and-mom-300x233.jpeg 300w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-and-mom-768x597.jpeg 768w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-and-mom-860x669.jpeg 860w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-and-mom-643x500.jpeg 643w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-and-mom-600x467.jpeg 600w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Titus Freeman with his mom. | Courtesy photo&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;  &lt;figure&gt;&lt;a href="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-honor-walk.jpeg" class="fancybox"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-honor-walk.jpeg" alt="Titus Freeman's donor honor walk that happened Oct. 22, 2025." class="alignnone size-full wp-image-805000" srcset="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-honor-walk.jpeg 900w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-honor-walk-270x300.jpeg 270w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-honor-walk-768x853.jpeg 768w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-honor-walk-860x956.jpeg 860w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-honor-walk-450x500.jpeg 450w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-honor-walk-600x667.jpeg 600w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Titus Freeman’s donor honor walk that happened Oct. 22, 2025. | Courtesy photo&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;  &lt;figure&gt;&lt;a href="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-truck.jpeg" class="fancybox"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-truck.jpeg" alt="Titus Freeman's truck he had been rebuilding and got running the day of his accident." class="alignnone size-full wp-image-805003" srcset="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-truck.jpeg 900w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-truck-245x300.jpeg 245w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-truck-838x1024.jpeg 838w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-truck-768x939.jpeg 768w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-truck-860x1051.jpeg 860w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-truck-409x500.jpeg 409w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-truck-600x733.jpeg 600w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Titus Freeman’s truck he had been rebuilding and got running the day of his accident. | Courtesy photo&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;  &lt;figure&gt;&lt;a href="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-playing-disc-golf.jpeg" class="fancybox"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-playing-disc-golf.jpeg" alt="Titus Freeman playing disc golf. " class="alignnone size-full wp-image-805002" srcset="https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-playing-disc-golf.jpeg 900w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-playing-disc-golf-300x267.jpeg 300w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-playing-disc-golf-768x683.jpeg 768w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-playing-disc-golf-860x764.jpeg 860w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-playing-disc-golf-563x500.jpeg 563w, https://s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Titus-freeman-playing-disc-golf-600x533.jpeg 600w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Titus Freeman playing disc golf. | Courtesy photo&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>East Idaho News</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:49:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizgFBVV95cUxPaHVsRGFXc3NxcmVoTWdlWTc4dC1TM0YtZEdwcmpDZFBOcTR4U2daRXZDa3NfUHlUYVp2LU1CZGEtaTdMSkNvWmdzSzdhNWVmYm5uNmdYckxmamR3SDdxMFBaeWZsc2VtUkhDTVF0em8xUE1BdXFWTUNUSkZ2QVRfNmRLemNoWGIzaGxOTXVLcWo3WnEwVlZTaVA0eGhWbTdBM253SW5tdzJBLUY0UXh4eF9lSTRKd3k2bGd6Y0hrNkxRbGVzWVUtMEVFaVdDQQ</guid></item><item><title>“维多利亚病”爆发袭击亚马逊仓库：您应该知道的事情-伦敦标准晚报</title><link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/uk/victorian-disease-outbreak-amazon-warehouse-what-you-should-know-b1267141.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="main" class="sc-iPahhU ifKSyh"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.standard.co.uk/business/business-news/milton-keynes-northampton-b1266524.html"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; has confirmed an outbreak of what has been referred to as “Victorian disease” at one of its major UK warehouses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term refers to illnesses once common in the 19th century, and in this case it relates to tuberculosis (TB), a bacterial infection that, while now largely preventable and treatable, still exists in &lt;a href="https://www.standard.co.uk/news/health/tuberculosis-tb-cases-london-six-year-high-b1112822.html"&gt;modern Britain&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outbreak occurred at Amazon’s Coventry warehouse, which employs around 3,000 people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the company, 10 workers tested positive for non-contagious &lt;a href="https://www.standard.co.uk/news/health/tuberculosis-tb-london-cases-uk-health-nhs-symptoms-b1139480.html"&gt;tuberculosis&lt;/a&gt; known as latent TB during screenings carried out in September 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Latent TB means the bacteria are present in the body but the person does not have symptoms and is not contagious in that state. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials have stressed that people with latent TB cannot spread the infection to others, and those diagnosed are reportedly responding well to treatment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-iUHWHT epNhre"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-khYOSX dQSoIL"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Safety measures and testing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon brought in staff from the NHS and the UK Health Security Agency (UKHSA) to conduct wider blood testing “out of an abundance of caution”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company says it has followed medical guidance throughout and that there have been no further confirmed cases since the initial detection. Operations at the warehouse, it adds, continue as normal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite reassurances from Amazon and health officials, the episode has triggered strong reactions from unions and politicians. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The GMB union, which represents many of the warehouse’s employees, called for the site to be temporarily closed and all staff sent home on full pay until proper infection control measures are in place, the BBC has reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some union leaders said the presence of TB, a disease once endemic in overcrowded Victorian cities, highlights ongoing concerns about workplace conditions in large warehouses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.standard.co.uk/news/politics/zarah-sultana-labour-mp-coventry-south-jeremy-corbyn-party-b1159562.html"&gt;Local MP Zarah Sultana&lt;/a&gt; described Amazon’s choice to keep the facility open as “outrageous” accusing the company of treating workers as if they were “disposable.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;She urged stronger protections for employees and said the situation was a reminder of long-standing debates around labour rights and public health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-iUHWHT epNhre"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-khYOSX dQSoIL"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How common is Tuberculosis today?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;TB itself is a bacterial infection primarily affecting the lungs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the UK has modern treatments, including antibiotics and vaccines, TB was once one of the country’s deadliest diseases, earning labels like “consumption” in the&lt;a href="https://www.standard.co.uk/news/london/new-interactive-map-of-100-000-photos-and-videos-reveal-lost-london-in-the-victorian-era-a3302496.html"&gt; Victorian&lt;/a&gt; era. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;UKHSA data suggests that TB cases have been rising in recent years, with nearly 5,500 reported in England in 2024, up from around 4,800 in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-gEvEer kGHzwr"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aXZVg iLuLZl"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health experts emphasise that latent TB is not immediately dangerous to the public, but recommend that anyone who believes they have been exposed undergoes screening. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>London Evening Standard</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:45:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQTjRZV2RmUTVTSTdkM1BTaVdhQ0F3RnotRVZCNmhqUVBkc0ZGZnh1N1RyVFJMaml3cUhjdW9EcTgxbHZwakJrXzB5M3dvUlpnMFZ4X3V0Ym1LYnpYMllDMTZQZmk3XzRKYjd0R1NCSW84UEV6d0xncmgxMHphUTgtSEkyRWQtRHU4emxwOVNmSW1rQzE5TWQ5SWtJMS1ab1VFS2h6RFlrVnZObks1a3I2YlJyMA</guid></item><item><title>流感无处不在。那么，为什么加拿大人没有接种病毒性疾病的疫苗？ -对话</title><link>https://theconversation.com/the-flu-is-everywhere-so-why-arent-canadians-getting-vaccinated-for-viral-illnesses-273354</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="grid-ten large-grid-nine grid-last content-body content entry-content instapaper_body inline-promos" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The death of &lt;a href="https://globalnews.ca/news/11590698/edmonton-grey-nuns-hospital-emergency-room-death/"&gt;Prashant Sreekumar&lt;/a&gt; made headlines across Canada when the 43-year-old father of three died in the emergency room of Edmonton’s Grey Nuns hospital after waiting for eight hours with chest pains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, there have been other reports of preventable deaths in &lt;a href="https://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-overcrowding-alberta-emergency-hospital-preventable-death/"&gt;Alberta ERs&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href="https://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-edmonton-doctors-call-on-alberta-government-to-declare-state-of/"&gt;Alberta doctors&lt;/a&gt; have called the emergency room situation a disaster, citing a tsunami of seasonal respiratory illnesses that have overwhelmed hospitals and led to crowded emergency departments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Widespread vaccination for common respiratory illnesses, including COVID-19 and the flu, would help to relieve the pressure on hospitals. Yet vaccination rates for seasonal illness &lt;a href="https://health-infobase.canada.ca/vaccination/seasonal-respiratory-vaccination-coverage-survey/report.html"&gt;are falling across Canada&lt;/a&gt;. Our research shows that conflicting messages across levels of government and skepticism about whether the vaccines work may be helping to fuel the emergency-room surge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This winter is not the first bad virus season in Alberta, nor is it the first time we’ve seen patients die waiting for care. During the 2022-23 viral illness season, a &lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/health/covid-flu-rsv-pneumonia-1.7052339"&gt;“tripledemic” of viruses&lt;/a&gt; rolled across the country, as COVID-19, influenza and respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) circulated simultaneously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s10826-024-02986-w"&gt;Our research showed&lt;/a&gt; how this tripledemic also slammed working parents trying to &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/as-back-to-school-season-approaches-canadian-employers-are-making-a-mistake-by-mandating-workers-back-to-the-office-263251"&gt;maintain their jobs&lt;/a&gt; while they and their children were infected over and over again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="align-center "&gt;
            
            &lt;figcaption&gt;
              &lt;span class="caption"&gt;With seasonal vaccination rates declining each year, Canada now falls far short of the 80 per cent vaccination coverage needed to protect at-risk groups such as seniors or people with chronic illness.&lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;span class="attribution"&gt;&lt;span class="source"&gt;THE CANADIAN PRESS/Jeff McIntosh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;
          &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year could prove even worse. The 2025-26 season marks a new height in influenza cases, &lt;a href="https://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-flu-cases-in-canada-rise-above-three-season-high/"&gt;rising above a three-season high&lt;/a&gt;. Hospitals across the country have been flooded with patients, and burnt-out health-care workers have been putting in &lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/health/canada-flu-season-hospitals-9.7025077"&gt;extra shifts&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite all of this — and the overwhelming research that shows influenza vaccines &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cmi.2025.09.023"&gt;keep people out of the hospital&lt;/a&gt; — &lt;a href="https://health-infobase.canada.ca/vaccination/seasonal-respiratory-vaccination-coverage-survey/report.html"&gt;fewer Canadians are getting vaccinated&lt;/a&gt;. With &lt;a href="https://health-infobase.canada.ca/vaccination/seasonal-respiratory-vaccination-coverage-survey/report.html"&gt;declining seasonal vaccination rates&lt;/a&gt; each year, Canada now falls far short of the vaccination coverage needed to protect &lt;a href="https://publications.gc.ca/collections/collection_2025/aspc-phac/H14-659-2025-eng.pdf"&gt;at-risk groups such as seniors or people with chronic illness, which is 80 per cent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who do Canadians trust on health care?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our research explored &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/00380253.2025.2539348"&gt;parental decision-making in Alberta&lt;/a&gt; during the tripledemic to understand why, or why not, people get themselves and their kids vaccinated for COVID-19 and influenza. Using &lt;a href="https://www.commongroundpolitics.ca/viewpoint-alberta"&gt;Viewpoint Alberta&lt;/a&gt; survey data, we found that who parents trust and the messages governments provide around vaccination strongly influence whether they and their kids get shots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the pandemic, parents in Alberta faced conflicting messages from governments. Despite the &lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/trudeau-tam-safe-effective-naci-1.6013297"&gt;promotion of vaccination&lt;/a&gt; by the federal government and public health agencies, the provincial United Conservative Party government took a &lt;a href="https://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/alberta/article-danielle-smith-alberta-unvaccinated/"&gt;strong stance&lt;/a&gt; against enforcing COVID-19 protective measures. For those who trusted the provincial government, this essentially negated any pro-vaccination messaging provided by other institutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our study found that those who trusted the federal government as a source of health information were more likely to have vaccinated their children for COVID-19 than those who supported the Alberta government’s messaging. The same was true for those who trusted Alberta Health Services and the Chief Medical Officer of Health. Those who placed their trust in the elected UCP government had much lower vaccination rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trust is important, but it’s not the only factor keeping seasonal vaccination rates low. The question of who is perceived to benefit from vaccination also shaped parents’ decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Are seasonal vaccines worth the trouble?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to looking at survey data, we also interviewed parents to better understand how they made their decisions regarding seasonal vaccination for themselves and their children. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="align-center "&gt;
            
            &lt;figcaption&gt;
              &lt;span class="caption"&gt;Persistent illness contributed to parents’ sense that infection was both inevitable and mild, often not even worth preventing.&lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;span class="attribution"&gt;&lt;span class="source"&gt;(Unsplash+/Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;
          &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were surprised to learn that after repeated viral illness infections, parents were actually less likely to vaccinate their children. Persistent illness contributed to a sense that infection was both inevitable and mild, often not even worth preventing. Some parents were also skeptical of the novelty of the COVID-19 vaccine compared to more established vaccinations, despite assurances from health-care professionals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These parents did not hold “anti-vaxxer” beliefs; instead they believed that viral illness season was inevitable, and of little risk to themselves and their children. On top of this, the struggle to balance work and child care already made it difficult for many families to get vaccinated. Because the vaccine didn’t prevent infections altogether, many parents believed it was not worth the added effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Canada needs a new approach&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Canada does not have the resources to continue this yearly severe illness cycle. Without better uptake of seasonal vaccines, we are doomed to repeat the same mistakes year after year, resulting in more needless deaths and health system crises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="align-center "&gt;
            
            &lt;figcaption&gt;
              &lt;span class="caption"&gt;All levels of government have a role to play in building public trust in seasonal vaccines, and in making sure those shots are accessible to everyone.&lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;span class="attribution"&gt;&lt;span class="source"&gt;THE CANADIAN PRESS/Lars Hagberg&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;
          &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clear and consistent messaging is key, and the messages of provincial leaders must match those of the federal government. Our research shows that all levels of government have a role to play in building public trust in seasonal vaccines, and in making sure those shots are accessible to everyone. Vaccines must be available freely, widely and early, without &lt;a href="https://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/alberta/article-albertans-brace-danielle-smith-covid-vaccine-program/"&gt;pre-booking and payment&lt;/a&gt; requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tragedy of patients dying while waiting for care in a busy emergency room illustrates the dangers of overcrowded facilities. Higher vaccination rates could help prevent respiratory illnesses from overwhelming hospitals. Our governments need to step up and step forward to build public trust and accessibility for seasonal vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

        

        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Conversation</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:38:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxNMHpySmRzSTdnOUNtekgzUUhONWtzZ085d2t5bERWYkhmNEx5bFhlNkxqamo5bmpwODZ6akl3Q0xoWVQyV2hQVVRVSzJ4YnV0QVFzdS1qM2kzSS0tV2tJNDd1MVZfSF8xd0xmQlFocTVERm5Cb1d3cnJQeXFZV01hSGpkTllvdE1tY1RuRWYtLXM2RE5LYnlMQ3d4aFA3b3JSQjlWOTRqNEpNeUFzS0VHd0lxZy1Ob2RWS2c</guid></item><item><title>专家说，手指刺血试验“可能彻底改变”阿尔茨海默氏症的诊断-地面新闻</title><link>https://ground.news/article/alzheimers-finger-prick-blood-test-could-transform-diagnosis-experts-say_2db12a</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="text-16 pt-[0.44rem] leading-8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay calm on Greenland UK tells Trump and EU&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ground News</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxOc3FaS0hibGpBaXVrQjBBNUtxYzJDdVdhSUV0Wkp2cFZKWXRRcUltRW1xLVVQVlVsX1F4ZUxWemNYZmpORUtHSHJzeTlaWFFOUmUyVE1xTzg2VUxGZlVRU0k3dncxdEtfdWpJSHZwWjhIR0dOX0hxNHdzbi14Rl9xVUVxclcxMDZRajZ4aWYydnJLY2VTZFB4WnZxS2pCREltNlR1Z0VfdHJqbEk</guid></item><item><title>为什么同样的感冒病毒会让一些人比其他人更痛苦-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/19/common-cold-virus-variability/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XMMS2EXGLFB4RFDCWN4VPBJRWY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;When the common cold rips through a household, it can leave a wildly uneven path of symptoms. The same  cold-causing rhinovirus that produces barely a sniffle in one person can cause a week of stuffy-nose suffering in the next and in others trigger coughing and trouble breathing that can send them to the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:31:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxOV3I4QjJLMjhodUd6cF9IRk1MdWhUR3RQWS1vYnMwR1p4VjQ0c09wRncwTkRySTZuZzRCaUtEU2oxNzlkTEYxLXhTR0lRd2lfdVplZEtzc2V5bzF4MXRPZjRhekhWeTNaZFFVUDZQcWNra2htWmkyODFETE1hNVZmYUsydnNtdw</guid></item><item><title>两所南卡罗来纳州大学在校园内确认麻疹病例- WIS新闻10</title><link>https://www.wistv.com/2026/01/19/two-sc-colleges-confirm-measles-cases-campus/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body | article w-100"&gt;&lt;p class="text | text-start article-text"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE: The above video is a livestream of WIS featuring current newscasts, Soda City Living and Gray Media’s Local News Live.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="divider | border-bottom mx-auto w-75 my-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | text-start article-text"&gt;GREENVILLE, S.C. (WIS/&lt;a href="https://www.foxcarolina.com/2026/01/19/student-anderson-university-confirmed-have-measles/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.foxcarolina.com/2026/01/19/student-anderson-university-confirmed-have-measles/"&gt;FOX Carolina&lt;/a&gt;) - Two South Carolina colleges have confirmed cases of measles on their respective campuses, &lt;a href="https://www.foxcarolina.com/2026/01/19/student-anderson-university-confirmed-have-measles/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.foxcarolina.com/2026/01/19/student-anderson-university-confirmed-have-measles/"&gt;FOX Carolina reports.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | text-start article-text"&gt;&lt;b&gt;ANDERSON UNIVERSITY&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | text-start article-text"&gt;On Monday, Anderson University confirmed one of its students was diagnosed and could have exposed others to the virus. That student is no longer on campus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="w-100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | text-start article-text"&gt;&lt;b&gt;MORE COVERAGE | &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wistv.com/2026/01/19/south-carolinas-measles-outbreak-surges-worst-country/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.wistv.com/2026/01/19/south-carolinas-measles-outbreak-surges-worst-country/"&gt;South Carolina’s measles outbreak surges to worst in the country&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;School officials are asking anyone who thinks they have been exposed to stay home from class, work and public areas. Measles is contagious for days before the rash appears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Anyone on campus who may have been exposed is asked to call Thrive Wellness Center at 864-622-6078 before visiting in person to prevent further spread or contact your personal health care provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | text-start article-text"&gt;&lt;b&gt;CLEMSON UNIVERSITY&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="w-100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | text-start article-text"&gt;Over the weekend, Clemson University announced the South Carolina Department of Public Health informed officials of the case. That person has since entered quarantine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;The most recent data from Student Health Services shows nearly 98% of main campus students have provided proof of immunity, according to the university.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | text-start article-text"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Feel more informed, prepared, and connected with WIS. For more free content like this, subscribe to our &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wistv.com/newsletter/" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;i&gt;email newsletter&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;, and &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wistv.com/page/apps/" rel="noreferrer"&gt;&lt;i&gt;download our apps&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;i&gt;Have feedback that can help us improve? &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:wis-webproducers@gray.tv?subject=[please%20include%20the%20article%27s%20headline%20here]" rel="noreferrer"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Click here&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="copyright |"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Copyright 2026 WIS. All rights reserved.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIS News 10</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:25:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQMWVJWFNDTFRKWkJFeU9zcmRES0tRbVE1TnNmOC0wVk5tS2pXaDR0a19qM2g1bURiWWpoc3BkeUtzc0F2YWFjZzZ0VDFEU01IcE1FT1RFQVM1Znd4VFpPSGpQUWhBWUdwVHotUWhNdUJmczlDZE9rX3VZN3hBWlo1WkxuSVc</guid></item><item><title>研究人员发现，心脏病发作后人体心脏再生肌肉细胞- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-human-heart-regrows-muscle-cells.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:16:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxPYXRmclp3YTRGSUFiR1ZPSWYyUHppNk9rNU9zNjRwSjA0NW1Cb1RUbGtZaDZIQXpFeC1tT3lFX1g5cmNIMWZCaFhzVTV3S2swWW5kOWp3SDBWSDZPS2lOT2RsbXRYQzdhN1UxUmM0VFFGOTdXeFJtTUxFUjN5MWVCdmpR</guid></item><item><title>在压力奥运会中没有金牌–这里是如何开始休息的-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2026/jan/19/how-to-start-resting</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;E&lt;/span&gt;very new year – after the holiday glut of travel, parties, shopping and baked goods – there can be pressure to do and be more: more active, more productive, more creative, more thrifty. Maybe this will be the year I finally start meal planning or doing morning pages. New year, new me!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But what if the thing we needed more of was to do less? What if this was the year we finally learned to rest?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We all involuntarily participate in the stress Olympics, and are aware that the busiest person wins gold,” says Amelia Nagoski, co-author of &lt;a href="https://www.burnoutbook.net/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Burnout: The Secret to Unlocking the Stress Cycle&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In a culture that glamorizes hard work, sacrifice and the grind, rest is often seen as self-indulgent and lazy, Nagoski says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Not only does this attitude leave us worn out, it’s counterproductive. “Rest is what helps us function at our highest level of capacity,” says Dr &lt;a href="https://www.drdaltonsmith.com/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Saundra Dalton-Smith&lt;/a&gt;, a physician and &lt;a href="https://www.drdaltonsmith.com/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;author&lt;/a&gt; of Sacred Rest. Although many people are accustomed to pushing through feelings of tiredness, doing so generally results in a lower quality of work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;So why not start this year more energized and less depleted? Here’s how to start resting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-is-rest" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is rest?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Rest is anything that gives you more energy,” says Nagoski.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;This doesn’t necessarily mean a cessation of activities, she adds: “Sometimes, it’s just doing different things.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Indeed, the most restorative rest is often more active than passive, argues Alex Soojung-Kim Pang, author of &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/money/2017/jan/22/alex-soojung-kim-pang-interview-rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Rest: Why You Get More Done When You Work Less&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“That’s not to say there’s anything wrong with sitting on the couch with a bag of salty snacks in one hand and the TV remote in another,” he says. “But the things that deliver the biggest restorative bang for your buck are things like going for a walk, spending time in nature or exercising.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-are-the-biggest-obstacles-to-rest" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the biggest obstacles to rest?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If a twisted scientist were to sit down and invent a society designed to de-legitimize rest, it would look a lot like ours, says Pang.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We all come with decades of cultural programming that tells us that in order to succeed, we have to spend enormous amounts of time at work,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There is another, more personal obstacle: many people don’t know what kind of rest they need. As we’ll see below, there are many ways to catch a break.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="take-rest-seriously" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take rest seriously&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;So you’re finally open to throwing off the yoke of overwork. But how does one actually incorporate more rest into their lives? If you’ve read this far, that’s a good start. “If you’re asking this question, you’re taking rest seriously,” says Pang. “That’s the first thing you’ve got to do.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="look-at-how-you-work" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look at how you work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If you are in a job that allows you to have some control over your schedule, Pang suggests combining periods of deep, focused work – 90 minutes to two hours – with breaks of about half an hour. The break could be running errands, going for a walk or having lunch – anything that’s not work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"index":19,"listId":6039,"identityName":"well-actually","description":"Practical advice, expert insights and answers to your questions about how to live a good life","name":"Well Actually","frequency":"Weekly","successDescription":"You are subscribed","theme":"lifestyle","idApiUrl":"https://idapi.theguardian.com","hideNewsletterSignupComponentForSubscribers":true}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;gu-island name="InteractiveBlockComponent" priority="critical" deferuntil="idle" props='{"url":"https://interactive.guim.co.uk/uploader/embed/2023/10/archive-zip/giv-13425WMrLo2pc9VIk/","scriptUrl":"https://interactive.guim.co.uk/embed/iframe-wrapper/0.1/boot.js","alt":"Graphic with three lines of text that say, in bold, ‘Well Actually’, then ‘Read more on living a good life in a complex world,’ then a pinkish-lavender pill-shaped button with white letters that say ‘More from this section’","format":{"design":10,"display":2,"theme":4},"elementId":"220f3eea-5cec-4929-85b5-c137a93f8211","isMainMedia":false}'&gt;&lt;figure id="220f3eea-5cec-4929-85b5-c137a93f8211" class="element element-interactive element--inline element-inline dcr-w422y2" data-alt="Graphic with three lines of text that say, in bold, ‘Well Actually’, then ‘Read more on living a good life in a complex world,’ then a pinkish-lavender pill-shaped button with white letters that say ‘More from this section’" data-testid="interactive-element-Graphic%20with%20three%20lines%20of%20text%20that%20say,%20in%20bold,%20%E2%80%98Well%20Actually%E2%80%99,%20then%20%E2%80%98Read%20more%20on%20living%20a%20good%20life%20in%20a%20complex%20world,%E2%80%99%20then%20a%20pinkish-lavender%20pill-shaped%20button%20with%20white%20letters%20that%20say%20%E2%80%98More%20from%20this%20section%E2%80%99" data-spacefinder-role="inline"&gt;&lt;a data-name="placeholder" href="https://interactive.guim.co.uk/uploader/embed/2023/10/archive-zip/giv-13425WMrLo2pc9VIk/" class="dcr-1eupayo"&gt;Graphic with three lines of text that say, in bold, ‘Well Actually’, then ‘Read more on living a good life in a complex world,’ then a pinkish-lavender pill-shaped button with white letters that say ‘More from this section’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If your job does not have a predictable schedule, Pang recommends better preserving nights and weekends. He points to &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8775585/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; that &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33424717/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;show&lt;/a&gt; that people who have better boundaries between work and non-work time are more likely to have longer, happier careers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="think-about-what-kind-of-rest-you-need" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Think about what kind of rest you need&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;When she worked in a hospital ICU, Dalton-Smith said she got eight hours of sleep a night, but still felt exhausted most days. Eventually, she realized the rest she needed was emotional, because the amount of energy required to appear calm in the face of horrible situations was leaving her depleted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Drawing on Dalton-Smith’s work, the &lt;a href="https://www.apa.org/topics/mental-health/seven-rest-types" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;American Psychological Association&lt;/a&gt; put together examples of how to practice the seven types of rest:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Physical rest: making sure you get enough sleep; taking naps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Mental rest: journaling; meditating; doing tasks that are not mentally taxing, like puzzles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Emotional rest: talking through feelings and experiences with a friend or therapist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Social rest: setting aside time alone to recharge; making sure you’re spending time with people who don’t leave you feeling drained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Sensory rest: spending time outdoors; taking breaks from screens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Creative rest: engaging in creative hobbies like drawing, reading or dancing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Spiritual rest: connecting to a cause or tradition that feels meaningful to you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 id="enlist-others-for-help" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enlist others for help&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Perhaps the most important and effective way to incorporate more rest into your life is to recruit other people in your efforts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Nagoski explains that she and her twin sister, sex educator and researcher Emily Nagoski, were inspired to write Burnout together after Amelia ended up in an emergency room with stress-induced illness. “My sister drove two-and-a-half hours to the hospital and fed me a big stack of journal articles about rest and the importance of overcoming burnout,” Nagoski says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Experts agree this kind of care and support – reminding loved ones that their wellbeing is more important than work – is essential to pushing back against a culture of overwork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“All these external pressures to sacrifice and give everything you have to give – it’s like a rushing river,” Nagoski says. “If you try to stand against it alone, you’re going to get washed away really fast. But if you surround yourself with people who care about your wellbeing as much as you care about theirs, you can all stand together, and that’s the only way to resist the river.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:06:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE81ZW5CRVU1ZUY3RjFHZU9aamJWZ2F1LVJlNGNvWE8ydllyRWJEVVdsd1J0SE1qVkczRmVlUlBZNmNXS2Y1azdUV2NZeGhDWU1XNk90ZjhsR0RHT05vRlFNNm5FVENxdTZVRnZKMExmNi1TaTBTSkhyeg</guid></item><item><title>我们都会犯的一个意大利面错误，以及为什么它会破坏晚餐- Ynetnews</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/food/article/r1phjk2h11e</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-contents="true"&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="714jr-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="714jr-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="714jr-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;She’s always there when you need something comforting and quick: just a pot of water with salt and a bit of sauce, and dinner’s ready. You don’t need a culinary degree to cook it — or an Italian grandmother (though that certainly helps). &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="1k5j3-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1k5j3-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1k5j3-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;But once you dig a little deeper, you’ll find that pasta is far more than just “noodles with sauce.” It comes with rules, traditions and a world of reasons why a simple dish can turn out either heavenly or totally forgettable.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="debdu-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide firstImageInArticle firstImageInArticleBody"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.ryesHeynr11l" id="image_ArticleImageData.ryesHeynr11l"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;7&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.ryesHeynr11l" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/18/BJ2ujAdqHbe/BJ2ujAdqHbe_0_0_720_1280_0_x-large.jpg" alt="פסטה" title="Pasta  (Photo: Sapir Gordo) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.ryesHeynr11l" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/18/BJ2ujAdqHbe/BJ2ujAdqHbe_0_0_720_1280_0_x-large.jpg" alt="פסטה" title="Pasta  (Photo: Sapir Gordo) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Pasta &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Sapir Gordo&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="ds9qk-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="ds9qk-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="ds9qk-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;To find out what we’ve been doing wrong and how to get it right, we set out to bust common myths (starting with the classic one about adding oil to the cooking water), uncover the secrets to matching shapes and sauces and discover surprising ways to make this beloved carb part of a balanced, healthy meal. Ready? The water’s boiling.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="44k8f-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="44k8f-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="44k8f-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Think the only difference between fusilli and spaghetti is how they look? Think again. Every twist, hole and fold in the dough serves a precise culinary-engineering function, all designed to ensure the pasta and sauce pair in perfect harmony. “Just like we wouldn’t expect an Italian to know how to make Israeli food, we also have gaps in understanding pasta,” explains Claude Ben-Itach, owner of the Fresh Pasta factory.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="7a0j3-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.ByevUeyhr11l" id="image_ArticleImageData.ByevUeyhr11l"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;7&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.ByevUeyhr11l" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/18/H17OjRd9HWe/H17OjRd9HWe_0_0_1280_720_0_x-large.jpg" alt="קלוד בן-איטח" title="Claude Ben-Itach  (Photo: Sapir Gordo) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.ByevUeyhr11l" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/18/H17OjRd9HWe/H17OjRd9HWe_0_0_1280_720_0_x-large.jpg" alt="קלוד בן-איטח" title="Claude Ben-Itach  (Photo: Sapir Gordo) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Claude Ben-Itach &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Sapir Gordo&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="cf8dg-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="cf8dg-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="cf8dg-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;So why are there so many shapes?
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="cf8dg-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“First, you’re talking about a country with a wide range of regions. There’s a big difference between the north and south of Italy — the ingredients behave differently, the temperatures vary. Then there’s the history: before the industrial revolution, most pasta was handmade. There are still shapes that machines can’t replicate. What started out as ‘mistakes’ at home often became classics.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="899rj-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="899rj-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="899rj-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;He divides pasta into families: “There are the long, wide noodles like fettuccine, tagliatelle and pappardelle; the short pastas like rigatoni and penne; and the stuffed pastas like ravioli and tortellini. Each of these works best with different kinds of sauces. Short pastas pair well with chunky sauces — seafood, meat, fish. Thin pastas like spaghetti, tagliolini and linguine go best with light, oil-based sauces. Stuffed pastas usually need something delicate like butter — you don’t want to overshadow the filling.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="f5ep6-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.HJeyDlJnrWl" id="image_ArticleImageData.HJeyDlJnrWl"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;7&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.HJeyDlJnrWl" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/18/r1gdoRdcrbl/r1gdoRdcrbl_0_0_1280_853_0_x-large.jpg" alt="פסטה" title="Ravioli  (Photo: Assaf Carla) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.HJeyDlJnrWl" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/18/r1gdoRdcrbl/r1gdoRdcrbl_0_0_1280_853_0_x-large.jpg" alt="פסטה" title="Ravioli  (Photo: Assaf Carla) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Ravioli &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Assaf Carla&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="2l1id-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2l1id-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2l1id-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;So how do you pair sauce and pasta correctly?
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2l1id-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“The critical point is that the pasta has to hold the sauce. Long, wide noodles need a thick, rich sauce that clings to them and doesn’t slide off. Take, for example, a mushroom ragù with pappardelle — olive oil wouldn’t cut it; you need something rich and reduced that sticks to the pasta’s width.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="2uqe0-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2uqe0-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2uqe0-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“On the other hand, thin pastas like linguine can’t carry heavy sauces — you’ll just end up with soup. There you need something light, like olive oil-based sauces (aglio e olio). Hollow pastas need sauces that can seep inside and coat them from within, so every bite bursts with flavor. The most important thing to remember: pasta is always the star of the dish — the sauce is the supporting act. If the sauce is what shouts the loudest, something’s gone wrong.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="4c4t3-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4c4t3-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4c4t3-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;After diving into the theory of pasta perfection, it’s time to step into the kitchen. But as it turns out, some of our most instinctive cooking habits may be the very ones sabotaging our pasta. Ben-Itach breaks down the most common mistakes and how to fix them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="bmib0-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="72dub-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="72dub-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="72dub-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;How do you really know when pasta is done?
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="72dub-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“We want to avoid overcooking. The classic and simplest method — no need for a culinary degree — is to taste it. Another way is to cut the pasta in half: you’ll see a small white dot in the center. That’s the point you want to reach — and not go past. Also, watch how the pasta behaves in the pot: it shouldn’t sink to the bottom, it should move in circulation. When it’s moving around in the pot, you’re close to done.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="bf6ir-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="bf6ir-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="bf6ir-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;What are the biggest mistakes we make in home cooking?
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="bf6ir-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“The number one mistake is adding oil to the water, thinking it prevents sticking. It doesn’t — and actually does damage. Pasta cooked in oily water comes out coated in oil, so the sauce won’t stick. Another major mistake is rinsing pasta with cold water, which washes away the starch — what we call ‘liquid gold.’ Starch is critical for helping the sauce cling to the pasta, and when you rinse it off, it all goes down the drain and the sauce won’t hold. Also, using a pot that’s too small or not enough water will throw things off.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="44tcr-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="e5eq2-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="e5eq2-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="e5eq2-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;What about sauce-making — where do we go wrong there?
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="e5eq2-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“A classic mistake is burning the onion or garlic. That ruins the flavor and spoils the sauce. With tomato sauce, people often overcook it — if you simmer it for over an hour, the acidity and sugars break down. Another issue is overcrowding the sauce with too many ingredients — people throw in too much, and the sauce becomes overloaded. You end up not really tasting anything. Minimalism is the way to go.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="cecc2-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="cecc2-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="cecc2-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Any advanced tips to elevate homemade pasta?
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="cecc2-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“Italians pull the pasta out two minutes early — even before it hits al dente — and add it directly into the sauce pan with a splash of the cooking water. Then you simmer everything together for two or three minutes, let it reduce, add a pat of butter at the end — and that’s it. It’s kind of like playing with Play-Doh with your kids. Pasta is forgiving — it’s not one of those dishes where if you mess up, it’s ruined and inedible. I highly recommend experimenting at home, even with your kids. It’s a great activity.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="c9eh4-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="c9eh4-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="c9eh4-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;After mastering how to cook pasta, it’s time to talk nutrition. Dietitian Meital Levy shares how to turn this beloved carb from foe to friend, and reveals a surprising tip that could change the way you think about leftovers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="8bf69-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="c7uhf-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="c7uhf-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="c7uhf-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;What are pasta’s main nutritional values?
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="c7uhf-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“That depends on the flour. Pasta made from white flour is a fairly simple carbohydrate. On the one hand, it provides quick energy, which makes it great before physical activity. On the other hand, if the pasta is made from whole wheat, it contains fiber, iron, magnesium and selenium. If it’s made from legumes, it offers all the nutritional benefits of legumes — more minerals and fiber. It’s easy to digest and provides long-lasting energy, without the digestive effects sometimes associated with legumes or rice.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="4bgpk-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4bgpk-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4bgpk-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;How does the sauce affect how healthy the dish is?
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4bgpk-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“The sauce is a major component of the meal. If you use saturated fat, like cream, the dish becomes less healthy. But if you use tomato-based or vegetable sauces, you’re adding fiber and antioxidants. A sauce made from olive oil and basil or pesto, for example, with added walnuts, is rich in healthy fats.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="7qu19-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="dlbed-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="dlbed-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="dlbed-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;How can home cooks maximize pasta’s health benefits?
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="dlbed-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“Shorter cooking times help preserve nutrients. But there’s a big bonus to eating pasta after it’s been cooled in the fridge, rather than fresh off the stove. Cooling turns its starch into what’s called ‘resistant starch,’ which causes a smaller spike in blood sugar and is easier on the gut — ideal for those with irritable bowel syndrome. For a balanced meal, aim to combine healthy fats (like olive oil or nuts), vegetables in or alongside the sauce, and a protein source.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="91j5a" data-offset-key="7tot7-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7tot7-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7tot7-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;What’s the healthiest combination?
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7tot7-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“Whole wheat or lentil pasta is best — it’s high in fiber and minerals. Pair it with a pesto or tomato-based sauce, or one combining olive oil and vegetables. Add in walnuts or pine nuts, and finish with protein — whether that’s cheese in the pasta or a side salad with tuna or another lean protein.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:00:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiXkFVX3lxTFBCNklCbHlCZ3pNT0h2VmNYU0ZFSGdSby1tT0tmb0Y3eXVVQTh6NHppMVZKN19aZXlvdjkxVzhkdDlfWV9pOVJVNHl4VlhxbE5ycTRCVE8ycHY4QkVpZVE</guid></item><item><title>我们向营养师询问了排名第一的烹饪技巧，以帮助降低胆固醇- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/cooking-tip-to-help-lower-your-cholesterol-11886146</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Swap saturated fats for unsaturated fats to help lower LDL cholesterol.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Replace butter, coconut oil and lard with olive, avocado or other plant-based oils.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Boost fiber, stay active and choose snacks that support heart health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; You’ve probably heard your doctor mention cholesterol at your last checkup, but what does it really mean for your health? Cholesterol is a waxy substance in your blood that, when elevated, can increase your risk for heart disease. High levels of LDL (“bad”) cholesterol can lead to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/high-cholesterol-cardiologist-recommendations-11780658" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;plaque buildup in your arteries&lt;/a&gt;, raising your risk of heart attack and stroke. While medication can help manage cholesterol, your diet and cooking habits can make a big difference too.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The good news? Heart-healthy meals don’t have to be complicated or bland. We asked registered dietitians for the single most impactful cooking tip for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/myths-about-high-cholesterol-to-stop-believing-11794255" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;managing cholesterol&lt;/a&gt;, and the answer is surprisingly simple.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-why-swapping-saturated-fats-for-unsaturated-fats-helps-lower-cholesterol"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Why Swapping Saturated Fats for Unsaturated Fats Helps Lower Cholesterol &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The cooking swap that can make a real difference for your cholesterol is replacing saturated fats—like butter, coconut oil and lard—with unsaturated fats such as olive oil, avocado oil and other plant-based oils. This simple change can help improve your cholesterol without overhauling your entire diet.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In fact, the science behind this swap is pretty impressive. &lt;a href="https://entirelynourished.com/about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Michelle Routhenstein, M.S., RD, CDCES, CDN&lt;/a&gt;, points to a study in which participants cut saturated fat from about 19% of total calories to under 10% and increased unsaturated fat from 15% to 25% of calories. In just four weeks, this led to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/290873/how-to-lower-triglycerides-ldl-cholesterol/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;meaningful improvements in LDL cholesterol&lt;/a&gt; and other markers of heart health.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Routhenstein explains that unsaturated fats can help remove LDL cholesterol already in your bloodstream and may modestly reduce vascular inflammation. Other recent studies support this approach, showing that lowering saturated fat intake can reduce heart disease risk—especially for those with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7894073/these-7-things-could-make-you-more-likely-to-get-heart-disease-according-to-the-american-heart-association/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;elevated risk factors&lt;/a&gt; or a family history of heart disease.&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The beauty of this cooking swap? It doesn’t mean sacrificing flavor, spending more money or changing how you cook. Unsaturated fats like olive oil and avocado oil are versatile, enhancing your dishes while supporting heart health. Whether you’re roasting vegetables, making salad dressings or cooking on the stovetop, this simple change can help improve your cholesterol over time.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-tips-for-managing-cholesterol"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Tips for Managing Cholesterol &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Swapping saturated fats for unsaturated fats is a top tip for managing cholesterol, but there are several other strategies that can help keep your lipid levels in a healthy range.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Eat More Fiber &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Most Americans fall short of the recommended 25 to 34 grams of fiber per day, making it an important focus for heart health.&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Research shows that every 5-gram daily increase in soluble fiber intake can help lower total cholesterol and LDL cholesterol.&lt;span data-cite="5" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One simple way to boost fiber is by &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/eat-more-beans-with-these-recipes-11709540" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;adding more beans to your diet&lt;/a&gt;, since they’ve consistently been shown to help reduce total and LDL cholesterol, says &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/veronicarouse/?originalSubdomain=ca" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Veronica Rouse, M.A.N., RD, CDE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span data-cite="6" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Other foods high in soluble fiber include oats, apples, nuts and seeds.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Eat Fewer Refined Carbohydrates &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Overdoing on simple carbs—like white bread, pastries and sugary snacks—can spike blood sugar and negatively impact cholesterol levels. “Swap refined sugars and white flour for whole grains like oats, barley, quinoa and brown rice,” explains Routhenstein. “These complex carbs help stabilize blood sugar and insulin levels. Better insulin control improves how the liver clears LDL and apoB cholesterol from the blood.”&lt;span data-cite="7" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Enjoy Heart-Healthy Snacks &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Choose &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/surprising-nutrient-for-better-heart-health-8686588" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;snacks rich in unsaturated fats&lt;/a&gt;, like apples and nut butter, roasted edamame trail mix, or avocado on whole-grain crackers. These choices deliver satisfying crunch and flavor while helping to support your cholesterol goals.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Move Your Body Regularly &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A large review of 148 randomized controlled trials found that exercise led to modest but meaningful improvements in cholesterol, including reductions in LDL cholesterol.&lt;span data-cite="8" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Walking after meals, cycling, swimming or strength training helps your body process fats and sugars more efficiently,” adds Routhenstein. Aim for at least 150 minutes of moderate-intensity aerobic activity per week, such as brisk walking or cycling, plus two strength-training sessions.&lt;span data-cite="9" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Swap Your Spreads and Condiments &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Instead of mayonnaise or creamy dressings, which are often high in saturated fat, Routhenstein recommends using mashed avocado, hummus, tahini or a homemade vinaigrette to add flavor and heart-healthy fats to your sandwiches and salads.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When it comes to cooking for healthier cholesterol, one of the simplest and most effective changes is swapping saturated fats for unsaturated fats—like using olive oil instead of butter. Combined with other lifestyle strategies, such as &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-much-fiber-should-you-be-eating-11752876" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;eating plenty of fiber&lt;/a&gt;, staying active and choosing heart-smart snacks wisely, these changes can make a meaningful impact on your heart health.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxOTmJHNEdCVUpTOU9tU1h1VFZkZ1JNOG13YmVoSEpuYUhZdlNiQWFSNDhreS0ya1UtU3pXZ0E3SUhibkswMUNUb2twcm1IZ2xwcXgtQldyb096dFg4aGJRclZrRUR5UDJ5LXY3cV91ekZlZHVETk5rSmFCRC1OTklmSlJNM00</guid></item></channel></rss>