<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>睡眠、压力和阳光：内分泌学家关于新陈代谢的11种方法-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2026/jan/18/sleep-stress-and-sunshine-endocrinologists-on-11-ways-to-look-after-your-metabolism</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;h2 id="get-to-know-your-hormones" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;Get to know your hormones&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Most people would like to have more energy and be leaner,” says Prof David Ray, an endocrinologist at the University of Oxford who also provides NHS services. “There is a connection between how we choose to live, what our bodies look and feel like, and the hormones that are going around the body. What endocrinologists deal with is disorders of either a lack of hormones, or too much of a hormone.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Hormones impact almost all bodily functions, from skin, to the gut, to our moods. “During an average day, the hormones in our body will vary depending on what time it is and what we’re doing,” he says. “For example, have we recently had something to eat or are we hungry? Are we having a stressful day or a calm and quiet day?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Metabolic rate refers to metabolism, which describes how the body uses different components from the foods that we eat and turns those into all the various things that it needs to fuel the body, build proteins and other essential molecules,” says Dr David Cavan, a consultant endocrinologist specialising in diabetes and weight management at University Hospitals Dorset and the London Diabetes Centre, and author of&lt;a href="https://www.hachette.co.uk/titles/dr-david-cavan/a-guide-to-weight-loss-injections/9781035430420/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt; A Guide to Weight Loss Injections&lt;/a&gt;, published on 29 January. “If you have a very slow metabolic rate, then you will use up less energy and gain weight more than if you have a faster metabolic rate, in which case you’re burning the energy up more quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Insulin regulates glucose metabolism and levels of sugar in the blood,” Cavan continues, “but if we have too much insulin in our body, it can lead to weight gain, high blood pressure and type 2 diabetes. Critically, because insulin is a fat storage hormone, high levels of insulin actually slow down the metabolic rate, and you get into a vicious cycle. The slower your metabolic rate, the less energy you use [and] the more you can store.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;According to Cavan, it is no surprise that the huge increase in obesity, type 2 diabetes and related conditions in the last 30 years has happened at the time that our food environment has been transformed by ultra processed foods high in energy, sugar and refined carbohydrates – leading to elevated insulin levels. Matters are made worse by the reduced physical activity characteristic of modern lifestyles – which means that while we consume more energy, we use up less.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="dont-rely-on-weight-loss-jabs-alone" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;Don’t rely on weight loss jabs alone&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Weight loss injections influence the levels of hormones that affect metabolism in a number of ways, says Cavan: “They slow down the rate at which food is absorbed from the gut, and affect the brain and satiety. The net effect is that insulin levels will begin to come down and help people to lose the excess fat that they are storing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;At present, “they are very restricted on the NHS, so most people are buying them privately through online pharmacies”, says Cavan. “Some people seem to get quite a lot of support, others get none at all. I would encourage people, if they are buying them online, to make sure that they’ve got access to good quality information about how to increase the dose and manage side effects.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="up-your-protein" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;Up your protein&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure id="baabfaea-1b8d-41e5-966b-194908b1c388" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Eggs are ‘a natural fast food.’&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Posed by model; GMVozd/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“If you have metabolic syndrome – which is characterised by being overweight, and brings an increased risk of pre-diabetes or type 2 diabetes, high blood pressure and sleep apnoea, the underlying problem is too much insulin,” says Cavan. “The trouble is, every time you eat carbohydrates, whether it is sugar or starch, it increases insulin. Moving away from carbohydrates is tackling the root cause and is so important. That is why I encourage my patients to base their meals on protein and vegetables first and foremost, rather than carbohydrates.” Cavan suggests a focus on natural or minimally processed proteins including meats, fish, cheese, pulses, tofu, plain Greek yoghurt and eggs. “So many people are still under the impression that eggs are unhealthy, even though it is more than 20 years since the advice changed,” he says. “Eggs are very nutritious, high in protein, contain almost zero carbohydrates and are very filling. It is a natural fast food.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Anjali Amin, an endocrinologist at Imperial College healthcare NHS trust, has researched the effect of protein on appetite regulation and says that a high protein diet may be helpful in the control of our appetites: “It is not going to boost metabolism but, from an appetite and energy perspective, it is the macronutrient that makes people feel most full.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="get-lifting" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;Get lifting&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It is not just about what you put into your body – it is what you do with all that energy you are consuming,” says Amin, which is why exercise, especially resistance training, is advisable to improve muscle mass. This is helpful once women enter menopause, she explains. “Their levels of oestrogen decline which impacts bone health. Resistance training helps strengthen muscle and bone.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Very simple strength training to maintain your muscle bulk is helpful,” agrees Cavan, “and that can be as simple as doing some squats or press ups.” This is “particularly important for people on weight loss injections, because we know that about &lt;a href="https://www.cam.ac.uk/research/news/lack-of-support-for-people-on-weight-loss-drugs-leaves-them-vulnerable-to-nutritional-deficiencies" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;40% of the weight lost is muscle&lt;/a&gt;”. Exercise isn’t the route to weight loss itself though, as Cavan explains: “I say to people, ‘If you want to lose weight, then exercise does not do it. Focus on what you eat,’” which many of his patients find surprising. There are some caveats: “I encourage people to walk as much as they can, because moving does burn off more energy than if you’re sitting down.” If people are very overweight, there is a real risk of injury through exercise, and it can also increase appetite, Cavan adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="work-in-an-inefficient-office" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;Work in an inefficient office&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Studies have shown that if we sit down for longer than an hour, our metabolism goes into a sort of ‘sleep mode’ to conserve energy, like a computer,” says Cavan. “I encourage people not to sit down for longer than an hour: get up, move around. If you work in an office, make it as inefficient as possible, so you’ve got to get up or walk to the other side. Literally any excuse to get on your feet can really help.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="80176153-0282-46b7-8eb9-46d2ef4cb3f8" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Resistance training can help improve muscle mass.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Posed by model; skynesher/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 id="sort-out-stress" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;Sort out stress&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dealing with stress plays an important role in managing weight. “Cortisol is the body’s stress hormone and it has metabolic effects,” says Cavan, “not least on pushing up your glucose and insulin levels, so it worsens metabolic health. Any type of stress can increase cortisol levels, be it emotional or work-related, which adds to metabolic ill-health.” Stress can also lead to comfort eating, he says: “It drives hunger and we can crave sugar if we are stressed. Poor sleep adds into that, because when we sleep, cortisol levels naturally go right down, which is key to a healthy metabolism. But if your sleep is disturbed, or if you’re not sleeping, they stay up, promoting poor metabolic health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="prioritise-sleep" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;Prioritise sleep&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Circadian rhythm is fundamentally tied to the regulation of energy metabolism,” says Ray. “People often don’t realise how much sleep is necessary for adults: between seven and nine hours a night. If you consider yourself, or ask your friends if they are getting seven to nine hours sleep a night, you’ll find that at least 50% won’t be. This is an immediate, highly prevalent cause of poor health and can lead to an increased risk of disease. If you’re not sleeping well, and you’re very tired during the day, that affects the kind of food you choose to eat and how full you feel after eating, which can lead to weight gain that further disturbs sleep. The heavier you are, the worse you sleep, and there are hormonal consequences that flow from that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We all know the consequences of trying to live against our circadian clock,” Ray continues. “If you’ve ever had jetlag or worked a night shift, do you remember how horribly disruptive it is on how you’re thinking, your appetite, what you want to eat and when you want to eat? About &lt;a href="https://www.ons.gov.uk/businessindustryandtrade/business/activitysizeandlocation/articles/thenighttimeeconomyuk/2022" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;one in five&lt;/a&gt; in the UK work some form of shift; as in, working outside core work hours – either early starts, late finishes or a night shift. And we know that increases, dramatically, the risks of obesity and diabetes. We can take healthy individuals and deprive them of a good night’s sleep for between one and three nights, and we see that their energy metabolism drastically shifts very much closer to the metabolism we see in people with type 2 diabetes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Exercising early, in natural light, can have a positive impact on circadian rhythm. “Try to ensure that you get enough physical exercise, ideally in external light,” says Ray.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="6acd88ae-7c9e-414f-aade-c1fd4a8a64d0" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Use hormone tech cautiously.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: SimpleImages/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 id="dine-early" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;Dine early&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“If your body is busy digesting food, it is going to be difficult for it to get into sleep mode, so eating late at night is not a good idea,” says Cavan. “There are also metabolic health benefits to time-restricted eating, by having a prolonged fast overnight. That is a very effective way of pushing your insulin levels down low,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;which helps burn off excess fat. You don’t need to go for days without eating. But try to have your evening meal as early in the evening as possible, no later than 7pm, and you can go into a fasting state before going to bed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="watch-out-for-signs-of-an-imbalance" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;Watch out for signs of an imbalance&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Amin says to look out for “unexplained changes” that could be the sign of a hormonal issue: “Persistent fatigue, weight changes without trying, heat or cold intolerance, irregular periods, difficulties getting pregnant or sexual dysfunction, hair loss or unusual hair growth. &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/diabetes" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, which may indicate there is a problem with the hormone insulin, can often present with thirst or excessive urination.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Treatment can initially focus on lifestyle. “Type 2 diabetes can respond well to diet and lifestyle interventions; ensuring a healthy, balanced diet and regular exercise, may have an impact on the hormone insulin,” says Amin. Other treatments include hormone replacement therapy but there are also medications that modify hormone action rather than replacing it – and very occasionally, there are surgical interventions for some hormonal conditions, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="use-hormone-tech-cautiously" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;Use hormone tech cautiously&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There has been a rise in home testing tech related to hormones – but how useful is this? “It is great that it increases awareness of hormonal conditions,” says Amin, “but I think it has the potential to oversimplify a very complex system, and you can take things out of context. I use wearable technologies such as&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;glucose monitors a lot with my patients who have diabetes, and they are&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;helpful to understand the changes in glucose that&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;patients get on a daily basis. But in somebody who does not have diabetes, they actually haven’t been shown to have any scientific benefit. In fact,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;they could promote unnecessary health anxiety and you can end up restricting foods that might actually be quite good for you.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiywFBVV95cUxPZFdQU0hGTldnMnJxN1h1YlpXNHZDcy14QzZFZXhCLVNQZHpZemJCcWcyb2ZuMzFGOWlzeDl3RzU4V3NuM01ycmRfd0o1OC1DT2NNdXpBLXhzc21LdW4xbktxSmRTeU1jLWlPUnZOb2otQU1paUl4WUs1cU1hUXFpZEFsbVBjUlQ5OERoYWNtQWN2aFUxZEhVUWNMaGtEcVJPc0tmWi1KRXhjQ0RJaF9QZDVkNV9HU0JwRDVSblc4azFKWC1FVHQxam1CVQ</guid></item><item><title>金毛猎犬遇见她的第一个雪人太可爱了，说不出话来- PetHelpful</title><link>https://pethelpful.com/pet-news/golden-retriever-meeting-her-first-snowman</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PetHelpful</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE5Na3dDaTZWY2s3TUlJUUZ4cXo4Wmh6T1Q4M1VrUDBKdi14azJ4UzV1aUxaTEx6b0xLbTFTc3RYRm03QWFuaV9ES3hUNFIyU2VlWkd4TDdKR19IZ3FlcUZuMjNhNFlpNlRacDktSEV1aGlWMkM2QklCZ0xMUlhKZXc</guid></item><item><title>科学家进行全面审查，展示冷水疗法的健康益处- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/comprehensive-study-cold-water-therapy-temporary-fix-or-long-term-health-benefits/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent years, cold water therapy has captured the imagination of wellness enthusiasts, athletes, and researchers alike. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From icy plunges in natural bodies of water to brisk cold showers at home, this practice has gained traction as a potential tool for improving health and well-being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But beyond the hype and anecdotal claims lies a question: does cold water immersion truly &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/wim-hof-method-helps-fight-stress-inflammation/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;deliver on its promises&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A team of researchers from the &lt;a href="https://www.unisa.edu.au/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;University of South Australia&lt;/a&gt; (UniSA) set out to answer this by conducting the most comprehensive systematic review and meta-analysis of its kind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings offer a nuanced perspective, shedding light on both the benefits and limitations of this increasingly popular practice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-impact-of-cold-water-therapy"&gt;Impact of cold water therapy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers analyzed data from 11 studies involving 3,177 participants, examining how cold water immersion influences stress levels, sleep quality, and overall quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the results suggest that cold water immersion may have positive effects, they also reveal that these benefits are often short-lived and highly context-dependent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Cold water immersion has been extensively researched and used in sporting contexts to help athletes recover, but despite its growing popularity among health and wellbeing circles, little is known about its effects on the general population,” explained UniSA researcher Tara Cain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-short-term-stress-relief"&gt;Short-term stress relief&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the key findings of the study was that cold water immersion could reduce stress levels – but only temporarily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants experienced lower &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/stress-eats-away-our-brains-cognitive-defenses/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;stress&lt;/a&gt; for approximately 12 hours after exposure. Interestingly, those who incorporated cold showers into their routines reported slight improvements in their quality of life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These showers lasted anywhere from 20 to 90 seconds, suggesting that even brief exposure to cold water might have some positive effects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the researchers noted that these benefits tended to fade after three months, indicating that consistency might be key to sustaining any gains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another intriguing discovery was the impact of regular cold showers on sickness-related absences. One study included in the analysis found that participants who took cold showers regularly experienced a 29% reduction in days missed due to illness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While this finding is promising, it raises further questions about the mechanisms behind such outcomes and whether they apply universally or only to specific groups. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We also found some links to cold water immersion and better sleep outcomes, but the data was restricted to males, so its broader application is limited,” noted Cain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-science-behind-cold-water-therapy"&gt;Science behind cold water therapy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cold water immersion involves submerging the body in water with temperatures typically ranging from 50-59 degrees Fahrenheit (10-15 degrees Celsius).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this study, data was included only if participants were immersed at or above chest level for a minimum of 30 seconds. Practices like cold showers, ice baths, and cold plunges were all included in the analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Ben Singh highlighted an unexpected aspect of the findings: cold water immersion causes a temporary increase in inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“At first glance this seems contradictory, as we know that ice baths are regularly used by elite athletes to reduce inflammation and muscle soreness after exercise,” said Dr. Singh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the initial spike in inflammation is not necessarily harmful. Instead, it represents the body’s response to cold as a stressor. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much like exercise causes short-term muscle damage before leading to stronger muscles, this inflammatory response may help the body adapt and recover over time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This insight could explain why athletes continue to use cold water therapy despite the temporary rise in inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-approach-with-caution"&gt;Approach with caution&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the study suggests potential benefits, it also highlights the need for caution, particularly among individuals with pre-existing health conditions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The temporary increase in inflammation, though beneficial in certain contexts, could pose risks for those with chronic illnesses or other medical concerns. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Knowing this, people with pre-existing health conditions should take extra care if participating in cold water immersion experiences as the initial inflammation could have detrimental health impacts,” noted Dr. Singh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research emphasizes the importance of understanding one’s own body and health status before diving into cold water practices. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For everyday wellness seekers, the findings serve as a reminder that what works for one person may not work for another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Whether you are an elite athlete or everyday wellness seeker – it’s important to understand the effects of what you put your body through,” said Cain. This personalized approach is crucial when considering any health intervention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-further-research-is-needed"&gt;Further research is needed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the promising findings, the study also revealed significant gaps in our understanding of cold water immersion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For instance, while there are many claims that it can boost immunity and mood, the evidence supporting these assertions remains weak. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers noted that more high-quality, long-term studies are needed to determine who benefits most and what the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/breathing-less-oxygen-could-extend-your-lifespan-by-50-or-more/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;ideal approach&lt;/a&gt; might be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Right now, there isn’t enough high-quality research to say exactly who benefits most or what the ideal approach is to cold water immersion,” said Cain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current data is limited in scope, focusing primarily on specific populations and short-term outcomes. Expanding research to include more diverse groups and longer observation periods will be essential to uncovering the full potential of this practice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such studies could provide clearer guidance on how to incorporate cold-water immersion into daily life effectively and safely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-cold-water-therapy-and-human-health"&gt;Cold water therapy and human health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those intrigued by the idea of cold water therapy, the study offers valuable insights but also calls for a measured approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the practice shows promise in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/embracing-stress-mindset-is-actually-a-good-thing-for-athletes/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;reducing stress&lt;/a&gt;, improving sleep, and enhancing quality of life, these effects are often fleeting and vary from person to person. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Incorporating cold showers or other forms of cold water exposure into a routine might yield some benefits, but consistency and individual tolerance are key factors to consider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, cold water therapy is not a magic solution but rather one piece of the larger puzzle of health and well-being. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As research continues to evolve, individuals are encouraged to listen to their bodies and consult healthcare professionals when necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re an athlete seeking recovery strategies or someone exploring ways to enhance your daily wellness, understanding the science and limitations of cold water immersion can help you make informed choices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0317615" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;PLOS ONE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 22:32:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPQXVvRXF0MmxDV2VhbzB5N09HR1MxbmNhNTMyY1lJZVFweGNhbVBQMFo0Z2k2ZTYtZENQaXFtMkZNLUxWZ2UxY0s0S3JwTGcza0dsVUFudlA1ZU5qVnVKSjRDRjRsdjJDSldNU250V1pOWXRVS1FSWDh6WVFZTXlWajEwMzV4TEk1dFIxdHBBUnlkbTQ4NjNiT3hKSmFzZnQ4RVBrQXBsTUxGbzhMa0E</guid></item><item><title>我的研究帮助发明了Ozempic —然后男性科学家获得了所有荣誉-泰晤士报</title><link>https://www.thetimes.com/uk/science/article/they-took-my-patent-the-scientist-wiped-from-the-ozempic-story-hvxwc5m3x</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;A Yugoslavian researcher leant over the stainless steel table, watching her colleague work. Fourteen years after she had arrived in America, Svetlana Mojsov was close to the breakthrough she had dreamt of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Gingerly the technician placed the pancreas in a small wooden chamber, warmed to exactly 37C — body temperature. Then, with practised precision, she flooded it with a new chemical cocktail that Mojsov had prepared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;They were at the Joslin Diabetes Center in Boston, working in the lab of Gordon Weir, one of America’s foremost authorities on the hormones that govern&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt; the body. He rang Mojsov with the results shortly afterwards — and they were beyond anything she had imagined.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“I still remember clearly the excitement,” Mojsov says today in her office in New York, where she is research associate professor at the Rockefeller University. The hope was that Mojsov’s mixture would coax the rat’s pancreas into doing what diabetes prevented it from doing in the body: releasing insulin when blood sugar rose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“Weir called to tell me that insulin levels were dramatically increased at very low concentrations [of the mixture]. That effect was not seen before.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Mojsov thought that success might open the way to a powerful new treatment for diabetes. Four decades later it has turned out to be much more important than that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/culture/books/article/off-scales-inside-story-ozempic-race-cure-obesity-aimee-donnellan-review-krqc66rgt" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The inside story of how Ozempic conquered the world&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The mixture that she had conjured up — known as GLP-1 (glucagon-like peptide-1) — is now the secret sauce in weight-loss drugs such as Ozempic, Wegovy, Mounjaro and Zepbound. Together these drugs are changing the world one injectable jab at a time. In the UK about 1.6 million people are now taking them. Their manufacturers believe their popularity will eventually be double or triple that. They can help users shed almost a quarter of their body weight. They treat or prevent diseases such as type 2 diabetes, kidney disease and non-alcoholic fatty liver disease. Dozens of studies are under way to discover if they can also address everything from dementia and polycystic ovary syndrome to skin conditions such as psoriasis and chronic inflammation. In other trials, scientists are investigating whether these drugs might treat addictions such as smoking, alcohol and gambling — in lab rats, the medications have reduced cravings for cocaine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Mojsov herself is now working full time, at 78, on how artificial intelligence can help figure out new uses for GLP-1 drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;All of this can be traced back to that day in a Boston laboratory in 1986. After watching the experiment Mojsov returned to her own much smaller lab at Massachusetts General Hospital — Mass General — where she worked, and began to write up her findings. Months earlier she had consulted her mentor, Bruce Merrifield. “I told him about my experiments,” she recalls. “He listened and then told me to go out and buy a stack of hardback notebooks and document everything carefully.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="4.9"&gt;&lt;div id="dc842cc3-bacc-49f0-8462-8b5d459467e8"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__PrimaryImg-sc-4v1r4q-3 hpWIYt"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__InsetCaptionStyle-sc-1io40fc-2 fkMBIX"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;Svetlana Mojsov with fellow students and her mentor, Bruce Merrifield, at Rockefeller University c 978&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;COURTESY OF SVETLANA MOJSOV&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Merrifield, a titan in his own field of chemistry who had just won a Nobel prize for developing a faster way to synthesise proteins, knew that in the scramble for scientific glory, the battles are not only fought in laboratories. Mojsov had no idea how valuable his advice would be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The experiment that she had just been central to was meticulously written up, peer-reviewed and ultimately published by one of the top scientific journals in the world, with Mojsov as the first named author.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Even so, over the subsequent decades her involvement would be slowly wiped from the record. Three men — two of whom she worked with — would go on to win the most prestigious prizes in biomedical science for their work on GLP-1, while she was relegated to nothing more than a footnote in the story. Svetlana Mojsov would need to prove herself all over again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;In 1972 a 25-year-old graduate of Belgrade University stepped off a plane from Europe into the busy arrivals hall of JFK airport in New York City. Short and slim, with hair cut into a bob that framed piercing and inquisitive blue eyes, Mojsov was looking for a chance to leave her mark on science. As her taxi crossed the Queensboro Bridge, the imposing steel structure carrying multiple levels of cars over the East River into Manhattan, she was amazed by its scale. The dark grey concrete skyscrapers and the bleak, dirty streets that she found on the far bank impressed her less but faded from view once she reached the leafy campus of the Rockefeller University, a private graduate university for biomedical research on the Upper East Side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Obesity was not yet on the radar of American doctors and nurses but she and her PhD classmates at Rockefeller learnt that the university’s hospital was conducting metabolic studies on severely overweight patients. “I thought that these people were an exception and not something we were going to see in the future,” she says now. Yet to Mojsov, who had grown up eating modest portions of Balkan staples such as spinach pie and goulash, the signs that Americans were already consuming vast amounts of unhealthy food were obvious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“I remember seeing all the pastrami and the big cheeseburgers,” she recalls. “I had never seen a steak before, let alone the giant steaks with potatoes. It was huge. The meals were huge.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Although it was widely believed at the time that obesity was solely due to a lack of willpower, some researchers were beginning to uncover more nuanced causes of severe weight gain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;A scientist named Doug Coleman had sutured two mice together, one obese and one thin, so they could share the same blood supply. After a few weeks the overweight mouse started losing weight, which led Coleman to suggest in 1973 that there was “a satiety factor” in the blood of the thin mouse that the obese one couldn’t make. “It was that experiment that showed there must be some factor that causes obesity,” Mojsov says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;In 1983 she moved to Boston with her husband, Michel, an immunologist who had a residency at Mass General. The huge complex, which includes a world-renowned diabetes centre, is the largest teaching hospital of Harvard Medical School and was intensely hierarchical. Harvard-trained physicians ruled. PhDs such as Mojsov were near the bottom. She was hired to create proteins for the other scientists in the building but quickly secured a senior research position that gave her some funding and therefore independence. “It was clear from the very beginning I would have my own project,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;She soon heard of Joel Habener, a balding and bespectacled endocrinologist, who worked two floors down from her. He was already a star. One year before, Habener and his team had identified a long chain of amino acids in fish that resembled glucagon. This proved to be a hormone involved in regulating blood sugar: GLP-1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/article/what-happens-when-you-stop-fat-jabs-bzx5lpsnp" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What happens when you stop fat jabs? The scientist who knows&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Mojsov became fascinated by the body’s different ways of working with blood sugar and spent months chemically synthesising GLP-1 and then tracking down its origins using antibodies. Word of her activities reached Habener’s lab. But rather than venture down to a relatively unknown chemist’s domain, he sent Daniel Drucker, a Canadian postdoctoral researcher working in his lab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Mojsov was wary of Drucker. On the surface he seemed pleasant — a young, energetic and handsome medic with soft brown eyes that creased at the edges when his smile would break out mid-speech. But as she listened to his proposal to join forces, it seemed transactional. “I couldn’t put my finger on it,” she says. “He looked entitled. But I was collaborative and I was discovering this new peptide and I was interested in what he was doing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Habener himself became friendlier. He would drop into Mojsov’s lab every few weeks seeking some of the GLP-1 she had synthesised for his own experiments. The two men, along with other members of Habener’s lab, began using her ingredients and techniques to track different forms of GLP-1 in rat tissue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;In September 1986 Habener and Mojsov published a joint paper. It detailed the discovery of GLP-1 in the gut, and Mojsov identified its active form. She is listed as first author on that paper and Habener is last, as is typical for the senior author on a paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“This was really a foundational paper,” she says. “It has it all. It is complete.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="4.30"&gt;&lt;div id="6b582f10-1229-4cb7-9578-8969b6292845"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__PrimaryImg-sc-4v1r4q-3 hpWIYt"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__InsetCaptionStyle-sc-1io40fc-2 fkMBIX"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;Medications such as Mounjaro mimic GLP-1, which Mojsov discovered while she was at the Howard Hughes Medical Institute, below&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;ALAMY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Endocrinologists agree with her assessment and consider this paper to be a watershed moment in the discovery of GLP-1 drugs. The timing was critical. It was published in the same month Jens Juul Holst from the University of Copenhagen presented the same findings at a conference in Rome. The transatlantic rivalry intensified as the two teams sought a much larger prize: to be the first to show that GLP-1 could treat diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Within a few months Mojsov teamed up with Weir for the landmark experiment with the rat pancreas that showed that GLP-1 controlled insulin levels. It depended on their shared expertise and that of Habener. Without his early research Mojsov would not have known about GLP-1, but without her subsequent mixing of the ingredients the breakthrough would have never been possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“That was a very critical experiment,” Mojsov says. “It shows how pure I got the GLP-1 to be.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The paper that detailed their findings was published in 1987 in The Journal of Clinical Investigation. Mojsov was listed as the first author, Weir was second and Habener last.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Meanwhile, in the same building, Drucker, the smooth Canadian, and another postdoctoral researcher called Jacques Philippe were working on different experiments but hoping for the same outcome. Habener had instructed Drucker to try to figure out how GLP-1 works. Mojsov didn’t realise it at the time, but this project was in competition with her own research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Like Mojsov, the duo found that one version of GLP-1 stimulates more insulin than a longer version of the peptides. Drucker’s paper was published in May 1987, three months after Mojsov and Weir’s. Mojsov was happy to help Drucker because they both worked for Mass General. Up until that point it all seemed relatively collegiate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;On a sunny day in May 1993, at the first international symposium on GLP-1, Mojsov ran into Habener walking on the lawn of the Vilvorde Conference Centre just north of Copenhagen. By then she was back at Rockefeller but she still wondered why Mass General had never applied for patent protection of GLP-1. After exchanging greetings, she asked Habener about patents. He just turned around and walked away. It was a bizarre, awkward interaction. Although the two scientists had never been friends, they had collaborated closely at a very important time in both of their careers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Eventually Mojsov put the pieces of the puzzle together. In 1996 a colleague on a separate project mentioned that Mass General had been granted patents for the discovery of GLP-1 in 1992, the year before she bumped into Habener. He was listed as its sole inventor. Without telling her, Habener had then applied for a separate patent using some of Mojsov’s research in 1993, a little over six months after he had bumped into her in Copenhagen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“When I found out I was shocked,” she says. “I hadn’t looked for the patents but I had always thought I would be on them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;She found a patent lawyer who looked through her notebooks and told her that he expected Mass General to roll over relatively easily and admit that a mistake had been made. A letter was fired off to the hospital. There was no response for a year, so Mojsov’s lawyer sent another letter. “I was really surprised and my lawyers were really surprised why Mass General ignored us,” Mojsov says. “It just went on and on.” Then Mass General hired an elite intellectual property law firm from Washington. They asked to interview Mojsov about her role in the GLP-1 discovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Much was at stake. The patent holder would receive a significant percentage of royalties from any GLP-1 drugs, not to mention the fame associated with inventing a novel and powerful drug. At this stage the Danish pharmaceutical giant Novo Nordisk had already bought the licensing rights for GLP-1 in 1992 from Habener. The company was actively seeking to create the world’s first diabetes drug, building on Mojsov’s discovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“I was advised to be very careful,” Mojsov says. “I needed to prove my contribution but not discredit Habener, or the patents could be in jeopardy — and that could have undermined Novo Nordisk’s efforts to make a drug.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The legal exchanges grew heated between Mojsov and Mass General’s lawyers. “I don’t remember crying because there was so much anger,” she says. “I had to calm myself down.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Then, out of the blue in 2006, the hospital agreed to amend five patents to include Mojsov as a co-inventor. For this Mojsov had to concede a lot of ground. “At first I insisted that we had to have half and half,” Mojsov says. “But my lawyer told me I had to compromise.” In the end she was awarded a third of drug royalties. Habener received the rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;It wasn’t much money anyway. By the time Novo Nordisk’s first GLP-1 drug was approved by the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) in 2010, there was only a year left on the patent. But Mojsov had been vindicated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;She thought back to the advice her mentor, Bruce Merrifield, gave her about the notebooks. “He told me to keep the dates. It was very helpful. That’s how I finally got the patent.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The fight was far from over, though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="4.49"&gt;&lt;div id="235f5b03-eca3-402d-b4bd-3a40a19b2eff"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__PrimaryImg-sc-4v1r4q-3 hpWIYt"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__InsetCaptionStyle-sc-1io40fc-2 fkMBIX"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;From left: Daniel Drucker, Svetlana Mojsov, Jens Juul Holst and the molecular geneticist Jeffrey Friedman at the Princess of Asturias awards, Spain, 2024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;ALAMY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Habener, Drucker and Holst all agree that Mojsov made an important contribution to the GLP-1 discovery. Habener says he told Mass General that she also deserved to be on the patents. Still, none of these men has gone to great lengths to ensure that the scientific community knows the extent of her involvement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;In 2021 the three men shared the Canada Gairdner International award, often seen as a precursor to a Nobel prize, for their work on GLP-1. The Gairdner was the third award in four years that they won for research that began in the 1980s. A week after the ceremony, Mojsov read a follow-up article about their work in Cell, a top academic journal. It was littered with inaccuracies. It incorrectly described Habener as the sole inventor of GLP-1. It wrongly described her as a junior member of his laboratory. There was no mention of Mojsov being a co-inventor on multiple patents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“I felt like this was becoming a pattern,” she says now. “One of the ways to diminish my work was to say I was a postdoctorate of Joel Habener because, in the Harvard Medical School hierarchy, medical doctors [such as Habener] are always above postdocs who have a PHD and are always at the lower level. I was aware of it but I didn’t pay attention.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;So on a crisp sheet of paper Mojsov hand-wrote a letter of complaint to the editor of Cell, correcting the errors in the article one by one. She received an apology and the article was amended. It was a small but vital victory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;As the Gairdner award indicated, the impact of GLP-1 puts its discoverers on course to win a Nobel prize in physiology or medicine. But the prize rules mean that the accolade can be split only three ways at most. So unless Mojsov can establish her claim, she will be left out of a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity to earn the highest accolade in her field. The correction in Cell marked the first moment that the wider scientific community embraced the true significance of her work. It also led to further supportive coverage in the science press.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/article/tim-spector-nutrition-weight-loss-jabs-ozempic-hdm72xc5v" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Spector: Weight-loss jabs are fine… if we stop eating junk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Finally, in September 2024, Mojsov received heavyweight public recognition for her role in the discovery of GLP-1. Along with Habener and Lotte Bjerre Knudsen, a medicinal chemist at Novo Nordisk, she won the Lasker-DeBakey Clinical Medical Research award, America’s top prize in biomedical research. The honour suggests that if and when the Nobel committee recognises the scientists who blazed a trial towards the Ozempic age, there is a good chance that Svetlana Mojsov will be one of the three on the podium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Habener called to congratulate her. The “short and cordial conversation” was the first time that they had spoken in more than 30 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The Lasker-DeBakey ceremony, a modest lunch of chicken and salad, was held at New York’s Pierre Hotel. Mojsov was accompanied by her husband, son and daughter. She stood up and made a brief speech, explaining what an honour it was to receive the award, thanking her mentor, Bruce Merrifield, and emphasising the importance of collaboration in science. Habener was sitting three seats to her right. She didn’t mention him once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;When she sat down, her son leant over and whispered in her ear, “You did it, Mum.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Off the Scales: The Inside Story of Ozempic and the Race to Cure Obesity&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; by Aimee Donnellan (Fourth Estate £20). To order a copy go to &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesbookshop.co.uk/off-the-scales-9780008719081/?utm_source=timesandsundaytimes&amp;amp;utm_medium=online&amp;amp;utm_campaign=weekly" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;timesbookshop.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;. Free UK standard P&amp;amp;P on orders over £25. Special discount available for Times+ members&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="bb7a3cdc-647e-497d-99ab-99f78fa47e15" class="responsive__Heading2-sc-4v1r4q-9 bQMpmd"&gt;Science’s overlooked heroines&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Named after the American suffragist Matilda Joslyn Gage, the “Matilda effect” is the phenomenon of female scientists being sidelined in favour of their male peers, writes&lt;i&gt; Julia Chadwick&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="79cdfe89-1ce7-49ae-a817-8348df9bf03a" class="responsive__Heading3-sc-4v1r4q-10 dxCaTt"&gt;Jean Purdy&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;A clinical embryologist whose work contributed to the birth of the first “test tube baby” in 1978. Her collaborator, who tried in vain to advocate for Purdy, was given the Nobel prize in physiology or medicine in 2010 and was knighted a year later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="3b1933dd-90d0-4609-af55-098a751cb8d8" class="responsive__Heading3-sc-4v1r4q-10 dxCaTt"&gt;Jocelyn Bell Burnell&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;While studying for her doctorate at Cambridge University in 1967, Bell discovered pulsars — rapidly rotating neutron stars. The find helped her supervisor win a Nobel prize in physics seven years later. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="457b533e-56a1-4c1e-91ce-d54560fe3194" class="responsive__Heading3-sc-4v1r4q-10 dxCaTt"&gt;Chien-Shiung Wu&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;A key member of the Manhattan Project, Wu disproved the “law of parity conservation” in 1956. The “Wu experiment” validated the theories of two scientists who went on to win a Nobel prize in physics the following year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="46895763-9b70-4d95-82ba-e8a2e098b180" class="responsive__Heading3-sc-4v1r4q-10 dxCaTt"&gt;Lise Meitner&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;An Austrian physicist who fled to Sweden to escape Hitler, Meitner became part of the team who discovered nuclear fission in 1938. Six years later her former colleague won the Nobel prize in chemistry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="285345a0-637f-46ab-9bfe-b69b23402ad5" class="responsive__Heading3-sc-4v1r4q-10 dxCaTt"&gt;Candace Pert&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Despite being told to abandon the work by her supervisor, Pert discovered the brain’s opiate receptor in 1973. This laid the groundwork for the discovery of endorphins by two British researchers two years later. They won the Lasker award — shared with Pert’s supervisor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="61519df4-8262-4716-ac26-2e0e75df9840" class="responsive__Heading3-sc-4v1r4q-10 dxCaTt"&gt;Alice Ball&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id="last-paragraph" class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The first woman to become a chemistry instructor at the College of Hawaii, Ball devised an effective treatment for leprosy at 23. She died shortly after in 1916 from suspected chlorine poisoning in a lab. The college president published her research under his own name.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxOYWFQcXZtT25FNzU5aVluc3RJeEFhUHczUzNWemJVck04T2VNcDdqV1dISHhhRVkxNzZpQ3lwVjRIdW5fMTRhOGNwNGQ4VEtCVlFQMjhWYXBBWHJGcW1tMWdfQVJpRFBZaDE5Q1l2RFNQeFB5WUZ3YW1TTExBUlFweW9CbUFEZ0JaaXJ0dFRRZkZtRUhsTjh3UzlENUtuNzdFWG9rT1FOOWRkVnIzOWJVWE01dkVmdGM</guid></item><item><title>研究证实了为什么有些人在不接触酒精的情况下会喝醉- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/study-confirms-why-some-people-get-drunk-without-touching-alcohol</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Scientists have confirmed in the largest study of its kind that bacteria, not fungi, are the major culprit in &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Auto-brewery_syndrome"&gt;auto-brewery syndrome&lt;/a&gt;, a rare medical condition where people become intoxicated after eating, despite not consuming any alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analyzing stool samples from 22 patients diagnosed with ABS, and their unaffected &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-people-in-your-life-are-sharing-their-gut-microbes-with-you"&gt;household partners&lt;/a&gt;, researchers identified two common bacterial species that are more abundant in people with the syndrome, reinforcing the findings of a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/brewing-bacteria-found-in-a-man-s-gut-could-solve-a-fatty-liver-disease-mystery"&gt;2019 study&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cases of auto-brewery syndrome are rarely diagnosed, and there is no consensus on how to treat the condition, so even though the study is small, it represents a meaningful number of patients who have been rigorously tested for ABS – and whose gut bacteria produced high levels of ethanol when cultured in lab experiments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/mysterious-rare-syndrome-causes-the-human-body-to-brew-alcohol"&gt;Mysterious, Rare Syndrome Causes The Human Body to 'Brew' Alcohol&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Many patients will visit multiple medical centers only to be dismissed as surreptitious drinkers and leave without a diagnosis," the team, led by infectious disease expert Elizabeth Hohmann of Massachusetts General Hospital and gastroenterologist Bernd Schnabl of the University of California San Diego, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41564-025-02225-y"&gt;writes&lt;/a&gt; in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The surging levels of ethanol in their bodies often cause liver damage, not to mention serious social, family, and legal problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_188675" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188675" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/ColorizedSEMKlebsiellaPneumoniae-642x672.jpg" alt="Two-rod shaped bacteria, end to end. " class="wp-image-188675 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/ColorizedSEMKlebsiellaPneumoniae-642x672.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/ColorizedSEMKlebsiellaPneumoniae-645x675.jpg 645w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/ColorizedSEMKlebsiellaPneumoniae-768x804.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/ColorizedSEMKlebsiellaPneumoniae-1468x1536.jpg 1468w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/ColorizedSEMKlebsiellaPneumoniae-1957x2048.jpg 1957w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/ColorizedSEMKlebsiellaPneumoniae-600x628.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-188675" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Klebsiella pneumoniae.&lt;/em&gt; (Callista Images/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study came about after microbiologist Jing Yuan of Beijing's Capital Institute of Pediatrics was &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/how-some-people-get-drunk-their-own-gut-bacteria"&gt;flooded with calls&lt;/a&gt; from patients desperate to be tested for ABS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was 2019, and Yuan (who was not involved in the current study) had just published research implicating the bacterium &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Klebsiella_pneumoniae"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Klebsiella pneumoniae&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; as the likely cause of ABS rather than &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK513346/"&gt;commensal forms of yeast&lt;/a&gt; as some suspected. She referred the callers to Schnabl, who began recruiting patients for a follow-up study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comparing gut microbes from ABS patients to those of people they live with, the new study effectively controlled for &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/daycares-in-finland-grew-forests-and-it-changed-kids-immune-systems"&gt;environmental&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/yo-yo-dieting-may-trigger-long-lasting-changes-in-gut-bacteria"&gt;dietary factors&lt;/a&gt; known to influence gut microbiomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Schnabl and colleagues found that bacterial cultures from patients experiencing 'flare-ups' – symptoms of intoxication – &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ethanol_fermentation"&gt;produced more ethanol&lt;/a&gt; than microbes from those in remission or from household members unaffected by the condition. This correlated with blood alcohol levels measured during the same period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_188672" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188672" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/GutMicrobialEthanolProductionInCultures-642x224.png" alt="" class="wp-image-188672 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/GutMicrobialEthanolProductionInCultures-642x224.png 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/GutMicrobialEthanolProductionInCultures-1200x420.png 1200w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/GutMicrobialEthanolProductionInCultures-768x269.png 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/GutMicrobialEthanolProductionInCultures-600x210.png 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/GutMicrobialEthanolProductionInCultures.png 1387w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-188672" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Bacterial cultures from ABS patients in remission (red line) and experiencing flares (yellow line) produced more ethanol than those from household controls (c). The difference after 24 hours (d) correlated with blood alcohol levels (e). (&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41564-025-02225-y"&gt;Hsu et al., &lt;em&gt;Nat. Microbiol.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/gut-microbiome-meet-klebsiella-pneumoniae-an-opportunistic-pathogen-that-is-harmless-to-some-but-causes-severe-disease-in-others-213197"&gt;&lt;em&gt;K. pneumonia &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Escherichia_coli"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Escherichia coli&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, two bacterial species known to produce ethanol, were both more prevalent in ABS patients, and &lt;em&gt;E. coli&lt;/em&gt; was particularly overabundant during ABS flares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One patient's symptoms markedly improved after he received two &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fecal_microbiota_transplant"&gt;stool transplants&lt;/a&gt; from an unaffected donor to reset his gut microbiota. The man remained in remission for more than 16 months after the second dose, and his family says his normal behavior has "&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41564-025-02225-y"&gt;essentially returned&lt;/a&gt;".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings suggest relief for ABS patients might lie in promoting or introducing, through dietary changes, stool transplants or probiotics, other strains of gut bacteria that readily metabolise ethanol. Although Schnabl &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/how-some-people-get-drunk-their-own-gut-bacteria"&gt;doesn't rule out&lt;/a&gt; the possibility that some cases of ABS may be caused by fungi or yeast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Potential treatments may also be able to target bacterial genes involved in metabolic pathways that the researchers found were more active during periods of remission, helping to resolve symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team also notes that ABS patients in this study had "extreme" imbalances in their gut microbiomes&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Other studies have reported low levels of ethanol production in patients with diabetes and implicated ethanol-producing gut microbes in fatty liver disease, the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jhep.2023.04.036"&gt;most common liver disease&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; globally.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This raises a broader question of how prevalent gut microbial ethanol production is in the general population and how widespread the pathological implications could be," Schnabl and colleagues &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41564-025-02225-y"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In addition, our study highlights the importance of the gut microbiome and microbial metabolites to human health," they &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41564-025-02225-y"&gt;conclude&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study has been published in&lt;em&gt; &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41564-025-02225-y"&gt;Nature Microbiology&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:02:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxQdFM4R3h4U1RkN2xPMnRXX04tX2lIMXV4dFJhN01McF9xYnZwV3JNWFZxU3ZoN2NicldCNElkZjh2R1A0OEM1R1d1TlRmX29GSXZKRXlNampzWmd4eHdQYzVBck5lanoyWGpCYjMzOE4xc28tUlZ5d3hqX0NyWlU4WGpxbmtVS2x1T0JGbG15WlBlUXV5N0FpTDFR</guid></item><item><title>1978年，一只巨大的深海野兽使一艘美国军舰瘫痪，科学家们说不出话来-印度国防评论</title><link>https://indiandefencereview.com/deep-sea-beast-crippled-u-s-warship-1978/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-entry-content"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 1978, the &lt;strong&gt;USS Stein&lt;/strong&gt;, a U.S. Navy frigate, returned to port with sonar equipment mysteriously shredded during a routine voyage off the coast of California. What the crew found in the ship’s damaged sonar dome baffled even marine scientists, an enigma that still fuels speculation nearly fifty years later. As first recounted in an interview archived by the &lt;strong&gt;U.S. Naval Institute&lt;/strong&gt;, the incident has become one of the most intriguing encounters between man and the unknown deep.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Attack That Left Sailors Speechless&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;USS Stein&lt;/strong&gt; was on its maiden voyage when its sonar systems suddenly went offline, forcing the ship back to San Diego for emergency inspection. Upon entering dry dock, Petty Officer &lt;strong&gt;Ira Carpenter&lt;/strong&gt; was assigned to examine the sonar dome, expecting a mechanical fault. Instead, he discovered deep slashes along the rubber coating, marks unlike anything he had ever seen.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’d never seen anything like this before, and this type of damage was brand new to me,” Carpenter said in an old interview shared by the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/watch/?v=2638767529558771&amp;amp;t=30" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;U.S. Naval Institute&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. “I used my knife to pick out this foreign object out of the […] coating, and it looked to me like a claw,” he added. “I quipped to my SW Officer, at the time: ‘Look here, it looks like we’ve been attacked by a bunch of small alligators.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The cuts were jagged and embedded with tiny organic fragments, resembling hooks or barbs. The crew had no rational explanation for the bizarre damage. The notion that a giant sea creature had physically attacked a military warship seemed almost impossible, and yet, the evidence suggested precisely that.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Scientist Who Faced The Unexplainable&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To make sense of the event, the Navy consulted &lt;strong&gt;Dr. Forrest Glenn Wood&lt;/strong&gt;, a marine biologist experienced in deep-sea species. After careful analysis, Wood concluded that the strange hooks could belong to a massive squid. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Squids do have claws similar to this. Nothing else that is known in the ocean has structures of this kind,” Wood commented.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The finding was extraordinary, suggesting that a &lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/deep-sea-squid-shows-off-disguise/" data-type="post" data-id="99307"&gt;colossal squid&lt;/a&gt;, a creature typically confined to Antarctic waters, might have ventured thousands of miles north into warmer seas. “This doesn’t rule out something that we haven’t found yet,” Wood added cautiously, leaving open the possibility that an unknown species could have been responsible.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;His remarks, preserved by the &lt;strong&gt;U.S. Naval Institute&lt;/strong&gt;, sparked decades of debate among naval historians, oceanographers, and cryptozoologists. If true, the USS Stein incident represented the first known case of a deep-sea predator physically damaging modern naval equipment and surviving to tell the tale.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Legend That Lingers Beneath The Waves&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To this day, no one has fully explained why a colossal squid, or any creature large enough to attack a warship, would surface near &lt;strong&gt;Southern California&lt;/strong&gt;, far from its natural habitat. Scientists know that colossal squids, &lt;em&gt;Mesonychoteuthis hamiltoni&lt;/em&gt;, can reach lengths of over 23 feet and weigh more than 1,000 pounds. Their tentacles are lined with rotating hooks designed to grip prey, or perhaps, unwittingly, a U.S. frigate’s sonar dome.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But that only deepens the mystery. The colossal squid is known to dwell in the frigid depths of the Southern Ocean, not in subtropical waters. Was this a lost or dying specimen that strayed into warmer regions? Or did it represent something entirely different, an undocumented species living far closer to human civilization than we imagine?&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Even today, the USS Stein incident is cited as evidence that the ocean still conceals creatures beyond our comprehension. While scientists remain skeptical, the story stands as a reminder that for all our technological advancement, the deep sea remains the planet’s last great frontier, and perhaps, its most unpredictable.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Beneath The Surface Of A Cold Case&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nearly half a century later, the USS Stein’s encounter endures as a maritime legend. The ship was repaired, its sonar restored, and the story quietly archived, but the questions it raised never truly sank. The fragments found embedded in the damaged dome disappeared into Navy files, fueling rumors of secrecy and classified research.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For those who believe the world’s oceans still hold ancient mysteries, the Stein case is a symbol of our ignorance, proof that &lt;strong&gt;Earth’s largest ecosystem&lt;/strong&gt; continues to surprise even the most advanced fleets. Whether it was a known giant squid or a yet-undiscovered creature, one thing is certain: something powerful enough to rip military sonar equipment apart lurked just beneath the waves that day in 1978.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Indian Defence Review</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFBxbDFqajlBOURXaFdnUlNZR0Vxemxza3h0RnFxRTlCVElLcVdwVkE5QVRaOEdIQWZ4b3JxbzdBck8tdC1VM0ZFY1hoVXZucWxmWXNIQ0otd2sydXpCTzVRVEVLdHdJTnNPM0FacGFrcWN6NzVyLXJGTWVSVE5Bdw</guid></item><item><title>美国最受欢迎的新零食实际上可能会将您的健康置于危险之中- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/rajpunjabi/protein-rich-snack-meat-sticks-carcinogen</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-14
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="140009065" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2&gt;So if you’ve been anxious about not getting enough protein, worry not! You probably are, but if you want an extra boost, reach for whole foods — and maybe skip processed meats as a regular part of your diet.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2&gt;We also chatted with Dunn about why we’re wasting our time and money if we’re getting too much protein, which nutrient we should probably be focusing on instead of protein, and much more.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;For more from Elizabeth Dunn, &lt;a href="https://www.elizabethgdunn.com/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="8010383" data-affiliate="true"&gt;visit her website&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://substack.com/@lizdunn183" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="8010383" data-affiliate="true"&gt;&lt;em&gt;subscribe to her Substack.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/protein-rich-snack-meat-sticks-carcinogen_l_6961173ee4b0120ab25d18a4" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="8010383"&gt;&lt;em&gt;HuffPost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:46:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNdFRTbGlsMWxBUHd0SFFMUzhDdVZBT2xmeHNjNmlxRzJCeXVxTnFPdlRoUHRTVDhSR2tzWTFldzRKa3VKZUUyTi1Zb2xzQU1Hb19PelVCcktsSHc5WTFGeWRHVXZuOXpTMGRZdUJUQWFOQXVjdzFQMk04QlNFd1Z1eklNWQ</guid></item><item><title>这种食物是美国增长最快的零食之一。它还伴随着一个非常令人担忧的风险。- Yahoo Lifestyle Singapore</title><link>https://sg.style.yahoo.com/food-one-fastest-growing-snacks-184602090.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="text-xs text-muted md:text-sm flex lg:block"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;time datetime="2026-01-17T18:46:02.000Z"&gt;Sat, 17 January 2026 at 6:46 pm UTC&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text-nowrap before:mx-1.5 before:content-['·'] lg:before:mx-0 lg:before:content-none"&gt;4 min read&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Lifestyle Singapore</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:46:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE41d0tnMmExRmNIU3pnMmFPb000enZvN09mZ3VlWnlWWnNtc3V0TVJsMXZmejVjTUNHLU11bE1YcEhpWjhzdGxKX3RSUmRyMjRXckZyYVh6bUVaYmY3aEhMQjMwZWNoZGpla1d2LWp1TzBUaHI5Z3BGNDQ0VzdmZw</guid></item><item><title>美国表示，尽管遭到强烈反对，但RFK支持的非洲婴儿疫苗研究仍将继续进行- “华盛顿邮报”</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2026/01/17/rfk-vaccine-trump-hepatitis-b-guinea-bissau-infant-trial/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3S2VZDNFBBAHNB3BJ6SQQM7CVA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A U.S.-backed study set to examine the overall health effects of hepatitis B vaccine dose timing on some 14,000 infants in the West African country of Guinea-Bissau has raised ethics concerns among scientists and former officials — and confusion amid conflicting reports on whether the research will proceed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:28:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxNUmg3QXA5dENmVFZPX0ZhRU9jYmRrcDJ6ZDdRMldwMjd3UzYyRWJDWDQyUXoxZ2ZfNkVtcWN0TUFHSFo1TkFyQm1SSGF0V2lQS3hzOFZndmIwdVpLR1JDR2t1STIwOF9mVTN1T3BONXVveGVab1did1JjQUNHN0EybzR0NmdtWEtmQW9jdWQ4UUdST0JJZ0tBR2ZEdzVlNHJpa1dZdUExaFI</guid></item><item><title>新的研究表明，少吃超加工食品有助于更健康的衰老- PBS</title><link>https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/new-research-shows-eating-less-ultraprocessed-food-supports-healthier-aging</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="theconversation-article-body"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ultraprocessed foods are made using industrial techniques and ingredients that aren't typically used in home cooking. They often contain additives such as emulsifiers, flavorings, colors and preservatives. Common examples include packaged snacks, ready-to-eat meals and some processed meats. Studies have linked diets high in ultraprocessed foods &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S0140-6736(25)01565-X"&gt;to poorer health outcomes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sdstate.edu/directory/moul-dey"&gt;My team and I&lt;/a&gt; enrolled Americans ages 65 and older in our study, many of whom were overweight or had metabolic risk factors such as insulin resistance or high cholesterol. Participants followed two diets low in ultraprocessed foods for eight weeks each. One included lean red meat (pork); the other was vegetarian with milk and eggs. For two weeks in between, participants returned to their usual diets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/heres-whats-in-new-dietary-guidelines-from-the-trump-administration"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;READ MORE:&lt;/strong&gt; Here's what's in new dietary guidelines from the Trump administration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A total of 43 people began the dietary intervention, and 36 completed the full study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In both diets, ultraprocessed foods made up less than 15% of the total calories – a significant reduction from &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.15620/cdc/174612"&gt;the typical American diet&lt;/a&gt;, where more than 50% of total calories comes from ultraprocessed foods. The diets were designed to be realistic for everyday eating, and participants were not instructed to restrict calories, lose weight or change their physical activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMAGE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="attachment_535225" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-535225" class="size-large wp-image-535225" src="https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/10/SplitEconomy-1024x683.jpg" alt='Announcent to remove petroleum-based synthetic" food dyes, in Medford' srcset="https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/10/SplitEconomy-1024x683.jpg 1024w, https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/10/SplitEconomy-300x200.jpg 300w, https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/10/SplitEconomy-768x512.jpg 768w, https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/10/SplitEconomy-425x283.jpg 425w, https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/10/SplitEconomy-1200x800.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px"&gt;&lt;p id="caption-attachment-535225" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Maintaining metabolic health promotes healthy aging. Photo by Brian Snyder via Reuters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We prepared, portioned and provided all meals and snacks for the study. Both diets emphasized minimally processed ingredients and aligned with the &lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2020-12/Dietary_Guidelines_for_Americans_2020-2025.pdf"&gt;2020-2025 Dietary Guidelines for Americans&lt;/a&gt;, the U.S. government's nutrient-based recommendations for healthy eating, while providing similar calories and amounts of key nutrients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://realfood.gov/"&gt;The 2025-2030 Dietary Guidelines for Americans&lt;/a&gt;, released on Jan. 7, 2026, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/new-us-dietary-guidelines-recommend-more-protein-and-whole-milk-less-ultraprocessed-foods-272990"&gt;explicitly recommend eating less ultraprocessed food&lt;/a&gt;, but the &lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2020-12/Dietary_Guidelines_for_Americans_2020-2025.pdf"&gt;previous versions of the guidelines&lt;/a&gt; did not specifically address food processing. Our feeding study design allowed us, for the first time, to examine the health effects of reducing ultraprocessed foods while keeping nutrient levels consistent with recommended targets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/show/emerging-field-of-culinary-medicine-helps-fight-diseases-through-better-food"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WATCH:&lt;/strong&gt; Emerging field of culinary medicine helps fight diseases through better food&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We compared how participants fared while eating their habitual diets with how they responded to the two diets that were low in ultraprocessed foods. During the periods when participants ate fewer ultraprocessed foods, they naturally consumed fewer calories and lost weight, including total and abdominal body fat. Beyond weight loss, they also showed meaningful improvements in insulin sensitivity, healthier cholesterol levels, fewer signs of inflammation and favorable changes in hormones that help regulate appetite and metabolism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These improvements were similar whether participants followed the meat-based or the vegetarian diet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why it matters&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ultraprocessed foods &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1017/S0007114523003033"&gt;make up more than half the calories&lt;/a&gt; consumed by most U.S. adults. Although these foods are convenient and widely available, studies that track people's diets over time increasingly link them with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S0140-6736(25)01565-X"&gt;obesity and age-related chronic diseases&lt;/a&gt; such as Type 2 diabetes and heart disease. With older adults making up a growing share of the global population, strategies that preserve metabolic health could support healthy aging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/show/why-san-francisco-is-suing-top-u-s-food-manufacturers-over-ultra-processed-foods"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WATCH:&lt;/strong&gt; Why San Francisco is suing top U.S. food manufacturers over ultra-processed foods &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most previous feeding studies testing how ultraprocessed foods affect people's health &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cmet.2019.05.008"&gt;haven't reflected real-world eating&lt;/a&gt;, especially among Americans. For example, some studies have compared diets made up almost entirely of ultraprocessed foods with diets that contain little to none at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our study aimed to more closely approximate people's experience while still closely tracking the foods they consumed. It is the first to show that for older adults a realistic reduction in ultraprocessed foods, outside the lab, has measurable health benefits beyond just losing weight. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s12603-021-1609-3"&gt;For older adults especially&lt;/a&gt;, maintaining metabolic health helps preserve mobility, independence and quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What's still unknown&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our study was small, reflecting the complexity of studies in which researchers tightly control what participants eat. It was not designed to show whether the metabolic improvements we observed can prevent or delay diseases such as diabetes or heart disease over time. Larger, longer studies will be needed to answer that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/show/new-fda-rules-aim-to-redefine-whats-considered-healthy"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WATCH:&lt;/strong&gt; New FDA rules aim to redefine what's considered 'healthy'&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the practical side, it's still unclear whether people can cut back on ultraprocessed foods in their daily lives without structured support, and what strategies would make it easier to do so. It's also not fully understood which aspects of processing – for example, additives, emulsifiers or extrusion – matter more for health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Answering these questions could help manufacturers produce foods that are healthier but still convenient – and make it easier for people to choose healthier food options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/us/topics/research-brief-83231"&gt;Research Brief&lt;/a&gt; is a short take on interesting academic work.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;img src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/271986/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/eating-less-ultraprocessed-food-supports-healthier-aging-new-research-shows-271986"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PBS</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:53:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxOcTlTRFBNRXRfQV9nclgtOEh6R2l6amNzbkNXN2pqalNxck9lUS0tbWpWN1VVdWxsMXUtZ2s4YUhGWWh5OGwtUVprOXk5dzBLazYwWVJ6ZHpHeFhYcUprTHJpT3NrUDFuQVU4aF9lc2xFOHBMbjVRN3N4VnY2YmhPWU5YNTVXVWg5Y0VSUWZlWnNZVVZkRmpnWUNmb2I2REY3QjZTOTV3eWQ2dEtVY0FWZQ</guid></item><item><title>“我看不见” ：女性在针灸事故后几乎失明- Ynetnews</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/health_science/article/bjaxltnh11g</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-contents="true"&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="e0ktn-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="e0ktn-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="e0ktn-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Sylvia Garcia, 51, of Ramat Gan, sought treatment for dry eyes through Chinese acupuncture and nearly lost her sight. “I never imagined acupuncture could end like this. Even now I see a black curtain in front of my eyes,” she told ynet and its parent newspaper Yedioth Ahronoth after being treated and hospitalized at Tel Aviv’s Sourasky Medical Center.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="4e62q-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4e62q-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4e62q-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Garcia has been coping for several years with dry eye syndrome, a common condition caused, among other factors, by dysfunction of the tear glands, poor quality of the tear film or improper positioning of the eyelids. She was initially treated with medication but was recently advised to try Chinese acupuncture. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="3n0o3-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide firstImageInArticle firstImageInArticleBody"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.B1lkZbTVB11x" id="image_ArticleImageData.B1lkZbTVB11x"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.B1lkZbTVB11x" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/12/S1eUDXWfHbe/S1eUDXWfHbe_0_68_1280_720_0_x-large.jpg" alt="סילביה גרסיה" title="Sylvia Garcia  (Photo: Yair Sagi) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.B1lkZbTVB11x" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/12/S1eUDXWfHbe/S1eUDXWfHbe_0_68_1280_720_0_x-large.jpg" alt="סילביה גרסיה" title="Sylvia Garcia  (Photo: Yair Sagi) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Sylvia Garcia &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Yair Sagi&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="7rpno-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7rpno-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7rpno-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“I went to a practitioner who was recommended to me, and he promised me he was an expert in treating dry eyes,” Garcia said. She had already undergone several treatments with him, but the most recent session last week was completely different. “It wasn’t the first time I was treated by him, but it was the first time the treatment was so intensive, with needles placed so close to the eye.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="5m8ii-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5m8ii-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5m8ii-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Garcia said she began to feel pain during the session. “I told him to stop, he paused briefly and then continued. He kept moving the needles so it wouldn’t hurt, but he didn’t touch the needles in the eye area.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="9ncvu-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9ncvu-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9ncvu-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;According to her, the practitioner used a technique combining electrical stimulation with traditional acupuncture. “I wasn’t familiar with that before. I had the needles in for half an hour, and throughout the treatment I was in pain. After he removed the needles, I opened my eyes and told him I couldn’t see out of my left eye,” she recalled. “I went into hysteria. He told me to rinse my eyes, but it didn’t help. I was panicking and terrified I would lose my vision. Horrible thoughts were running through my head.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="e6cmh-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="e6cmh-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="e6cmh-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Despite her fears, Garcia waited through the weekend in the hope that her condition would improve. “I didn’t realize how serious it was. I thought it would pass. The practitioner told me to put compresses on my eyes, but on Sunday morning I opened my eyes and saw that I still couldn’t see out of my left eye. I went to an urgent care clinic, and from there they sent me immediately to the emergency room.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="am8oh-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.Hklfd11aNBZe" id="image_ArticleImageData.Hklfd11aNBZe"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.Hklfd11aNBZe" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/12/SkVLP7WGS11e/SkVLP7WGS11e_0_114_910_512_0_x-large.jpg" alt="העין של סילביה מרקס נפגעה במהלך דיקור סיני" title="Sylvia Garcia's eye  (Photo: Sourasky Medical Center) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.Hklfd11aNBZe" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/12/SkVLP7WGS11e/SkVLP7WGS11e_0_114_910_512_0_x-large.jpg" alt="העין של סילביה מרקס נפגעה במהלך דיקור סיני" title="Sylvia Garcia's eye  (Photo: Sourasky Medical Center) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Sylvia Garcia's eye &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Sourasky Medical Center&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="f27kt-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="f27kt-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="f27kt-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Dr. Shulamit Schwartz, head of the retinal surgery and ocular trauma unit at Sourasky, said the patient arrived at the hospital unable to see in her left eye. Tests revealed significant internal bleeding within the eye, caused by one of the needles that was apparently placed incorrectly and inserted into the eye socket. “The source of the bleeding was a needle that penetrated inward, through the wall of the eye, straight into the eye cavity, injured blood vessels and caused bleeding,” she explained.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="9sjt5-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9sjt5-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9sjt5-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The patient was immediately hospitalized in the ophthalmology department and underwent an extensive series of tests and imaging studies to characterize the puncture site and the damage caused. She was also kept under observation to ensure that no infection developed inside the eye. At this stage, the bleeding continues to impair Garcia’s vision. “It will take time for the bleeding to be absorbed,” Dr. Schwartz said. “Fortunately, the hole created by the needle did not become infected, and the injury was several millimeters near the center of vision and the optic nerve, but not through them, preventing irreversible damage.” She estimated that it would take several more weeks for Garcia to fully regain her vision.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="730q0-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="730q0-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="730q0-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;According to Dr. Schwartz, such an injury can lead to serious complications. “A puncture of the eye wall can cause an intraocular infection, retinal detachment or the formation of a scar that can lead to permanent visual distortion. There are quite a few potential consequences of this kind of injury.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="13hi3-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="13hi3-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="13hi3-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The patient was discharged home last week but remains under close follow-up to ensure that no infection or additional complication develops. Dr. Schwartz noted that the medical literature includes a handful of cases of eye perforation following acupuncture performed in East Asia, describing it as a rare but very dangerous situation. “There is a wide range of treatments for dry eyes, including drops, ointments and medications. Alternative treatment for dry eyes is only a complementary therapy,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="68hha-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.BJg1Gz6VrWx" id="image_ArticleImageData.BJg1Gz6VrWx"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.BJg1Gz6VrWx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/12/Syjx811fBWl/Syjx811fBWl_1_86_973_548_0_x-large.jpg" alt='ד"ר שולמית שורץ' title="Dr. Shulamit Schwartz  (Photo: Sourasky Medical Center) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.BJg1Gz6VrWx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/12/Syjx811fBWl/Syjx811fBWl_1_86_973_548_0_x-large.jpg" alt='ד"ר שולמית שורץ' title="Dr. Shulamit Schwartz  (Photo: Sourasky Medical Center) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Dr. Shulamit Schwartz &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Sourasky Medical Center&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="copct-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="copct-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="copct-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Garcia said the vision injury has had a dramatic impact on her daily life. “I work as a private chef specializing in superfoods and healthy food, and you can’t function at 100 percent when you can barely see. It’s very uncomfortable. I’m patient, but someone else might already have lost it.” In the wake of the incident, she sought to send a message to the public. “I wholeheartedly recommend going only to certified clinics, and for any medical problem, first getting professional medical advice. At the end of the day, an acupuncturist is not a doctor. The practitioner I went to didn’t know how to diagnose what happened to me.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="ccjqs-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="ccjqs-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="ccjqs-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Dr. Schwartz added that “there is a difference between performing acupuncture on the wrist or the leg, for example, and performing acupuncture near the eye socket. In such cases, the practitioner must be certified and skilled, with thorough knowledge of the anatomy of the eyeball and the orbit. Inserting needles into the orbit by people who do not sufficiently understand the anatomy of the orbit and the eyeball can cause damage similar to what our patient experienced.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="ebq45-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="ebq45-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="ebq45-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Chinese acupuncture is a treatment method from traditional Chinese medicine based on the insertion of very thin needles into specific points on the body, with the aim of balancing the flow of energy, or qi, relieving pain and treating a variety of medical and functional problems. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="amcr-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="amcr-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="amcr-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;In recent years, Chinese medicine, and acupuncture in particular, has gained wide popularity, and Israel’s health maintenance organizations offer the service through supplementary insurance plans. Basic studies in Chinese medicine last about four years and include training in acupuncture, hands-on therapies such as shiatsu, herbal medicine, professional ethics and an internship. Despite the field’s popularity, it is not an academic degree recognized by the state. The practice of Chinese medicine in Israel is not properly regulated by law and is not under official government supervision.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="e4shu-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta wrapped"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleWrappedImageComponenta"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleWrappedImageData.HJlthG6Vr11g" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/12/HkIwXZMHWg/HkIwXZMHWg_0_39_408_544_0_medium.jpg" alt="אבי פלד" title="Avi Peled (Photo: Hila Peled) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="caption" contenteditable="false"&gt;Avi Peled&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span disabled class="credit" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Hila Peled&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="5vsq8-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5vsq8-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5vsq8-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The Israeli Association of Chinese Medicine has been working for years to regulate the field. Avi Peled, a certified practitioner and spokesman for the association, warned that the lack of oversight has led to a troubling phenomenon. Over the years, he said, various entities have taken advantage of the lack of legal regulation to develop accelerated courses for those seeking to practice acupuncture.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="7g3tn-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7g3tn-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7g3tn-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“I have about 30 schools on the blacklist. It’s an insane number,” he said. “These are colleges where students study only 200 or 300 hours, compared with 3,800 hours at supervised schools. It’s absurd. These people go out and treat patients with acupuncture and play with human health.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="bd458" data-offset-key="hdiv-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="hdiv-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="hdiv-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;According to Peled, health maintenance organizations are careful to hire only practitioners who have undergone proper training. He advised patients not to be embarrassed to ask where a practitioner studied. “Once you know where they studied, you can check whether the college is recognized by the association and know whether this is a certified practitioner.” He also recommended relying on recommendations from friends and acquaintances before seeking treatment and choosing a practitioner who is a member of the association. “That way you can be sure you’re in reliable hands.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:32:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMia0FVX3lxTE1nNEd4bU5rUHZHVUUzU2UwZFZUZHdPZ0ZOYndEXy1rU3JOb0U1dzc4Sk15aXNyYlhtdDNEcUc5Ym5XUWFZWGNyUVV2QmFnc0tBMmhvUXk2aUZlM0tfNXAwWC03dFFrVnZKTksw</guid></item><item><title>这是心脏病专家真正吃的心脏健康午餐-很美味- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/heart-healthy-lunch-a-cardiologist-recommends-11885239</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A cardiologist recommends a heart-healthy salad that’s both nourishing and filling.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Add leafy greens, colorful vegetables and lean protein to keep you full and support heart health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Include complex carbs like quinoa, beans or whole grains for lasting energy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Making mindful food choices is a powerful way to support your &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/small-habits-for-heart-health-11796620" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;long-term heart health&lt;/a&gt;. Every meal offers an opportunity to nourish your body with vitamins, minerals and nutrients that keep your cardiovascular system running smoothly. Yet one meal is often an afterthought in busy schedules: lunch. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Lunch is often the most rushed meal of the day, yet it can play a meaningful role in long-term heart health,” says &lt;a href="https://www.steponefoods.com/pages/about-elizabeth-klodas-md?srsltid=AfmBOorWhwyv8Sdo1NMRgXsu_bzHQ6I_3eyPRH_TOaijWaXfoT12iOKO" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Elizabeth Klodas, M.D., FACC&lt;/a&gt;. When you’re short on time, it’s easy to reach for convenient options that don’t always support heart health.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To avoid this midday pitfall, Klodas recommends simple, repeatable lunches that are easy to assemble and rich in heart-supportive nutrients. Her go-to choice is a vibrant, flavorful leafy green salad packed with arugula, roasted vegetables and a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-protein-for-heart-health-11803980" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;heart-healthy protein like salmon&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Here we explain why this lunch is fantastic for supporting heart health and how to customize it to your preferences.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-why-this-salad-is-the-lunch-for-heart-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Why This Salad Is the Lunch for Heart Health &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This cardiologist-approved lunch is a well-balanced powerhouse of nutrients. It combines fiber, healthy fats, lean protein and complex carbohydrates that work together to support heart health and keep you satisfied.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Its Foundation Is Nutrient-Dense Greens &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The base of a salad is just as important as the toppings. Klodas emphasizes leafy greens for their impressive nutritional profile. “Leafy greens are high in nutrients and antioxidants while remaining low in calories. Arugula in particular provides potassium and folate that support cardiovascular function and makes an easy base for a filling lunch salad,” she explains.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These nutrients help support blood pressure and overall heart function, making leafy greens an essential part of a heart-smart diet.&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Other great options include spinach, cabbage, kale, romaine lettuce or a spring mix.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Roasted Vegetables Add Nutrients and Flavor &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Adding a colorful mix of roasted vegetables enhances both the flavor and texture of the salad while also boosting its nutritional value. “Ready-to-eat roasted vegetables are a staple at lunchtime,” says Klodas. She includes certain vegetables for their unique heart-health benefits.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Beets help support healthy blood pressure through naturally occurring nitrates, while broccoli and cauliflower contain plant sterols that help block absorption of LDL (“bad”) cholesterol,” she explains.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; ,&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Beyond their heart benefits, roasted vegetables are rich in fiber and complex carbohydrates, which helps promote fullness and steady energy through the afternoon, reducing the likelihood of a midday energy crash.&lt;span data-cite="5" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Short on time? Roast vegetables at dinner the night before and use the leftovers for lunch. You can also add pickled beets for convenience, just choose low-sodium or sodium-free options.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lean Protein Supports Strength and Satiety &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A satisfying lunch should help you stay full and focused, and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-proteins-to-help-you-lose-weight-11770165" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;lean protein plays a key role&lt;/a&gt;. Choosing lean proteins keeps saturated fat low while providing the protein needed to support both muscle and heart health. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Klodas often adds salmon to her salad for its well-known cardiovascular benefits: “Salmon provides omega-3 fatty acids that lower triglycerides, improve cholesterol levels and reduce inflammation.”&lt;span data-cite="6" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; These healthy fats help support flexible arteries and help reduce the risk of cardiovascular events, such as a heart attack.&lt;span data-cite="6" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re not a fan of salmon, other great options include tuna, sardines, chicken and turkey. For a plant-based protein, Klodas recommends legumes—such as chickpeas, black beans, kidney beans and lentils—which also provide fiber and carbohydrates for energy support. Adding cooked quinoa or whole grains can further boost fiber, complex carbohydrate and protein content.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Complex Carbohydrates Provide Energy &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For a well-rounded salad, don’t forget to include complex carbohydrates. This may include cooked grains like quinoa, beans, lentils or even having a piece of whole-grain bread on the side. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Complex carbohydrates digest more slowly, supporting more stable blood sugar levels and consistent energy.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Heart-Healthy Flavorings Keep Sodium and Fat Low &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A healthy meal doesn’t have to rely on high-sodium dressings or toppings. “To keep lunch flavorful without relying on salt, use olive oil and fresh herbs like dill, cilantro and rosemary,” says Klodas. When she includes cheese, she opts for small amounts of goat cheese, which is lower in saturated fat and sodium than many other cheeses.&lt;span data-cite="7" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-lunch-options"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Lunch Options &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Variety is important for sticking with any healthy eating plan. If you want to mix things up, here are a few other heart-healthy lunch ideas:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Turkey &amp;amp; Avocado Wrap:&lt;/strong&gt; Use a whole-wheat tortilla and fill it with lean turkey slices, mashed avocado, spinach and tomatoes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quinoa Bowl:&lt;/strong&gt; Combine cooked quinoa with black beans, corn, chopped bell peppers and a lime-based vinaigrette. Add chicken for additional lean protein.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lentil Soup:&lt;/strong&gt; A hearty bowl of lentil soup provides plenty of fiber and plant-based protein. Pair it with a slice of whole-grain bread. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yogurt with Berries &amp;amp; Nuts:&lt;/strong&gt; For a lighter option, combine plain strained (Greek-style) yogurt with antioxidant-rich berries and a handful of walnuts or almonds for healthy fats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-tips-for-supporting-heart-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Tips for Supporting Heart Health &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Incorporating a healthy lunch is a great step, but you can further &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-activity-for-heart-health-recommended-by-cardiologist-8419619" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;support your heart health&lt;/a&gt; with these simple, effective habits: 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stay Active.&lt;/strong&gt; Aim for at least 150 minutes per week of moderate-intensity exercise, like brisk walking or cycling, along with at least two days of strength training. Regular physical activity strengthens your heart muscle and helps maintain a healthy weight.&lt;span data-cite="8" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manage Stress.&lt;/strong&gt; Chronic stress can contribute to high blood pressure and other heart risks. Practice stress-reducing activities like meditation, deep breathing, yoga or spending time in nature.&lt;span data-cite="9" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quit Smoking.&lt;/strong&gt; If you are a smoker, you should try to quit, as this significantly increases the risk of heart disease.&lt;span data-cite="10" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eat a Heart Healthy Diet.&lt;/strong&gt; Focus on a diet rich in whole foods like fruits, vegetables, whole grains and lean proteins while limiting saturated fat and sodium.&lt;span data-cite="11" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Building a heart-healthy lifestyle doesn’t require a complete overhaul. It starts with small, consistent choices—and your midday meal is a perfect place to begin. By focusing on simple, repeatable meals grounded in sound nutrition, you can make a meaningful impact on long-term heart health. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Cardiologists recommend meals like a satisfying salad made with leafy greens, roasted vegetables, lean protein and ideally a whole grain to support heart health while keeping you full and energized. Pairing these smart food choices with regular exercise, stress management and avoiding smoking creates a well-rounded strategy for keeping your heart strong for years to come.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOTklGS2VLdXlKakFFQmlzZ0xkYW1YeGpTa2tCN1hOUDhWazJUYldZRzJ5MVBySjB3ZHpveFQxRk1JZGJNSk40UEEzUlptcmozRFZJejRGYjRSeUxqRXN6a05HX1dyWHE3MFlmb2pTQjhtZHZjejdBSF9mWC1rZ2tSSnktdVhHWXNS</guid></item><item><title>特朗普自闭症声明引发的研究表明，怀孕期间的泰诺是安全的- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51434450/tylenol-in-pregnancy-is-safe-says-research-prompted-by-trump-autism-claims</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON — Taking paracetamol, known as Tylenol in the U.S., during pregnancy is safe, a group of European ​researchers has said, after compiling data in response to U.S. President Donald Trump's claims of a link to autism last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a review published in the British journal The Lancet Obstetrics, Gynaecology &amp;amp; ⁠Women's Health on Saturday, the team said they had focused on amassing the best-quality evidence to address the claims.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Paracetamol is safe to use ‌in pregnancy," said lead author Asma Khalil, professor of obstetrics and maternal fetal medicine at City ⁠St George's, University of London.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The key message is reassurance: When used as recommended, the best available evidence does ‌not support a causal link ‍with autism, ADHD (attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder) or intellectual disability."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Tylenol not linked to autism or ADHD&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Khalil said ⁠she had been asked about the popular pain medication – also known ⁠as acetaminophen – by her patients after Trump in September told pregnant women not to take the drug. At the time, national and international medical groups decried the president's comments, saying they were not evidence-based.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paracetamol/Tylenol is the only pain reliever considered safe for pregnant women, and doctors already advise them to use the smallest amount for the shortest time to control pain and fever during pregnancy. Untreated, these conditions can be risky for both pregnant women and their babies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ‍researchers conducted a systematic review and meta-analysis of existing data, finding 43 studies that were then assessed for quality and bias using a standard tool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team particularly focused on studies that looked at children born to the same mother who took paracetamol/Tylenol during one pregnancy but not the other. These take into account shared genetic factors and family environments that could be linked to autism or the other conditions studied, Khalil said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were only three studies of this type, but they were large, ‌covering more than 260,000 children assessed for autism, and around 335,000 and 405,000 for ADHD and intellectual disabilities, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Accounting for bias&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;They showed no significant ‌link between use of the drug and any of the conditions studied. This remained the case when results from all of the high-quality studies that were assessed were pooled, the authors said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Khalil said much of the work showing a potential link, including a review of 46 studies cited by Trump officials, was prone to bias or confounding factors that ⁠her team's review had tried to ​account for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grainne McAlonan, professor of Translational Neuroscience at King's College ⁠London, who was not involved ‌in the research, praised the study, adding: "I hope the findings of this study bring the matter to a close."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:20:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxQTmJlUkstUlY5Z2RVSUVjVkhXTFppaF9HQ0hTbTNDS1lacWJRTDE5bjhIeDdQMDN2dnN0RE1ncTNuNV9LMzR2UzRfOXBfRllBSFVjMDhUdXo3aFktY1UxN3g3cWpiWHMtODdlNEN3TzR0YVpmai10ZzF0Z1dhbFo4UldEam9Db3Utbk8tNUMxUzRqS2pFUUtnVU9GamdvZktUdm9JLU1wcFZhcFM3VkFmcg</guid></item><item><title>科学家准备在超级计算机上模拟人脑-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/simulate-human-brain-supercomputer</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;In 2024, researchers &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/complete-map-fruit-fly-brain-circuitry-unveiled" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;completed the first-ever map&lt;/a&gt; of the circuitry of a fruit fly’s brain. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Despite its diminutive size, the organ packs almost 500 feet of wiring and 54.5 million synapses into the size of a grain of sand — an astonishing feat of computational neurology research that allows scientists to better understand how signals travel throughout the brain.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;And thanks to significant advances of some of the world’s most capable supercomputers, researchers at the Jülich Research Centre in Germany are now aiming their sights at a far more ambitious goal: a simulation at the scale of the entire human brain.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Previous attempts, dating back a decade, like the Human Brain Project, &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/simulate-human-brain-fell-flat"&gt;fell largely flat&lt;/a&gt;, despite considerable government funding. But as &lt;a href="https://www.newscientist.com/article/2510892-were-about-to-simulate-a-human-brain-on-a-supercomputer/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;New Scientist&lt;/em&gt; reports&lt;/a&gt;, the Jülich researchers think they can push things forward. The idea is to bring together several models of smaller regions of the brain with a supercomputer to run simulations of billions of firing neurons.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The team, which is being led by Jülich neurophysics professor Markus Diesmann, will leverage the Joint Undertaking Pioneer for Innovative and Transformative Exascale Research (JUPITER) supercomputer for their simulation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;JUPITER is currently the fourth most powerful supercomputer in the world &lt;a href="https://top500.org/lists/top500/2025/11/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;according to the TOP500 list&lt;/a&gt;, and features thousands of graphical processing units.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The team demonstrated last month that a “&lt;a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2512.09502" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;spiking neural network&lt;/a&gt;” could be scaled up and run on JUPITER, effectively matching the cerebral cortex’s 20 billion neurons and 100 trillion connections.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Once up and running, the simulation could be a major upgrade, Diesmann told &lt;em&gt;New Scientist&lt;/em&gt;, compared to previous, much smaller simulations.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“We know now that large networks can do qualitatively different things than small ones,” he said. “It’s clear the large networks are different.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;At the end of the day, we’re still only scratching the surface of an organ that &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/gb/blog/communications-that-matter/202307/new-studies-prove-the-brain-is-still-a-mystery" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;remains mysterious&lt;/a&gt; to scientists. Even simulations at the scale of a human brain will only teach us so much about how it functions.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“We can’t actually build brains,” University of Sussex mathematical physics professor Thomas Nowotny told &lt;em&gt;New Scientist&lt;/em&gt;. “Even if we can make simulations of the size of a brain, we can’t make simulations of the brain.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on brain simulations:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/health-medicine/lab-grown-human-brain-poll"&gt;&lt;em&gt;People Are Horrified by Lab-Grown Human Brains&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE9ubWZlVWt4QUFxM2EzZmJya2Jvc0NUS2YtRUVEWVRET21jWVJYY0xtU3NNeU1DZ1FrMWRUZEdoSmk1MElpQVpIWDFGR0dOSGY0T3RBWnBVNS15ZGcxdzg1NUMzb1NzZjQ4ZUxYaUVNMkVyQnJyOHI5X2Z1Yw</guid></item><item><title>圣安东尼奥附近1125万$的新公园将是史无前例的--MySA</title><link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/hill-country/article/kendall-county-guadalupe-river-park-21290771.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>MySA</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:18:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPMEhhaFN2eEIwVk1kcUNmQmx3YWQ2UE1FU3pCVjVNcjI4X1hDbDZfSTJuRWp4bTRiTVdyNG5jRnAxUnBNVXhrOHVzcXZFR1Azbm1INjd4ZFNwN0kyNDVFVlNsQlJPUEYwd2xIRURHa191OGp5NDhfLXNCelE0OVF6X295U05kQzNjSUtkQjh0Q012N0NOWjRWNkpOX0pNV1Z1NlRJbmtB</guid></item><item><title>医生对关于从未骨折的人的奇怪理论也有同样的反应- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/community/weird/why-havent-i-broken-bone-doctor-explains-theory-018670-20260117</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Two doctors have weighed in on why some people are more susceptible to breaking bones, after a strange theory gripped the internet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Have you ever wondered why some people seem to have bones made out of glass while others have never spent a day in a cast?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;If you have, then you're not the only one, as a rather strange &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/conspiracy-theory"&gt;conspiracy theory&lt;/a&gt; suggests there was some kind of 'divine' hidden meaning behind why some people can go their entire lives &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/community/weird/why-youve-never-broken-a-bone-theory-spiritual-meaning-888269-20250511"&gt;without breaking a bone&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The theory, which went viral on &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/tiktok"&gt;TikTok&lt;/a&gt; last year, suggested that broken bones were the result of someone having a lack of spiritual protection. Or an abundance of bad karma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Either way, the entire theory hinged on the idea of a higher power 'choosing' who does and doesn't snap a wrist or fracture an ankle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Some people seem to spend half their lives in a cast (Getty Stock Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It's an argument which certainly gives us food for thought, although I'd imagine that most of us would assume that your risk of breaking a bone is down to something much more straightforward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Such as the number of potentially bone-breaking accidents you've been involved in or the overall &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/health"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; of your skeleton.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;And spoiler alert, these are arguments which are backed up by doctors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Speaking about the theories in a &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/why-youve-never-broken-a-bone-medical-answer-173021-20250515"&gt;previous interview&lt;/a&gt; with LADbible, &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://drsuhailhussain.com/"&gt;Dr Suhail Hussain&lt;/a&gt; said your odds of breaking a bone weren't 'random' or 'down to divine protection'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;So, what is it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genetics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;While others have bones of steel (Getty Stock Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Your likelihood of ending up in A&amp;amp;E with a broken leg is something which you inherit from your parents, with Dr Hussain saying inherited traits like bone density or the way in which your body processes calcium are crucial to whether or not you're more likely to break a bone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Bone strength is largely inherited. That includes how dense your bones are, how well your body processes calcium, and even how your skeleton is built," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Some of us are naturally more prone to thinner bones — and those can snap more easily under pressure."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;This is something which the Royal Osteoporosis Society (ROS) agrees with, with a spokesperson previously telling LADbible that you're more likely to break a bone if one of your parents has broken their hip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Age&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Age is another important factor in our risk of ending up in plaster, with a person's bone density gradually beginning to decline after the age of 30. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Meanwhile, Dr Claire Merrifield - who works as a GP and medical director at &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.selph.co.uk/"&gt;Selph&lt;/a&gt; - previously &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.tyla.com/life/broken-bone-explanation-conspiracy-theories-806647-20250205"&gt;explained&lt;/a&gt; to Tyla that menopause also increases the risk of older women breaking a bone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"As women go through menopause and lose the protective effect of oestrogen, bones become more brittle and can break from much less force, such as fall from small height," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;However, this isn't due to luck or divine intervention but instead a combination of diet, lifestyle and genetics (Getty Stock Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lifestyle&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;One factor which is in our control though is diet and &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/lifestyle"&gt;lifestyle&lt;/a&gt;, with both Dr Hussain and Dr Merrifield agreeing that making healthy choices protects us against breaking a bone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"It’s essential to eat enough calcium, take vitamin D in winter and take part in exercise with force - things like strength training, running, dancing and jumping are all great for this," Dr Merrifield advised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Meanwhile, Dr Hussain added that people who smoke, &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/alcohol"&gt;drink excessively&lt;/a&gt; and don't exercise are at a greater risk of breaking a bone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Lifestyle plays a huge role in whether or not you’ll suffer a fracture one day. In fact, there is probably more you can do to protect yourself from this phenomenon than you realise," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:10:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxNRjNheWRkOUZCdS1XZVVVeWJxekstRjdwRUN3ZnRHd3JzZzFYOEZuYlJVamxuMG8wVzlrbkpjZ004STB5ZHBVOGpPYUhDNEgyZGdwZ0pScWNYMGc4amVIanExdDNyMndhYWdNejFPNVlPa040QkQweWN1ZGhhMkpYNjNObjdzS2VBQ1pfVERSVDBKbVFNSDR6UjV6X19rWnJNeWRNMGxYdw</guid></item><item><title>纤维正在为咖啡的蛋白质热潮而来- Salon.com</title><link>https://www.salon.com/2026/01/17/fiber-is-coming-for-coffees-protein-craze/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="article__content page-article"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an August podcast episode of The Daily, titled &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=59uxFA5lyO0"&gt;“How America Got Obsessed With Protein,”&lt;/a&gt; food journalist Elizabeth Dunn delves into what was undoubtedly the &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2025/12/18/salons-most-popular-recipes-of-2025/"&gt;biggest food trend&lt;/a&gt; of 2025: protein-maxxing. Everyone, it seemed, was scrambling to load up on the humble macro. Influencers gleefully showed off their &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@sohonutrition/video/7594540935577439495"&gt;high-protein diets&lt;/a&gt;, complete with eggs, cottage cheese, poultry and red meat. Many also touted their high-protein snacks, which ranged from slices of cold cuts to &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@livcarbonero/video/7531124775947652365"&gt;homemade chicken chips&lt;/a&gt; made from seasoned, ground meat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Major food companies were even hellbent on following the bandwagon. Protein was added to classic buttermilk pancakes, &lt;a href="https://www.ihop.com/en/menu/world-famous-buttermilk-pancakes/protein-power-pancakes"&gt;courtesy of IHOP&lt;/a&gt;. Protein was sprinkled onto popcorn, thanks to &lt;a href="https://khloudfoods.com/?srsltid=AfmBOoom0b7mKSSXf49H6zo3brMA_FxsIZskw9nl1Rmv-sw03zkdMWFj"&gt;Khloud by Khloé Kardashian&lt;/a&gt;. And protein was steeped in our favorite beverages, thanks to both &lt;a href="https://protein.starbucks.com/?utm_source=google&amp;amp;utm_medium=search&amp;amp;utm_campaign=ProteinLP&amp;amp;gad_source=1&amp;amp;gad_campaignid=23056097230&amp;amp;gbraid=0AAAAADoJV5tYxOR0Grzcgnxxximib642V&amp;amp;gclid=CjwKCAiAvaLLBhBFEiwAYCNTfyzUnCyibr5DiIMF28dZfuJNf66l1jsmqMVnatMrrJc6OSpcV3BlhBoCKTsQAvD_BwE"&gt;Starbucks&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://news.dunkindonuts.com/news/dunkin-protein-milk-2026"&gt;Dunkin’&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protein’s sheer prevalence prevails in the new year, especially in the wake of &lt;a href="https://www.usda.gov/about-usda/news/press-releases/2026/01/07/kennedy-rollins-unveil-historic-reset-us-nutrition-policy-put-real-food-back-center-health"&gt;new dietary guidelines&lt;/a&gt; that place red meat at the very top of the food pyramid. But it’s slated to face some competition from yet another macronutrient.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;That’s according to Oatly’s first-ever &lt;a href="https://www.oatly.com/en-us/things-we-do/initiatives/future-of-taste"&gt;Future of Taste report&lt;/a&gt;, which predicts that fiber is coming for protein’s crown within the coffee scene.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“After first emerging on TikTok in Autumn 2024, ‘fibremaxxing’ (or fibERmaxxing) suddenly spiked this summer, sending the world’s media into a chia-induced frenzy. Pageviews for articles mentioning the term jumped 9500% between June to July,” states the report, which features insights from over 200 expert interviews, baristas and partners at &lt;a href="https://culturelab.co/"&gt;CultureLab&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Indeed, fiber has been enjoying a moment recently. Last March, The New York Times published the article, &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/26/style/prebiotic-gut-soda.html"&gt;“Why Are We Living in the Golden Age of ‘Gut Soda’?”&lt;/a&gt; pointing to the rising popularity of prebiotic sodas like Olipop and Poppi. According to &lt;a href="https://www.arizton.com/about"&gt;Artizon&lt;/a&gt;, a market research platform, the global prebiotics market is set to increase from $6.95 billion in 2023 to $13.26 billion by 2029.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Big macro-level shifts tend to be reactive,” Oatly’s report states. “If the ‘20s have so far belonged to protein, itself a reaction to the vegan-mania of the ‘10s, we’d expect to see a digestion-conscious movement coming down the line in response. Cue [fiber’s] walk-on music.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Want more great food writing and recipes? &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/newsletter?utm_source=onsite&amp;amp;utm_medium=organic&amp;amp;utm_campaign=the-bite-edit-signup"&gt;Sign up for Salon’s free food newsletter&lt;/a&gt;, The Bite.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Understandably, fiber’s takeover of the coffee space raises several questions. What does that actually look like? How much is too much? And what are the nutrition benefits — and, possible, detriments?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I spoke with a few coffee experts to dissect what “fibermaxxing” our coffee entails:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What exactly is fibermaxxing, explained in simple terms?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like its name suggests, fibermaxxing is an ongoing, social media-centric trend of maximizing dietary fiber intake by consuming fiber-rich foods like fruits, veggies, legumes, seeds, nuts, whole grains and supplements (psyllium, methylcellulose, or polycarbophil).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think this trend is the meeting point of a couple different trends that were existing already, one being gut health,” explains Cara Harbstreet, M.S., R.D., L.D., Oatly’s Director of Nutrition. “A lot of folks have taken a big interest in overall health and wellness and just how they feel day to day. Linking that to gut health was an obvious next step. So, we’ve seen that growing interest there with probiotics and prebiotics and more of the supplement space. But now, that has trickled into other foods and just a growing awareness of the role of fiber for health and well-being.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Current dietary guidelines say that most people should consume 14 grams of fiber for every 1,000 calories in their daily diet. That’s approximately 25 to 28 grams of fiber per day for women and 28 to 34 grams per day for men. However, many U.S. adults aren’t meeting those requirements. The American Society for Nutrition reported in 2021 that only five percent of men and nine percent of women were eating the recommended daily amount of dietary fiber. Additionally, colorectal cancer (CRC) rates have been on the rise in young adults. The American Cancer Society (ACS) reported that “one in five people diagnosed with CRC are now under the age of 55.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hence why fiber intake has become such a newfound craze. Harbstreet says fibermaxxing is an “evolution” of the protein-maxxing trend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is where I think there’s still a lot of confusion with fiber,” she adds. “As we’ve seen with protein, a lot of folks tend to adopt the thinking that if a little bit of something is good for me, then more must be better. And, therefore, the maxxing component comes into play, where all of a sudden this interest kind of overtakes other aspects of a balanced diet.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insoluble vs. soluble fibers?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I like to think of soluble fiber as a sponge,” Harbstreet says. “That’s an easy way to remember that it’s going to draw in that liquid. It’s going to expand and add bulk as it travels through the GI system.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She continues, “Insoluble fiber is a little bit different. It’s more like a broom, where it’s going to come through and sweep things along, kind of help clear things out.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Neither type of fiber is better than the other, but they are different functionally, Harbstreet underscores. Soluble fibers tend to add thickness and a creamy component, which is preferable when making a latte. Insoluble fibers, since they lack that absorptive effect, may cause separation when added to a cup of coffee or settle at the bottom of the mug. From a palatability standpoint, soluble fibers are more favorable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We know that fiber is showing up in in current conversations around changes to the dietary guidelines,” Harbstreet says. “That distinction is important when you think about fiber in the big picture — and understanding that both types have a role to play and which food sources, or in this case, beverages, can provide those.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What does fiber in coffee look like?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s important to note that brewed coffee already contains soluble dietary fiber. An eight-ounce cup of coffee could contain nearly 1.5 grams of fiber, while 3.2 cups could have nearly five grams, according to &lt;a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/need-fiber-have-some-coff/"&gt;Scientific American&lt;/a&gt;. However, drinking coffee alone isn’t enough to meet the minimum daily dietary fiber requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes to making a fiber-rich cup of joe, plant-based milks are a great addition, says Nethra Rajendran, Beverage Experience Developer, Oatly North America. “Oat milk has a great neutral flavor and naturally-occurring fiber,” she explains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another easy incorporation is chia seeds. “They add a great texture that is sippable and can be used in pudding form,” Rajendran says. For an indulgent breakfast option, she suggests making a tiramisu chia seed pudding with freshly-brewed espresso, oat milk, chia seeds, granola crumbles and a cacao dusting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can even add a tablespoon or two of chia seeds to your favorite latte recipes and let them sit for 30 minutes before adding ice. “When they are ready, I like to think of them as mini-fiber-bobas when I slurp them through a straw,” Rajendran says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seeds and pitted fruits can also be added in the form of pastes, purees and syrups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ingredients like dates and figs can really shine in drinks for natural sweetness and minerals,” Rajendran explains. “They are little fiber bombs and great prebiotics, as well as a source of unrefined sugar.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Black sesame is also having a moment, she continues. “I love a black sesame latte with homemade black sesame paste that I throw in the food processor and then add that paste to oat milk with a shot of espresso. Not only are black sesame seeds high in fiber, but they are an excellent source of iron and are used as a hair growth super food in Asian cultures.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are some unconventional ways to “fiber-fy” your coffee?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You would be surprised by how many ingredients you can turn into a syrup, puree, paste or concentrate,” Rajendran says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That includes corn tortillas, which can be infused alongside agave into your plant-based milk of choice, and sweet corn, which is Rajendran’s personal favorite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You can achieve a gorgeous slightly umami and sweet flavor by blending steamed or canned sweet corn kernels with oat milk and straining it,” she explains. “Some people like to keep in a little pulp for extra texture and fiber.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who aren’t big on crafting their own syrups or infusions, Rajendran recommends experimenting with fermented, umami flavors made from fiber-containing foods, like miso, tahini and gochujang, and adding them to your lattes for a hint of savory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a sweet alternative, Rajendran points to Tepache, a traditional Mexican beverage made by fermenting pineapple peels and core with piloncillo (or brown sugar) and other spices (like cinnamon) in water for a few days at room temperature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The result is a tangy, and fizzy drink,” she continues. “We are seeing people get creative with the Tepache coffee fusion — either adding finished Tepache to cold brew or adding coffee beans in the initial fermentation process with the pineapple rinds. We find that adding some oat milk balances the high acid profiles from both the coffee and Tepache and adds a creamier, rounded taste.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How much fiber is too much?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the old adage goes, too much of a good thing can be bad, which applies to fiber intake too. The main concern is people not getting enough fiber. But on the flip side, exceeding the recommended amounts of daily dietary fiber can cause several unpleasant GI symptoms, like bloating, abdominal pain, flatulence and constipation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“In addition to thinking about proteins spread evenly throughout the day, include fiber with that too,” Harbstreet says. “Loading it up in one large dose at a time likely does contribute to some of those GI symptoms that that can make us feel uncomfortable.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harbstreet also recommends pairing your fiber coffee with a complete meal, especially if you’re planning on drinking it early in the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Something as simple as pairing it with a serving of fruit, getting protein from another whole grain or high fiber food source,” she says. “This is an additive approach. We’re not looking to replace things that you’re already including in your diet. We’re looking to add something that carries that benefit through even more strongly.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, many people are indulging in coffee later in the day, as a way to have mindful moment or take a break from work, Harbstreet says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We see fiber and coffee also playing really well in that space,” she adds. “You’re sort of mentally and emotionally fulfilled by that break. But also, you walk away from it feeling like, ‘Hey, I’m not actually feeling hungry still.’”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Salon.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:30:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxNM2V3c3gzQkNVSk5mMEQ2S2d6ZUZRS1ltWXZRWUstN1Rlalp5ZHBTSGJNSEpqUVFfbm5VYkhfNEE3TloxTG41cnN1d0ttVkdmcFFtbktqbGI4YVprNUJBdEMyaXdNRng4Qk1VVlVoWE9nVkZBeTd5b2U3S1JGV3k4UA</guid></item><item><title>一位科学家质疑微塑料的新发现。然后其他研究人员反击。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/climate-environment/2026/01/17/microplastics-research-debate/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JKLB2T4DEBDZJGGXVVHJGA43YQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Over the past year, scientists have searched brain tissue, arteries and even joints for the &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/climate-environment/2026/01/04/microplastics-science-discoveries/" target="_blank"&gt;presence of microplastics&lt;/a&gt;. The tiny particles, they have found, are ubiquitous in the human body — littering testicles, placentas, blood and the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:43:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxOU1h5QjV0dVpwVHFUTG9Wc05WTm5XclFKMTJQX0xVYm4yUTI4OVlzTlZObzZXaUktaEM4bW5YRFVDMXVqR1VrYWJPY1RMUUpySjEyeERYWTBoNFJsNWEyRVBEZXRQeDhuZkdrelZxajRkcnZ5NF90WGNjTWlhbXFWQzJrdklPRGRTNWd3WmIwQks5ZmMtSUxJ</guid></item><item><title>曾经“因生命而瘫痪”的患者通过植入式神经疗法显示出持久的恢复- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/patients-once-paralyzed-by-life-show-lasting-recovery-with-implanted-nerve-therapy/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:40:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxPb08wVUJ6RWxya3RBUm9ndGVFOVhteE5MM0dpNHhzbWdOaW1HY1lMV0FZZThPR1V1V3NkX1FxU0VnVEo0dGowakhZUzJ3anY5QjcxelBPNHVzQkpjOG9FcUYya0J5dDk2SnVfVEdkTVRZbUhtcHY3YlFRYlV0c3RWNUFKVVZJSW1XX01hbGY0dkdrZVcwZjQzZkdGckZmQml4NlZhcGFfQmZGTE1W</guid></item><item><title>根据注册营养师的说法，每天吃希腊酸奶会发生什么-非常简单</title><link>https://www.realsimple.com/what-happens-when-you-eat-greek-yogurt-every-day-11887764</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="realsimple-sc-page_1-0" class="comp realsimple-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--summary realsimple-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eating Greek yogurt daily can support muscle, bone, and gut health thanks to its high protein content, calcium, B vitamins, and beneficial probiotics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It may help with appetite control, steadier blood sugar, and digestion, especially compared to regular yogurt, since it’s thicker, more filling, and lower in lactose.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To maximize benefits, dietitians recommend choosing plain varieties with minimal added sugar and selecting low-fat options if you’re mindful of saturated fat intake.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/greek-yogurt-health-benefits-7182253" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Greek yogurt&lt;/a&gt; is already found in the kitchens of many Americans as a satisfying, delicious, and healthy food choice. In fact, many people enjoy this dairy product on a daily basis as an easy addition to both sweet and savory recipes. These range from yogurt bowls, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/easy-fruit-smoothie-recipes-7375286" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;smoothies&lt;/a&gt;, and baked goods, to dips, sauces, and dressings.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; But what can you expect to happen in the body if you eat Greek yogurt every single day? Do these effects vary depending on the type of Greek yogurt you choose? We spoke with three registered dietitians to discover the answers to these questions, and more.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-greek-yogurt-nutrition"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Greek Yogurt Nutrition &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; First, let’s take a closer look at the nutrition plain whole milk Greek yogurt&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;offers in a serving (around 1/2 cup), according to USDA data&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Macronutrients&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calories: &lt;/strong&gt;95 calorie&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protein: &lt;/strong&gt;9 grams (g)&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total Carbohydrates: &lt;/strong&gt;5 g&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fat: &lt;/strong&gt;4.4 g&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturated Fat: &lt;/strong&gt;2.4 g
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Micronutrients&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Riboflavin (Vitamin B2):&lt;/strong&gt; 0.24 milligrams (mg), 19 percent of Daily Value (% DV)*&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin B12: &lt;/strong&gt;0.8 micrograms (mcg), 33% DV&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin A: &lt;/strong&gt;38 mcg, 5% DV&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calcium:&lt;/strong&gt; 111 mg, 11% DV&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zinc: &lt;/strong&gt;0.5 mg, 5% DV&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Phosphorus:&lt;/strong&gt; 126 mg, 10% DV&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Selenium:&lt;/strong&gt; 9.7 mcg, 18% DV&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sodium:&lt;/strong&gt; 34 mg, 2% DV
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--meetourexpert mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--meetourexpert mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-meetourexpert callout--bordered" data-text="Meet the Expert" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newstorynutrition.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Liz Daniels&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, DO, RD, FAAP, a dietitian, pediatrician, and founder of New Story Nutrition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/dominguez-danielle/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dani Dominguez&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MS, RDN, registered dietitian nutritionist and founder of SunBright Wellness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/in/elizabeth-keck-ms-rd-57895014b" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Elizabeth Keck&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MS, RD, a clinical dietitian in Michigan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; From this, we can see that Greek yogurt is pretty darn nutrient-dense. “Greek yogurt is packed with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/dietitian-favorite-sources-of-protein-11820661" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;protein&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/high-calcium-foods" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;calcium&lt;/a&gt;, vitamin D (depending on the brand), and vitamin B12,” says Dr. Liz Daniels, DO, RD, FAAP, dietitian, pediatrician, and founder of New Story Nutrition.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And when it comes to protein, Greek yogurt has a leg up on many other types of yogurt. “Unlike regular yogurt, Greek yogurt is strained, which removes extra liquid and leaves behind a thicker texture and a higher protein punch. Protein plays a key role in weight support and muscle health. It slows digestion, helping you feel fuller longer, and gives your body the building blocks it needs to repair and maintain muscle,” adds Daniels.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; That said, the other nutrients found in Greek yogurt support overall health, too. “It also contains calcium, which helps keep your bones and teeth strong, supports muscle movement, and helps control blood pressure,” says Elizabeth Keck, MS, RD, clinical dietitian in Michigan. The &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-high-in-phosphorus-7567264" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;phosphorus&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-high-in-vitamin-d-8781864" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;vitamin D&lt;/a&gt; it contains supports bone health as well. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Vitamin B12 is a harder-to-get nutrient that this popular yogurt also boasts higher amounts of. “Vitamin B12 is a nutrient essential for red blood cell formation and neurological health,” explains Dani Dominguez, MS, RDN, registered dietitian nutritionist and founder of SunBright Wellness&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In addition to these macronutrients and micronutrients, Greek yogurt is even an excellent source of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/recipe-collections-favorites/healthy-meals/what-is-a-probiotic" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;probiotics&lt;/a&gt;, depending on the brand. “Greek yogurt has good bacteria called probiotics that help keep your gut healthy and support your immune system. It is also lower in lactose, so it can be easier to digest for people who are sensitive to lactose,” adds Keck.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; However, there are a few potential nutritional downsides to this beloved dairy product. “Full-fat varieties contain saturated fats, which should be consumed in moderation, particularly for individuals managing cholesterol levels or heart health,” explains Dominguez, as this type of fat can raise LDL (low-density lipoprotein or ‘bad’) cholesterol&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/CIRCULATIONAHA.122.061010" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;i&lt;/a&gt;ncreasing heart disease risk.&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Additionally, some Greek yogurts may contain unwanted additives—particularly pro-inflammatory added sugar. &lt;span data-cite="5" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;“Many flavored Greek yogurts have a lot of added sugar, sometimes 10 to 20 grams in one serving. Eating too much added sugar can upset your stomach and cause quick rises in blood sugar,” explains Keck.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And, of course, those allergic or sensitive to dairy should use caution around Greek yogurt. “Greek yogurt is a dairy product, which means it contains &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/recipe-collections-favorites/popular-ingredients/cheese-can-eat-lactose-intolerant" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;lactose&lt;/a&gt; as the carbohydrate source.  Some people have a hard time digesting lactose and get gastrointestinal discomfort (like gas, bloating or diarrhea) from eating too much. However, while lactose is in Greek yogurt, it is partially broken down by the probiotics, so it tends to have fewer side effects than milk or soft cheeses,” shares Daniels.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-happens-when-you-eat-greek-yogurt-every-morning"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What Happens When You Eat Greek Yogurt Every Morning?  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; With this information in mind, what can you expect if you eat Greek yogurt every single day?
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Eating Greek yogurt can help you get more protein each day, keep your bones strong over time, and support &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/gut-healthy-lunch-ideas-11709481" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;healthy digestion&lt;/a&gt;,” explains Keck. Daniels agrees, adding that this practice will, “support gut health, appetite control, and stable blood sugars because of its balanced macronutrients and probiotics.” Dominguez concurs, concluding, “for most individuals, eating Greek yogurt daily can be a part of a balanced diet.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; But not all Greek yogurts are created equal when it comes to these health benefits. If you have any heart health concerns, choosing a low-fat Greek yogurt may be a smart choice—especially if you eat it everyday. Opting for a low-added sugar option is also a must. “As a dietitian, I recommend to my clients that they buy plain Greek yogurt and sweeten it themselves with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/low-sugar-fruits-7481285" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;fruits&lt;/a&gt;, nuts, seeds, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/healthy-eating/cinnamon-benefits" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;cinnamon&lt;/a&gt;, and a drizzle of honey,” explains Keck.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When looking for the optimal probiotic content, take a close look at the food packaging. “Because probiotic content can vary widely between brands, not all Greek yogurts offer the same digestive benefits. Food brands can participate in a voluntary certification program called the Live &amp;amp; Active Culture (LAC) Seal. This program is administered by the International Dairy Foods Association (IDFA) which verifies the levels of live and active cultures, specifically the bacteria Lactobacillus bulgaricus and Streptococcus thermophilus content. By seeing this label on the container, it can give you more confidence that the Greek yogurt contains beneficial live cultures that support digestive health,” says Dominguez.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And once your Greek yogurt is home, there are so many delicious ways to enjoy it. “Consider trying it in smoothies, as a substitute for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/browse-all-recipes/sour-cream" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;sour cream&lt;/a&gt; or veggie dip, in baked goods like muffins or banana bread, homemade popsicles and as a base for overnight oats to get more variety,” Daniels offers.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Real Simple</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxOWGFfTG41dDdjQ1RfZXNKaDBGXzJZX1o4d0ZvcEU2SnBkalFPTjJjYnFXTUZXbUxuZjVsV2lNZEZnZWRIcHJXVXN2TG9TR2RocllBUk9fbjV6TnJpU1hIMXFnaDNfdHU5M251TTM5b0J5WU0tbUFSYjFwYnVBejdydmxCelk4QUZ1OV9DVw</guid></item><item><title>西澳多年来首次出现麻疹疫情--《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/4-wa-measles-cases-leave-health-officials-racing-to-quell-outbreak/</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitwFBVV95cUxQVmJDakcwZjlnMzN4cnRZUmR4T0diWV9kRXpzVGJrRUFJUVlhSFl0c2Y5Z0xkNGhKemx2cEhMWEZjZVZjak9kbnFrWDBfN1pmekFRRFRBenVBeUVobmVzOV9KZlByS0pNZXNPSHJnaGRsMmg2aFBIMlhuNld4Si1yV3M2YlFGLVV2SV9fMjRNQTJDRWN6bGt4YUVoWDFjYm84VDhpRUo0Ul9NSHcxUG9paXF2UUhCTnM?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;WA sees measles outbreak for first time in years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi-gFBVV95cUxQdDhib1FWcGVNYXNCWGNPYjh2OGxOWkJSaWtFLS1TQ2Y5bHZSSzdmSGpqUzJjVmdCaXk5UXYxMXlTN09nR3pxbjFEVUFBcUY2RzJ0UkdjLVpYQ3lzNDh1WDBaa3lpUGFrWkM0X1Z3RjNuYlIyYUxwRGVvSVdUQmNrQTJvYXZmT3ZOYnFoQnpFdFd3M3BOTVVRQ2l4ZWV1TUc5OTQzZldBTl9tS2xWWGEwOTJ3aDMyTlZySUVjbGxBSTNpS0JEQTlHNHJVdXEwTXpibW04STlRUGhUeXlNQmM5M1NTT2hORzVzaVNYaDVLYmNwRC1sNm5YdEpn?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Health officials monitor spread of measles virus in Snohomish County following outbreak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;KOMO&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi5AFBVV95cUxPYktaWVRNT19ZemU3SmkwM0RUY1NtbUhqaW96cVo4YnFqdDBDUEFndzFHMC1Ib0xXQTFtNGttUVZ6YVlEYlA2ZTVsTnhLbUFMSUVwNDRJalZ5bU8tWk5aRkJTWmhYMnlZYld5NUZRSm5lbm1Tbk43bE1xbDdCZ2tZelNxazlZWFVpNHRMUzBtb0RLM2tiZmZfNUpaSWtVYmIxTGhUdDJnMzdXWTQxdWNNRzJDZEVzSkZXeU9mV083MkVUOFM1ckJ6NzNjSGJXQlk5RWc4TDlrSjdnb29mWVJEMkNsTHE?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;A family visiting Washington over the holidays exposed others to measles at these locations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;king5.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi4gFBVV95cUxPZEFPUjN2QW9ETnhXcDdnc3FqX0paTzhhSTBFSmFTa3FYMFRGRmpoWXkwcFUtak9wLXc0M3h2Zk52N3FadFVTWU9TU2hTSFlBaXBzZ0xSX0lObHRvMnZINjdZTHhEbzg2YlVORlhjTjNYRmpIaTdSN09uaWp6ai1IUDM1YjhocGZMbU1kY0JzU3pLRmEwdDI5WGpUZlNJWGFKXzRLT3FFM2pWWlZUMVQ1TlFYOUxJYzBfQWVzdEZtS3J4VlVENkw5bzZCb0VrVmZYeWc3blBOWE5fY0hmZGg5bHZn0gH2AUFVX3lxTE5yaFpLbng4MlJqdWc2amVydFZaSkt3UXFLS2Q5OEJfOGF5NVBLalBUdUFMYTdtTndGR1pSMXJDTDRnZGpYNk1kX0Q4eEplOVA1M090dm1FUU1yUEtHdzF3N0h2dlFsYXBmVG9VbmowSU11SEVQbHN0djZfN3gzZzg0SGNJZkhubEFaelVnTmVxc2RCb21lcTBraTVrcUlUaTYzQVlXRUI5WUtNMDNBNkNqTnFxeE1FeC1iWDQyelFsNzhlbE9Td2FNSHBSZnJCOEpSOVNfcjNGWHhZUUpjZVR3TFJKZ3VIVEZUeVVzNEhFX2hKVW9yZw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Fourth exposure site confirmed in Snohomish County measles outbreak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;KIRO 7 News Seattle&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimwFBVV95cUxQSUJFWkRqUXVFUHRVQnlVcnBiNWJFdk00aVNqV2E3c1NwRTFvczI3VFdST1htRDc4SDdneS1CV1otdk5HNkNyMVlYVlNZclJCM2JZX2hNbFA2Y3hrMERzU0plMW5VZXBFM1RLcVVWdXZZTjA2TFFiQW45cTBaR1AxYzJrZE1BcXhSZVhCY1NwN01yLVJCYkJTazE4Zw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Snohomish County declares measles outbreak, confirms 3 new cases&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Everett Herald&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxQVmJDakcwZjlnMzN4cnRZUmR4T0diWV9kRXpzVGJrRUFJUVlhSFl0c2Y5Z0xkNGhKemx2cEhMWEZjZVZjak9kbnFrWDBfN1pmekFRRFRBenVBeUVobmVzOV9KZlByS0pNZXNPSHJnaGRsMmg2aFBIMlhuNld4Si1yV3M2YlFGLVV2SV9fMjRNQTJDRWN6bGt4YUVoWDFjYm84VDhpRUo0Ul9NSHcxUG9paXF2UUhCTnM</guid></item><item><title>等等……所有这些研究都可能因为严重的错误而“检测到”人体中的微塑料-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/science-energy/microplastics-studies-human-body-error</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="article-featured-image-figure"&gt;
			
			
	&lt;p class="article-featured-image-caption-container"&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="article-featured-image-caption"&gt;
			Illustration by Tag Hartman-Simkins / Futurism. Source: Getty Images
 		&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/figure&gt;
	
	
	
	
	
	&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;A deluge of research has painted a picture of our world being drowned in tiny, inescapable microplastics. Our guilt over plastic particles being found in even the &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/microplastics-sediment-layers"&gt;most remote regions&lt;/a&gt; on Earth turned into paranoia once scientists started discovering them in our own bodies, too — riddling our &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2022/mar/24/microplastics-found-in-human-blood-for-first-time" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;blood streams&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/insights/2025/01/microplastics-in-body-polluted-tiny-plastic-fragments.html" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;organs&lt;/a&gt;, and even &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/brains-microplastics-study"&gt;our brains&lt;/a&gt;, stoking a rush of scientific inquest.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;But now, there’s a growing contingent in the scientific community that’s casting significant doubts on these claims, &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2026/jan/13/microplastics-human-body-doubt" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Guardian &lt;/em&gt;reports&lt;/a&gt;, criticizing the methodologies used in some of the most notable papers behind them.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;One &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-024-03453-1" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Nature Medicine &lt;/em&gt;last February claimed to have documented a rise in micro and nanoplastics (MNPs) in human brain tissues by autopsying preserved cadavers of people who had died between 1997 and 2024. But in November, another group of researchers contested the findings in a &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-025-04045-3.epdf?sharing_token=Swtp3rys_E2BRMy_4UzjxNRgN0jAjWel9jnR3ZoTv0PS5QtSs_irU94U55JE4Ar4Z5UOMBpR3_t_yCh0UzMgGKL-GztU5e15cffbRpDb67AMozIXlp82gM9YW2QGk63C5OxsW_ncVxqYJfdR7JAeVCZI4Lm6SNe2MQ8ERqGifs1OgQsP5qE_G-FoRGaatnnKUVXs-mVt2rnDNZCH-KhkeAl8JJ6iMM5a0HkEMmh7iEykGmqbwM7HNfyR0WQXdXyZG_lEJi-kldTxX-9AEdPLcphyK-h1_XS0ZkOypNJl5Nc%3D&amp;amp;tracking_referrer=www.theguardian.com" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;letter&lt;/a&gt; published in the same journal, criticizing them for “limited contamination controls and lack of validation steps,” per &lt;em&gt;The Guardian&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“The brain microplastic paper is a joke,” coauthor of the letter Dušan Materić, from the Helmholtz Centre for Environmental Research in Germany, told the newspaper. “Fat is known to make false-positives for polyethylene. The brain has [approximately] 60 percent fat.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;In reality, Materić suggests that rising obesity rates could explain the trend.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“That paper is really bad, and it is very explainable why it is wrong,” he added, warning that there’s serious doubts over “more than half of the very high impact papers” over microplastics in tissues.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;One core issue arises from the prevailing method for measuring the mass of micro and nanoplastics. Called Py-GC-MS, it involves pyrolyzing the sample, or heating it in an oxygen free environment until it vaporizes. The fumes this process produces are then separated and measured so the nature of the original substance can be analyzed.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;But as it turns out, the same fume signatures for the materials used in microplastics like polyethylene can also be produced from the fats present in human tissue. And while studies purport to chemically remove the tissues before subjecting the samples to pyrolysis, critics are skeptical that some traces aren’t being left over and producing false positives. This led University of Queensland environmental chemist Cassandra Rauert to conclude in a January 2025 &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.est.4c12599" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt; that Py-GC-MS “is not currently a suitable technique for identifying polyethylene or PVC due to persistent interferences.” In all, the paper points to 18 studies that didn’t properly account for the risk of false positives.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“I do think it is a problem in the entire field,” Rauert added to &lt;em&gt;The Guardian&lt;/em&gt;. “I think a lot of the concentrations [of MNPs] that are being reported are completely unrealistic.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Another problem is that while the field of analytical chemistry has guidelines on how to analyze certain samples, these guidelines don’t exist yet for microplastics, according to Frederic Béen at Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“But we still see quite a lot of papers where very standard good laboratory practices that should be followed have not necessarily been followed,” he told &lt;em&gt;The Guardian&lt;/em&gt;, such as measures for removing background contamination. “So you cannot be assured that whatever you have found is not fully or partially derived from some of these issues.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The debate underscores how nascent the field of exploring the environmental and health impact of microplastics is, meaning it will take many more years of patient science before the dust is settled. At present, experts aren’t sure how microplastics affect our health, nor have they definitely proven that they’re harmful to us (though there are &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/health-medicine/microplastics-degrading-bones"&gt;no shortage of studies&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/microplastics-brain-mental-health"&gt;suggesting they do&lt;/a&gt;). Still, no one can be blamed for being unsettled by the idea of having a plastic spoon’s worth of the stuff in their noggin, but if the skeptics are believed, maybe that claim is up for review, too.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“We do have plastics in us — I think that is safe to assume,” Materić said. “But real hard proof on how much is yet to come.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on microplastics:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/health-medicine/microplastics-clogging-arteries"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Doctors Find Evidence Microplastics Are Clogging Arteries, Leading to Heart Attacks and Strokes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTFBxdmxMRDRmSXcwTVRhMlhaUnNmQmQxYmw5S0U2VXhpTC1WMEExSlJfbmpjeHZCY3JYRWpjcnR1bFZ0NklyVmpueDk1dlZQY190V0pzQzFhdlM4UU9pNS11SUdtSHBIeDNfLXdCMlpZdnhzOUI2UzFiMmd6SnZ2NUU</guid></item><item><title>人民药房：睾酮替代疗法是否会增加心脏病发作和癌症的风险？ - OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/advice/2026/01/peoples-pharmacy-doesnt-testosterone-replacement-therapy-contribute-to-risk-of-heart-attacks-and-cancer.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BWVOY24CQBDELDXQ6NXPISPPEE"&gt;Q. You recently wrote that testosterone does not increase the risk for heart attacks. But you overlooked the real risk of testosterone therapy: cancer!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RVLUGOAY7BAMJFLS2HHBKTFF3A"&gt;I survived advanced prostate cancer seven years ago by having my testes removed because prostate cancer needs testosterone to grow. Most men with prostate cancer get leuprolide injections for several months to suppress testosterone production while they wait for radiation or surgery. They get off it as quickly as possible though, because men would rather die than give up sex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JFYCFN5YNRHCPNAHZG5PLM3IH4"&gt;A. For decades, physicians believed that elevated testosterone levels increased the risk for prostate cancer and heart disease. A large clinical trial published in the New England Journal of Medicine (July 13, 2023) contradicted that conviction. It concluded that testosterone replacement therapy (TRT) did not contribute to cardiovascular events. The same study also determined that men with low PSA levels were no more likely to develop prostate cancer on TRT than on placebo (JAMA Network Open, Dec. 1, 2023). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DQ2RQWBV2NEFLEMF4MJPUI5KOA"&gt;As you note, prostate cancer is frequently treated with androgen deprivation therapy (ADT). This can be achieved with drugs such as leuprolide or the surgical removal of the testes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AW27S6DSHFCL3LRTWJSJCAN7NU"&gt;* * *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JV6MCHOH2VEWXPLJQLBNMTAT4M"&gt;&lt;i&gt;In their column, Joe and Teresa Graedon answer letters from readers. Write to them in care of King Features, 628 Virginia Drive, Orlando, FL 32803, or email them via their website: www.PeoplesPharmacy.com. Their newest book is “Top Screwups Doctors Make and How to Avoid Them.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5AFBVV95cUxOMFpfRWVidl9PNTloRmk1bzNZbF9WTk9hdlU1ZHdBWTFYTmxXcXFhWmJWODBPQVFCWGNaZHRhTkFXb19qSjNUS29sRVNCR3FfTTB2UXFQZTNJRWpKTFdyNDVLZTZDTXhjQW5SMzNiamhTcnc2QTJ3OWFmUDk2U0tieF9IeXhxRnEwa2Q5MlUxQ3Nnem5fX0Z1YnkzVndJOUFxVDFiYnNPYUZja0VSOTV1Z3otTUF1bHg0dWdteUFMZTdXY1hDeHpzQXFkWXRQdEFab2dSZUZLSlN6SENrWTJBRFAzLUvSAfgBQVVfeXFMTWpGRGRIR0VDbzg3WHkzc0l1VVotVWJsamZIYktESjlmLWRmZUN2S1hiMFBzbk1NNi13STZtM2gtbERFWFJGc1JYTnI3Vy1KMDZqRXlrd2ZqOFBmRVdmbmdEYXd3NS1BZ1JQbnhFNzNJN1o3aTVfcUwyUmZtVTU1SzFxUFN3ckVlVTNtWXJtZVQwUlk0bEU0QkVmazNRYVQwbUQ1STEzQUxtRHdxSmIwUk0ycTlIMWtiWTQ4dDFOSmZmUjE2ZnNGR3l1QXpTand6QzU5UWtqY1NmWmY5UWJzdFJ4by1rWjNmLXR1eDFfb1VPeTNtZ2Q0X3c</guid></item></channel></rss>