<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>斐济的HIV病例因蓝斑、化疗和共用针头而激增--英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c0m42dwvlk8o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;'They're not just sharing needles, they're sharing blood': How HIV cases soared in Fiji&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 kSquvq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/11fb/live/1d4988b0-9f6f-11f0-99d3-79886bca9dc5.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Three syringes, seemingly used, lying on a tattered orange blanket" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Intravenous drug use is fuelling Fiji's HIV epidemic&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ten: that's the age of the youngest person with HIV that Sesenieli Naitala has ever met.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;When she first started Fiji's Survivor Advocacy Network in 2013, that young boy was yet to be born. Now he is one of thousands of Fijians to have contracted the bloodborne virus in recent years – many of them aged 19 or younger, and many of them through intravenous drug use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"More young people are using drugs," Ms Naitala, whose organisation provides support to sex workers and drug users in the Fijian capital Suva, tells the BBC. "He (the boy) was one of those young people that were sharing needles on the street during Covid."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Over the past five years, Fiji – a tiny South Pacific nation with a population of less than a million – has become the locus of one of the world's fastest growing HIV epidemics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In 2014, the country had fewer than 500 people living with HIV. By 2024 that number had soared to approximately 5,900 – an elevenfold leap. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;That same year, Fiji recorded 1,583 new cases – a thirteenfold increase on its usual five-year average. Of those, 41 were aged 15 or younger, compared to just 11 in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7b4b/live/5dd4aa90-9f6f-11f0-9bc3-493c32f03408.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A view of the Suva waterfront, with a dock in the foreground and multi-storey buildings in the background" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Fiji's assistant health minister has called the HIV epidemic a "national crisis"&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Such figures prompted the country's minister for health and medical services to declare an HIV outbreak in January. Last week, assistant health minister Penioni Ravunawa warned Fiji may record more than 3,000 new HIV cases by the end of 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"This is a national crisis," he said. "And it is not slowing down."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The BBC spoke to multiple experts, advocates and frontline workers about the reasons for such a meteoric rise in case numbers. Several pointed out that, as awareness around HIV spreads and stigma diminishes, more people have been coming forward and getting tested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;At the same time though, they also noted that countless more remain invisible to the official figures – and that the true scale of the issue is likely much bigger than even the record-breaking numbers suggest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;'Sharing the blood'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Underpinning Fiji's HIV epidemic is a spiralling trend of drug use, unsafe sex, needle sharing and "bluetoothing". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Otherwise known as "hotspotting", this latter term refers to a practice where an intravenous drug user withdraws their blood after a hit and injects it into a second person – who may then do the same for a third, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Kalesi Volatabu, executive director for the NGO Drug Free Fiji, has seen it happen firsthand. Last May, she was on one of her regular early morning walks through the Fijian capital of Suva, offering support and education to drug users on the streets, when she turned a corner and saw a group of seven or eight people huddling together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I saw the needle with the blood – it was right there in front of me," she recalls. "This young woman, she'd already had the shot and she's taking out the blood – and then you've got other girls, other adults, already lining up to be hit with this thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It's not just needles they're sharing – they're sharing the blood."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Bluetoothing has also been reported in South Africa and Lesotho, two countries with some of the world's highest rates of HIV. In Fiji, the practice became popular within the past few years, according to both Ms Volatabu and Ms Naitala.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/de66/live/54020880-a007-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Supplied: Kalesi Volatabu A woman in a black and turquoise dress, wearing glasses and speaking into a microphone in front of several onlookers. Behind her is a wall with several pieces of paper attached to it" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Supplied: Kalesi Volatabu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Kalesi Volatabu has spent more than a decade working at the frontline of drug awareness and advocacy in Fiji&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;One reason for its appeal, they explain, is a cheaper high: multiple people can chip in for a single hit and share it among themselves. Another is the convenience of only needing one syringe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;These can be difficult to come by in Fiji, where pharmacies, under police pressure, often demand prescriptions for syringes, and there is a lack of needle-syringe programmes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Although there is growing acceptance and approval for the rollout of such programmes – which provide clean injecting equipment to drug users in an attempt to reduce the transmission of blood-borne infections like HIV – implementation in the highly religious and conservative country has proven challenging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ms Volatabu says there is a "drastic shortage" of needle-syringe sites, which is fuelling dangerous practices like needle-sharing and bluetoothing and putting the onus on NGOs to distribute syringes as well as condoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In August 2024, Fiji's Ministry of Health and Medical Services (MOH) recognised bluetoothing as one of the drivers for the country's rise in HIV cases. Another was chemsex, where people use drugs - often methamphetamine - before and during sexual encounters. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In Fiji, unlike most other countries around the world, crystal meth is predominantly consumed via intravenous injection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;MOH also found that of the 1,093 new cases recorded in the first nine months of 2024, 223 – about 20% – were from intravenous drug use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Kids on meth&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Fiji has become a major Pacific trafficking hub for crystal meth over the past 15 years. A large part of this is due to the country's geographic location between East Asia and the Americas – some of the world's biggest manufacturers of the drug - and Australia and New Zealand – the world's highest-paying markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;During that same period, meth has spilled into and spread throughout local communities, developing into a crisis that, like HIV, was recently declared a "national emergency". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;And according to those on the frontlines, the age of users is trending downwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We see more and more of these young people," says Ms Volatabu. "They are getting younger and younger."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Fiji's most recent national HIV statistics cite injectable drug use as the most common known mode of transmission, accounting for 48% of cases. Sexual transmission accounted for 47% of cases, while mother-to-child transmission during pregnancy and childbirth was cited as the cause of most paediatric cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Everyone the BBC spoke to agreed that lack of education is a central factor in the epidemic. Ms Volatabu and Ms Naitala are both working to change that – and Ms Naitala says that as a greater awareness around the dangers of HIV spreads throughout the community, "bluetoothing" has, in her experience, fallen out of favour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;More people are getting tested and seeking treatment for HIV, leading to more robust data around the scale of the crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But there is still a worry that the official case numbers are merely the tip of the iceberg – and a fear of what may lie beneath the surface.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;The avalanche&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;José Sousa-Santos, head of the Pacific Regional Security Hub at New Zealand's University of Canterbury, says "a perfect storm is brewing".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"The concern is across all levels of society and government in regards to Fiji's HIV crisis – not just what's happening at the moment, but where it's going to be in three years' time and the lack of Fiji's resources," he tells the BBC. "The support systems - the nursing, the ability to distribute or to access the drugs for treatment of HIV - just aren't there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"That's what terrifies us, the people that work in the region: there is no way that Fiji can deal with this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/18f8/live/83b21860-9ffb-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Supplied: José Sousa-Santos A man with a goatee wearing a blue suit and blue shirt" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Supplied: José Sousa-Santos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;José Sousa-Santos has been ringing the alarm bell on Fiji's HIV epidemic for years&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Following its declaration of an outbreak in January, the Fijian government has sought to improve its HIV surveillance and enhance its ability to address the likely underreporting of cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The Global Alert and Response Network, which was called upon to provide that support, stated in a recent report that "addressing these pressing issues through a well-coordinated national response is crucial in reversing the trajectory of the HIV epidemic in Fiji".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;That report also noted that staffing shortages, communication issues, challenges with lab equipment and stockouts of HIV rapid tests and medicines were impacting screening, diagnosis and treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Data collection is slow, difficult and error-prone, it added – hampering efforts to understand the extent of Fiji's HIV epidemic and the efficacy of the outbreak response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;That leaves many experts, authorities and everyday Fijians in the dark.  And Mr Sousa-Santos is predicting an "avalanche" of cases still to come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"What we're seeing at the moment is the beginning of the avalanche, but you can't stop it, because the infections are already happening now, or they've already happened – we're just not going to be able to see them and people aren't going to look to get tested for another two to three years," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"There's nothing that we can do at the moment to stop the number of infections that have already happened over the past year, and that are happening now. That's what's really terrifying."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 00:58:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE40M0FvM0gtUTdVN1lyUmNCZ01fbUd0blcwQUxPSlc1QzUyekRqTmx5eG5vWndubkNZVVQ4QU1nM0NodERrcW1kN2lrR3RuR0hIU09pSGRTazdKQdIBX0FVX3lxTE01bFhzMmVvczN4VU9HUno1RThPeXhYMFBWVVBIZF9EVVgtOElhMW00S2pPY2tDVk9ZZndGOS1WdkJ6QXk4NmZ6b3VXakduTzlWYmRiVTFGSzhzTnNiT3Rn</guid></item><item><title>南卡罗来纳州证实麻疹爆发，美国病例达到25年高位- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/south-carolina-confirms-measles-outbreak-with-us-cases-at-25-year-high_n_68e152b6e4b01314b83e05ae</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Carolina officials have confirmed an outbreak of measles in the state, contributing to what has been the &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/measles-cases-rise-to-highest-level-since-its-elimination_n_686d1da6e4b0525032870a1a" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="highest level of cases" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e152b6e4b01314b83e05ae" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="686d1da6e4b0525032870a1a" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;highest level of cases&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. since the disease was declared &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/history.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="eliminated in 2000. " data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e152b6e4b01314b83e05ae" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/history.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;eliminated in 2000. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of Wednesday, eight cases had been reported in the Upstate region of the state, according to the &lt;a href="https://dph.sc.gov/news/dph-confirms-measles-outbreak-upstate-region" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="South Carolina Department of Public Health." data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e152b6e4b01314b83e05ae" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://dph.sc.gov/news/dph-confirms-measles-outbreak-upstate-region" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;South Carolina Department of Public Health.&lt;/a&gt; A measles outbreak is defined as three or more cases that are linked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The people involved in the outbreak are unvaccinated and did not have immunity from a previous measles infection,” DPH said. The agency added that it’s notifying people who may have been exposed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far this year, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has identified &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="more than 1,500 cases " data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e152b6e4b01314b83e05ae" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;more than 1,500 cases &lt;/a&gt;of measles in the U.S. across 41 states, the largest surge in 25 years. Ninety-two percent of those who have gotten measles are unvaccinated or their vaccination status is unknown, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Measles is an airborne, extremely infectious, and potentially severe rash illness,” the CDC’s website says. “&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/history.html" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Before the measles vaccine" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e152b6e4b01314b83e05ae" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/history.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;Before the measles vaccine&lt;/a&gt; was introduced, an estimated 48,000 people were hospitalized and 400–500 people died in the United States each year.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/measles-cases-us-texas-900_n_680d0467e4b04560cabe9300" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="majority of cases have been reported in Texas" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e152b6e4b01314b83e05ae" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="680d0467e4b04560cabe9300" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;majority of cases have been reported in Texas&lt;/a&gt;, where two school-aged children died while living in outbreak areas earlier this year. In August, Texas state health officials &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/measles-outbreak-texas-over-health-officials/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="officially declared the outbreak over" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e152b6e4b01314b83e05ae" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/measles-outbreak-texas-over-health-officials/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;officially declared the outbreak over&lt;/a&gt; as cases continued to rise in other states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;As cases grow, anti-vaccine conspiracy theorist and Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has been &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/top-covid-vaccine-adviser-quits-after-rfk-jr-changes-recommendations_n_6840b913e4b00b2e94c56f20" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="remaking" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e152b6e4b01314b83e05ae" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="6840b913e4b00b2e94c56f20" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;remaking&lt;/a&gt; the CDC &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/rfk-jr-new-members-cdc-vaccine-panel_n_68c9270de4b056d71f62649c" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="in his own" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e152b6e4b01314b83e05ae" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="68c9270de4b056d71f62649c" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;in his own&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/rfk-jr-to-require-placebo-testing-for-all-new-vaccines_n_6814f8a9e4b0c553a15cbfec" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="image" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e152b6e4b01314b83e05ae" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="6814f8a9e4b0c553a15cbfec" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;image&lt;/a&gt; in an effort to loosen vaccine requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="support-huffpost-entry-support-huffpost-mid-article" class="cli support-huffpost-mid-article primary-cli cli cli-text cli-support-huffpost hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__content-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title default-title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;20 Years Of&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Free&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Journalism&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;Your Support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Fuels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Our Mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;Your Support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Fuels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Our Mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message-container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message support-huffpost__message--main"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__sub-headline"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For two decades, HuffPost has been fearless, unflinching, and relentless in pursuit of the truth. Support our mission to keep us around for the next 20 — we can't do this without you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We remain committed to providing you with the unflinching, fact-based journalism everyone deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for your support along the way. We’re truly grateful for readers like you! Your initial support helped get us here and bolstered our newsroom, which kept us strong during uncertain times. Now as we continue, we need your help more than ever. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;We hope you will join us once again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We remain committed to providing you with the unflinching, fact-based journalism everyone deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for your support along the way. We’re truly grateful for readers like you! Your initial support helped get us here and bolstered our newsroom, which kept us strong during uncertain times. Now as we continue, we need your help more than ever. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;We hope you will join us once again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a class="cli-support-huffpost__support-button accent-button" href="https://www.huffpost.com/support?utm_campaign=mid-article-web" data-vars-item-name-overwritable="support-huffpost" data-vars-item-name="Support HuffPost" data-vars-item-type="button" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;Support HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="support-huffpost-login"&gt;Already contributed? &lt;a class="js-entry-link-no-impression" href="https://login.huffpost.com/login?dest=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.huffpost.com%2Fentry%2Fsouth-carolina-confirms-measles-outbreak-with-us-cases-at-25-year-high_n_68e152b6e4b01314b83e05ae%3Fhp_auth_done%3D1" data-vars-item-name="Log in to hide these messages" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68e152b6e4b01314b83e05ae" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/login" data-vars-target-content-type="utility" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component"&gt;Log in to hide these messages.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Carolina state epidemiologist Dr. Linda Bell said she expects cases in the state to rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We anticipate more cases will be identified and implore community members to act responsibly,” Bell said. “If you are ill, stay home.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 18:27:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixwFBVV95cUxNell4VGR4c3F6MC1odHgzU0Y3ZVNmWUpQRGFzQ29seTZsNVZYQmZPZDZTaVoyRzRtSEFBc05jbjFfckRvckpxR1c5V2d0TG93bnU2TlhmQ2hGdnVFakpwMk5tWmx6VUZfQWxoRUxFUjE3MDl5U0VQMHN1ZGVuUkViakp2RU9FZ3dYMHhPdV90ZHFGMDV1ZkFvQ1BKc2VFVmNmV2UxRl9kSm9JX2NHWXppbUJuYlRsc21HY0JpUGxFVnZudk1lOHFR0gHMAUFVX3lxTE96RFU0RlgxbWhOeUVqOThqNWJTb2RnbVJfZlQyd3R3a054Y3FiM29QSFJ2ekVISlJmb3pjWjVwT2hPeUZWa3ZJSnphS0lVLW0wNzVPMHF1Zk1pWGJVcEVPSy03c3lzM2YzbzFLTUxtcDdSQ01VRmwyMi1qTFdab3FSeWdOT3hHTlVaWHZ0R2JMdVUzTXZsNXJxV2ZUTTFPcGlxSXZQMXlfZFlLWGtzNXZVR2JfUTBGNUZUb1U3ZFBJUkpMSUVoVXhmTUZvQg</guid></item><item><title>每天吃肉桂对身体有什么影响- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/benefits-of-cinnamon-11822645</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="What to Know About Cinnamon" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cinnamon’s antioxidants may protect cells, lower inflammation and reduce chronic disease risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Around a teaspoon a day may help control blood sugar, boost insulin sensitivity and support heart health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be mindful about consuming large doses or cinnamon supplements, as they can interact with medications and have negative health effects.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Cinnamon isn’t just a cozy spice for your latte or oatmeal—it’s one of the oldest known spices, used for centuries for both flavor and potential health benefits.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; And according to dietitians, modern research is beginning to confirm what ancient traditions may have believed. “Cinnamon offers several health benefits thanks to its high antioxidant content and anti-inflammatory properties,” says &lt;a href="https://www.samanthadevitonutrition.com/about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Samantha DeVito, M.S., RD, CDN&lt;/a&gt;. Keep reading to learn why cinnamon is so good for you, plus the best ways to add it to your routine. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-why-we-love-cinnamon"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Why We Love Cinnamon &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; It’s Rich in Antioxidants &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Cinnamon is full of antioxidants, particularly polyphenols like cinnamic acid and cinnamaldehyde,” says &lt;a href="https://www.diabetesteam.com/writers/683f0deb46c7aa1e0f3349e2" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Avery Zenker, RD, M.A.N&lt;/a&gt;.  Antioxidants help the body neutralize oxidative stress, a process that can otherwise damage cells and contribute to chronic inflammation. When the body is exposed to inflammation over extended periods, the risk of metabolic diseases increases.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Cinnamon’s abundant antioxidant profile could help protect your cells from damage, slow aging-related processes and may reduce the risk of chronic diseases,” Zenker adds.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; It May Support Healthy Blood Sugar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Cinnamon has been widely studied for its potential role in regulating blood sugar levels. Its plant compounds may mimic insulin, making it easier for the body to move glucose into cells and lowering blood sugar levels.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Research has tested a range of cinnamon doses to see if more is better, but benefits don’t seem to depend on the amount consumed. “Even as little as a teaspoon (about 2 grams) per day could improve blood sugar regulation in some individuals,” says Zenker. “It has also been shown to improve insulin sensitivity and reduce post-meal blood sugar spikes, which is particularly relevant for people with prediabetes or type 2 diabetes,” DeVito tells &lt;em&gt;EatingWell.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Whether consumed in foods, teas or supplements, cinnamon may help improve blood sugar control in people with and without diabetes,” says &lt;a href="https://sheridietitian.com/about-me/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Sheri Gaw, RD, CDCES&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; It Could Benefit Heart Health &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; According to both Zenker and DeVito, cinnamon may also play a supportive role in maintaining healthy cholesterol and triglyceride levels—two key markers of cardiovascular risk. Some recent studies suggest that regular cinnamon intake is linked to lower total and LDL (often called “bad”) cholesterol levels, reductions in triglycerides and improvements in HDL cholesterol—the “good” cholesterol that helps protect your arteries.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Cinnamon may also have modest benefits for blood pressure, though findings are mixed,” adds Zenker. One study found that consuming cinnamon consistently for eight weeks led to lower blood pressure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While cinnamon alone won’t replace other heart-healthy habits or doctor-recommended treatments, adding it regularly to meals is one simple way to give your cardiovascular system an extra boost.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; It Might Help Reduce Inflammation-Related Disorders &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Many health conditions are influenced by chronic inflammation, and the plant compounds in cinnamon may help calm inflammatory pathways. These benefits could be particularly beneficial for individuals managing arthritis, heart disease and type 2 diabetes.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Cinnamon intake has been associated with reduced systemic inflammation, including lower levels of C-reactive protein (CRP), a marker of inflammation,” says Zenker.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Further research is needed to investigate the long-term effects. Still, adding cinnamon to meals may offer gentle support against the kind of ongoing inflammation that can worsen symptoms of chronic disease.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-nutrition-information"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Nutrition Information &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Cinnamon is usually consumed in small amounts, so it doesn’t provide a significant source of calories or major nutrients. Here’s the breakdown for 1 teaspoon (2.6 grams) of ground cinnamon:&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calories&lt;/strong&gt;: 6&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carbohydrates&lt;/strong&gt;: 2g&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dietary fiber&lt;/strong&gt;: 1g&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total sugar&lt;/strong&gt;: 0g&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Added sugar&lt;/strong&gt;: 0g&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protein&lt;/strong&gt;: 0g&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total fat&lt;/strong&gt;: 0g&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturated fat&lt;/strong&gt;: 0g&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cholesterol&lt;/strong&gt;: 0mg&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sodium&lt;/strong&gt;: 0mg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-is-cinnamon-safe-for-everyone"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Is Cinnamon Safe for Everyone? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For most people, cinnamon is generally safe in the small amounts typically used for flavoring food. Studies on potential health benefits have examined doses of about 1 to 6 grams per day—roughly ½ teaspoon to 2 teaspoons of ground cinnamon.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Dietitians say that the type of cinnamon you choose may make a difference. Cassia cinnamon, the variety most often sold in grocery stores, contains higher levels of coumarin, a natural compound that can be harmful to the liver in large amounts.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “Excessive coumarin intake can lead to liver damage, and symptoms like dizziness, diarrhea and vomiting,” says Zenker.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Ceylon cinnamon—sometimes called “true cinnamon”—has very little coumarin and is considered a safer choice if you use cinnamon regularly.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It’s also important to be cautious with supplements or very large amounts. “Large doses of cinnamon, either in the powder or supplement form, may interact with some medications (blood thinners, antibiotic and diabetes or heart medications) or cause mouth irritation or liver toxicity,” says Gaw.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-ways-to-enjoy-cinnamon"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Ways to Enjoy Cinnamon &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Cinnamon is one of the easiest spices to incorporate into your diet. Here are some dietitian-approved ideas:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Stir into oatmeal, yogurt, smoothies or coffee for a delicious addition.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sprinkle on roasted sweet potatoes, squash or carrots.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mix into homemade granola, energy bites or baked goods for a cozy treat.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Add a dash to chili, curries or stews for extra depth.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pair with fruit like apples, pears, peaches or bananas for a natural flavor boost.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Cinnamon is a staple in the spice rack with several potential health benefits. Its antioxidants and anti-inflammatory compounds could support blood sugar control, heart health and even help ease the effects of chronic inflammation. Still, experts emphasize that cinnamon works best as part of an overall balanced diet—it’s not a substitute for medical care or other healthy lifestyle habits.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you consume it frequently, keep portions moderate and be aware of potential medication interactions. Ask a health care provider if you’re unsure. Otherwise, sprinkling cinnamon into your meals is an easy, flavorful way to add a bit of extra wellness to your routine.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-faq mntl-sc-block-universal-faq"&gt;&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-faqs-f9b3acdd-1028-41d8-8ff7-69cd97d48802"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__title"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content mntl-accordion js-accordion"&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="1"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_1-0-section-0"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;What are the main health benefits of cinnamon?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cinnamon may help lower inflammation, support blood sugar control and improve heart health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="2"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_2-0-section-1"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;How much cinnamon should I eat daily?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_2-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Studies suggest ½ teaspoon to 2 teaspoons a day may be enough to see potential benefits. Be sure to talk to a health care professional or registered dietitian for individualized advice before adding cinnamon into your daily routine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="3"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_3-0-section-2"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Can cinnamon interact with medications?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_3-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, large doses may affect blood thinners, antibiotics and diabetes or heart medicines. Always talk to a health care provider for specific information on how foods (including cinnamon) may impact any medications you’re taking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZ0FVX3lxTE85RDZHRllRT0FqbmhlMEZwTm9YWEhfMHlFRnRnZkxCOWplS1RKNnV5OFRrc3NhWEtKT0FpdEo2QVh2OW9vNmFrM25LRkN6Q3JUT0FmNVM1RnN5c2VhdHl4MTJwY1dYaVE</guid></item><item><title>顶级整形外科医生透露，美元杂货店是逆转衰老的主食-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15146217/dollar-grocery-store-staples-reverse-aging-revealed-plastic-surgeon.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;We are what we eat, as the saying goes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And acclaimed plastic surgeon Dr Amir Karam said this is especially true when it comes to our skin and appearance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The San Diego-based aesthetician has revealed his inexpensive go-to ingredients available at the grocery store for keeping skin youthful and radiant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;On Dr Karam's list are foods that boost collagen and promote hydration, which improve skin elasticity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He has also recommended foods with prebiotics and probiotics as they help smooth skin texture and prevent breakouts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He explained in a &lt;a target="_self" href="/sciencetech/youtube/index.html" id="mol-3091cea0-9e11-11f0-a9b9-b94c99276d56" class=""&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt; video: 'So many of us invest so much time and money in procedures, skin care products, and treatments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'And those things are important, but we often overlook probably the most important strategy in creating that youthful, beautiful skin, which ultimately comes by addressing the changes at the cellular level. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'And that can be addressed by the foods that we eat.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;We are what we eat, as the saying goes. And acclaimed facial plastic surgeon Dr Amir Karam says this is especially true when it comes to our skin and appearance (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;First, Dr Karam highlighted the importance of collagen-boosting foods that can help to improve skin elasticity, resilience and hydration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He recommended stocking up on organic chicken breasts as they are an excellent source of protein, providing all nine essential amino acids, including lysine, which is vital for collagen production. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another food on his shopping list to aid collagen production is bone broth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Karam explained: 'Consuming it gives your body exactly what it needs to create and build collagen, as well as hydrate the skin and just give areas outside of the skin, joints, everything else, all those important things that it needs to function better.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With the skin constantly bombarded by pollutants and toxins in a modern environment, Dr Karam stressed the importance of foods rich in antioxidants, substances that protect cells from toxins, and vitamin C to help create a protective barrier. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Vitamin C packs a double punch, the surgeon said and is also essential for boosting collagen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One of the 'easiest and most delicious and ways' to get both vitamin C and antioxidants, Dr Karam said, is through berries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;His go-tos are blueberries and strawberries, but other foods he recommended include bell peppers and grapefruit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He suggested infusing water with berries and grapefruit as a refreshing, sugar-free way to stay hydrated while getting the nutrients back into your body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Karam also said leafy green vegetables are important sources of vitamin C and antioxidants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He said broccoli sprouts are exceptionally high in sulforaphane, a powerful compound that helps protect the skin against UV-induced damage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sprouts can contain 10 to 100 times more sulforaphane than mature broccoli.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Organic chicken breasts are an excellent source of protein, providing all nine essential amino acids, including lysine, which is vital for collagen production&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Avocados are deemed the best food for supple, moisturized skin as they are rich in healthy fats&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A balanced gut is key to achieving clear, radiant skin, Dr Karam revealed, through a complex network called the gut-skin axis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A healthy gut promotes a strong immune system, reduces inflammation, and aids in the absorption of vital nutrients for skin regeneration and protection, leading to a glowing complexion. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He told viewers: 'So having probiotics and prebiotics in your diet helps with the inflammation that helps calm and prevent acne, redness, and skin sensitivity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'So absolutely important to have that really strong gut skin connection.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He explained that probiotics are the healthy gut bacteria, while prebiotics are the fuel that helps them do their job effectively. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some of Dr Karam's 'gut healthy heroes' include sauerkraut and probiotic yogurt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Meanwhile, his prebiotic recommendations are chia seeds, green leafy vegetables and avocados.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Avocados are also deemed the best food for supple, moisturized skin as they are rich in healthy fats. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The healthy monounsaturated and polyunsaturated fats found in avocados, including oleic acid, help strengthen the skin's moisture barrier. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This reduces water loss from the skin, helping to keep it hydrated, soft, and supple. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Other sources of healthy fats, Dr Karam said, come from nuts and seeds as well as extra virgin olive oil. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dr Karam highlights the importance of collagen-boosting foods which can help to improve skin elasticity, resilience and hydration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lastly, the surgeon suggested gravitating toward foods rich in omega-3s to combat inflammation because these fatty acids are powerful anti-inflammatory agents that reduce inflammation, which is linked to aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Omega-3s, such as EPA and DHA (found in eggs and fatty fish such as salmon and sardines) and plant-based ALA (found in flaxseed and chia seeds) help regulate the body's inflammatory processes, thereby supporting overall health and potentially slowing the aging process by helping to prevent wrinkles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Karam eats salmon several times a week with his family. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Along with food, the Californian said that seasonings and spices can play a role in skin health, as well. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He revealed certain spices like turmeric and ginger contain powerful antioxidants and anti-inflammatory compounds that can combat oxidative stress and cellular damage not only on skin level but in the body too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The doctor concluded: '&lt;span&gt;So, that's an incredible comprehensive list of foods that are great for our bodies that taste wonderful and make a huge impact in our skin health moving forward.'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Along with a nutrient-rich diet, Dr Karam said other products that can help prevent premature aging includes sun protection and a daily skincare routine that 'complements everything else that you're doing.'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox health" data-version="2" id="mol-bce99ec0-9e1e-11f0-a9b9-b94c99276d56" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15146217/dollar-grocery-store-staples-reverse-aging-revealed-plastic-surgeon.html"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;Dr Amir Karam's top grocery store items for youthful skin &lt;/h3&gt; &lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt; &lt;ol class="mol-bullets-with-font"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bone broth&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chicken breasts &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Berries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Grapefruit&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bell peppers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;Leafy green vegetables &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;Sauerkraut &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;Probiotic yogurt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;Avocados &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;Chia seeds &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;Nuts &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;Extra virgin olive oil &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;Salmon &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;Eggs &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;Sardines &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;Ginger&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;Tumeric &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:45:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPME9lclRhQ3NnYzBKVmJIYlV0b01hYmtjODUxd3RNZU82RFpZSUpPZDZfVnNzNE9kYXc5Z2tSSlFhMnQxTFNmejJhbmlSRk5nQVpqUUZUQUxDZDZETXdCd0EwNlRGQjBXaVhUSmN0UDVMQ050MTh3eExoNWs5MjBlZWN1SG8xd2szYktDdklqMmtadGpYZHI1bVdXUjZZbDE0UkhfWk52UjAwelVyUnRqN09pNGJQU0hPTnFITXFaNWwxQdIBxwFBVV95cUxNaFdDNm5IbW5ZaGd1UDIzeHZycFh6WG1LSWFoTU5NcmFVRm5hVVNjRVBJSjRQZnp1N0ozOEgzRnBZRVJSZUdpQTByZjJTZTBzc004YlNqQ1B2cXpDTkNkR0k2UlZrZ2JjRS12VlFEaHpOcVVsdzlwbXZPdTVPUkhvMjBQeUQ5YlRZWDl4T0pZUWxvbFlERjZXYm1zRXVXNllVUzEtY2ludy1Yckt5N3p1ejhteGxXM3hnN0xINmpCcDQwcVRMdktz</guid></item><item><title>维生素D错误削弱您的免疫力- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/10/251004092911.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Taking vitamin D2 might lower the body's levels of the more efficient form of vitamin D, vitamin D3, according to new research from the University of Surrey, John Innes Centre and Quadram Institute Bioscience. Many people take vitamin D supplements to support their bone and immune health and meet the UK government recommendation of 10 micrograms (µg) each day, especially during the winter months.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are two forms of vitamin D supplements available: vitamin D2 and vitamin D3. Researchers have found that taking vitamin D2 supplements can lead to a drop in the body's concentration of vitamin D3, which is the form our bodies naturally produce from sunlight and use most effectively to raise overall vitamin D levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study, published in &lt;em&gt;Nutrition Reviews&lt;/em&gt;, analysed data from randomised controlled trials and found that vitamin D2 supplementation resulted in a reduction in vitamin D3 levels compared to those not taking a vitamin D2 supplement. In many of the studies, the vitamin D3 levels went lower than in the control group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emily Brown, PhD Research Fellow and Lead Researcher of the study from the University of Surrey's Nutrition, Exercise, Chronobiology &amp;amp; Sleep Discipline, said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Vitamin D supplements are important, especially between October and March, when our bodies cannot make vitamin D from sunlight in the UK. However, we discovered that vitamin D2 supplements can actually decrease levels of vitamin D3 in the body, which is a previously unknown effect of taking these supplements. This study suggests that subject to personal considerations, vitamin D3 supplements may be more beneficial for most individuals over vitamin D2."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professor Cathie Martin, Group Leader at the John Innes Centre, said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This meta-analysis highlights the importance of ensuring plant-based vitamin D3 is accessible in the UK."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This research supports a previous study published in &lt;em&gt;Frontiers in Immunology&lt;/em&gt;, led by Professor Colin Smith from the University of Surrey, which suggests that vitamin D2 and D3 do not have identical roles in supporting immune function. Vitamin D3 has a modifying effect on the immune system that could fortify the body against viral and bacterial diseases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professor Colin Smith said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We have shown that vitamin D3, but not vitamin D2, appears to stimulate the type I interferon signalling system in the body -- a key part of the immune system that provides a first line of defence against bacteria and viruses. Thus, a healthy vitamin D3 status may help prevent viruses and bacteria from gaining a foothold in the body."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further research into the different functionalities of vitamin D2 and D3 should be a priority in deciding whether vitamin D3 should be the first-line choice of vitamin D supplement, subject to individual requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professor Martin Warren, Chief Scientific Officer at the Quadram Institute, said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Vitamin D deficiency represents a significant public health concern, especially during the winter months with significant deficiency across the UK population. This collaborative research effort aligns well with the Quadram Institute's mission to deliver healthier lives through food innovation to enhance the nutrient density of the food we eat. Tackling this with the most effective form of vitamin D supplementation or fortification is of the utmost importance to the health of the nation."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:35:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFB2NWpUZ3p4c3hVOVpTSXRDWC1Wb25YVmZKT2EzZnE0MVFwZHN5alY0UXd3RE9GOVN6ejhDUG1MQVZNam00bHJwczMyNU5DZndBVkJVSTB1QlZwMElLYi1SdWRkRzFsNk0tZ3NkNGRDOA</guid></item><item><title>癌症警报：口腔微生物被确定为胰腺癌的新风险因素（早期体征，其他风险-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/cancer-alert-oral-microbes-identified-as-new-risk-factor-for-pancreatic-cancer-early-signs-other-risk-factors-and-prevention-tips/articleshow/124304435.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Known as a “silent killer,” pancreatic cancer mostly creeps in quietly with almost undetectable symptoms, and yet remains a significant health challenge across the globe. With over half a million new cases and an almost equal number of deaths worldwide in 2021, this disease is a concern with increasing incidence and mortality rates worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pancreatic cancer is often considered deadly due to its tendency to be diagnosed at a late stage, its aggressive nature, and the lack of effective treatments for advanced cases. Now, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaoncology/article-abstract/2839132" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;a groundbreaking new study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; has uncovered a surprising connection: microbes in your mouth – certain bacteria and fungi – may significantly raise the risk of developing pancreatic cancer. This discovery opens up a fresh way of thinking about prevention, diagnosis, and oral care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Cancer is curable if detected early: Signs to pay attention to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What did the study find&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers from &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/news/oral-microbes-linked-increased-risk-pancreatic-cancer" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;NYU Langone Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and the Perlmutter Cancer Center analyzed saliva samples from a massive cohort of over 122,000 people, tracking them over nearly nine years. In that time, 445 participants developed pancreatic cancer. The scientists compared those individuals’ oral bacterial and fungal profiles with a matched control group to see which microbes were more common in the “cancer group.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="u" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What are the key findings?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers identified 24-27 species of oral bacteria and fungi that were individually associated with increased, or in some cases decreased, risk of pancreatic cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among the standout 3 bacteria were Porphyromonas gingivalis, Eubacterium nodatum, and Parvimonas micra – species already linked to gum disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In terms of fungi, species of the Candida genus showed an association with higher pancreatic cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When these risk microbes were combined into a microbial risk score (MRS), people with higher scores had about a 3.4 to 3.5-fold greater risk of pancreatic cancer compared to those with lower scores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because pancreatic cancer is often diagnosed late, the authors propose that profiling the mouth’s microbiome might one day serve as a noninvasive biomarker to flag high-risk individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, the researchers emphasize that the study finds correlation, not clear causation. More research is needed to confirm how, and if, these microbes directly contribute to cancer formation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Pancreatic cancer: What it is and the early signs to watch for&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pancreatic cancer is a disease in which malignant (cancerous) cells form in the tissues of the pancreas. The pancreas is a gland located behind the stomach that plays a crucial role in digestion and blood sugar regulation by producing enzymes and hormones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the exact causes are not always clear, risk factors include smoking, family history of pancreatic cancer, long-standing type 2 diabetes, and chronic pancreatitis. Pancreatic cancer is often difficult to diagnose early because symptoms may be subtle or absent in the early stages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;As pancreatic cancer is notoriously stealthy in its early stages and many cases are found late, knowing possible early signs and symptoms can help with earlier detection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are some red flags to watch out for:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Abdominal pain that radiates toward the back&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Unexplained weight loss&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Loss of appetite or feeling full quickly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Jaundice (yellowing of skin or eyes), especially if accompanied by dark urine or pale stools&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;New-onset diabetes or worsening control in someone who already has diabetes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Digestive issues like nausea or indigestion, sometimes after meals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because these symptoms are common to many other conditions, they are often overlooked until the disease progresses. When pancreatic cancer is detected early, outcomes are better, but that remains a significant challenge in current medical practice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Risk factors&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While oral health is an emerging risk factor, several other factors contribute to pancreatic cancer risk:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="72"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Age:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The risk increases with age, particularly after 60.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Smoking:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Cigarette smoking is a major risk factor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="78"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Family history:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; A family history of pancreatic cancer can elevate risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="81"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Chronic pancreatitis:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Long-term inflammation of the pancreas is linked to increased risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="84"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Diabetes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Having diabetes, especially type 2, may raise the risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="88"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Obesity:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Being overweight or obese increases the likelihood of developing the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="91"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="93"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="94"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Prevention tips&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="95"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While not all risk factors are controllable, several lifestyle changes can help reduce the risk of pancreatic cancer:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="97"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Maintain good oral hygiene:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Regular brushing and flossing can help prevent gum disease and reduce the presence of harmful oral microbes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="100"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Healthy diet:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Consume a balanced diet rich in fruits, vegetables, and whole grains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="104"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Regular exercise:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Engage in physical activity to maintain a healthy weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="107"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Quit smoking:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Eliminating tobacco use significantly lowers cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="110"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Limit alcohol consumption:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Excessive drinking can increase risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="113"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Regular medical check-ups:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Routine screenings can help detect potential issues early.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="116"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="117"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizgJBVV95cUxPZ0Q0cmo0RzVqV0dnMG9lVWlZNkZKdzJsMnZ3VUZoYjNTMXBiVjRNTWtaVG11MFFPa1hPRkxCYk5KN0xseTkwTFJmZFo1ZmxmUEpJbExoY1RxWVlXNmM5cWVaWXpCVEZzNnFRUGJjRHNrLUNMSER3TUdkV3pVb1EyazN2Z3hGeG44QTNheTREQnp0RFNqNTJzUUdhZ21FYmdpcG5weUpHb3E2U0dRNzJFYzFRV29QYmliLXFZYTFUQUE0UWdkbHVNZ21Ed3RBZjEtamExRC1hLVBOUkhUSjk2RmNKeGFmRHo0RUZlZlczMTVFNVpJX2ZrWkpmcjR5VWNybkdZRUVRN1pyRmZWSmRoUW00eVZ0U1JqXzk2WGdtcVdhTURIbHF2aTZZeWZDdzFEbEphd2JhWnpFRTJxVGJuM29pbXhhb1hjSFhhRDZB0gHTAkFVX3lxTFBpYzk4TTFJTnk0Q1FUTGRYLU9RVFJmWEVRNldkQkJVUHFDTG91bnd2MG8yV1RRNGJta3B4NDFoRlRheDM1VUdla3BFc3VVMmFkTHlTMmJVNnhPZEZBOG5KdExDcy0zN1hPY1hTX3VsLVRSYUZEekRGYUpfYzR2MEhzTlhiVzRlRTd0RXV6aVdCc2w2bWxfRlVZNmVJcnd5MkdOb1ljTzQ2WXEyLXdzaEVUT0ROSDh4eDRDbTVMcGJ0S3NKVm1zSVFPajQtV1lVTVA4X2MxZ2lKZWl0RktLRzR3TXRndmlOSGZ1QW80YjRIbGVielBhczFBMEVVczFaVm1UR1lXeUhxRTZBQ29EeEgtb1dESlp1VW5OR1VYWFY4LTlqQUd5ZHVlWFRSSlkzanlnTEZYTmc2cEs2VGNxN2Z0ZDl0Q25JZU5oU2o2SjlLOHF3aw</guid></item><item><title>根据专家的说法， 5种有助于降低55岁后认知能力下降风险的食物- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-reduce-risk-cognitive-decline-after-55-11822443</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Diet is a powerful tool in helping to reduce the risk of cognitive decline as we age.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Foods like fatty fish, blueberries, eggs, walnuts and leafy green veggies top the list.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Other lifestyle factors like staying connected to others and regular exercise can also help.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; What if choosing your next snack or dinner dish could help keep your mind sharp and vibrant for years to come? After age 55, it’s not just our joints that creak; our brains crave some extra TLC, too. The good news? Delicious food is on your side. Science highlights certain foods that deliver &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/antioxidants-cognitive-impairment-study-11762761" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;key nutrients that may help protect against cognitive decline&lt;/a&gt; and maintain strong memory and focus.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Making simple, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/290550/10-everyday-superfoods/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nourishing choices every day&lt;/a&gt; can have a big impact on how our brains age,” says &lt;a href="https://datatodiet.com" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;Johannah Katz, M.A., RD&lt;/a&gt;. In other words, a few simple tweaks to your weekly menu can turn mealtime into brain-supporting time. If you’re looking to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7915302/habits-to-add-to-your-day-to-prevent-cognitive-decline/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;support a healthy mind as you age&lt;/a&gt;, here are five notable foods backed by science that can help protect your cognitive function.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-fatty-fish"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 1. Fatty Fish &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fatty fish like salmon, mackerel and sardines are often hailed as brain food, and for good reason. Packed with omega-3 fatty acids, especially docosahexaenoic acid (DHA), these fish provide essential nutrients that play a key role in brain health.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “DHA is a powerhouse for the brain,” says &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jillkoegel" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Jill Koegel, RD, CDCES&lt;/a&gt;. “It helps maintain brain cell membranes, reduces inflammation linked to cognitive decline, and boosts blood flow—key for memory and learning.” To better understand how omega-3s affect the brain, researchers reviewed studies spanning more than 12 years and found that these fats are linked to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7897905/this-healthy-habit-can-help-boost-brain-health-later-in-life/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;improved learning, memory and overall brain health&lt;/a&gt;. They also supported blood flow to the brain.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Adding just one or two servings of fatty fish to your weekly meals is an easy, delicious way to nourish your brain and keep it sharp.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-blueberries"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 2. Blueberries &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These small berries pack a big punch when it comes to brain health. They are loaded with powerful plant compounds called flavonoids, specifically anthocyanins, which give them their deep blue color. But the anthocyanins do more than make these berries colorful.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Blueberries are one of the most studied foods for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/top-mistakes-to-avoid-for-cognitive-health-11779797" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;protecting brain health in older adults&lt;/a&gt;,” shares Katz. “They’re &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai pseudoStyle" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-rich-in-anthocyanins-11727484" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;rich in anthocyanins&lt;/a&gt;, which are antioxidants that cross the blood–brain barrier, reduce inflammation and improve brain-derived neurotrophic factor (BDNF), which supports memory and learning.”&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For an extra boost, consider wild blueberries. “Compared to regular blueberries, wild blueberries have 33% more anthocyanins, two times the antioxidants and a more intense blueberry taste,” notes &lt;a href="https://www.nutricomm.com/about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Kitty Broihier, M.S., RD, LD&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Some data suggest that regularly eating wild blueberries may be linked to improved brain function in older adults, particularly in processing information faster. While this study specifically used blueberry powder, it remains relevant because the powder contains the same beneficial compounds, like antioxidants and flavonoids, found in whole wild blueberries.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3-eggs"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 3. Eggs &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Eggs are often called a “nutritional powerhouse” for brain health, offering an accessible and versatile way to support cognitive function. “Eggs are rich in &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/choline-dementia-study-8779484" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;choline, a nutrient that supports mood and memory&lt;/a&gt;,” explains &lt;a href="https://drewramseymd.com" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Drew Ramsey, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “Though choline is crucial for brain health, 90% of Americans don’t get enough of this nutrient.”&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Eating two eggs at breakfast provides a strong start to your day with 12 grams of high-quality protein and 60% to 80% of your daily choline requirement.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Recent research further emphasizes the importance of eggs, suggesting an association between eating eggs and a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/alzheimers-risk-mediterranean-diet-study-11812128" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;reduced risk of Alzheimer’s disease&lt;/a&gt; in older adults, shares Ramsey.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “These findings are important as the prevalence of Alzheimer’s dementia—the most common type of dementia—is expected to increase with an aging population,” says Ramsey.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-4-walnuts"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 4. Walnuts &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re looking for a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-snack-for-better-brain-health-8733684" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;brain-healthy snack&lt;/a&gt;, look no further than walnuts. Their unique shape, which resembles a tiny brain, is a fitting hint at their cognitive benefits. Walnuts stand out among nuts due to their concentration of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/291962/8-best-vegan-omega-3-rich-foods/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;alpha-linolenic acid (ALA)&lt;/a&gt;, a plant-based omega-3 fatty acid. In fact, they are the only tree nut that is considered to be an excellent source of ALA omega-3 fatty acids.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; According to &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/megantomlinrd/?hl=en" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Megan Tomlin, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;, “Walnuts are &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-antioxidant-packed-foods-11813913" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;rich in antioxidants, omega-3 fatty acids and fiber&lt;/a&gt;, all of which are crucial for brain health and aging.” The combination of these nutrients helps combat oxidative stress and inflammation, two key contributors to age-related cognitive decline.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Observational research consistently shows that those who eat more walnuts tend to have &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7915302/habits-to-add-to-your-day-to-prevent-cognitive-decline/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;better cognitive outcomes&lt;/a&gt;, including improved memory and thinking skills.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; For example, one study analyzed data from older adults in the U.S. to explore the link between eating walnuts and brain health. People who ate walnuts, even in small amounts, scored higher on cognitive tests at the start of the study compared to those who didn’t eat walnuts. Walnut eaters also tended to have healthier lifestyles and diets rich in brain-boosting nutrients, which may have contributed to their higher cognitive scores.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Yet, because many studies focusing on walnut intake and outcomes used inconsistent methods to measure brain health, experts suggest that more reliable research is needed before a definitive link can be established between walnut consumption and cognitive health outcomes.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-5-leafy-green-vegetables"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 5. Leafy Green Vegetables &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Vegetables like spinach, kale, collard greens and broccoli are &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/7995454/mediterranean-diet-brain-health-dinners/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;fundamental to a brain-healthy diet&lt;/a&gt;. They are packed with nutrients like &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-rich-in-vitamin-k-8635254" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;vitamin K and lutein&lt;/a&gt;, which have been linked to slower cognitive decline.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These nutrients work together to protect the brain. For example, vitamin K is involved in forming sphingolipids, a type of fat densely packed into brain cells. This is a good thing because sphingolipids are essential for maintaining the structure and function of brain cells, which supports overall brain health and cognitive function.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Studies also showed that higher lutein levels are linked to better brain structure and more efficient brain function during cognitive tasks.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One study looked at how eating these vegetables might affect brain health in older adults (aged 60 and up) in the U.S., using data from over 2,300 participants. The results showed that eating more &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8036861/dietitian-product-that-helps-me-save-money-eat-more-greens/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;dark green vegetables&lt;/a&gt; (like spinach) was linked to better overall brain function, particularly in immediate and delayed memory tasks. People who ate the most dark green vegetables performed significantly better on these tests compared to those who didn’t eat any. Interestingly, the study also found that some of the benefits might come from the vegetables’ ability to lower blood neutrophil levels, which are linked to inflammation.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-strategies-to-help-reduce-cognitive-decline"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Other Strategies to Help Reduce Cognitive Decline &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7945038/heart-healthy-lifestyle-could-keep-your-brain-healthier-research/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;healthy diet is a cornerstone of brain health&lt;/a&gt;, it is most effective when combined with healthy lifestyle habits. Here are a few other strategies to help protect your cognitive function:&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stay Physically Active:&lt;/strong&gt; Regular exercise increases blood flow to the brain and can help grow new brain cells. Aim for at least 150 minutes of moderate-intensity activity, like brisk walking or swimming, each week.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Challenge Your Mind:&lt;/strong&gt; Keep your brain engaged by learning new skills, playing strategy games, reading or doing puzzles. Mental stimulation helps build cognitive reserve, making your brain more resilient.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stay Socially Connected:&lt;/strong&gt; Maintaining strong social ties and engaging in meaningful conversations can help preserve cognitive function and reduce the risk of dementia.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manage High Blood Pressure&lt;/strong&gt;: Having high blood pressure in your 40s to early 60s can increase the risk of memory and thinking problems later in life.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Enough Sleep&lt;/strong&gt;: Experts recommend getting seven to nine hours of sleep every night. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Protecting your cognitive health as you age is an achievable goal, and your diet is one of the most powerful tools. Incorporating &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/breakfast-recipes-to-help-support-brain-health-8581993" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;brain-supportive foods&lt;/a&gt; like fatty fish, wild blueberries, eggs, leafy green vegetables and walnuts can provide essential nutrients to help fight inflammation and support brain cell structure as well as memory and learning processes. These foods are not only beneficial for your brain, but they also contribute to your overall well-being.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Remember that diet is just one part of the equation. Combining a brain-healthy eating plan with regular physical activity, mental challenges and strong social connections creates a robust defense against cognitive decline. While there are some factors that may contribute to cognitive decline that are out of our control, like our genetics, by taking these proactive steps, you may help ensure your mind stays sharp and vibrant for many years to come.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxPaDUzUjlLNDdPTWI5Qk13cTJsb3VwUldiWU93YzZuNmZGeDc2MG5yUzUyVzI0TTMtMXZMYXZjTE90enppVEJTYjFHYmVNR2loalFFcWNPYVYxdnJXR2R5Tmg2Z084SXExV21aNjViajFmamROdHV6TGtTVWNBYTYyZUpaZGRZaHM</guid></item><item><title>科学家加速醋杀死致命的超级细菌- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/scientists-supercharge-vinegar-to-kill-deadly-superbugs/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 12:25:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOVVp6ZkJfckxCYTVmWW15djJmOWlZcmRuSGZzeHJMWS1HUEVETXJmVm45cjAzX1Z6aWZ5ZFFjNktTTGVOa0djWnh5Z1Q2dVVNREJ2LUU4d1VOWmhmYkVvR1BDcE5yM3duVjFuQUk4dXRnM0VtanlRZWpiLVJPMTA2cXc4Qjgwa2Jm</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现令人惊讶的过敏修复：紫外线- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-discover-surprising-allergy-fix-uv-light-2000665955</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl "&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;People with allergies can suffer long after the offending organism has been removed. Researchers, however, are now envisioning a future with portable devices that can clear a room of airborne allergens using ultraviolet (UV) light.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In new research published in the journal &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acsestair.5c00080"&gt;ACS ES&amp;amp;T Air&lt;/a&gt;, researchers have found a way to change the structure of allergy-causing airborne proteins with UV light. This approach reveals a better alternative to months of cleaning carpets and cats, and in extreme cases, it could even save lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“We have found that we can use a passive, generally safe ultraviolet light treatment to quickly inactivate airborne allergens,” Tess Eidem, a microbiologist at the University of Colorado Boulder and a co-author of the study, said in a university &lt;a href="https://www.colorado.edu/today/2025/09/15/new-way-fight-allergies-switch-light"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt;. “We believe this could be another tool for helping people fight allergens in their home, schools or other places where allergens accumulate indoors.”&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;You’re not allergic to cats&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you’re allergic to things like cats, dogs, mold, or plants, you’re probably not allergic to those organisms per se, but to a protein they emit. Cats, for example, emit a protein in their saliva called Fel d1 that, when they lick themselves, becomes airborne in tiny flakes of dead skin. When we breathe in allergens like these particles, our immune system creates antibodies that lock onto the protein’s special 3D structure, triggering an allergic reaction.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;That’s why you might still sneeze when you shake out a carpet, even though a cat hasn’t walked on it for months. The proteins are still there, and they can’t be killed like microbes because they aren’t alive. Diminishing allergens via typical methods such as using a filter, vacuuming, and washing walls and pets is helpful but difficult to keep up in the long term.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;As such, Eidem and her colleagues investigated an alternative method: instead of trying to get rid of allergy-causing proteins, they changed their structure to make them unfamiliar to the immune system. The team likens it to unfolding an origami animal. “If your immune system is used to a swan and you unfold the protein so it no longer looks like a swan, you won’t mount an allergic response,” Eidem explained.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;Less intense lights&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Cue UV light. Ultraviolet light is already used to eliminate airborne &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/ventilation/germicidal-ultraviolet/index.html"&gt;pathogens&lt;/a&gt; and to disinfect equipment in institutions such as hospitals and airports. But the bandwidth is usually so strong—a 254-nanometer wavelength—that people have to don equipment to protect their eyes and skin to use them.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As such, the team tested the less-intense 222-nanometer-wavelength lights, which are deemed to be safe for populated rooms because they don’t penetrate deep into cells. Eidem, however, admits that there are some risks, such as the production of ozone, which can be &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/indoor-air-quality-iaq/ozone-generators-are-sold-air-cleaners"&gt;harmful&lt;/a&gt; if inhaled. As such, human exposure should still be restricted.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Eidem and her colleagues released tiny allergens from mites, pet dander, mold, and pollen into a chamber and turned on four lunchbox-sized UV222 lamps on the ceiling and floor. They tested the air in 10-minute intervals and found that immunorecognition of treated samples was reduced. In other words, antibodies did not identify many of the proteins and bind to them.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Aeroallergens were quantified using an antibody-based immunoassay, which relies on intact protein conformation for antibody-allergen recognition, binding, and quantification,” the researchers explained in the paper.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;After half an hour, airborne allergen levels saw an average drop of 20 to 25%, depending on the type of allergen, how long the light was on, and what the allergen was floating in, such as dust or droplets. In one situation, 40 minutes of UV light exposure saw Fel d1 diminish by 61% compared to untreated, allergen-filled air.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;“Those are pretty rapid reductions when you compare them to months and months of cleaning, ripping up carpet, and bathing your cat,” said Eidem.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;Personal applications&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;While UV222 lights are already available to consumers, they are mostly for industrial applications, so Eidem hopes to see the day when people could have access to portable UV222 lights to use for more personal activities, such as visiting that one friend with three cats. On a more serious note, UV222 lights might even be lifesaving.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Asthma attacks kill about 10 people every day in the United States, and they are often triggered by airborne allergies,” Eidem concluded. “Trying to develop new ways to prevent that exposure is really important.”&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 12:00:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOZk1CNURTYzFlVEo2cVZIU2liMDAyNHM4V2tmWGc5SHJtVmdVM05OS3RLeS13alcwUmUxVUNiX3k3YnJMc3lxNlNwUGlVRlpoZmkxUk4ycjgtZ0c4clNyY3I2ZUR0NjhBZ1h1cXRJYVlkZGFIVXhxVEFSWWV2UmxOeWI3TXFrY1VTbEE</guid></item><item><title>每个成长中的孩子每天都应该吃的12种食物-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/parenting/moments/12-foods-every-growing-child-should-eat-daily/articleshow/124305981.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Growing children need a balanced and nutrient-rich diet, daily, to support their physical growth, cognitive development, immune function and overall health. Good nutrition in childhood fuels kids' growth, learning and lifelong health. No single “superfood” makes a child smart or healthy overnight but what matters is daily patterns of a variety of fruits and vegetables, reliable sources of protein and iron, dairy or calcium for bones, DHA for brain support, whole grains for steady energy and healthy fats to build the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Where risk of deficiency exists, fortified foods or clinical supplementation matter. Small, consistent swaps like fruit instead of sugary snacks or whole grains instead of refined, compound into big benefits for growth, attention and long-term health. Based on extensive nutrition research, here are 12 essential foods every growing child should consume daily -&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;How to make sure your kid is having a heart-healthy meal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Fruits (whole fruits like apples, berries, oranges)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientific evidence has shown the relationship between consumption of fruits and vegetables and their polyphenols with the prevention or treatment of diseases and possible cognitive benefits in young populations. Reviews of observational and experimental studies link higher fruit intake (rich in vitamins, fiber and polyphenols) with better mood and some aspects of cognitive function in children. According to a 2019 study published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Nutrients&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, whole fruits provide micronutrients, fiber and antioxidants that support immunity and brain health and replacing sugary snacks with fruit raises overall diet quality. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Vegetables: Especially leafy greens (spinach, kale)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leafy greens supply folate, iron-helping nutrients, vitamin K, and phytochemicals linked to brain development. Regular vegetable intake supports micronutrient status and is associated with better academic and cognitive scores in observational studies. Polyphenols of fruits and vegetables can exert cognitive benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Whole grains (oats, brown rice, whole-grain bread)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whole grains provide fiber, B vitamins and slow-release carbohydrates that stabilise energy and support gut health that is important for attention, mood and sustained learning in school. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Current US dietary guidance includes recommendations to increase intakes of both dietary fiber and whole grain. Public-health data emphasise increasing whole-grain intake in kids because average fiber intake is low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Dairy (milk, yogurt, cheese): For calcium, protein and vitamin D (when fortified)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dairy supplies calcium, protein and often vitamin D (if fortified) are nutrients that are essential for building bone mass during childhood and adolescence. A 2023 study, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;The Effects of Dairy Product Supplementation on Bone&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, found that consuming dairy products during growth may favourably affect bone mineral mass parameters. Meta-analyses of RCTs and cohort studies show dairy intake improves bone mineral measures, a key outcome for long-term skeletal health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Eggs: Nutrient-dense brain &lt;keyword id="6181" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="food" source="Orion"&gt;food&lt;/keyword&gt; (choline, protein, B-vitamins)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eggs are a rich source of nutrients important for brain development, including choline (critical for brain development), high-quality protein and micronutrients. Randomised or quasi-experimental egg-feeding trials in low-resource settings have shown benefits for growth and some cognitive outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Fatty fish (or other DHA sources): Salmon, sardines, mackerel (omega-3 DHA/EPA)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Omega-3 supplementation shows short-term positive impacts on visual attention, working memory and executive function in some trials. As per a 2021 review in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Nutrients,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Docosahexaenoic acid (DHA) is an omega-3 fatty acid concentrated in the brain. Systematic reviews of supplementation trials indicate modest, domain-specific benefits for attention, working memory and early neurodevelopment (especially when dietary DHA is low). Fatty fish twice weekly or DHA-fortified foods help provide this nutrient. Evidence strength: moderate (best when baseline intake is low).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Legumes and beans (lentils, chickpeas, kidney beans): Plant protein, iron, fiber&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bean consumption during childhood is associated with improved nutritional outcomes in the first two years of life. Legumes are protein-rich, provide iron and folate and raise fiber intake that supports steady energy, gut health and micronutrient sufficiency. A 2024 study in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Public Health Nutrition,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; found that in many settings beans are linked to better growth and nutrient status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;8. Nuts and seeds (walnuts, almonds, flaxseed): Healthy fats, vitamin E, plant-based omega-3s&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nuts deliver unsaturated fats, vitamin E and micronutrients that support neuronal health. Available evidence suggests a possible role for nuts in the maintenance of cognitive health across the lifespan. While most high-quality trials focus on adults, growing evidence from observational and early-stage trials suggests nuts improve markers of cognition and they are a concentrated, healthy snack for children (age-appropriate portions, mindful of choking risk). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Iron-rich foods (lean red meat, fortified cereals, spinach): Prevent iron deficiency anaemia&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iron is essential for neurotransmitter function and myelination. Longitudinal and intervention studies show iron deficiency (especially in infancy/toddler years) associates with lasting deficits in cognition and behaviour. A 2007 review of studies on the effect of iron deficiency on cognitive development, published in the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Journal of Nutrition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, revealed that infants with iron-deficiency anaemia are at a risk for poorer cognitive, motor, social–emotional and neurophysiologic development. Including iron sources (heme iron from lean red meat or iron-fortified cereals, plus vitamin C to enhance absorption) helps prevent deficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Iron-fortified breakfast cereals or other fortified staples (for at-risk populations)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Where diets lack heme-iron foods, fortified cereals and staples are an effective, scalable way to deliver iron (and folic acid/B12) to children and many RCTs show cognitive gains when iron deficiency is corrected early. Reviews of iron deficiency and intervention trials 2001–2007 indicate that treating iron deficiency can improve developmental outcomes if done early.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Healthy monounsaturated fats (avocado, extra-virgin olive oil): Part of a Mediterranean-style pattern&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diet patterns rich in olive oil and avocados (monounsaturated fats), vegetables, whole grains and fish i.e., Mediterranean-style diets are associated with better cardiometabolic profiles and, in recent trials, small cognitive advantages in children. Including healthy oils supports brain health and replaces saturated fats and ultra-processed foods. Evidence strength: growing and increasingly robust. A 2023 study in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;JAMA Network Open&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, established that compared with usual care, children in the Mediterranean diet group had higher scores in the cognitive domain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;12. Plain water (adequate hydration): Essential for attention and physical performance&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While not a “food”, daily plain water is essential. Even mild dehydration impairs attention and working memory in children while regular water intake (and replacing sugary drinks with water) supports learning and reduces excess calories. Various school-based trials and reviews show that hydration affects cognition and mood in children. Hydration supports physical performance, attention and mood in children. Providing plain water during school hours is linked to better concentration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parents should aim to combine these foods across the day rather than forcing all 12 at every meal. However, a few cautions are that whole nuts are a choking hazard for young toddlers so use nut butters or finely ground nuts for under-4s and follow paediatric guidance. Nutrient-dense foods matter most but overall calorie balance and variety are key so avoid added sugars and excess ultra-processed foods. In low-resource settings, eggs, fortified staples and legumes can produce big gains while in wealthier settings, focus on replacing processed snacks with whole foods. When diets lack key nutrients (iron, vitamin D, DHA), targeted supplementation under a clinician’s advice can be useful but food sources are preferable when feasible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="77"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="78"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 11:42:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0gFBVV95cUxNVnlVaFAtWUNlc2pjanBZdGdQUlJnTG1qYW1Qck5kanliaHF3ejY2M0pWTldnQ1lYOUhRdmthOGlnQk9hRmFPRlJHX1g3ZDBGNzIwSERaV0NwdVNKZ2FOdVJTT2hEb1VYOTBIUFo5T0ppaGp2emE2SnQtRTJVQjNJaTNkVHdVaTNoWHlIVnBfNGxmVHBSUElRd2cweGxPaWc1LVB1ZXRqcl9xSmRvTWU4d1ZpbXM2M2N2WmJHQVE3LWZtZS1ENUk5OW52ejNtc0wxaWfSAdcBQVVfeXFMUDVrcVBOU01uZkdzZDkxZGJDa19WdVliYmxpZ0RFdlcwalJ3WGE5WFotSVRseW9zVnFnNjNITk1kUktBNWJZOHktdjNuempZNm50MlUwOUIzaTQ1b2ZQbFJPbjhOMlp1aG8tUjhaOFNJTWdiUllJZWwzVjZvc3FlUmxuczVDemg5X1VyaGNDdkhqZ1hwaXQ1T2ZvTmtueEw0MlhKQks1NV9VeThXOE5mXzk2M1RXQ0tldkk1TFg1UGhOcVVoWDBxMGE4MWxSVmctNjBqQ0F2RDQ</guid></item><item><title>不仅仅是抽筋：这就是女性大脑在经期内的变化-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/its-not-just-cramps-this-is-how-a-womans-brain-changes-during-periods/articleshow/124306780.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When people talk about periods, the focus lands on cramps, mood swings, and hormonal chaos. But behind the scenes, something far more fascinating is happening, the brain itself is changing. According to a 2023 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39031470/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;led by neuroscientists from the University of California, Santa Barbara, the menstrual cycle doesn’t just influence the reproductive system, it physically reshapes parts of the brain every month. It’s a reminder that the menstrual cycle is not just a body event; it’s a brain event too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The study that saw the brain in motion&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research, published in the journal Human Brain Mapping, followed 30 women throughout their menstrual cycles. Using advanced MRI scans, scientists observed what happens inside the brain as hormones rise and fall. Instead of looking at mood or behaviour, which is what most studies have done, this one looked at structure: how the brain’s white and gray matter physically change with each phase of the cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Sadhguru on Period Taboos: What Society Got Wrong About Women&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their findings were striking. As hormones like estrogen and progesterone fluctuated, the brain’s white matter (which connects different brain regions) and gray matter (which handles processing and thinking) subtly shifted too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These changes happened not just in hormone-sensitive areas like the hypothalamus, but across the entire brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;When estrogen peaks, the brain sparks&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just before ovulation, estrogen levels soar, and so does brain activity. The researchers found that during this phase, white matter becomes more efficient at sending information, almost like upgrading internet speed. It suggests that estrogen could be fine-tuning communication between different brain regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This might explain why many women report feeling sharper, more creative, or socially confident around mid-cycle. While the study didn’t directly test mental performance, it gives a biological clue: the brain could be running in a more “connected” mode when estrogen is high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Progesterone’s calming construction work&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;After ovulation, progesterone takes the lead, and it seems to give the brain a quiet makeover. During this phase, researchers noticed an increase in brain tissue volume and a slight drop in cerebrospinal fluid. Think of it as the brain’s “rest and rebuild” period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Progesterone is often linked to calmness and introspection. These structural changes may explain why many women feel more reflective or inward-focused in the days after ovulation. It’s not just hormones affecting emotions; the brain is literally reorganising itself to match the body’s rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This discovery highlights something deeply human: the brain isn’t static. It breathes, adapts, and transforms along with the body’s natural cycles. Over a lifetime, a woman may experience around 450 menstrual cycles, which means 450 rounds of brain remodelling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding these shifts isn’t just scientific curiosity. It could help explain why certain neurological or emotional conditions, like migraines, anxiety, or mood changes, fluctuate with the cycle. And it could lead to more personalised treatments that respect the hormonal rhythm instead of fighting it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The missing piece in women’s health research&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, most brain studies focused on men, partly because the female hormonal cycle was seen as a “variable.” But this study turns that idea on its head. Hormonal variation isn’t noise, it’s crucial data. By studying these patterns, scientists are finally beginning to understand how female biology truly works, not just during reproduction, but throughout life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This insight brings empathy into the conversation. The brain is not betraying women during their periods, it’s adapting, recalibrating, and preparing for what comes next. Every cycle is a quiet example of resilience in motion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is based on scientific research published in Human Brain Mapping by neuroscientists Elizabeth Rizor and Viktoriya Babenko from the University of California, Santa Barbara. It is meant for informational purposes only and should not be used as a substitute for professional medical advice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 11:36:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_gFBVV95cUxNYVpWSGdyY0JxQ0I4WjZGRHhGVGJab0s5M3U3UTF5WlZyb3BFUUJISmNQcnRNTGhUNnZuVXJyVThQTGVtTUNDVFdrLU5YYk1Bcnc3SkNfSlV0cUN4U0tlX0FVd1l4bVdnbVNyeDNRZzdOTnlUd29MVmNqRURRNEJPVHB4bGxWSGk1S2txM2haVnNSSWlhWTd0OFFlendwcmxMQTdyejgzTmFkSTM5ZmdSQWtnZmVsSVowTXVlV2gxUW8wSUtDLXZXa1BJd08ybmQ2ZFRMTi02YXFVcV9PTk5tQW5VT1BOVkppZEtLZTUxcHNacktoWFh2U0oxb2Rhdw</guid></item><item><title>医学之谜：一名患有髋关节疼痛的高中生，然后被诊断为危及生命-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/10/04/rare-medical-condition-spinal-cord/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="7WS7EBIUYVAH7NHYACCJDU2FXM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Lauren Casey was 15 and a tenor sax player in her Minnesota high school marching band when the pain in her hip and lower back became severe. It hurt when she walked and when she stood for hours at her fast-food job. Soon, she began feeling like her ribs were popping out of place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 11:32:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxOaVF1U1RsbGlDWF9fNDR2YVdxNzZvSzJ5UG9HdXFTejhKZnJpaFRIOFI0T0t5ajRtR1BQNF9mUFp2WVhXRW1fNDlsR3FfdmdySVpIMFo1M2FZamVHRUI1RWxzSU5fMnZUSVVyUjZTRS1EanpYS0pJOEszV285UHhYUXhoOTF6WWhKQkt6bA</guid></item><item><title>不同的蘑菇如何学会相同的迷幻技巧- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/science/2025/10/how-different-mushrooms-learned-the-same-psychedelic-trick/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
                      
                      
          &lt;p&gt;Magic mushrooms have been used in traditional ceremonies and for recreational purposes for thousands of years. However, a new study has found that mushrooms evolved the ability to make the same psychoactive substance twice. The discovery has important implications for both our understanding of these mushrooms’ role in nature and their medical potential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Magic mushrooms produce psilocybin, which your body converts into its active form, psilocin, when you ingest it. Psilocybin &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/pdf/10.1021/acschemneuro.8b00186"&gt;rose in popularity&lt;/a&gt; in the 1960s and was eventually classed as a &lt;a href="https://www.drugs.com/article/csa-schedule-1.html"&gt;Schedule 1 drug&lt;/a&gt; in the US in 1970, and as a &lt;a href="https://www.gov.uk/penalties-drug-possession-dealing"&gt;Class A drug&lt;/a&gt; in 1971 in the UK, the designations given to drugs that have high potential for abuse and no accepted medical use. This put a stop to research on the medical use of psilocybin for decades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But recent clinical trials have shown that psilocybin &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/full/10.1021/acsmedchemlett.3c00390"&gt;can reduce depression&lt;/a&gt; severity, suicidal thoughts, and chronic anxiety. Given &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/brain-altering-fungi-could-lead-the-next-frontier-in-mental-health-care-203371"&gt;its potential&lt;/a&gt; for medical treatments, there is &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/lasting-relief-from-depression-after-magic-mushroom-treatment-new-study-265219"&gt;renewed interest&lt;/a&gt; in understanding how psilocybin is made in nature and how we can produce it sustainably.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/anie.202512017"&gt;The new study&lt;/a&gt;, led by pharmaceutical microbiology researcher Dirk Hoffmeister, from Friedrich Schiller University Jena, &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/anie.202512017"&gt;discovered that&lt;/a&gt; mushrooms can make psilocybin in two different ways, using different types of enzymes. This also helped the researchers discover a new way to make psilocybin in a lab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on the work led by Hoffmeister, enzymes from two types of unrelated mushrooms under study appear to have evolved independently from each other and take different routes to create the exact same compound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a process known as convergent evolution, which means that unrelated living organisms evolve two distinct ways to produce the same trait. One example is that &lt;a href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/full/10.1073/pnas.1602575113"&gt;of caffeine&lt;/a&gt;, where different plants including coffee, tea, cacao, and guaraná have independently evolved the ability to produce the stimulant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the first time that convergent evolution has been observed in two organisms that belong to the fungal kingdom. Interestingly, the two mushrooms in question have very different lifestyles. &lt;em&gt;Inocybe corydalina&lt;/em&gt;, also known as the greenflush fibrecap and the object of Hoffmeister’s study, grows in association with the roots of different kinds of trees. Psilocybe mushrooms, on the other hand, traditionally known as magic mushrooms, live on nutrients that they acquire by decomposing dead organic matter, such as decaying wood, grass, roots, or dung.&lt;/p&gt;

          
                      &lt;p class="ars-interlude-container in-content-interlude mx-auto max-w-xl"&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 11:00:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxQWW0tMWxja1hYajVLTEJzQXZmUnU1eEhtWjJYdm9xWnpVdXVaZjRhTzNCb082bk9xSUFGS3lkSS1aN1BrNEFYRVlxTHhISDlaWHdLQUtZc1JhOVZob015cklnVGhvY1U1NDNQQzl2Si00WXFxbUlpVDZiTG5pY0MtTGUyamhlNTVLNlJJMDBHRHFDZC1QSS1Hb2NBUUFOX2tj</guid></item><item><title>莱姆病：蜱叮咬后“我的独立性完全消失” - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c99glenl34jo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Lyme disease: 'Crying an hour wiped me out for a week'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 kSquvq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/9753/live/6ff136e0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/9753/live/6ff136e0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/9753/live/6ff136e0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/9753/live/6ff136e0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/9753/live/6ff136e0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/9753/live/6ff136e0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/9753/live/6ff136e0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/9753/live/6ff136e0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="PA Media Two pictures side by side of a young woman, with fair skin and dark brown hair. In the photo on the left, she is standing in a hilly area on a footpath, looking at the camera and smiling, while wearing blue jeans, a black top, a green winter hat, and an unzipped bright yellow jacket. In the photo on the right, she is sat on a sofa with pillows behind her, smiling with her eyes closed and holding a plate with food on it. There is a dog next to her on the right." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;PA Media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Maia Pavey says her independence has gone after long Covid reactivated Lyme disease &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A few years ago, Maia Pavey was busy running a photo lab studio in Woolwich. Now she is bedridden, suffering "crushing" fatigue, numbness, limb pain, dizziness and nausea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"My independence is gone completely. Being bedridden and not being able to do anything is incredibly difficult, so I'm quite sad all the time," Maia, 27, said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It's even harder when I can't do anything to cheer myself up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In March 2022 she contracted Covid-19, which rapidly deteriorated her health, leaving her bedbound since August 2023. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Her family spent more than a year not knowing what caused her symptoms, until she was diagnosed with Lyme disease in December 2024. It is thought Covid reactivated the disease which had been dormant for years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d779/live/1c7137d0-9f74-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d779/live/1c7137d0-9f74-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d779/live/1c7137d0-9f74-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d779/live/1c7137d0-9f74-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d779/live/1c7137d0-9f74-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d779/live/1c7137d0-9f74-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d779/live/1c7137d0-9f74-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d779/live/1c7137d0-9f74-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="PA Media A woman with fair skin and brown hair laying asleep on a sofa, with her head buried in a red and white pillow. A fluffy dark grey and white dog is beside her." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;PA Media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Maia remains bedridden, having been diagnosed with long Covid and postural tachycardia syndrome alongside Lyme disease&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Maia, from Erith in south-east London, has also been diagnosed with a long list of complex and overlapping medical conditions, alongside Lyme disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;These include long Covid and postural tachycardia syndrome, which prevents the normal functioning of the nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Her immune system was weakened [by Covid-19], and it opened the door to any prior infections that were lurking," her mother Helene explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It has left her unable to work or care for herself, with Helene becoming her full-time carer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Maia says she was "shocked" and "cried a lot" when she received the diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"At that point, I was struggling to do anything, so crying for an hour wiped me out for over a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Then eventually when I was told about the disease, so much of my life made sense. I realised I've been suffering from this for a long time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/ae97/live/d3be60d0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/ae97/live/d3be60d0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/ae97/live/d3be60d0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/ae97/live/d3be60d0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/ae97/live/d3be60d0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/ae97/live/d3be60d0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/ae97/live/d3be60d0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/ae97/live/d3be60d0-9f73-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="PA Media Two people, a mother and daughter, sat together on a wall next to a river, with a bridge and trees in the background. The daughter has fair skin and brown hair, and is cuddling a white and grey fluffy dog in her arms. Her mother is sat on her right, with fair skin and grey hair. They are both looking at the camera and smiling." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;PA Media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Maia (left) now lives with her parents, and her mother Helene (right) has become her full-time carer&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Her family believe Maia was bitten by a tick during her teenage years when she was involved in the Scouts and spent hours outdoors in woodland and grassy areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;With no obvious illness, she continued with her life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We didn't suspect anything - maybe Maia didn't have symptoms at the time, or maybe she had a slight flu or fever that we didn't connect to anything else," Helene said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Maia encouraged people to "educate yourself about tick-borne illnesses and the ways to avoid them or protect yourself".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"If you know anyone who is suffering but doctors have disregarded their symptoms, consider checking whether it's Lyme disease via a specialist," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"And if you know someone dealing with a chronic illness, reach out to them regularly. They are probably quite lonely."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Although she remains bedridden for now, the delivery of antibiotics via an IV drip has improved Maia's condition, and she hopes to manage her symptoms or even achieve remission in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"There are bad days and there are worse days, and sometimes there are OK days. I cry a lot, but I just have to keep going," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;What is Lyme disease?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7509/live/3a059600-9f75-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7509/live/3a059600-9f75-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7509/live/3a059600-9f75-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7509/live/3a059600-9f75-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7509/live/3a059600-9f75-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7509/live/3a059600-9f75-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7509/live/3a059600-9f75-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7509/live/3a059600-9f75-11f0-9ccd-4dc2d8fa5ad2.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="AFP via Getty Images A zoomed-in picture of a tick on human skin." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;AFP via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Lyme disease is spread to humans by infected ticks&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Lyme disease is a bacterial infection that is spread to humans by infected ticks, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/lyme-disease/" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;according to the NHS&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A circular or oval shape rash around a tick bite may appear up to three months after being bitten by an infected tick. This is not usually hot or itchy, can have a darker or lighter area in the centre, and may look like a bruise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ticks are found all over the UK, but high-risk places include grassy and woodland areas in southern England and the Scottish Highlands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The best way to reduce your risk of Lyme disease is by avoiding tick bites by:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Covering your skin while walking outdoors&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Using insect repellent containing DEET&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Staying on clear paths&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;Wearing light-coloured clothing so ticks are more visible and can be brushed off&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;If you do get bitten, you should remove the tick quickly with tweezers or a tick-removal tool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 07:03:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBlRHQtQk5oZmtxSlIzNXZScmZzenFCY2lUMzE4RmkzNUlVRlliVXRqVHVVVHN4UlJuUDZvQXp1dkRrZHk0eTY5Ymt5Tzd2Sm1STHlpcnR3cHRtd9IBX0FVX3lxTE1RS0xBdzRIRXRjNS1MYlVRS0g1T24xRVhTc2FtM0Npbk5pTDZTZndOX1FhN3F0Qkp4bGJYbjZHdEo5MW1KN0hCYjZNeExkMUo0ajhEYnY3ZkJUNnNuMG1z</guid></item><item><title>心脏病专家分享了他吃的3种食物，以减少隐藏的脂肪并保护他的心脏健康|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-shares-3-foods-he-ate-to-lose-hidden-visceral-fat-and-protect-heart-health-101759213784348.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storyMainDiv" class="fullStory tfStory current videoStory story__detail storyAf101759213784348 " data-vars-storyid="101759213784348" data-story-section="lifestyle" data-story-subsection="health" data-vars-author="Tavishi Dogra" data-premium-story="false" data-performance-type="not-set" data-story-title="Cardiologist shares 3 types of foods he ate to lose hidden fat and protect his heart health"&gt; &lt;p class="htEchoTopPageBanner dHide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="stickyCard"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;h1 class="hdg1"&gt;Cardiologist shares 3 types of foods he ate to lose hidden fat and protect his heart health&lt;/h1&gt;  &lt;div class="actionDiv flexElm topTime"&gt; &lt;p class="dateTime secTime storyPage"&gt;Updated on: Oct 04, 2025 12:09 pm IST &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="googleFollow mHide"&gt; &lt;button class="htEchoShareBarDesk"&gt;&lt;/button&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;h2 class="sortDec"&gt;Cardiologist Dr Sundeep Mishra recommends adding fatty fish, leafy greens, and whole grains to your diet to reduce visceral fat and improve heart health.&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;div class="storyDetails taboola-readmore"&gt; &lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-shares-3-foods-he-ate-to-lose-hidden-visceral-fat-and-protect-heart-health-101759213784348.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;As more people become aware of the dangers of hidden visceral fat, many are working to improve their heart health. To manage this type of fat effectively, it is important to employ effective techniques. Team &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.healthshots.com/" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Health Shots"&gt;Health Shots&lt;/a&gt; spoke with cardiologist Dr Sundeep Mishra, Chairman of Cardiac Sciences at Ujala Cygnus Group of Hospitals, who shared three simple dietary changes he made to reduce hidden fat. These changes can help lower visceral fat and improve heart health, making them important for anyone seeking to enhance their overall well-being.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/09/30/550x309/collage_1759215726710_1759215748559.png" alt="What are three foods cardiologists say to eat?(Adobe Stock)" title="What are three foods cardiologists say to eat?(Adobe Stock)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/09/30/550x309/collage_1759215726710_1759215748559.png" alt="What are three foods cardiologists say to eat?(Adobe Stock)" title="What are three foods cardiologists say to eat?(Adobe Stock)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;What are three foods cardiologists say to eat?(Adobe Stock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr highlighted the dangers of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/india/how-to-watch-out-for-hidden-fat/story-sVR2DgMiqiPfRHuvO1FYCM.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="hidden fat"&gt;hidden fat&lt;/a&gt;, also known as visceral fat, for heart health. “This fat surrounds important organs, including the liver, pancreas, and heart. It can release harmful substances that raise the risk of heart disease, diabetes, and high blood pressure.” There is no miracle food to eliminate visceral fat quickly. Instead, he emphasises a balanced approach that includes a healthy diet, lifestyle changes, and regular exercise to reduce this harmful fat and improve heart health.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;What is visceral fat?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visceral fat is different from subcutaneous fat, which you can feel under the skin. It is active in the body and can be harmful, as it releases substances that cause inflammation and serious health problems. Due to this, Dr Mishra recommends that "patients pay attention to their diet and the choices they make in their daily lives. This can help reduce visceral fat and improve &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/gynaecologist-warns-against-severe-hypertension-in-pregnancy-symptoms-who-is-at-higher-risk-how-to-protect-heart-health-101759210225366.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="heart health"&gt;heart health&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Heart-friendly diet&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This meal plan is designed to improve heart health and reduce the risk of heart disease. It mainly focuses on three food groups:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Fatty fish&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt; Fatty fish like salmon, mackerel, and sardines are rich in omega-3 fatty acids. These healthy fats help reduce inflammation and support heart health. "Incorporating fatty fish into your meals a few times a week to help create a heart-healthy diet", recommends Dr Mishra.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reduction of inflammation: &lt;/strong&gt;Omega-3 fatty acids help reduce systemic inflammation, a critical factor in preventing heart disease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improved cholesterol ratios:&lt;/strong&gt; By improving HDL/LDL ratios, fatty fish can contribute to better heart function.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visceral fat loss:&lt;/strong&gt; Patients who incorporate fatty fish into their diet often experience a reduction in waist circumference of 1–2 cm without needing to reduce their calorie intake significantly.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. Leafy greens&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt; Leafy greens, such as spinach, kale, and broccoli, are rich in nutrients and play a critical role in maintaining heart health. "Incorporating a variety of leafy greens into salads, smoothies, and cooked meals to help reduce fat and improve heart health", recommends Dr Mishra.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Low in calories and high in fibre: &lt;/strong&gt;This combination promotes feelings of fullness while supporting digestive health, making it easier to manage weight.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gut health support: &lt;/strong&gt;The fibre in leafy greens feeds beneficial gut bacteria, which produce short-chain fatty acids with anti-inflammatory properties.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Antioxidant properties: These greens work as antioxidants in the body, promoting vascular health and protecting the heart as fat levels decrease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. Whole grains&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits: &lt;/strong&gt;Whole grains, such as oats, quinoa, and brown rice, are important for a heart-healthy diet, offering numerous benefits. "Patients to replace refined grains with whole grains, as this simple dietary change is directly linked to a reduction in visceral fat", advises Dr Mishra.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High fibre content: &lt;/strong&gt;The fibre in whole grains helps regulate insulin levels and slow digestion, reducing sugar spikes and abdominal fat storage.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improved insulin sensitivity:&lt;/strong&gt; This effective management of insulin can lead to decreased visceral fat over time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reduced risk of heart disease: &lt;/strong&gt;Consuming whole grains instead of refined carbohydrates has been linked to lower visceral fat levels and improved cardiovascular health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is the best way to eliminate visceral fat?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To achieve the best results, these food choices should be part of a balanced lifestyle. Dr Mishra shared some important suggestions:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regular physical activity: &lt;/strong&gt;Engaging in regular exercise helps maintain a healthy weight and burns visceral fat. Even moderate activities, such as walking, can make a significant difference.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quality sleep: &lt;/strong&gt;Ensuring sufficient and restful sleep is important for managing stress and supporting overall metabolic health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimise sugar intake: &lt;/strong&gt;Cutting back on added sugars and ultra-processed foods can further help prevent the accumulation of visceral fat.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;(&lt;strong&gt;Note to readers: &lt;/strong&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always consult your doctor for any questions about a medical condition.)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="recommendedSliderContextual" id="recommendedSliderContextual-101759213784348" data-vars-story_id="101759213784348" data-vars-story_section="lifestyle" data-vars-author="Tavishi Dogra" data-vars-story_headline="Cardiologist shares 3 types of foods he ate to lose hidden fat and protect his heart health"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" class="trendTopsSHow" id="trendTopsSHow-101759213784348"&gt; &lt;div class="trendTops"&gt;  &lt;div class="trendInlineSeo"&gt;&lt;p&gt; Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;label class="moreBtn1" for="trendTopsSHow-101759213784348"&gt;&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="followHT trendSeo__1"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="htEchoEOALite"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="bottomSeoParaEcho1"&gt; &lt;div id="bottomSeoParaEcho"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="mb5 mt5" id="bottomBreadCrumb"&gt; &lt;div class="breadcrumbs"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Home_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/" data-vars-event-cta="News"&gt;News&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Lifestyle_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle" data-vars-event-cta="Lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Health_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle/health" data-vars-event-cta="Health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Cardiologist shares 3 types of foods he ate to lose hidden fat and protect his heart health &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="bottomSeoParaEcho pb0"&gt; &lt;label class="moreBtn" for="trendTopsSHow-101759213784348" id="spanSeeLessEcho"&gt;See Less&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;p class="relatedStoryCricket"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="saranyuPlayer" id="saranyu-player"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="relatedStory2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="us-ad align-center mb10 mt10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="htEchoShortsEntryPoint" data-size="enlarged"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="affiliate-shop-now" id="affiliate-shop-now"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 06:39:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7AFBVV95cUxQWkJPZ1hYT0hPODJ5eUJIZkZLM29KVjJhZ3RFcDExS0EtRXk0WkI0cTNYOGszMVF6eUZlYWlVNVpVS2RDdm1DNEp1Z0x4X1lxeTBTVE5FbHI2VkdEMERYQ0E0OU0xQ0JMRDlWaUlGU0dkS2xYZGVyM3pHbVgzQVJwTU51b2QxeDlMMlNQaXlEMDlJeV9ldVlvNzFNZUMxVHZCTDJjcGlRRkEtdl9sN3dPTWYzaHRXR1hlaWh4ZUY4UV9VSmJGWUNjbVRSenZmQU8wSkZGQldGMTFFbDBsN2lKWVotQmx2MDNnX1VXUtIB8gFBVV95cUxQXzE5ODVSclJJNi1GZERLdWFZRDVRSmZYRzFHV19xZXM5UmZQVmRiczVCdDQ2aXpUamJFR0tCSUpXLUdQdmlOTXdhdmRhWktNWkFuSUM5RmZUaXdWT0tHTHE5allEUGVSMFpqMjdFd25FUlFYU1NiRnJUQ0ZxbFdFNTduTWRxNUJGX2xNd3VlUGJxd1RTamk5NVZDSzdHRlp4Mmh4WnYtX2pETmJCemVqcENZYThTUDBXcU11anlaTmgwdGhNNWhodHYzbndnQWl2NS1teEFTX2F1ckFmeXZGczJmU0pPSXZ0Z3lRYTh2MFNyZw</guid></item><item><title>令人惊讶的研究揭示了真正杀死脂肪肝患者的原因- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/10/251003033924.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;More than a third of the world's population is affected by metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease, or MASLD, the most common chronic liver disease in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MASLD occurs when fat builds up in the liver and is associated with one or more of five conditions: obesity, Type 2 diabetes, high blood pressure, high blood sugar and low HDL cholesterol, known as "good" cholesterol. These conditions are characterized as cardiometabolic risk factors because they affect the heart or metabolism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MASLD can lead to serious illness, such as advanced liver, heart and kidney disease, but little research has been done to examine if certain cardiometabolic risk factors for those with MASLD are more associated with death than others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The deadliest cardiometabolic risk factors &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, a new study from Keck Medicine of USC published in &lt;em&gt;Clinical Gastroenterology and Hepatology&lt;/em&gt; reveals that three of the cardiometabolic risk factors carry the greatest risk of death for those with MASLD: high blood pressure, pre-diabetes or Type 2 diabetes, and low HDL, which raise the risk of death by 40%, 25% and 15%, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These results were independent of how many or which combination of cardiometabolic risk factors patients had, and held steady despite individuals' gender, sex, race or ethnicity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"MASLD is a complicated disease, and this study sheds new light on where doctors may want to focus their efforts when treating patients," said Norah A. Terrault, MD, a hepatologist with Keck Medicine and a senior author of the study. "Knowing which aspects of MASLD might lead to poorer outcomes can help us offer patients the best possible care."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers were especially surprised to discover that high blood pressure was associated with a higher chance of death than diabetes, said Matthew Dukewich, MD, PharmD, MS, a USC transplant hepatology fellow and lead author of the study. "Until now, it was commonly thought that diabetes was the most pressing health problem for MASLD patients, which is a key insight."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study also found that obesity, the most common cardiometabolic risk factor of MASLD, can substantially raise the risk of mortality depending on a patient's body mass index (BMI), which is a formula used to estimate body fat percentage based on an individual's height and weight. The higher a patient's BMI, the higher the association with death.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the research adds to the growing body of research that patients with more cardiometabolic risk factors have poorer outcomes. The study found that the risk of death in MASLD patients increased by 15% for each additional cardiometabolic risk factor present.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How the study was conducted &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers used data from the National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (NHANES), which collected health information about children and adults in the United States from 1988-2018, the most current year for which data was available for their study. Out of 134,515 participants 20 years or older, some 21,000 patients qualified as having MASLD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study authors tracked all-cause mortality rates by individual cardiometabolic risk factors to reach their conclusions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, the study authors hope to conduct further studies examining patients' genetic background, dietary habits and alcohol use in relation to MASLD outcomes to provide more comprehensive risk profiles. "The more we can understand about the drivers of the disease, the more we can identify those most in need of interventions and prioritize our resources for enhanced outcomes," said Terrault.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liyun Yuan, MD, a transplant hepatologist with Keck Medicine, is also a study author.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 05:57:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBKNkt6SFZQUzltMVUtaDR1bDkxWTZrNV81NTJFRWM1ejNvTjNtRWU3MDgxNDNHUHJ2UXdXSGVqMHF5ZFBRRHlCNTkyQkdYWk5zajlDd2hLM1MyRnAxVXdGYjZjcHNyRlRUQXlqNEQyaw</guid></item><item><title>自闭症是人类进化的标志吗？ -今日医学新闻</title><link>https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/autism-human-evolutionary-processes</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-12va8w7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="css-yhe8zq"&gt;&lt;span class="css-rwmw5v"&gt;&lt;span class="css-mjp0j9"&gt;&lt;picture class="css-16pk1is"&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/10/Autism-Human-Intelligence-Child-Play-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 1190px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/10/Autism-Human-Intelligence-Child-Play-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 990px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/10/Autism-Human-Intelligence-Child-Play-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 879w" media="(min-width: 768px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/10/Autism-Human-Intelligence-Child-Play-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg" alt="young child looking through two differently coloured plastic pieces, once red, one green" class="css-1jytyml"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;hl-share-overlay class="css-1mqo1cs"&gt;&lt;a class="icon-hl-pinterest css-11oz8gb" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" data-event="Any Page|Image Pinterest Click|Icon Clicked" data-element-event="OPEN|CONTENTBLOCK|Any Page|Article Body|BUTTON|Image Widget Pinterest Click|" href="https://www.pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicalnewstoday.com%2Farticles%2Fautism-human-evolutionary-processes&amp;amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.post.rvohealth.io%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fsites%2F3%2F2025%2F10%2FAutism-Human-Intelligence-Child-Play-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg&amp;amp;description=Is%20autism%20a%20mark%20of%20human%20evolution%3F" title="Share on Pinterest" data-pin-custom="true" data-share-url="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/10/Autism-Human-Intelligence-Child-Play-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg"&gt;&lt;span class="css-z1zfa"&gt;Share on Pinterest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-share-overlay&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;figcaption class="css-13b3g0x"&gt;Human brain cell evolution may be linked to autism, neurodiversity, according to a new study. Image credit: Lauren Lee/Stocksy&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A new study concludes that the speed at which the human brain evolved may help explain why our species experiences autism.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;According to the authors, certain genes associated with autism are downregulated in humans compared with other species.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They argue that autism in humans may be a byproduct of the rapid evolution of human cognitive traits.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although we humans like to think of ourselves as the pinnacle of evolution, that does the rest of the natural world a serious injustice. Humans cannot spin webs, fly, breathe underwater, produce venom, or swing through the trees. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, we certainly do have a uniquely powerful and intricate brain. Complex language, in-depth forward planning, deep empathy, and vibrant culture are just some of the feats that this powerful organ has enabled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our neurological capabilities undoubtedly imparted evolutionary benefits to our ancient ancestors. They allowed us to spread throughout the world and adapt to all the environments that Earth has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the authors of a new study, however, the dizzyingly complex circuitry of our brains — and the speed at which some of it evolved — may also be the reason why &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/323758" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;autism&lt;/a&gt; is common in our species.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using single-cell RNA-sequencing, scientists have now shown that, in the mouse brain, there are &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4985242/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;at least 49 cell types&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps surprisingly, the human brain has no brain cell types that are specific to only us. We use the same collection of cell types as a rodent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This, as the authors of the new study infer, means that the incredible difference between human and other minds cannot be due to specialized cells. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather, it is due to the ways in which they are connected and the levels of &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10659116/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;gene expression&lt;/a&gt; within each cell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists have long noted that some proteins evolve and change much more quickly than others. Certain proteins in mice, for instance, are almost identical to proteins found in the human body. Others, however, are so different that they barely seem related at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists have conducted studies to understand what factors influence whether a protein is conserved over millennia or quickly altered as species evolve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;These studies suggest that the greatest influence on the rate of change is how prevalent that protein is in the body: If a protein is expressed in large amounts throughout the whole body, it is unlikely to change quickly. This is because any modifications to it are likely to upset a pathway or function somewhere in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, proteins that are relatively rare in the body have a little more freedom: If they change, even if the outcome is negative, they will tend to have less impact on the whole organism. This gives them more room for evolutionary maneuvering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors of the recent study wondered whether this same rule might also be true for cell types. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Could it be that the rarest brain cell types have the most freedom to evolve, and that in our case, this freedom resulted in our outsized cognitive prowess? And could this help explain brain changes related to ASD?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In agreement with the authors’ hypothesis, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11406188/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;previous research&lt;/a&gt; showed that certain genes involved in autism susceptibility are often found in so-called human-accelerated regions (HARs) of the genome. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;HARs are sections of the genome that are well conserved in other mammals but evolved relatively rapidly in humans. This swift evolution implies that they might be involved in some of the traits that make humans different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This might mean that, at some point between now and our last shared ancestor with chimpanzees, we developed some neuronal changes specific to our cognitive ability that also increase the likelihood of autism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists involved in this study theorize that that might be the case. So, they set out to test that hypothesis. As mentioned before, the brain cell types in mice and humans are identical. However, the gene expression within each type of cell differs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, even though a mouse and a human cell might look the same and do a similar job, when you look at how active individual genes are, you can find significant differences. So, this is where they focused their efforts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In agreement with their hunch, the scientists found that the more abundant a cell type was, the more similar its gene expression was across six mammalian species. Conversely, rarer cell types showed large differences in gene expression between the six species.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the authors write that “L2/3 IT neurons evolved unexpectedly quickly in the human lineage compared to other apes.” They also noted a disproportionate down-regulation of genes associated with autism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Medical News Today&lt;/em&gt; reached out to &lt;a href="https://sensiqnootropics.com/about-medical-advisory-board/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Luke Barr&lt;/a&gt;, MD, a board-certified neurologist and Chief Medical Officer at SensIQ, who was not involved in the study. He explained the importance of these particular neurons, saying that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Layer 2/3 intratelencephalic excitatory neurons are critical for higher-order cortical processing. They form long-range connections across different regions of the cortex, essentially integrating information and supporting complex cognition, such as abstract reasoning, social cognition, and language.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research suggests that these communication pathways are particularly important in cognitive skills that are &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9561064/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;specific to humans&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Importantly, Barr also told us that, because of their role in linking distributed brain regions, problems in their development or the way in which they work, “could have significant downstream effects on how the brain coordinates information, which may relate to [autism].”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, the study authors believe that as the human brain rapidly evolved, it caused changes that made autism more likely to occur. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barr commented on these conclusions, noting that “the idea that [autism] may represent an evolutionary trade-off is provocative.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“While speculative, this is consistent with a long-standing hypothesis in neuroscience: That the very features which make human cognition extraordinary — such as enhanced connectivity and cortical expansion — may also introduce vulnerabilities,” he told us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barr was careful to remind us that correlation is not the same as causation, and that “this work remains more theoretical than clinically actionable at this stage.” However, he remained hopeful for the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“By focusing on how these specialized neurons develop, communicate, and adapt in both typical and atypical brains, we may uncover new mechanisms of [autism].”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This could eventually inform targeted interventions,” Barr told &lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt;, “whether pharmacologic or behavioral, that support connectivity and functional integration in the cortex.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overall, this study adds to the growing body of evidence suggesting that, rather than a disorder, autism is a “neurodevelopmental variation that may be linked to the very neural systems that enable uniquely human cognitive abilities,” Barr concluded.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; also spoke with &lt;a href="https://www.faculty.uci.edu/profile/?facultyId=2313" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;John Jay Gargus&lt;/a&gt;, MD, PhD, a professor of medical genetics and genomics, pediatrics, and physiology and biophysics, at the University of California, Irvine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gargus, who was not involved in the study, has conducted research on the role of mitochondria in autism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mitochondria are often referred to as the powerhouses of the cell. Present in nearly all cell types, they produce adenosine triphosphate (ATP), the energy currency of the cell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the recent study, Gargus told &lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; that: “The observations are useful but are simply an elaboration of data already out in a variety of genome-wide association studies (GWAS), and most significantly, they lack an underlying hypothesis of why these evolutionary changes have occurred.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gargus believes that the researchers did not account for the importance of energy production. Our brain makes up &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8364152/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;just 2% of our body weight&lt;/a&gt;, but uses up around 20% of our energy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A rapidly expanding brain during evolution would have caused a huge increase in energy demands, which Gargus believes provides insights into autism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his view, autism “reflects a mismatch between the evolutionary demands of our modern brains and the metabolic systems that support them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than autism being caused by evolution, Gargus believes that because our brains are so energy-hungry, disturbances during childhood — for instance, even minor mitochondrial issues — could “tip the scale toward developmental conditions like [autism].”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is clearly a complex topic, and no doubt researchers will continue to investigate well into the future. Casting a scientific lens far back into our evolutionary history is certainly a challenging endeavour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical News Today</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 05:21:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQOUhsTU9JMEo5STE1bFRjaDNMaEx2UjdzSWpYT0dkdkUwaFMwOElNcDV0cjZNamhvOFRaUzNteEhiQVppNlIyaTh3SllWWkdlTDJJUk1LNUNtZjBzSDZ2ZFQ2Z19fdXA0UFctWmtCX2JTV0ozLXdnQmtzSEVxN0Fmb05yVQ</guid></item><item><title>每日茶或咖啡可以保护您免受头颈癌的侵害：晨茶的惊人好处-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/daily-tea-or-coffee-may-protect-you-against-head-and-neck-cancer-surprising-benefits-of-your-morning-brew/articleshow/124284395.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;For many people, starting the day with a steaming cup of tea or coffee is a comforting ritual. Beyond the energy boost, new research suggests these popular beverages may also play a role in lowering the risk of certain cancers, potentially due to their antioxidant and anti-inflammatory compounds. According to a large-scale analysis, individuals who regularly consume tea or coffee appear to have a slightly reduced risk of developing head and neck cancers, although the relationship is more complex than it first appears and may depend on consumption patterns, type of beverage, genetic predispositions, and broader lifestyle factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Head and neck cancers are among the more common forms of cancer worldwide. In the UK alone, there are around 12,800 new cases each year, leading to more than 4,000 deaths annually, according to Cancer Research UK. Any factor that could help reduce this risk is of considerable public health interest, highlighting the importance of dietary choices, lifestyle considerations, and early preventive strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Side effects of caffeine overdose on overall health&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Tea and coffee consumption linked to &lt;keyword id="20775483" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="head-and-neck-cancer" source="keywords"&gt;head and neck cancer&lt;/keyword&gt; risk in global study&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research, published in the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39711146/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;journal Cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, was carried out by an international team led by Dr. Yuan-Chin Amy Lee from the Huntsman Cancer Institute and the University of Utah School of Medicine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team analysed data collected from 14 studies conducted across Europe, North America, and Latin America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In total, the researchers examined health and lifestyle information from 9,548 individuals diagnosed with head and neck cancers and compared them to 15,783 people without the disease. Participants were asked to provide detailed information about their coffee and tea drinking habits, including whether they drank caffeinated or decaffeinated coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The analysis also took into account other risk factors such as age, gender, smoking, alcohol consumption, and diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Coffee and tea intake effects on head and neck cancer risk&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most striking findings was linked to coffee. Individuals who drank more than four cups of caffeinated coffee daily were found to have a 17% lower chance of developing head and neck cancers overall compared with non-drinkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The protective effect of coffee was strongest in reducing the risk of cancers in the oral cavity and the oropharynx, the section of the throat just behind the mouth. Interestingly, even decaffeinated coffee appeared to offer some benefit, although its impact was mainly associated with lowering the risk of oral cavity cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This suggests that compounds other than caffeine—such as antioxidants and polyphenols naturally found in coffee—may play a role in reducing cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to tea, the picture is less straightforward. The study showed that drinking one cup or less of tea per day was associated with a 9% lower chance of head and neck cancers overall. In particular, this limited intake seemed to reduce the risk of hypopharyngeal cancer, which develops in the lower part of the throat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the benefits appeared to reverse when tea consumption increased. Drinking more than one cup of tea daily was linked to a 38% higher chance of laryngeal cancer—a cancer that develops in the larynx, or voice box. Researchers suggest this may be due to tea contributing to acid reflux, a known risk factor for laryngeal cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Health benefits of tea and coffee for head and neck cancer&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Lee and her team suggest that the anti-cancer benefits of tea and coffee may not be due to caffeine alone. Both drinks contain a wide range of bioactive compounds—such as flavonoids, tannins, and polyphenols—that have antioxidant and anti-inflammatory properties. These compounds could help reduce DNA damage and slow the development of cancer cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, the evidence is not conclusive. As Dr. Lee emphasized, the varying effects of tea and coffee highlight the need for more targeted studies on how these beverages affect different parts of the throat and oral cavity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Challenges in linking tea and coffee to cancer risk&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the promising findings, the study has several limitations. One major issue is that participants self-reported their tea and coffee consumption, which can sometimes be inaccurate. The research also did not differentiate between types of tea (such as green, black, or herbal) or how the drinks were prepared, both of which could influence results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts also caution that the findings do not prove direct cause and effect. Professor Tom Sanders, emeritus professor of nutrition and dietetics at King’s College London, noted that people who consume large amounts of tea and coffee may also engage in healthier lifestyle habits overall, such as avoiding smoking or limiting alcohol intake. These factors, rather than the beverages themselves, might help explain the reduced cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Moderate tea and coffee consumption may offer cancer protection&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those who worry that their daily tea or coffee habit might increase cancer risk, this study offers some reassurance. Moderate consumption—especially of coffee—may provide protective effects against certain types of head and neck cancer. However, drinking excessive amounts of tea could increase the risk of laryngeal cancer, suggesting moderation is key.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new research adds to growing evidence that tea and coffee may offer some health benefits beyond boosting alertness. However, experts stress that these drinks should not be seen as a substitute for proven cancer prevention strategies such as avoiding smoking, limiting alcohol intake, eating a balanced diet, and staying physically active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, if you enjoy a warm cup of tea or coffee, you can continue indulging—but with the understanding that balance matters. As scientists continue to explore the complex relationship between hot beverages and cancer risk, one thing is clear: your daily cup is probably doing more good than harm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also Read | &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/recurrent-utis-a-sign-of-kidney-cancer-silent-symptoms-hidden-risks-and-when-to-see-a-doctor/articleshow/124284131.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Recurrent UTIs a sign of kidney cancer: Silent symptoms, hidden risks, and when to see a doctor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 05:09:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgJBVV95cUxNdHlUVndyQTZJOXR3cHBiblVCOUJKcVhvSVhoRDRySld1ZWZwVEFkd3M4TzhfRFlUUTJmUTI0R1N0VS03YTZwTkktcHZHTHVjS29mcWZKd1hYQWZUbVVKZUdmOWg2Rzc4OE5WMTU0Mi03ZXdWVGt3OGJ1aExHTFplMmdKZHZkbDdDWmliVG9sT3MyRm4tR0NNR2tjcmFlRUc3a0JyZ0VMMFRKclpSNWthRnpYX2NMQzI2UWRYb2lVSGducGhQRVh2WTEyOG9pU2hENkJtZEJDMlVuaklDSUF2YmUzVTJKRUxMZVdnaFpMMzBnS3ZsMXR2X2cxRXBnQnJ4RFFhclZQQ2NJSWN6MHI2dUctOHB6bWpmc1FCNkhwR2hmUHZ6Qm5GNUVUZmlpd9IBswJBVV95cUxQX0hobGNFdC0yQXRpUmVPdlVxRGE0MUxVcnVmSlIzSGpVd1paRGZhcU85Z2o0am9XbXZQdThBaFA5aV9HRE9jUzZRMC1lVmVHZlFfcXFEZDhWOTg3eV83emVralotUmkweTF4dmU3WkZwVDluRzhLX1AySUU2QWk4bTFJTFExRXZ6TnJTdEpRZGpURnVmOGRLWlBJSllUMGwwMFAyYU13QWF5aEpheEhCZnFGRF9EWW1fckhtdUJmM3VObDBCY1FrQzZzUmRTemVsSkFMMnl5Z1JLQ0dXNm10d3FKUmZ5alRKcXpGeENkbU9qV2J2cXhyV2RTLTRNYWw2NVE5Zm5RXzJPdkI2MHhvX2ZFLU1GdEVKMktXanlLbUtQemZ0SkV1V1VZSDcxQlB5UXhN</guid></item><item><title>医生对廉价药物抗结肠癌的力量感到震惊- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/10/251003033921.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A Swedish-led research team at Karolinska Institutet and Karolinska University Hospital has shown in a new randomized clinical trial that a low dose of the well-known medicine aspirin halves the risk of recurrence after surgery in patients with colon and rectal cancer with a certain type of genetic alteration in the tumor.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every year, nearly two million people worldwide are diagnosed with colorectal cancer. Between 20 and 40 percent develop metastases, which makes the disease both more difficult to treat and more deadly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Previous observational studies have suggested that aspirin may reduce the risk of certain cancers and possibly also the risk of recurrence after surgery in patients with colorectal cancer harboring mutations in genes within the PIK3 signaling pathway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These genes regulate key cellular processes such as growth and division. When mutated, these processes can become dysregulated, leading to uncontrolled cell proliferation and cancer development. However, prior findings have been inconsistent and no randomized clinical trials had previously confirmed the association. To address this gap, the ALASCCA trial was initiated and has now been published in &lt;em&gt;The New England Journal of Medicine&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The current study included more than 3,500 patients with colon and rectal cancer from 33 hospitals in Sweden, Norway, Denmark, and Finland. Patients whose tumors showed a specific genetic mutation in the PIK3 signaling pathway -- a mutation found in approximately 40 percent of patients -- were randomized to receive either 160 mg of aspirin daily or a placebo for three years after surgery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For patients with the genetic mutation in PIK3, the risk of recurrence was reduced by 55 percent in those who received aspirin compared with the placebo group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Aspirin is being tested here in a completely new context as a precision medicine treatment. This is a clear example of how we can use genetic information to personalize treatment and at the same time save both resources and suffering," says first author Anna Martling, professor at the Department of Molecular Medicine and Surgery, Karolinska Institutet, and senior consultant surgeon at Karolinska University Hospital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So how does aspirin reduce the risk of recurrence of colon and rectal cancer? The researchers believe that the effect is likely due to aspirin acting through several parallel mechanisms - it reduces inflammation, inhibits platelet function and tumor growth. This combination makes the environment less favorable for cancer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Although we do not yet fully understand all the molecular links, the findings strongly support the biological rationale and suggest that the treatment may be particularly effective in genetically defined subgroups of patients," says Anna Martling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers believe that the results could have global significance and influence treatment guidelines for colon and rectal cancer worldwide. Anna Martling sees the fact that the drug is well established as a major advantage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Aspirin is a drug that is readily available globally and extremely inexpensive compared to many modern cancer drugs, which is very positive," says Anna Martling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study was funded in part by the Swedish Research Council and the Swedish Cancer Society. The researchers state that there are no conflicts of interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facts: What is aspirin?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aspirin is a medicine that contains acetylsalicylic acid, a substance that relieves pain, fever, and inflammation. It belongs to the group of NSAIDs (non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs). The effect usually occurs within 30 minutes. In low doses, it is also used to prevent blood clots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Common side effects include stomach problems and increased bleeding tendency. People with stomach ulcers, bleeding disorders, or asthma should avoid aspirin. Aspirin is available over the counter in higher doses, but should be used with caution, especially in combination with other blood-thinning agents or alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 05:05:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE8yQm13a3JaZEp4R25oeEFJSk1uNWdGdXl2LUhocFY5LWxKZWRnN1FRNkIzOTZ0T0YtaXFfU0dUdE1WeVpyR2I4VlRoOVM3WXI5UXFzSjk1ZkhQaVBzcDdRM3JVallBOGN5VklOd1hhcw</guid></item></channel></rss>