<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>“显着”结果–科学家说这种补充剂逆转了心脏损伤- SciTechDaily | “Remarkable” Results – Scientists Say This Supplement Reversed Heart Damage - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxQQjVmQjJpRG54Vi1CSlg4SE1aWUJvT1hER1c0UjMyV1p3SFFhbVZJakM5UWduTVBzZlpUTkZRdkZROS1SQVdxYmc4N04wcmo3OUM4bmwtbWtDbE1WYWlNNkpZUmNvRTB0Vk5JWndQQ1BKdlRhOThjZmc5Mm05bk9QRVZrY1BMcXdMSmJOSzBZWmIweERmUUtrOWI5d1ByZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 22:23:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQQjVmQjJpRG54Vi1CSlg4SE1aWUJvT1hER1c0UjMyV1p3SFFhbVZJakM5UWduTVBzZlpUTkZRdkZROS1SQVdxYmc4N04wcmo3OUM4bmwtbWtDbE1WYWlNNkpZUmNvRTB0Vk5JWndQQ1BKdlRhOThjZmc5Mm05bk9QRVZrY1BMcXdMSmJOSzBZWmIweERmUUtrOWI5d1ByZw</guid></item><item><title>精神分裂症患者大脑内膜中发现的病毒痕迹- ScienceAlert | Virus Traces Discovered in The Brain Lining of People With Schizophrenia - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxQRlpCVTEwYS01cGZrdnVHLWQ5QkpZWnlPSjEtVDBGYXExNkZDNHNueDFxbFZKbzdhWkgyVU1zTEpkel8yRmI2ZDZQUjhUbkxBckpESmx6SkVpMm9yWGFXSGdwXzF2Q3RweWQ0enVVUFl3THFDLTJEczZ5MmduMThzN1JfQ1MzSzJTbkhxYnBPNl9zeThkRUpvcTRWSUEtRklxbXNn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The hepatitis C  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="168137" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;virus&lt;/a&gt; (HCV) may play a role in mental health disorders such as  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/schizophrenia" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73022" data-postid="168137" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;schizophrenia&lt;/a&gt;, bipolar disorder, and major  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/depression" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73097" data-postid="168137" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt;, according to a new study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts have long &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/people-with-schizophrenia-have-a-strange-telling-response-to-the-epstein-barr-virus"&gt;noted links&lt;/a&gt; between these psychiatric disorders and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/v15061345"&gt;certain viral infections&lt;/a&gt;, but direct evidence of the &lt;span&gt;viruses&lt;/span&gt; inside human brains is lacking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the brain's protective lining, however, the new study found traces of 13 different viral species. HCV showed a significant association with both schizophrenia and bipolar disorder, compared to healthy controls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/mysterious-viral-dna-in-human-genome-linked-with-psychiatric-disorders?utm_source=SA_article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related_link"&gt;Mysterious Viral DNA in Human Genome Linked With Psychiatric Disorders&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, led by researchers at Johns Hopkins University, analyzed postmortem brain samples from patients diagnosed with schizophrenia, bipolar disorder, and major depression, as well as unaffected subjects to serve as controls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They focused on the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Choroid_plexus"&gt;choroid plexus&lt;/a&gt;, a network of capillaries and connective tissue that&lt;span&gt; controls production of cerebrospinal fluid. This stuff surrounds the brain and spinal cord to cushion against impact, helps remove metabolic waste from the brain, and regulates the exchange of incoming and outgoing molecules.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The choroid plexus is known to be a target for &lt;span&gt;viruses&lt;/span&gt;, and since previous studies have found so few viral traces in the brain itself, the authors of the new study deemed this structure a good place for a closer look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They acquired samples from the Stanley Medical Research Institute collection, a repository of brain tissue to study people with mental health disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To hunt for hidden &lt;span&gt;viruses&lt;/span&gt;, the researchers conducted sequencing with the Twist Comprehensive Viral Research Panel, which can help identify more than 3,000 different &lt;span&gt;viruses&lt;/span&gt; in human samples.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This revealed an array of viral sequences in the choroid plexus, especially in samples from patients who had schizophrenia or bipolar disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While those samples were more likely to contain &lt;span&gt;viruses&lt;/span&gt; in general, HCV was the only viral species with a  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/p-value" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73101" data-postid="168137" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;statistically significant&lt;/a&gt; link, the study found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thus, the researchers chose it "to characterize the association between psychiatric disorders and &lt;span&gt;viruses&lt;/span&gt;," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41398-025-03387-3"&gt;they write&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_168251" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-168251" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/HCV-642x260.jpg" alt="Hepatitis C Virus" class="wp-image-168251 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/HCV-642x260.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/HCV-768x311.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/HCV-600x243.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/HCV.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-168251" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;"It's possible that some people may be having psychiatric symptoms because they have an infection," researchers say. (&lt;a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/niaid/53073046390/"&gt;Maria Teresa Catanese/Charles M. Rice/Rockefeller University/NIAID&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a second phase of the study, the authors zoomed out from individual brain samples to analyze TriNetX, a vast database of health records from 285 million patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using these records, they found HCV in 3.5 percent of patients with schizophrenia and 3.9 percent of those with bipolar disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's nearly twice the prevalence of HCV in patients with major depression (1.8 percent), the researchers note, and seven times the prevalence in the control population (0.5 percent).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study found evidence of &lt;span&gt;viruses&lt;/span&gt; only in the brain lining, despite also inspecting samples of the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hippocampus"&gt;hippocampus&lt;/a&gt; – a brain region involved with learning, memory, and emotion, among other roles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hippocampus was reliably clean, even if the lining wasn't. It appears the protective layer was effectively doing its job of keeping pathogens out of the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet patients with HCV in the lining did show altered gene expression in the hippocampus, hinting at how a virus might still wield influence from the brain's margins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More research is still needed to clarify the associations between &lt;span&gt;viruses&lt;/span&gt; and psychiatric disorders, and to explore possible mechanisms that could let pathogens pull strings from the periphery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if HCV can contribute to these conditions, that wouldn't mean it's the only factor. The new findings don't suggest everyone with schizophrenia or bipolar disorder has HCV, the authors point out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They do, however, offer hope for novel tactics against devastating psychiatric disorders, says Sarven Sabunciyan, a neuroscientist at Johns Hopkins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our findings show that it's possible that some people may be having psychiatric symptoms because they have an infection, and since the hepatitis C infection is treatable, it might be possible for this patient subset to be treated with antiviral drugs and not have to deal with psychiatric symptoms," Sabunciyan &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/news/newsroom/news-releases/2025/07/new-study-finds-evidence-of-hepatitis-c-virus-in-cells-lining-human-brain"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41398-025-03387-3"&gt;Translational Psychiatry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 19:02:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQRlpCVTEwYS01cGZrdnVHLWQ5QkpZWnlPSjEtVDBGYXExNkZDNHNueDFxbFZKbzdhWkgyVU1zTEpkel8yRmI2ZDZQUjhUbkxBckpESmx6SkVpMm9yWGFXSGdwXzF2Q3RweWQ0enVVUFl3THFDLTJEczZ5MmduMThzN1JfQ1MzSzJTbkhxYnBPNl9zeThkRUpvcTRWSUEtRklxbXNn</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，这种简单的日常活动可以将癌症风险降低高达16% - Earth.com | Study shows this simple daily activity can reduce cancer risk by up to 16% - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxQUnQ1YUl1Rm5jM0NOQnN2cTh4emxWd1R2Zk9aeUVjY3lGbjkwbVpkMWx4ajFSdnVicFdFX3Y5cUV5aWZuZWlvQmVEQUViVktSY2RKOWVWbVZ0WnZpYjVaUzRUb19sbEtDbzcwaU84TlBQNXlvNWlmT0NFUFpUUmhDR0xlNDNxeVpRNVRLWW5zbEhuRWd6NE5HR1Y3U2RMbEVnTV8xbDBiRW1lcWVIa2c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nine thousand steps sound like an easy stroll on a sunny day. According to a massive analysis of wrist‑worn tracking data, that simple daily target could reduce cancer risk by roughly one‑sixth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The joint project by &lt;a href="https://corp.oup.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Oxford University&lt;/a&gt; and the U.S. National Institutes of Health &lt;a href="https://www.nih.gov/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;(NIH)&lt;/a&gt; combed through the movements of more than 85,000 adults born in the United Kingdom and followed for almost six years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-small-effort-can-reduce-cancer"&gt;Small effort can reduce cancer&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A daily average of 9,000 steps, when compared with 5,000, corresponded to a 16 percent decrease in the likelihood of developing 13 common &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cancer-cells-create-power-waves-to-fuel-invasion/"&gt;cancers&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That &lt;a href="https://bjsm.bmj.com/content/59/12/839" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;benefit&lt;/a&gt; started to emerge around 7,000 steps, where risk was 11 percent lower, and leveled off beyond the 9,000‑step mark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the study captured entire days of ordinary movement, the team could separate the effect of step count from walking speed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pacing faster did not add extra protection once total steps were considered, a nuance that helps reassure people who cannot or do not wish to run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-from-accelerometers-not-anecdotes"&gt;From accelerometers not anecdotes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier research leaned on questionnaires that asked volunteers to remember their workouts, a method that often misses slow, sporadic movement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Self‑reports also blur the difference between strolling to the mailbox and sprinting for a bus, making risk estimates fuzzy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Total physical activity, LIPA, MVPA and step counts were inversely associated with incident cancer,” &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40139674/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; lead analyst Alaina Shreves, M.S., who works with both Oxford and the NIH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Light housework and moderate gardening helped as much, step for step, as a run around the block, a payoff that will surprise many weekend warriors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-nine-thousand-not-ten"&gt;Why nine thousand not ten&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In public health circles 10,000 steps became folklore, yet the number came from a 1960s pedometer marketing slogan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.K. sample showed that risk curves flattened at roughly 9,000 steps, echoing &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/physical-activity-basics/benefits/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Centers for Disease Control&lt;/a&gt; findings that mortality gains taper between 8,000 and 10,000 daily steps for adults under 60.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For older adults, similar plateaus appear closer to 8,000 steps, yet the protective trend is consistent. The lesson is simple: any increase matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-most-adults-fall-short"&gt;Most adults fall short&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent wearable‑device studies suggest that the typical American takes only about 4,000 steps a day, a level that specialists classify as sedentary. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Closing the 5,000‑step gap would require roughly 40 extra minutes of relaxed walking, spread conveniently across errands, commutes, and coffee breaks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Work‑from‑home patterns have trimmed incidental steps that were once earned on commutes, and long video meetings encourage near‑continuous sitting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adding a standing reminder or a short timer that signals a one‑minute march on the spot every half hour can restore many of the “lost” strides.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-light-activity-can-reduce-cancer-risk"&gt;Light activity can reduce cancer risk&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Replacing an hour of sitting with gentle chores can reduce &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/simple-blood-test-detects-cancer-before-symptoms-appear/"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; risk by 6 percent, the analysis found. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measured, moderate‑to‑vigorous bouts offered slightly more reduction, yet simply staying on one’s feet proved meaningful when the clock ticked into place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Adults should get 150‑300 minutes of moderate intensity or 75‑150 minutes of vigorous intensity activity each week,” stated the &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A brisk, 30‑minute walk five days a week already lands inside that target.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-biology-behind-the-reduced-cancer-risk"&gt;Biology behind the reduced cancer risk&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regular movement regulates insulin, tames chronic inflammation, and keeps sex hormone levels in check, three pathways that are tied to tumor growth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The World Health Organization (&lt;a href="https://www.who.int" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;WHO&lt;/a&gt;) notes that people who are insufficiently active face up to a 30 percent higher risk of premature death from non‑communicable diseases, including cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exercise may also improve DNA repair and immune surveillance, giving errant cells less room to multiply unchecked. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These physiological ripples grow with each step, making walking a potent tool that demands no gym membership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-turning-evidence-into-daily-habits"&gt;Turning evidence into daily habits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nine thousand steps translate to about 4.5 miles (7.2 kilometers), or roughly 90 minutes of total walking accumulated throughout a day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parking at the far end of the lot, pacing during phone calls, and choosing stairs can all nudge the counter upward without scheduling a workout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smartphones and inexpensive fitness bands make tallying straightforward. For readers uncomfortable with gadgets, a lap around the block after each meal approximates three thousand steps, leaving six thousand to everyday errands and normal indoor movement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-keep-moving-to-reduce-cancer-risk"&gt;Keep moving to reduce cancer risk&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Oxford‑NIH study relied on middle‑aged and older volunteers, largely of European descent, so findings may not apply identically across ages and ethnicities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, its message lines up with decades of data tying movement to reduced &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/walking-each-day-at-any-speed-lowers-the-risk-of-cancer/"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; and cardiovascular burdens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walking will not replace screening or a balanced diet, yet it is a low‑cost habit with few negative side effects. Even if nine thousand steps seem high today, adding an extra five hundred each week will gradually bridge the gap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://bjsm.bmj.com/content/59/12/839" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;British Journal of Sports Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 18:33:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxQUnQ1YUl1Rm5jM0NOQnN2cTh4emxWd1R2Zk9aeUVjY3lGbjkwbVpkMWx4ajFSdnVicFdFX3Y5cUV5aWZuZWlvQmVEQUViVktSY2RKOWVWbVZ0WnZpYjVaUzRUb19sbEtDbzcwaU84TlBQNXlvNWlmT0NFUFpUUmhDR0xlNDNxeVpRNVRLWW5zbEhuRWd6NE5HR1Y3U2RMbEVnTV8xbDBiRW1lcWVIa2c</guid></item><item><title>Benadryl与致残性疾病有关：医生向风险最高的年龄组发出警告-每日邮报 | Benadryl linked to crippling DISEASE: Doctors issue warning to age group at highest risk - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxNY1lPcGRITVN2b0dyRHNGM29MaFg5aDlmVlBrYWRDYjN1SkNSaEl5cDVNWk5oOFkwTU5rMHl6U3BIRkpoQks2VTRiTkpHUXJudnNWNU91TUNlUEJ4NlQ0cVFOalh3TmZTUmVJUFRJQ21MTDNPaXhsVV9HVGNjZW9ZWXV6RWRXTkxocjhyS1hiU2pnQ1hKeHc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Millions of Americans take Benadryl every year to relieve allergies, but &lt;span&gt;doctors have uncovered a shocking link between the medication and a devastating disease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Benadryl's active &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14555093/urgent-warning-Nytol-Panadol-Tylenol-Banylin-Benadryl-dementia.html"&gt;drug diphenhydramine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; blocks receptors for histamine, an inflammatory chemical released by the immune system that can trigger symptoms like a runny nose and itchy skin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;But doctors say the 15-cent tablets can also cross the blood-brain barrier and block receptors for a neurotransmitter, acetylcholine, that is crucial for attention, memory and learning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamainternalmedicine/fullarticle/2091745"&gt;One study&lt;/a&gt; found that Benadryl's active drug and similar medications raised the risk of dementia by 54 percent and Alzheimer's by 63 percent among those who take the drug regularly compared to those who do not use the medication.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Other studies have linked the drug to a higher risk of drowsiness, falls and car accidents, with people in Europe advised not to drive after taking the substance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'There have been several studies over the past decade that show an association between Benadryl and dementia, particularly in older patients,' Dr Joao Lopes, a pediatrician at Case Western University, told the Daily Mail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It is not our first option and it has not been for a long while, given the existence of safer and more effective medications.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Still, Dr Anna Wolfson, an allergist at Massachusetts General Hospital, said, 'If you're on a deserted island and Benadryl is the only allergy drug available, you should take it. But, in almost every other case, there are safer, better options.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Doctors raised the alarm over anti-allergy medication Benadryl and a potential link to dementia (stock photo)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A spokeswoman for Kenvue, which makes Benadryl, said in a statement, 'We are not aware of any studies that show a causal link between labeled use of diphenhydramine and an increased risk of developing dementia. Diphenhydramine is an ingredient which is generally recognized as safe and effective by health authorities in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Safety is always our top priority, and we recommend that consumers carefully read and follow the label when using any medication.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a major study into Benadryl's potential links with the cognitive disorder published in &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamainternalmedicine/fullarticle/2091745"&gt;JAMA Internal Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, researchers tracked 3,400 people over 65 years old in Seattle, Washington, including 2,200 individuals (64 percent) who took antihistamines like diphen&lt;span&gt;hydramine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Patients were recruited in 1996 or in the years between 2000 and 2003, and were tracked for more than a decade. None had dementia at the start of the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Over the 10-year period, there were nearly 800 cases of dementia recorded (23 percent of all the participants).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers found those taking at least two doses per week of an anticholinergic medication - like Benadryl or an antidepressant - had a 54 percent higher risk of dementia compared to those who were not taking the drug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Benadryl is sold for as little as 15 cents a tablet, but there are concerns that its active ingredient can cross the blood-brain barrier and affect brain cells&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The study was observational, and could not definitively prove that there was a link between dementia and Benadryl, although it was part of a growing body of literature suggesting a possible connection between the two. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors said that taking the medication occasionally was safe, but warned those who take the drug more regularly or around two to three times per week should consider speaking to their healthcare provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In place of Benadryl, physicians recommended newer antihistamines like cetirizine, often sold under the brand name Zyrtec, or fexofenadine, sold widely as Allegra.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Wolfson, told The &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/07/15/well/benadryl-health-risks.html?partner=slack&amp;amp;smid=sl-share"&gt;New York Times&lt;/a&gt;, 'Occasional use [of Benadryl] is fine and nobody needs to run home and throw out their stash.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Olalekan Otulana, a physician in the UK, said, 'The risk appears to be more significant when these types of drugs are used frequently and over many months or years, and particularly in older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Occasional use (say for a short bout of hay fever or trouble sleeping) is unlikely to carry the same level of concern.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He added that 'People should not panic if they have taken it in the past. But they should have an informed conversation with their doctor if they are using it regularly.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Benadryl has been available in the US since the 1940s, with many taking the drug simply because they did during childhood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Benadryl has been available in the US since the 1940s, and many still take the drug because it is familiar (stock photo)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In some European countries, like the UK, Benadryl does not contain diphenhydramine, instead swapping it got newer and safer antihistamines like acrivastine or cetirizine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In Germany, Sweden and some other European countries, access to first-generation antihistamines like diphenhydramine has been restricted. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was not clear why Benadryl maker Kenvue uses different ingredients in the US compared to elsewhere in the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 1.5 million prescriptions for diphenhydramine are written in the US every year, with millions more given out over-the-counter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many doctors have previously called for people to use alternatives to Benadryl for years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a paper published in February this year in the &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11803843/"&gt;World Allergy Organization Journal&lt;/a&gt;, doctors wrote, 'Diphenhydramine, once a pioneering antihistamine, is now overshadowed by second-generation antihistamines with similar efficacy and fewer adverse effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Based on a comprehensive evaluation of practice patterns and the prevalence and incidence of adverse clinical events, we believe that diphenhydramine has reached the end of its life cycle, and in its class of therapies it is a relatively greater public health hazard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We recommend it should no longer be widely prescribed or continue to be readily available over the counter.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 17:07:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNY1lPcGRITVN2b0dyRHNGM29MaFg5aDlmVlBrYWRDYjN1SkNSaEl5cDVNWk5oOFkwTU5rMHl6U3BIRkpoQks2VTRiTkpHUXJudnNWNU91TUNlUEJ4NlQ0cVFOalh3TmZTUmVJUFRJQ21MTDNPaXhsVV9HVGNjZW9ZWXV6RWRXTkxocjhyS1hiU2pnQ1hKeHc</guid></item><item><title>Albany Med和Saratoga医院的潜在麻疹暴露- Times Union | Potential measles exposures at Albany Med and Saratoga Hospital - Times Union</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogFBVV95cUxNVGEzXzF0SHhiTjJtWW45QWpjZHpjd0xDanlwbERnSGMyS2JoTjJLekc2YlNDVGhyMHNiSWF0RDQzam5pQWVXZjN1bEZqTFE3RU5ydVV4aG90M3M1RnM4MHc0bWExU2d4cWQzcWtIc01hU3BDdDNaTVJLSUNzbGFwVGw3TjlvaVlZMTFad2FlbkFNM2lyVDB3OGtLYlFRQVY2RFE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>Times Union</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 16:57:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxNVGEzXzF0SHhiTjJtWW45QWpjZHpjd0xDanlwbERnSGMyS2JoTjJLekc2YlNDVGhyMHNiSWF0RDQzam5pQWVXZjN1bEZqTFE3RU5ydVV4aG90M3M1RnM4MHc0bWExU2d4cWQzcWtIc01hU3BDdDNaTVJLSUNzbGFwVGw3TjlvaVlZMTFad2FlbkFNM2lyVDB3OGtLYlFRQVY2RFE</guid></item><item><title>我以为我离婚是因为我的妻子是同性恋。现在我正在学习这一切可能是一个巨大的谎言。-石板杂志 | I Thought I Got Divorced Because My Wife Is Gay. Now I’m Learning It All Might’ve Been a Huge Lie. - Slate Magazine</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxQNmxuNlZpaDdWckNPd0NHd29wdUpWR2NiZHplaU9hdnBvOTU0Vmdpc0xQLW1LLXZyMlE1Y3JTZWpxRk1VZUJPQmlhb0JQMXg1SHZhSlpQdVRYVjZOc3pMc3VjQWJOSVJ1d25yRzJxOTJMclVPdnQxNUVXUldubnBaWXlQSmF0ZzFzd3E2aENYSzlvb1VP?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmd98muc80011nfm6168hk408@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Stoya and Rich here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmd98vnkb002w3b77vi4gg4pv@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="53" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmd98nlg4000w3b77fzvxd51n@published"&gt;A year and a half ago, my wife came out as a lesbian. While losing her this way was painful, I agreed to end the marriage because I didn’t want her to have to live a lie. We’ve stayed in touch, which has been nice, but I recently heard something that made me really mad.&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="37" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmd98s2o8002p3b77y8a3f7cp@published"&gt; It turns out that she and her wife sometimes have threesomes in which they include a guy. Now a part of me feels like she ended our marriage under false pretenses and I feel betrayed. Did she deceive me?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="7" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmd98nlj4000x3b77ut2u6qfz@published"&gt;—I Thought She Didn’t Go For That&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="8" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmd98nlm1000y3b77cpbx50t3@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear I Thought She Didn’t Go For That,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="97" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmd98nlqj000z3b77akzs4bor@published"&gt;Your ex-wife may have deceived you. Maybe when she told you she was a lesbian, she had lingering doubt or even full knowledge that she still had sexual attraction to men. Maybe she thought it would be too complicated to explain this, that other present issues with your relationship (including the sexual aspect of it) were too much to get into so that “I’m gay” was the most efficient explanation. I’m not in her head and neither are you, so while it is reasonable to mull these possibilities, we can’t say for sure if they are real.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="105" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmd98nltp00103b772hj6uhx4@published"&gt;There are many other potential explanations. Maybe your ex-wife realized that she is homoromantic (that is, only interested in romantic relationships with women) but bisexual. Maybe she doesn’t subscribe to these labels at all and is just feeling her way through. Maybe when she came out to you, she thought she’d only have sex with women for the rest of her life but discussions with her wife and/or other surfaced feelings have caused her to reconsider. All of these things are valid if true. Sexuality evolves. Life is a journey. Her truth a year and a half ago may not be what it is today.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="145" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmd98nlws00113b77wbthv245@published"&gt;She moved on from you rather quickly, it seems—in a year and a half, she came out, left you, and managed to remarry. That must have been difficult and it seems that it is &lt;em&gt;still&lt;/em&gt; difficult. While reasons can give us some sense of comfort in their promise of closure, the truth is that life is complex. Not every decision people make has ironclad rationale, or rationale that can be verbalized with clarity. Despite recent evidence, it seems fair to continue believing your wife that her sexuality was a key factor in your divorce. The bigger picture is that regardless of sexuality, she knew that your relationship wasn’t right for her. It’s sad—devastating, even—but these things happen. I think most people would agree that someone should not be in a relationship that isn’t working for them. In that sense, her reasons and explanations are immaterial.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmd98nqdy001f3b777sg16wr2@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Rich&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmd98o0n8001s3b779syuok9p@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="69" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmd98o6fn001z3b775x0f00to@published"&gt;I’ve been with my boyfriend for 8 years. We’re planning on moving in together, but I don’t think he’s going to like it, for one big reason: I don’t want to have sex. He thinks living together will significantly improve our sex live and help us rekindle the flame, but that’s not what I want at all. I love him and he’s my best friend. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/03/moving-in-sex-life-advice.html"&gt;What should I do?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmd98muc80014nfm6anbja3cl@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;The latest sex, parenting, and money advice from our columnists delivered to your inbox three times a week.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate Magazine</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQNmxuNlZpaDdWckNPd0NHd29wdUpWR2NiZHplaU9hdnBvOTU0Vmdpc0xQLW1LLXZyMlE1Y3JTZWpxRk1VZUJPQmlhb0JQMXg1SHZhSlpQdVRYVjZOc3pMc3VjQWJOSVJ1d25yRzJxOTJMclVPdnQxNUVXUldubnBaWXlQSmF0ZzFzd3E2aENYSzlvb1VP</guid></item><item><title>在意想不到的地方找到青春之泉- TheStreet | Fountain of youth found in unexpected source - TheStreet</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihAFBVV95cUxQSWRDM3Z3MG1VaHBjTUoyYjNzdXJwUkdncWRnRmJjS1QweGl0RGNsV0drZU9UaUdNNlB0T3ZIWFdHSDRwMWk5c3lWenZIblZubXE5dnZsTHhDQnhpY1BHbFFGSGJ2V19aNWgyUS1sUzBWc0J0VFAxUTRTYzlOWHFGb1p0Ni0?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TheStreet</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 15:17:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQSWRDM3Z3MG1VaHBjTUoyYjNzdXJwUkdncWRnRmJjS1QweGl0RGNsV0drZU9UaUdNNlB0T3ZIWFdHSDRwMWk5c3lWenZIblZubXE5dnZsTHhDQnhpY1BHbFFGSGJ2V19aNWgyUS1sUzBWc0J0VFAxUTRTYzlOWHFGb1p0Ni0</guid></item><item><title>与脑细胞损伤和中风风险相关的流行糖替代品- ScienceDaily | Popular sugar substitute linked to brain cell damage and stroke risk - ScienceDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMib0FVX3lxTE9kbVNRQUZtRnJYY1JlWWtWTldYai01QnozbzRWTGxsSmdQaFl2d1dVX0RQR1BqMnU1OWFCRXVYTDI4U0VNTnYwM2w2M0tCWUUtdDdfOHR2MkRIYS05OWNZWDRjMVVoeVpiaTR5bUo4OA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;From low-carb ice cream to keto protein bars to "sugar-free" soda, the decades-old sweetener erythritol is everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But new University of Colorado Boulder research shows the popular sugar substitute and specialty food additive comes with serious downsides, impacting brain cells in numerous ways that can boost risk of stroke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study was published in the &lt;em&gt;Journal of Applied Physiology&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Our study adds to the evidence suggesting that non-nutritive sweeteners that have generally been purported to be safe, may not come without negative health consequences," said senior author Christopher DeSouza, professor of integrative physiology and director of the Integrative Vascular Biology Lab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First approved by the Food and Drug Administration in 2001, erythritol is a sugar alcohol, often produced by fermenting corn and found in hundreds of products. It has almost no calories, is about 80% as sweet as table sugar, and has negligible impact on insulin levels, making it a favorite for people trying to lose weight, keep their blood sugar in check or avoid carbohydrates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But recent research has begun to shed light on its risks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One recent study involving 4,000 people in the U.S. and Europe found that men and women with higher circulating levels of erythritol were significantly more likely to have a heart attack or stroke within the next three years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DeSouza and first author Auburn Berry, a graduate student in his lab, set out to understand what might be driving that increased risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers in the lab treated human cells that line blood vessels in the brain for three hours with about the same amount of erythritol contained in a typical sugar-free beverage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They observed that the treated cells were altered in numerous ways: They expressed significantly less nitric oxide, a molecule that relaxes and widens blood vessels, and more endothelin-1, a protein that constricts blood vessels. Meanwhile, when challenged with a clot-forming compound called thrombin, cellular production of the natural clot-busting compound t-PA was "markedly blunted." The erythritol-treated cells also produced more reactive oxygen species (ROS), a.k.a. "free radicals," metabolic byproducts which can age and damage cells and inflame tissue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Big picture, if your vessels are more constricted and your ability to break down blood clots is lowered, your risk of stroke goes up," said Berry. "Our research demonstrates not only that, but how erythritol has the potential to increase stroke risk."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DeSouza notes that their study used only a serving-size worth of the sugar substitute. For those who consume multiple servings per day, the impact, presumably, could be worse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The authors caution that their study was a laboratory study, conducted on cells, and larger studies in people are needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That said, De Souza encourages consumers to read labels, looking for erythritol or "sugar alcohol" on the label.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Given the epidemiological study that inspired our work, and now our cellular findings, we believe it would be prudent for people to monitor their consumption of non-nutrient-sweeteners such as this one," he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 14:50:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE9kbVNRQUZtRnJYY1JlWWtWTldYai01QnozbzRWTGxsSmdQaFl2d1dVX0RQR1BqMnU1OWFCRXVYTDI4U0VNTnYwM2w2M0tCWUUtdDdfOHR2MkRIYS05OWNZWDRjMVVoeVpiaTR5bUo4OA</guid></item><item><title>根据胃肠病学家的说法， 6种可以降低结肠癌风险的零食- EatingWell | 6 Snacks That Can Reduce Colon Cancer Risk, According to a Gastroenterologist - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiekFVX3lxTFBoU1NOanpOenJkUmI1WXVDb0FTV1JjVnplWDl3VHpHdkpJNWV3LTVzUWNVem5VTlBsY19oYXBRbUJhWlMwd2NpLU42WlQ4Q1FLOUxpemxFZElXUmh3eW81T0lOcU9mVjRBRkhXNlVmS1UwRjZuUTEtUXdB?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gut-healthy snacks like yogurt, citrus and nuts may help lower your risk of colon cancer.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gastroenterologist-approved foods like apples, watermelon and guacamole support digestion.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A healthy diet can't replace medical care, but it plays a key role in lowering chronic disease risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/cancer-and-how-diet-and-lifestyle-choices-lower-the-risk-8777651" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Colon cancer rates are on the rise&lt;/a&gt;, especially for young adults, so it’s more important than ever to prioritize gut-healthy foods. Gastroenterologist Joseph Salhab, M.D., has been providing tips to his millions of social media followers about the best foods and lifestyle choices to make for optimal gut health and digestion.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Recently, he took to Instagram and shared some of his favorite food recommendations to mitigate colorectal cancer risk. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Remember that lowering your risk is not the same as eliminating your risk,” Salhab writes on his Instagram post. “Diet never replaces medical therapy or evaluation but should always be discussed because we know people with healthier diets have a lower risk of chronic disease.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; We couldn’t help but notice that the majority of his picks were healthy snacks you can easily incorporate into your routine. Here are some gastroenterologist-approved snacks to help keep your gut health in check. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-embed mntl-sc-block-universal-embed mntl-sc-block-embed--instagram"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-yogurt"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Yogurt &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Yogurt isn’t just the base for a delicious parfait. It provides &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7962133/is-yogurt-healthy-heres-what-a-dietitian-has-to-say/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;ample benefits&lt;/a&gt;, from supporting bone health to heart health. And a meta-analysis shows that higher yogurt consumption is correlated with a 7% decreased risk of colorectal cancer.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Parfaits topped with berries and granola are a simple, healthy snack. Take it up a notch this summer with these refreshing &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7937679/mini-frozen-yogurt-parfaits/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Mini Frozen Yogurt Parfaits&lt;/a&gt; or our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/259080/strawberry-chocolate-greek-yogurt-bark/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Strawberry-Chocolate Greek Yogurt Bark&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-citrus-fruits"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Citrus Fruits &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you love packing an orange in your bag for an easy snack option, you’re in luck. Citrus fruits are some of the best options for your gut health, thanks to their fiber and water content. Regularly eating citrus can lower cancer risk associated with the digestive and upper respiratory tract, research shows.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Enjoy an orange, grapefruit or clementine as is, add them to a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/high-protein-orange-mango-smoothie-11713716" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;smoothie&lt;/a&gt;, or embrace these fruits in a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/8023984/grapefruit-salad/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;colorful fruit salad&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-tree-nuts"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Tree Nuts &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Tree nuts, such as almonds, cashews and Brazil nuts, are packed with protein, making them a satisfying snack. But that's not the only benefit they provide. For example, the gastroenterologist references research that shows how two servings of tree nuts per day may help lower disease recurrence risk for those with a later stage of colon cancer by 42%.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8027688/are-nuts-good-for-you/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Nuts&lt;/a&gt;’ gut-healthy properties are worth keeping your pantry stocked for. Roast them with your favorite seasonings, like &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7881665/everything-seasoned-almonds/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;everything bagel seasoning&lt;/a&gt; or with a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/sesame-honey-roasted-cashews-11742706" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;sesame-honey glaze&lt;/a&gt;. For a double whammy, add chopped nuts to your yogurt for a snack your gut will thank you for.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-apples"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Apples &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; An &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/17769/5-health-benefits-of-an-apple/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;apple&lt;/a&gt; a day may quite literally keep the doctor away. With heart-healthy fiber, apples are equally delicious and nutritious with a slew of research supporting its nutrient density. A case-control study showed that eating apples daily reduced colorectal cancer risk by 47%.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Pair with nut butter or cheese for a filling snack loaded with protein and fiber.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-watermelon"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Watermelon &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Watermelon wears its name with pride, as 92% of it is made up of water. Staying hydrated is super important for healthy digestion as it keeps things moving in your colon, so upping your water intake as well as eating enough hydrating fruits like watermelon is key.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; There’s nothing quite like fresh watermelon on its own, but you can elevate it even more by topping a slice with &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7995523/cucumber-watermelon-with-mint-basil-dressing/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;mint-basil dressing&lt;/a&gt; or with &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/263891/watermelon-with-lime/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;lime zest and salt&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-salsa-and-guacamole"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Salsa and Guacamole &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Tomatoes and avocado have both been shown to reduce risk of colon cancer, thanks to their fiber and antioxidant content.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The best part about these fruits being gut-healthy powerhouses is that they’re the stars of some of our favorite dips!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Salsa and guacamole are nutritious choices for a snack or appetizer. And there’s nothing quite like homemade; Recipes like our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/249129/fresh-tomato-salsa/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Fresh Tomato Salsa&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/261795/almost-chipotles-guacamole/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Almost Chipotle’s Guacamole&lt;/a&gt; are meant to be served together.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTFBoU1NOanpOenJkUmI1WXVDb0FTV1JjVnplWDl3VHpHdkpJNWV3LTVzUWNVem5VTlBsY19oYXBRbUJhWlMwd2NpLU42WlQ4Q1FLOUxpemxFZElXUmh3eW81T0lOcU9mVjRBRkhXNlVmS1UwRjZuUTEtUXdB</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，女性随着年龄的增长会感到更多的愤怒，但表现出更少的愤怒--《华盛顿邮报》 | Women feel more anger as they age, but show it less, study suggests - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigwFBVV95cUxNOTdMNFRLSjJSNF9uU2tBODljRGp1ci1zYWhQa1ZmS1NhRzRwX1ROanh0Q2UyS01jVGFuTmNjb1FNX05QN3hGbnNxV05oMjNEM3Q5N1FVMl8wQV96MVJ5N1E5TzE4Z3cxZUh0RXNJaWlHNEtweFJ4ODFFSVMwNFluS1gwVQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6KHXUGDZBNEG3EUFGBONAD7ILM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Women feel more anger but express less of it as they age, according to a &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/menopausejournal/fulltext/9900/anger,_aging,_and_reproductive_aging__observations.483.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;recent analysis&lt;/a&gt; in the journal Menopause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XVDI6ACATFAYLINGHVS5V7QXRI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Researchers looked at health reports and menstrual data from 501 participants in the &lt;a href="https://womensmidlifehealthjournal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s40695-016-0019-x" target="_blank"&gt;Seattle Midlife Women’s Health Study&lt;/a&gt;, analyzing a subset of data from 271 women to look for possible connections between age, reproductive stage and anger in women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HQJPJYLWQVF2DMQW3QPCBXXCLM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The women who were studied were between 35 and 55 and still menstruating. The average participant was 41.6 years old, well educated, employed, married and in a median income range when the study began in 1990 and 1992. The majority were White.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="V7JUJXQDPNE55PUP3DSCLFHXZE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Angry feelings, or “state anger,” increased with age, the researchers found. But expressions of anger decreased as women aged, suggesting that anger control grew with chronological age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="LF4TEVZVVJHDNPII4CVM7GFOYI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Participants’ anger spiked in the late reproductive stage of women’s lives, but as menopause approached, participants expressed their anger less frequently and with less aggression or hostility. Just one anger measure, “anger suppressed,” had no link to age, the researchers found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6YB7F6VKRFF65HNA36BOCW3OSI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Anger could play an important role during midlife, the researchers suggest. Perhaps women get practice being angry as they approach menopause, leading to increasing emotional regulation and control over their anger as menopause progresses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AX5FJWK2QZHIVCQCSQ5VD2TYPY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“The mental health side of the menopause transition can have a significant effect on a woman’s personal and professional life,” Monica Christmas, the associate medical director of the Menopause Society, said in a news &lt;a href="https://menopause.org/press-releases/women-get-better-at-managing-their-anger-as-they-age" target="_blank"&gt;release&lt;/a&gt;. “Educating women about the possibility of mood changes during these vulnerable windows and actively managing symptoms can have a profound effect on overall quality of life and health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ZTRHWOJSAFBOFJYR76S3RNVBS4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The researchers call for more research on anger and women as they age, especially given a seeming connection between suppressing anger long-term and cardiac issues such as blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 13:32:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNOTdMNFRLSjJSNF9uU2tBODljRGp1ci1zYWhQa1ZmS1NhRzRwX1ROanh0Q2UyS01jVGFuTmNjb1FNX05QN3hGbnNxV05oMjNEM3Q5N1FVMl8wQV96MVJ5N1E5TzE4Z3cxZUh0RXNJaWlHNEtweFJ4ODFFSVMwNFluS1gwVQ</guid></item><item><title>不仅仅是血清素：迷幻药如何吸引全脑-神经科学新闻 | More Than Serotonin: How Psychedelics Engage the Whole Brain - Neuroscience News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMicEFVX3lxTFBITzl4ckxsOXNXbDRYZzczWFJiSDJrWUhrMU02T0tUazZUMzF3LUczdEdMcDNxUnVTNTE3amU3dHhORlJtaVcxMDNyZC14VS1tcDlHN0owdWYzWUc1M1AwU0p0WG0zWXRSSDByLVlkNkk?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;Classical psychedelics like LSD, psilocybin, and mescaline are known for activating the 5-HT2A serotonin receptor, but a new study reveals their effects go far beyond. Researchers profiled 41 psychedelics against over 300 human receptors and found potent activity at serotonin, dopamine, and adrenergic sites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also showed that psychedelics activate multiple intracellular pathways, which may help separate their therapeutic and hallucinogenic effects. These findings highlight the complexity of psychedelic pharmacology and open doors to more targeted therapies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Psychedelics activate nearly every serotonin, dopamine, and adrenergic receptor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;LSD, psilocybin, and mescaline stimulate multiple 5-HT2A receptor signaling pathways.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Broader receptor activity may underlie both therapeutic and hallucinogenic effects.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In recent years, classical psychedelics such as LSD, psilocybin, and mescaline have made a remarkable comeback—not just in popular culture, but in serious scientific research. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once relegated to the fringes of pharmacology due to their association with counterculture movements, these compounds are now being rigorously studied for their therapeutic potential in treating mental health disorders such as depression, anxiety, post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD), and substance use disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite their promising clinical effects, the molecular mechanisms underlying their action in the brain have remained incompletely understood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study has taken a major step toward decoding these mechanisms, offering the most comprehensive look yet at how psychedelics interact with the human brain at the receptor level. Researchers investigated the pharmacological profiles of 41 classical psychedelics—spanning tryptamines, phenethylamines, and lysergamides—against a wide panel of human receptors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their findings reveal a fascinating and complex picture: these compounds are far from “single-target” drugs and instead interact with dozens of neural receptors and pathways that may each contribute to their profound effects on perception, mood, and cognition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Beyond the 5-HT2A Receptor&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, it’s been known that psychedelics exert their hallmark effects by activating a particular serotonin receptor, known as the 5-HT2A receptor (5-HT2AR). This receptor, distributed widely across the cortex, is thought to underlie the perceptual and cognitive distortions characteristic of a psychedelic trip. Indeed, blocking 5-HT2AR prevents many of these effects, confirming its central role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the current research highlights that the story does not end there. The team profiled these psychedelics against an unprecedented 318 human G-protein-coupled receptors (GPCRs)—a vast family of receptors involved in transmitting signals from neurotransmitters and hormones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition, LSD was further tested against over 450 human kinases, enzymes that regulate various cellular processes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results were striking: psychedelics exhibited potent and efficacious activity not only at nearly every serotonin receptor subtype, but also at a wide array of dopamine and adrenergic receptors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This suggests that the subjective experience of psychedelics—and their potential therapeutic benefits—may emerge from the interplay of multiple receptor systems. For example, activity at dopamine receptors could help explain the mood-elevating and motivational effects sometimes reported, while adrenergic receptors may influence arousal and attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Mapping Psychedelic Signaling Pathways&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the more intriguing findings from the study was that psychedelics don’t merely turn receptors “on” or “off,” but rather engage them in unique ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using advanced techniques to measure how these drugs activated different intracellular signaling pathways, the researchers showed that psychedelics stimulate multiple transducers downstream of 5-HT2AR. These include pathways mediated by G proteins as well as β-arrestins—proteins that regulate receptor desensitization and signaling diversity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s more, the degree to which a psychedelic activated these different pathways correlated with its potency and behavioral effects in animal models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This points to the possibility that the therapeutic and hallucinogenic properties of psychedelics might be separable by targeting specific downstream pathways—an exciting prospect for developing “non-hallucinogenic” psychedelics that retain their antidepressant or anxiolytic effects without altering perception.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Why So Many Targets?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fact that psychedelics act on so many different receptors raises an important question: why? One possibility is that this broad activity contributes to their unique therapeutic potential.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mental health conditions such as depression and PTSD involve dysregulation of multiple neurotransmitter systems—serotonin, dopamine, norepinephrine—so a drug that can modulate all of them simultaneously may be more effective than one that targets only a single system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another intriguing idea is that the intricate receptor interactions contribute to the subjective experience of “ego dissolution” and enhanced emotional processing reported by many psychedelic users.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These experiences are thought to facilitate psychological healing by allowing individuals to confront traumatic memories or entrenched thought patterns from a new perspective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Toward Precision Psychedelic Medicine&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings from this research also underscore the need for a more nuanced understanding of how individual psychedelics differ. Although LSD, psilocybin, and mescaline all activate 5-HT2AR, their broader receptor profiles vary considerably, which may explain their differing durations, intensities, and therapeutic applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LSD, for example, is notably longer-lasting and more potent than psilocybin, which may stem from its strong binding to certain dopaminergic and adrenergic receptors in addition to 5-HT2AR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By mapping these pharmacological fingerprints, researchers can begin to tailor specific compounds to specific conditions—or even engineer novel psychedelics that maximize therapeutic benefits while minimizing side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This aligns with growing efforts to develop next-generation psychedelics that are more targeted, better tolerated, and easier to administer in clinical settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Road Ahead&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This landmark study provides a compelling reminder of just how complex the brain’s signaling networks are, and how much we still have to learn about how psychedelics interact with them. It also reinforces the idea that these compounds are not merely tools for altering consciousness, but also powerful probes for exploring the fundamental biology of the mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As clinical trials of psychedelics for depression, PTSD, and addiction continue to expand, understanding their molecular mechanisms will be key to unlocking their full potential.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By charting the diverse pathways through which they act, researchers are laying the foundation for a new era of precision psychedelic medicine—one that promises to transform how we treat some of the most challenging mental health conditions of our time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, one thing is clear: psychedelics are more than just serotonin agonists. They are intricate molecular keys, unlocking a symphony of neural receptors and pathways that together orchestrate the profound changes in mood, thought, and perception we are only beginning to comprehend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this psychopharmacology and neuroscience research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://neurosciencenews.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Neuroscience News Communications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://neurosciencenews.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Neuroscience News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Neuroscience News Communications – Neuroscience News&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Closed access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.neuron.2025.06.012" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;The polypharmacology of psychedelics reveals multiple targets for potential therapeutics&lt;/a&gt;” by Manish K. Jain et al. &lt;em&gt;Neuron&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The polypharmacology of psychedelics reveals multiple targets for potential therapeutics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The classical psychedelics (+)-lysergic acid diethylamide (LSD), psilocybin, and mescaline exert their psychedelic effects via activation of the 5-HT&lt;sub&gt;2A&lt;/sub&gt; serotonin receptor (5-HT&lt;sub&gt;2A&lt;/sub&gt;R).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent clinical studies have suggested that classical psychedelics may additionally have therapeutic potential for many neuropsychiatric conditions including depression, anxiety, migraine and cluster headaches, drug abuse, and post-traumatic stress disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this study, we investigated the pharmacology of 41 classical psychedelics from the tryptamine, phenethylamine, and lysergamide chemical classes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We profiled these compounds against 318 human G-protein-coupled receptors (GPCRs) to elucidate their target profiles, and in the case of LSD, against more than 450 human kinases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We found that psychedelics have potent and efficacious actions at nearly every serotonin, dopamine, and adrenergic receptor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We quantified their activation for multiple transducers and found that psychedelics stimulate multiple 5-HT&lt;sub&gt;2A&lt;/sub&gt;R transducers, each of which correlates with psychedelic drug-like actions &lt;em&gt;in vivo&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our results suggest that multiple molecular targets likely contribute to the actions of psychedelics.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 13:27:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTFBITzl4ckxsOXNXbDRYZzczWFJiSDJrWUhrMU02T0tUazZUMzF3LUczdEdMcDNxUnVTNTE3amU3dHhORlJtaVcxMDNyZC14VS1tcDlHN0owdWYzWUc1M1AwU0p0WG0zWXRSSDByLVlkNkk</guid></item><item><title>周六引用：像电视这样的狗； mRNA疫苗增强癌症治疗；旧韵不准确- Phys.org | Saturday Citations: Dogs like TV; mRNA vaccine enhances cancer therapy; old rhyme inaccurate - Phys.org</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMidEFVX3lxTFBfZHZUZVM0cm16cFJOWHBFdVJWTWRJV0VrTG9LUG9TMGpIb3R5SVduZ0xqbWdsU2Y4VkpDQkl2VUdSNnZ4YnByZ0RrYUhlNC15aVBRVGxmWERsT2hjZWRMa1drSFU1RXFzbm92N2V6RU9hZkQ50gFzQVVfeXFMTlVQZjA5WXVQeVdOVHFTWGRzeFQzZGQzR1RCT053NkNVeUpLY3JjZ25xY2xvVVNmVnRXZWZWUWZyOWNJOXI4anJNWUsyNk5hSDFIa20tNklqZXhsWDdXTGx3SFFFZk90VVRUd1RIdHZReS1DVQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
										
&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2025/saturday-citations-dog.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2025/saturday-citations-dog.jpg" data-sub-html="Credit: Unsplash/CC0 Public Domain"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2025/saturday-citations-dog.jpg" alt="Saturday Citations: Dogs like TV; mRNA vaccine enhances cancer therapy; old rhyme inaccurate" title="Credit: Unsplash/CC0 Public Domain"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-darken text-low-up text-truncate-js text-truncate mt-3"&gt;
                Credit: Unsplash/CC0 Public Domain
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week in science news: Researchers from the National Museum of Natural Sciences in Madrid, Spain, digitally reconstructed the ribcages of four prehistoric Homo sapiens and theorize that &lt;a href="https://phys.org/news/2025-07-links-human-ribcage-climate.html"&gt;climate influences ribcage evolution&lt;/a&gt;. A century after it was predicted, physicists have reported the &lt;a href="https://phys.org/news/2025-07-scientists-experimental-transverse-thomson-effect.html"&gt;first observation&lt;/a&gt; of the transverse Thompson effect, which causes volumetric heating or cooling when an electric current and a temperature gradient flow in the same direction through a conductor. And researchers found neotropical bats in Mexico &lt;a href="https://phys.org/news/2025-07-large-furry-creatures-mexico-forest.html"&gt;far beyond their known range&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;


										      
																																	&lt;p&gt;Additionally, researchers enhanced immunotherapeutic cancer treatment with an mRNA &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/vaccine/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;vaccine&lt;/a&gt;; researchers quantified dogs' interest in watching TV; and researchers in England debunked a venerable old nursery rhyme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;mRNA vaccine sensitizes tumors to immunotherapy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers at the University of Florida &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-pave-universal-cancer-vaccine.html" target="_blank"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; that an experimental mRNA vaccine in conjunction with immune checkpoint inhibitors boosted the immune systems of mice to attack tumor cells. The results of their study strongly suggest that a universal vaccine for cancer could be on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most current immunotherapy research seeks either to identify a common target expressed in people with cancer or to create custom vaccines tailored to specific targets in an individual's cancer. But the new study suggests a novel approach: The vaccine itself doesn't target any specific protein expressed in cancer cells. Instead, it makes tumors more sensitive to immunotherapy by stimulating the expression of a tumor protein called PD-L1, priming the immune system itself to respond as though it were fighting a virus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Senior author Elias Sayour says, "This paper describes a very unexpected and exciting observation: that even a vaccine not specific to any particular tumor or virus—so long as it is an mRNA vaccine—could lead to tumor-specific effects."&lt;/p&gt;

																																						&lt;p class="w-100 mb-4 ads"&gt;
    
     
&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="8188791252"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
																																			&lt;h2&gt;Dogs like TV, study finds&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So my personal anecdotal evidence for dogs' interest in TV is that during a Christmas holiday gathering, my family was watching "Scrooged" at my sisters house, and during the flashback scene where Bill Murray walks onscreen wearing a giant dog costume, my sister's two golden retrievers absolutely lost their freakin' minds, jumping around and yelling at the TV. In accordance with scientific practice, we were able to replicate those results by replaying the scene.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notably, these two goldens were low-anxiety, high-excitability guys—like pretty much every &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/golden+retriever/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;golden retriever&lt;/a&gt; I've ever met—and a &lt;a href="https://phys.org/news/2025-07-dogs-tv-viewing-habits-vary.html"&gt;new survey study&lt;/a&gt; about "trends in dogs' TV viewing habits" published in &lt;i&gt;Scientific Reports&lt;/i&gt; finds that high-excitability dogs are more likely to respond to onscreen animals while high-anxiety dogs are more alert to doorbells and cars on TV. The authors note that the participants were pet owners whose dogs regularly watched TV, so the study may not be representative of all dogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Wednesday's child just fine, actually&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's a mid-19th-century poem that attempts to predict outcomes for neonatal subjects based on temporal factors:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monday's child is fair of face,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tuesday's child is full of grace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wednesday's child is full of woe,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thursday's child has far to go.&lt;/p&gt;

																									&lt;div class="ads w-100 my-4 article-main__more bg-light p-3 border" aria-hidden="true"&gt;
    &lt;p class="mb-3"&gt;
        Discover the latest in science, tech, and space with over &lt;strong&gt;100,000 subscribers&lt;/strong&gt; who rely on Phys.org for daily insights.
        Sign up for our &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/help/newsletter/" target="_blank"&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; and get updates on breakthroughs,
        innovations, and research that matter—&lt;strong&gt;daily or weekly&lt;/strong&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;/div&gt;
																																			&lt;p&gt;Friday's child is loving and giving,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday's child works hard for a living.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the child that is born on Sabbath day,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is bonny and blithe, good and gay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-wednesday-child-full-woe-debunking.html" target="_blank"&gt;new study&lt;/a&gt; by researchers at the University of York debunks all of the poem's contentions, finding that plenty of churlish kids are born on Tuesday and children with reasonable commutes are also born on Thursday. The researchers analyzed data from a large study of over 1,000 families with twins, which tracked the children from ages five to 18. They tested the rhyme's predictive utility by looking for self-fulfilling prophecy effects, confirmation bias and parental influence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study found no connection between the day of week when the child was born and their outcomes. The family's socioeconomic background, the child's sex and their birth weight were much more predictive. But the point wasn't really to refute the poem, but rather to encourage parents to talk about messages their children encounter and offer reassurance.&lt;/p&gt;

																																	
																					&lt;div class="article-main__support"&gt;
												    &lt;p&gt;
    Written for you by our author &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/help/editorial-team/#authors" target="_blank"&gt;Chris Packham&lt;/a&gt;,
    edited by &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/help/editorial-team/" target="_blank"&gt;Gaby Clark&lt;/a&gt;, and fact-checked and reviewed by &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/help/editorial-team/" target="_blank"&gt;Andrew Zinin&lt;/a&gt;—this article is the result of careful human work. We rely on readers like you to keep independent science journalism alive.
    If this reporting matters to you,
    please consider a &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/donate/?utm_source=story&amp;amp;utm_medium=story&amp;amp;utm_campaign=story"&gt;donation&lt;/a&gt; (especially monthly).
    You'll get an &lt;b&gt;ad-free&lt;/b&gt; account as a thank-you.
    &lt;/p&gt;

											&lt;/div&gt;
																														
																				
                               														
																															 &lt;p class="article-main__note mt-4"&gt;
												  © 2025 Science X Network
											 &lt;/p&gt;
										                                        
										
										&lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
											 &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
												&lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
												Saturday Citations: Dogs like TV; mRNA vaccine enhances cancer therapy; old rhyme inaccurate (2025, July 19)
												retrieved 20 July 2025
												from https://phys.org/news/2025-07-saturday-citations-dogs-tv-mrna.html
											 &lt;/p&gt;
											 &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
											 This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
											 part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
											 &lt;/p&gt;
										&lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 13:00:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTFBfZHZUZVM0cm16cFJOWHBFdVJWTWRJV0VrTG9LUG9TMGpIb3R5SVduZ0xqbWdsU2Y4VkpDQkl2VUdSNnZ4YnByZ0RrYUhlNC15aVBRVGxmWERsT2hjZWRMa1drSFU1RXFzbm92N2V6RU9hZkQ50gFzQVVfeXFMTlVQZjA5WXVQeVdOVHFTWGRzeFQzZGQzR1RCT053NkNVeUpLY3JjZ25xY2xvVVNmVnRXZWZWUWZyOWNJOXI4anJNWUsyNk5hSDFIa20tNklqZXhsWDdXTGx3SFFFZk90VVRUd1RIdHZReS1DVQ</guid></item><item><title>为什么抗抑郁药对某些人更有效-神经科学新闻 | Why Antidepressants Work Better for Some - Neuroscience News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMidkFVX3lxTE1GU2RncW1meFJvbFNheklZazA3UnhMQ1JjYkU5Njd6ZzVpdFZMSi1vZHV4ZzFUaTdqUFJkTmtwLVprSDV5RDhrTXpvYllVRC13bEhNVllqVGhkaWc1SEdUMkZhR1ZNQ3NBWFk1eTBTdGxscnVZZFE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;A meta-analysis of gene expression data from humans and rodents reveals key biological pathways influencing response to the antidepressant fluoxetine. The study highlights the role of immune-related pathways, including toll-like receptor signaling, and neural signal transduction mechanisms in distinguishing responders from non-responders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Findings also show consistent changes in protein metabolism and GABAergic signaling after fluoxetine treatment, suggesting broader molecular effects. These results underscore the complexity of antidepressant response and point toward pathways that could guide future precision psychiatry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Immune Pathways:&lt;/strong&gt; Toll-like receptor and NF-κB pathways were consistently altered between responders and non-responders.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neural Mechanisms:&lt;/strong&gt; Signal transduction and GABAergic synapse pathways showed consistent changes with fluoxetine treatment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heterogeneity Noted:&lt;/strong&gt; Patterns of gene expression varied across tissues, models, and individuals, emphasizing the need for larger, more targeted studies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why do some people respond well to antidepressants while others do not? This question has long puzzled clinicians and scientists alike. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major depressive disorder (MDD) remains a leading cause of disability worldwide, yet nearly half of patients fail to achieve remission with their first prescribed antidepressant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding what drives response — or resistance — is critical to improving treatments for millions who struggle with depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-111775"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc.jpg" alt="This shows a brain and DNA." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/genetics-SSRIs-neuroscienc-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Immune signaling and neuroplasticity emerge as central nodes in this network. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new systematic meta-analysis brings fresh insight into the biological underpinnings of fluoxetine (Prozac) treatment, synthesizing gene expression data from both human patients and rodent models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By analyzing patterns across dozens of studies, the research identifies immune pathways, particularly toll-like receptor (TLR) signaling, and signal transduction networks as consistently involved in fluoxetine response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also highlights distinct molecular signatures of treatment and sheds light on the biological heterogeneity underlying antidepressant efficacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A Complex Puzzle: Why Study Gene Expression?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although selective serotonin reuptake inhibitors (SSRIs) like fluoxetine have been prescribed for decades, their precise mechanisms of action remain incompletely understood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Antidepressants are thought to modulate neurotransmitter systems and neuroplasticity, but emerging evidence implicates broader processes such as inflammation and cellular signaling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genomic and transcriptomic (“omics”) technologies have allowed researchers to probe gene-level changes associated with antidepressant treatment. However, individual studies are often inconsistent, reflecting differences in methodology, sample types, and biological variability. Meta-analysis — a statistical method for combining results across studies — offers a powerful way to identify shared patterns and separate signal from noise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this study, researchers followed PRISMA guidelines to systematically search the Gene Expression Omnibus (GEO) database for gene expression studies of fluoxetine treatment. They included both human and rodent studies examining depression- or anxiety-related contexts, then applied a unified analytical pipeline to reanalyze and synthesize the data at both gene and pathway levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What They Found: Pathways That Matter&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team screened 74 datasets and ultimately analyzed 20 — two in humans and 18 in rodent models — spanning brain and peripheral tissues. Studies varied widely in size, design, and stress paradigms. While heterogeneity was evident, the meta-analyses revealed robust trends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across six datasets examining responders versus non-responders to fluoxetine, 18 biological pathways were consistently enriched in good responders. Among the most prominent were immune pathways, including TLR signaling, NF-κB activation, and downstream cascades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toll-like receptors, expressed in microglia and other glial cells, trigger inflammatory cytokine release. Intriguingly, these immune pathways were upregulated in blood-derived tissues from non-responders but modestly elevated in brain tissues of responders — a finding that suggests peripheral and central immune responses may diverge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another key finding was the consistent involvement of protein metabolism pathways — notably ribosomal subunit pathways — in non-responders. Ribosomal proteins have been previously linked to antidepressant resistance and immune regulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When examining treatment effects (fluoxetine vs. control), the researchers found 17 pathways consistently altered. GPCR (G-protein coupled receptor) signaling and GABAergic synapse pathways were among those most consistently downregulated, while signal transduction and neurotrophic factors like BDNF were upregulated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, when focusing on stressed rodent models and MDD patients — arguably closer to the clinical scenario — even more pathways emerged, particularly those involved in immune signaling and neurotrophic regulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Why Immune Pathways?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consistent appearance of immune-related pathways adds to mounting evidence that inflammation plays a central role in depression and its treatment. Elevated pro-inflammatory cytokines have been observed in subsets of patients with MDD, and anti-inflammatory agents have shown some efficacy in treatment-resistant depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TLR signaling, in particular, has been implicated in stress-induced neuroinflammation and depressive-like behaviors in rodents. Inhibiting TLR2 and TLR4 in animal models reduces neuroinflammation and improves behavior, suggesting that excessive TLR activation may contribute to treatment resistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The apparent discrepancy between immune pathway directionality in blood and brain samples underscores the complexity of the immune system in depression. While blood-based markers may serve as accessible biomarkers, they may not fully reflect central nervous system processes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Signal Transduction and Neuroplasticity&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond the immune system, the study reinforces the importance of signal transduction and neuroplasticity pathways in antidepressant response. Fluoxetine has been shown to enhance BDNF expression and neurogenesis in the hippocampus, effects thought to underlie some of its therapeutic benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consistent downregulation of GABAergic signaling in treatment suggests a shift in excitatory-inhibitory balance that may also facilitate neuroplastic changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Strengths, Limitations, and the Road Ahead&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is one of the first systematic meta-analyses to examine both treatment and response signatures to an antidepressant across multiple species, tissues, and study designs. By applying consistent reanalysis and pathway-level synthesis, the researchers overcame many of the inconsistencies plaguing prior studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, limitations remain. Only two included datasets were in humans, both small and female-biased, while rodent studies were almost exclusively in males. Larger, sex-balanced human cohorts are needed to validate and refine these findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, the heterogeneity between blood and brain results, and the modest agreement even in consistent pathways, underscore the complexity of antidepressant biology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Toward Precision Psychiatry&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings support the notion that antidepressant response is not determined by a single gene or pathway but by a network of interacting biological processes. Immune signaling and neuroplasticity emerge as central nodes in this network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research could leverage these insights to develop better predictive biomarkers of response, potentially through blood-based tests that reflect central processes. Understanding how stress, inflammation, and neurotrophic signaling interact could also lead to novel combination therapies targeting both neurotransmitter systems and immune pathways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Depression is a multifaceted disorder, and antidepressant response is equally complex. This meta-analysis moves the field closer to understanding the molecular underpinnings of fluoxetine treatment and response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By highlighting immune and signal transduction pathways, it provides a roadmap for future investigations — and a glimmer of hope that more personalized, effective treatments may soon be within reach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this genetics and psychopharmacology research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://neurosciencenews.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Neuroscience News Communications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://neurosciencenews.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Neuroscience News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Neuroscience News Communications – Neuroscience News&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41380-025-03118-6" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Gene expression signatures of response to fluoxetine treatment: systematic review and meta-analyses&lt;/a&gt;” by David G. Cooper et al. &lt;em&gt;Molecular Psychiatry&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gene expression signatures of response to fluoxetine treatment: systematic review and meta-analyses&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Background&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genomic (and other ‘omic) data have provided valuable insights on the pharmacological signatures of antidepressant response, but results from individual studies are largely heterogeneous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this work, we synthesized gene expression data for fluoxetine treatment in both human patients and rodent models, to better understand biological pathways affected by treatment, as well as those that may distinguish clinical or behavioral response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Methods&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following the PRISMA guidelines, we searched the Gene Expression Omnibus (GEO) for studies profiling humans or rodent models with treatment of the antidepressant fluoxetine, excluding those not done in the context of depression or anxiety, in an irrelevant tissue type, or with fewer than three samples per group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Included studies were systematically reanalyzed by differential expression analysis and Gene Set Enrichment Analysis (GSEA). Individual pathway and gene statistics were synthesized across studies by three p-value combination methods, and then corrected for false discovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Results&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of the 74 data sets that were screened, 20 were included: 18 in rodents, and two in tissue from human patients. Studies were highly heterogeneous in the comparisons of both treated vs. control samples and responders vs. non-responders, with 691 and 357 pathways, respectively, identified as significantly different between groups in at least one study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, 18 pathways were identified as consistently different in responders vs. non-responders, including toll-like receptor (TLR) and other immune pathways. Signal transduction pathways were identified as consistently affected by fluoxetine treatment in depressed patients and rodent models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Discussion&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;These meta-analyses confirm known pathways and provide new hints toward antidepressant resistance, but more work is needed. Most included studies involved rodent models, and both patient studies had small cohorts. Additional large-cohort studies applying additional ‘omics technologies are necessary to understand the intricacies and heterogeneity of antidepressant response.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 12:48:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE1GU2RncW1meFJvbFNheklZazA3UnhMQ1JjYkU5Njd6ZzVpdFZMSi1vZHV4ZzFUaTdqUFJkTmtwLVprSDV5RDhrTXpvYllVRC13bEhNVllqVGhkaWc1SEdUMkZhR1ZNQ3NBWFk1eTBTdGxscnVZZFE</guid></item><item><title>我的四肢因常见感染而被截肢，每年影响1500万女性-每日邮报 | My limbs were amputated because of a common infection that affects 15 million women each year - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivwFBVV95cUxNZlpMZWREQkJFOHZ5MWtoU1VNbFJnSUJ0V2VrZ3VyZ1NrWU5LMGcxdFYzcm1DNlAxMzhXREZ0TkF5VVI2b0liOEprRFphLW5BSWd5QnltdTdvS0JDbllfN290N1JuR25qNE9wWV93ZVptU2g1RzlBLWNmNFMxdlFydFNYcldHZ3F2d2lIZVliZ1JERVFtU3c0TDNjOENLMWdBNE8tajFIc1pBUVhxQzZuVkZwcERlR0VXUkpBM2xFQdIBxAFBVV95cUxOeVZ3MklOWHhEeTJrSmt3QlVDbVJSWnU1Zlo3X21KM2pIdTdzbGh4UmFyUHhNbGNER0pKV24teTY5TnBDbElqUVZUTk43a1R0cUd3TzJZenllV0sycnV2SkJNNktGTFVqY1NyUGZTWlMyQ3BqYWpwOGtRZTZyMjZjYjJ2cHZMU0ZXeDgxQ1NmbkVVeFpQRDJ4X1ZMVjh3NUMzU2dWdFQ0UGpZOUNLaHhGRExYM09ETkhmTnVkaE91S0t0alhr?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A British woman nearly died after contracting an infection that strikes at least 15 million American women annually, leaving her a quadruple amputee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Kim Smith is now &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14842203/Terrified-mom-wakes-limbs-amputated-catching-two-common-infections-time.html"&gt;a quadruple amputee&lt;/a&gt;, having lost both her hands at the wrists and her legs above the knee after a &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/uti/index.html" id="mol-04e6b3b0-641e-11f0-970a-09a9b27031ec"&gt;urinary tract infection&lt;/a&gt; went untreated for too long, morphing into life-threatening &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/sepsis/index.html" id="mol-04e5c950-641e-11f0-970a-09a9b27031ec"&gt;sepsis&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;UTIs are exceedingly common. Around 15 million American women get one every year and more than half of women and about 12 percent of men will experience at least one episode in their lifetime. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Smith has had bladder issues for years, she said, and UTIs were not uncommon for her. They are the result of bacteria entering the urinary tract through the urethra and beginning to spread in the bladder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Poor hygiene, sexual activity, or even just the anatomy of the urinary tract can give bacteria an easy entry point. Once inside, these microbes attach to the bladder lining, triggering inflammation and the familiar symptoms, including a relentless urge to urinate, burning discomfort, and sometimes cloudy or bloody urine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Left unchecked, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14797205/UTI-amputated-limbs.html"&gt;the infection can&lt;/a&gt; climb toward the kidneys, turning a mild to moderate pain into a serious health threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Smith noticed pain in her lower back while on vacation with her husband. She suspected a UTI was coming, but tried to enjoy her vacation until she woke up one night in agonizing pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At the hospital, Smith was placed in a medically-induced coma as a runaway immune response to a standard UTI spiraled into catastrophic damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Kim Smith is now a quadruple amputee after a urinary tract infection went untreated for too long and she developed sepsis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Smith and her husband had sought medical care &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.justgiving.com/crowdfunding/kim-smith-520?utm_medium=CR&amp;amp;utm_source=CL"&gt;in early 2018&lt;/a&gt; before her body devolved into septic shock. According to Smith, they were turned away by the doctors but given a prescription for antibiotics that the local pharmacy was not able to fill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The following night, she awoke in pain and struggled to breathe. Her speech was slurred, and she was out of sorts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As inflammatory chemicals flood the bloodstream, they damage the delicate blood vessels in the lungs, causing fluid to leak into the air sacs, which causes a condition called acute respiratory distress syndrome (ARDS).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This drowns the lungs from within, stiffening them like waterlogged sponges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At the same time, plummeting blood pressure (septic shock) starves tissues of oxygen, while muscle weakness from acidosis and organ failure makes the physical act of breathing more difficult.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sepsis also plunges the brain into a state of chaos, causing confusion and speech difficulties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A storm of inflammatory chemicals can disrupt signaling between brain cells, while liver or kidney failure allows toxins like ammonia to build up, further clouding cognition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Even when oxygen reaches cells, toxins and mitochondrial dysfunction prevent them from using it. As tissues suffocate, organs fail in a domino effect, starting with the kidneys, then the lungs, which fill with fluid, and then the limbs, which can turn black from gangrene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;When Smith was airlifted back to the UK, her limbs had turned black from the lack of oxygenated blood, forcing doctors to amputate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Without immediate medical attention, widespread oxygen deprivation leads to irreversible damage. Nearly half of septic shock patients progress to multi-organ failure, where survival odds plummet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When Smith was airlifted back to the UK, her limbs had turned black from the lack of oxygenated blood, forcing doctors to amputate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘How I survived, I do not know. It’s a miracle, but I think it’s so that I can warn you and save your life,’ she &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/@kims2dchance/video/7525781719782296854"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;More than one million patients are hospitalized for sepsis each year, surpassing even heart attack and stroke combined in hospitalization rates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Those with chronic illnesses, including cancer, kidney disease, or neurological disorders, face especially high risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Between one in eight and one in four patients with sepsis will die during hospitalization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I’m here to warn you that if you’ve got any infection at all, don’t think it won’t happen to you because I was fit and healthy and it happened to me. And it could be you. Watch out for symptoms of sepsis,’ Smith said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 12:37:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxNZlpMZWREQkJFOHZ5MWtoU1VNbFJnSUJ0V2VrZ3VyZ1NrWU5LMGcxdFYzcm1DNlAxMzhXREZ0TkF5VVI2b0liOEprRFphLW5BSWd5QnltdTdvS0JDbllfN290N1JuR25qNE9wWV93ZVptU2g1RzlBLWNmNFMxdlFydFNYcldHZ3F2d2lIZVliZ1JERVFtU3c0TDNjOENLMWdBNE8tajFIc1pBUVhxQzZuVkZwcERlR0VXUkpBM2xFQdIBxAFBVV95cUxOeVZ3MklOWHhEeTJrSmt3QlVDbVJSWnU1Zlo3X21KM2pIdTdzbGh4UmFyUHhNbGNER0pKV24teTY5TnBDbElqUVZUTk43a1R0cUd3TzJZenllV0sycnV2SkJNNktGTFVqY1NyUGZTWlMyQ3BqYWpwOGtRZTZyMjZjYjJ2cHZMU0ZXeDgxQ1NmbkVVeFpQRDJ4X1ZMVjh3NUMzU2dWdFQ0UGpZOUNLaHhGRExYM09ETkhmTnVkaE91S0t0alhr</guid></item><item><title>不要忽视这些40多岁、50多岁和60多岁的心脏警告标志-印度时报 | Don’t ignore these heart warning signs in your 40s, 50s, and 60s - The Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi8wFBVV95cUxPdE9kTE1LU181MUE4ME5CR3NBNWFwWFVNM2NxaG1FS2xYZTMwT18yNVdjTS0xMENLSDFEcmxjS0dRQmQxZ1UyMnRnRzdHQkZrSS1leWRtZ3BRLWhwaEIwSEFHMnBBTUV4MkhncVZWcGJhMDdraWcyVWJULWE2SWlIZVVIVVNiM1hBUEphLUR1Sk5PVm5zOFFjX0pVUmRHZ1FXbTlLUG5MU0lNbWNweERvR2o5N2lzTVdjZ0k0WGZiZTd0VzRnb19jT0ZYNGplRm80ZTN1bVRrakYxR2pHVXZqaXpONUEzYWExQWdtUDY1TExubjQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart attacks are no longer just a concern for seniors. New research reveals that heart disease is hitting younger adults, especially women, harder than ever. With a 66% rise in heart attacks among adults aged 18 to 44, it's critical to recognise early warning signs of heart trouble. Experts say lifestyle habits, rising obesity, and even past COVID infections are driving this surge. If you're in your 40s, 50s, or 60s, now is the time to take charge of your heart health and prevent a silent crisis. Here’s what you need to know and how to protect yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart disease is often considered a concern for older adults, but new findings show a troubling trend: heart attacks are on the rise among younger adults, particularly women. In an interview with &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cedars-sinai.org/newsroom/yahoo-life-heart-attacks-in-young-people-are-rarebut-rates-are-rising" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Yahoo! Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, Dr. C. Noel Bairey Merz, director of the Barbra Streisand Women’s Heart Center at Cedars-Sinai's Smidt Heart Institute, shared her insights into this alarming development. She pointed out that while heart attacks among adults aged 18 to 44 are still relatively rare, their incidence has jumped by over 66% since 2019. Meanwhile, heart attack rates have decreased in other adult age groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Apollo Hospitals, it is true that increasing age is a risk factor, and heart attacks are more common after 45 in men and after 55 in women, with risk increasing as one grows older. A heart attack is far from rare in the younger age group of 30 to 40 years. Coronary Artery Disease (CAD) occurs at a younger age in Indians, with over 50% of CAD mortality occurring in individuals aged less than 50 years. Prevalence of acute MI (heart attack) as high as 25 to 40% has been reported in the young, that is,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; patients below 40 years of age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Warning signs behind the sudden rise in heart attacks&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obesity is rising, and it’s hitting young adults hard. Obesity is a growing issue in all age groups, but younger adults seem to be feeling the effects on their heart health more than older generations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.genmed.columbia.edu/profile/andrew-e-moran-md#research" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Dr. Andrew Moran&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, a preventive cardiologist and epidemiologist at Columbia University, told Yahoo Life that the rise in obesity is happening faster in people under 50 than in older adults. One reason may be that eating habits often form early in life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. C. Noel Bairey Merz, a cardiologist at Cedars-Sinai, explained to Yahoo Life that she still eats the way she did growing up, before the fast food boom. In contrast, today’s younger adults were raised on fast food, sugary drinks, and processed snacks like Doritos and snack bars. Many continue those habits into adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;These poor diets, combined with more sedentary lifestyles, have contributed to what Bairey Merz calls the “diabesity” epidemic—a dangerous combination of obesity and diabetes. Both of these conditions raise the risk of high blood pressure, heart disease, and heart attacks because they damage blood vessels and put extra strain on the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;COVID-19 may have worsened heart health&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;COVID-19 doesn’t just affect the lungs; it can also harm the heart. The virus can cause heart inflammation (myocarditis) and other cardiovascular issues, even in younger people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Moran noted to Yahoo Life that many young adults who had serious cases of COVID also had other risk factors like obesity. One study found a 30% rise in heart attack deaths among people ages 25 to 44 during the first two years of the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even after recovering from COVID, around 4 out of every 100 people in the U.S. experience heart-related symptoms within a year. Dr. Ashish Sarraju from the Cleveland Clinic added that while traditional risks like obesity and high blood pressure matter, the impact of COVID on heart health is something doctors are still studying closely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Young men often don’t get heart screenings&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Men are generally more likely than women to have heart attacks. But younger men may be even more at risk because many don’t regularly visit the doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Moran explained that young women are more likely to see a doctor each year for gynaecological checkups, but young men often miss these routine visits. As a result, many men don’t realise they have high blood pressure or diabetes until they end up in the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Unique heart risks facing younger women&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart attack rates are increasing fastest among women ages 35 to 54. Between 1995 and 2014, hospitalisations for heart attacks in this group jumped from 21% to 31%, according to one study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Bairey Merz told Yahoo Life she’s trying to understand why, and several factors may be playing a role:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diabesity&lt;/strong&gt;: Diabetes is a stronger risk factor for heart disease in women than in men, though it’s not clear why.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smoking and vaping&lt;/strong&gt;: Many young women start smoking or vaping in college, often to manage their weight. Bairey Merz warns that e-cigarettes and cannabis are just as harmful to the heart as regular cigarettes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stress and hormonal changes&lt;/strong&gt;: High stress levels—often made worse by social media—can disrupt menstrual cycles. Missing periods can lower estrogen levels, which may increase heart disease risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What you can do to protect your heart&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though the warnings are constant, you can do some damage control and restore the health of your heart, or in other words, you can take steps now to reduce your risk of heart disease and heart attacks. Here’s what professionals suggest:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eat more fresh foods&lt;/strong&gt;: Dr. Moran recommends eating more fruits and vegetables and cutting back on packaged and processed foods. This helps lower your sodium intake, which is important for your heart health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be physically active: &lt;/strong&gt;Try to stay active most days of the week, even if it’s just a walk. Consuming healthy food and doing physical exercise help you to maintain a healthy weight and reduce the chances of developing high blood pressure. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t smoke or vape: &lt;/strong&gt;Avoid all tobacco and cannabis products; they can all harm your heart.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manage stress: &lt;/strong&gt;Pay attention to your mental health, especially if you feel overwhelmed or anxious.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 12:36:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi8wFBVV95cUxPdE9kTE1LU181MUE4ME5CR3NBNWFwWFVNM2NxaG1FS2xYZTMwT18yNVdjTS0xMENLSDFEcmxjS0dRQmQxZ1UyMnRnRzdHQkZrSS1leWRtZ3BRLWhwaEIwSEFHMnBBTUV4MkhncVZWcGJhMDdraWcyVWJULWE2SWlIZVVIVVNiM1hBUEphLUR1Sk5PVm5zOFFjX0pVUmRHZ1FXbTlLUG5MU0lNbWNweERvR2o5N2lzTVdjZ0k0WGZiZTd0VzRnb19jT0ZYNGplRm80ZTN1bVRrakYxR2pHVXZqaXpONUEzYWExQWdtUDY1TExubjQ</guid></item><item><title>新研究揭示了增加心脏病风险的单一饮食因素： “我们的研究结果加强了重要性” - yahoo.com | New study reveals single dietary factor that increases risk for heart disease: 'Our findings strengthen the importance' - yahoo.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigwFBVV95cUxQV1dqbi10Z2NXa2dqLWctdDJmYVI4M1dXRWpJbWpWWkJISXh3T253MjNkSURtY0NnU3Q4OEEwSHdnNC1LSUhiSzZpQkoxNXJ4ZTRqWmxlU2tTbU5FSDF6MjVPN0ozMS1ZREU5dTJWNWtNVFF5ZWc4TzZ6WVpwd2htdGFTRQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;An international &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/cardiovascres/advance-article/doi/10.1093/cvr/cvaf088/8162637?login=false" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; found that diets low in fiber may contribute to a higher risk of heart attacks, offering another reason to eat more plants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Researchers analyzed heart scans from nearly 1,400 people across Europe and Australia and discovered a clear link between low fiber intake and the buildup of dangerous plaques in the arteries. These plaques were more likely to rupture and lead to serious cardiac events. The study was &lt;a href="https://www.news-medical.net/news/20250618/Heart-scan-study-reveals-low-fiber-diets-drive-dangerous-heart-plaques.aspx" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:published;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in the journal Cardiovascular Research and focused on people with existing coronary artery disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Our findings strengthen the importance of cardioprotective dietary recommendations," the researchers noted in the study's conclusion. The benefits of fiber were consistent even among those already taking heart medications or cholesterol-lowering drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While fiber has long been associated with improved digestion, reduced inflammation, and better blood sugar control, this study is among the first to directly connect fiber intake to the makeup of arterial plaques. Specifically, people who ate less fiber were more likely to have lipid-rich plaques, which are softer and more prone to rupture than fibrous or calcified plaques. That rupture risk can trigger heart attacks, even in people already on medication, making fiber an important yet often overlooked part of long-term heart care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A 2025 &lt;a href="https://www.acc.org/About-ACC/Press-Releases/2025/03/17/15/35/Healthy-Plant-Based-Foods-Could-Help-People" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:report;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; from the American College of Cardiology linked plant-based eating patterns to a reduced risk of heart disease and stroke, indicating that other researchers have come to similar conclusions. And a long-term &lt;a href="https://hsph.harvard.edu/news/substituting-healthy-plant-proteins-for-red-meat-lowers-risk-for-heart-disease/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; from the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health found that replacing red meat with legumes, nuts, or whole grains significantly lowered the risk of heart-related death, especially in younger adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There are several health benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/1422-0067/26/5/2000" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Fiber-rich diets;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Fiber-rich diets&lt;/a&gt; are tied to reduced inflammation, improved cholesterol control, and more stable blood sugar, all of which can help prevent artery damage over time. Heart-healthy eating patterns such as the Mediterranean and DASH diets emphasize whole grains, vegetables, and legumes not only for weight control but also because they support long-term cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;These findings align with other recent research that shows how dietary changes, even small ones, can lower the risk of chronic illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/hacks-newsletter/?recAL5sHV6ul6uvXx" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for easy tips to &lt;strong&gt;save more&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;waste less&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>yahoo.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 11:15:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQV1dqbi10Z2NXa2dqLWctdDJmYVI4M1dXRWpJbWpWWkJISXh3T253MjNkSURtY0NnU3Q4OEEwSHdnNC1LSUhiSzZpQkoxNXJ4ZTRqWmxlU2tTbU5FSDF6MjVPN0ozMS1ZREU5dTJWNWtNVFF5ZWc4TzZ6WVpwd2htdGFTRQ</guid></item><item><title>医生正在重新考虑减肥建议。这就是旧规则不再起作用的原因-以及什么起作用-女性健康 | Doctors Are Rethinking Weight Loss Advice. Here's Why The Old Rules Don't Work Anymore—And What Does - Women's Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijAFBVV95cUxPMHYxT2RXWENSUENNS1BLVFZBMkpDUzZ3WmtGMWxZdkRuVThCNmN5YUQ4dVFJd1VZZzVsSVlVOTJUSmxxRmh4WG1BdE1sUFFqMHVabENySG5TdFc1TFNyX0JxQlREOThDSy03TGhRaVQ1WGltc3ZpWG1NbTFQckc0cGltZ2Y2ZlFtXzhIcQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-journey-body="standard-article" class="article-body-content article-body standard-body-content css-zl6cs0 et2g3wt6"&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="0" class="css-1wk73g0 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.0"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.0.0"&gt;A new scientific analysis takes a close look at effective weight loss strategies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.1"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.1.0"&gt;The findings suggest that simply being told to lose weight may not be the best thing for some people's weight loss goals.&lt;br data-node-id="0.1.0.1"&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.2"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.2.0"&gt;Here's what doctors say can *actually* help when older tactics fail.&lt;br data-node-id="0.2.0.1"&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr data-node-id="1" class="css-18pb4rg emevuu60"&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="2" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Recceiving the same old blanket advice from your doctor about &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a62963725/counting-macros-hiit-barbell-success/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a62963725/counting-macros-hiit-barbell-success/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="tweaking your diet " data-node-id="2.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;tweaking your diet &lt;/a&gt;and &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/fitness/a64218691/mom-lifting-heavy-increasing-protein-intake-strength-transformation/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/fitness/a64218691/mom-lifting-heavy-increasing-protein-intake-strength-transformation/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="moving more " data-node-id="2.3" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;moving more &lt;/a&gt;if you want to lose weigh can be pretty infuriating, especially if those maxims haven't worked for you in the past. After all, weight is complicated—and most of us are already well aware of these principles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="3" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Enter: A new scientific analysis published in &lt;em data-node-id="3.1"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/389/bmj-2025-084654" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.bmj.com/content/389/bmj-2025-084654" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="BMJ" data-node-id="3.1.0" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;BMJ&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;that breaks down the importance of personalized weight loss strategies, arguing that these old school insights have the ability to help patients reach their weight goals—or make things worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="4" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;In some situations, simply being told you need to &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a64866768/how-alcohol-affects-weight-loss/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a64866768/how-alcohol-affects-weight-loss/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="lose weight" data-node-id="4.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;lose weight&lt;/a&gt; may not actually be the healthiest path forward, the researchers argue. The paper raises some red flags in the way weight loss is typically approached at the doctor’s office right now, and urges healthcare providers to make a change. Here’s why that is, and what you should know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="6" class="body-tip css-18qyn7q emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="6.0"&gt;Meet the experts&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/mir-b-ali" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/mir-b-ali" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Mir Ali" data-node-id="6.2" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Mir Ali&lt;/a&gt;, MD, medical director of MemorialCare Surgical Weight Loss Center at Orange Coast Medical Center in Fountain Valley, CA; &lt;a href="https://www.uniklinik-duesseldorf.de/en/institute-of-general-practice/cochrane-metabolic-and-endocrine-disorders-group" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.uniklinik-duesseldorf.de/en/institute-of-general-practice/cochrane-metabolic-and-endocrine-disorders-group" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Juan Victor Ariel Franco" data-node-id="6.4" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Juan Victor Ariel Franco&lt;/a&gt;, MD, lead study author and researcher at Heinrich Heine University Düsseldorf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-did-the-study-find" data-node-id="7" class="body-h2 css-1eo7s1x emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="7.0"&gt;What did the study find?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="8" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;The analysis looked at several previous studies on weight loss and weight loss interventions. The researchers found that while doctors usually recommend lifestyle changes to &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a46539898/1200-calorie-diet-plan/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a46539898/1200-calorie-diet-plan/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="restrict calories" data-node-id="8.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;restrict calories&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/fitness/g64814478/epoc-afterburn-explained/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/fitness/g64814478/epoc-afterburn-explained/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="exercise more" data-node-id="8.3" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;exercise more&lt;/a&gt;, these moves don’t always help with &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a65157747/healthy-eating-metabolism-weight-loss-study/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a65157747/healthy-eating-metabolism-weight-loss-study/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="sustained weight loss" data-node-id="8.5" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;sustained weight loss&lt;/a&gt; or lower a person’s risk of cardiovascular issues or death. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="9" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Current recommendations can also lead to weight loss stigma, points out &lt;a href="https://www.uniklinik-duesseldorf.de/en/institute-of-general-practice/cochrane-metabolic-and-endocrine-disorders-group" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.uniklinik-duesseldorf.de/en/institute-of-general-practice/cochrane-metabolic-and-endocrine-disorders-group" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Juan Victor Ariel Franco" data-node-id="9.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Juan Victor Ariel Franco&lt;/a&gt;, MD, lead study author and researcher at Heinrich Heine University Düsseldorf. “When people with obesity or different types of bodies receive this advice, pursue it, and don’t get the results they expect, it generates a lot of frustration and could make them feel bad about themselves. People with higher weight have already tried several times in their life to lose weight,” he points out. “They have the expectation that following the doctor’s advice will lead to better outcomes, but that can lead to more frustration and self-esteem issues when it doesn’t.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="why-is-weight-loss-not-always-healthy-for-someone" data-node-id="11" class="body-h2 css-1eo7s1x emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="11.0"&gt;Why is weight loss not always “healthy” for someone?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="12" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;After being told by a doctor to lose weight, some people may be driven to diet or exercise in a way that’s not healthy, Dr. Franco says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="13" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;These folks may also get frustrated if their doctor tells them that tweaking their diet or exercising more will lead to weight loss—especially when it doesn’t happen or the results aren’t sustained, says &lt;a href="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/mir-b-ali" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/mir-b-ali" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Mir Ali" data-node-id="13.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Mir Ali&lt;/a&gt;, MD, medical director of MemorialCare Surgical Weight Loss Center at Orange Coast Medical Center in Fountain Valley, CA. “When you reach a certain weight, your body becomes resistant to losing more weight,” Dr. Ali says. “I’ve seen patients get frustrated and say, ‘I’m only eating this much and I’m not losing weight. I’m trying to exercise.’ We tell patients that it’s not just about self-control. There are metabolic and hormonal changes that impact weight, too.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="14" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;And of course, Dr. Franco points out that a person’s weight doesn’t always correlate to how healthy they are. Ultimately, Dr. Franco and his fellow researchers concluded in the paper that “acknowledging that weight alone might not give an adequate picture of someone’s health, and recognizing the limitations of lifestyle interventions for weight loss, could pave the way for more effective and patient centered care.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-are-the-most-sustainable-ways-for-higher-weight-people-to-maintain-weight-loss" data-node-id="16" class="body-h2 css-1eo7s1x emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="16.0"&gt;What are the most sustainable ways for higher weight people to maintain weight loss?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="17" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;If you have excess weight and haven’t been able to lose it on your own, experts say it’s a good idea to talk to a doctor to get some personalized advice. “It’s very important that people try to pursue a healthy lifestyle that works for them,” Dr. Franco says. “People have different needs, and person-centric care is important.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="18" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Dr. Franco says it’s also crucial for doctors to talk about why someone may benefit from weight loss from a total-body health perspective vs. just giving blanket advice to lose weight. “For patients, it’s important to find the right motivation,” Dr. Franco says. That may mean knowing that weight loss could impact your heart health or even that you’ll be able to be more mobile after losing weight, he says.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="19" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;And Dr. Ali says patients shouldn’t get discouraged if they want to lose weight and haven’t been successful in the past. “By the time patients see me, they have tried all kinds of things and they’re having no success. That’s where we have to decide on what is the best intervention we can use,” he says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="20" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;At the end of the day, it’s crucial to frame weight and health in the context of your goals, per Dr. Franco. “If you want to be more active and agile, that might result in weight loss,” he says. “But, in the end, it’s not just about what you see in the mirror. It’s how you feel about your body. Even if you don’t lose weight but you engage in physical activity, you can still feel better about yourself.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-journey-blur="partial" data-ad-exclude="true" class="css-19m4yzp e1jy25xv0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-sfzxfp ev8dhu59"&gt;&lt;span class="css-3mrz81 ev8dhu51"&gt;&lt;img src="https://hips.hearstapps.com/rover/profile_photos/ea27d1a6-ecd9-4da8-b2a7-049a03b4ab93_1528214135.file?fill=1:1&amp;amp;resize=120:*" alt="Headshot of Korin Miller" title="Headshot of Korin Miller" decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="css-o0wq4v ev8dhu53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="css-1dsojn8 ev8dhu55"&gt;&lt;p class="css-1y37fga ev8dhu54"&gt;Korin Miller is a freelance writer specializing in general wellness, sexual health and relationships, and lifestyle trends, with work appearing in Men’s Health, Women’s Health, Self, Glamour, and more. She has a master’s degree from American University, lives by the beach, and hopes to own a teacup pig and taco truck one day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-ad-exclude="true" id="journey-inline" class="css-ciejky e1ye6jr30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Women's Health</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxPMHYxT2RXWENSUENNS1BLVFZBMkpDUzZ3WmtGMWxZdkRuVThCNmN5YUQ4dVFJd1VZZzVsSVlVOTJUSmxxRmh4WG1BdE1sUFFqMHVabENySG5TdFc1TFNyX0JxQlREOThDSy03TGhRaVQ1WGltc3ZpWG1NbTFQckc0cGltZ2Y2ZlFtXzhIcQ</guid></item><item><title>吃乳制品是我睡前问题的原因吗？ Dr ELLIE -每日邮报 | Is eating dairy the cause of my bedtime problems? DR ELLIE - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi5AFBVV95cUxNaWpfT2ZyTmRTS2NTSWQ4dHpLZlNXNENjbkZOZnNIMHdqMlJKMEdXNUFKcXkyVTJCUjI3Nm1xSl9CR1Fxc2dGOXY2WDFfMTRBZlRETUkzaW53LVdOX2JXS0hDQmdLWlVteE9Gbi1jaFBqRlFyZnZMbXRoUVRjUWo4cHk0ZHVYUGlCZnhNdmRKaGh2QkVmRlBIN0RnSU9nNkpsaFA1OGdqbGZjMzd2TEtwV2xBNm14RnFTU1RzRHVqNFppYmU0dDFpdXZLbEQ5SkdibXJsaWtUUUJaZ1dXMVVXa0dTZ0Q?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-bold mol-style-italic"&gt;I suffer from nightmares that wake me up. I read that they can be caused by a dairy intolerance, but I don’t have any other symptoms. Do you think this might be what’s behind them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Dr Ellie Cannon replies:&lt;/span&gt; Some research suggests lactose intolerance, where the body has trouble breaking down dairy, can increase the frequency and severity of bad dreams, but this isn’t common enough for them to be considered a symptom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Instead, most people with lactose intolerance experience bloating, abdominal pain, diarrhoea and excessive gas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The simple way to find out if a symptom is due to an intolerance is to exclude that food from the diet from two to four weeks, and see if the issue resolves itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nightmares tend to be worse in women and are more common in people with anxiety, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/depression/index.html" id="mol-a3004bb0-648c-11f0-9b97-41d0af826f89"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt; or those suffering from stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They also typically get worse when people are sleep-deprived.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So anyone suffering from bad dreams should try to go to bed earlier and improve their sleep environment. This might mean blackout blinds to reduce light in the bedroom and a fan to cool it down, or avoiding phones and tablets an hour before bedtime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Prescription medicines, including certain antidepressants and beta blockers, can trigger nightmares. Patients should talk to their pharmacist to see if the medication they take is linked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Some research suggests lactose intolerance, where the body has trouble breaking down dairy, can increase the frequency and severity of bad dreams&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nightmares are also a known feature of post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD), a mental health condition caused by experiencing or witnessing a distressing event. It can lead to persistent negative thoughts and feelings, and is usually treated with talking therapy and antidepressants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;GPs can refer anyone with suspected PTSD to a psychologist for diagnosis and treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-bold mol-style-italic"&gt;My wife, 80, gets terrible hot flushes, but does not want to take HRT. What should she do instead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Dr Ellie Cannon replies:&lt;/span&gt; It is important that anyone experiencing hot flushes tells their GP, because they are not always triggered by the menopause. While most women go through the menopause in their 50s, the hot flushes linked to it – sudden feelings of heat on the face, neck and chest – can continue for decades, even into their 80s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, they can also be triggered by thyroid issues, certain prescription medicines and the skin condition rosacea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In rare cases, it can also be a symptom of some cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If hot flushes are triggered by menopause, the best treatment is hormone replacement therapy, or HRT – gels, tablets and patches that replace the lost female sex hormones oestrogen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But not all women can take HRT. Those who have had breast cancer, especially, should avoid it, as it can raise the risk of their disease returning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But for those who can’t use hormones, there are other options. One is a medicine called clonidine, which reduces the blood pressure, so also lowers the risk of flushing. However, it is unsuitable for those with already low blood pressure. Certain antidepressants, including paroxetine, can reduce the severity of hot flushes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Excitingly, there are a number of new medicines which are about to be rolled out to treat hot flushes, including a tablet called elinzanetant, which was approved for use in the UK last month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is likely to become available on the NHS within the next few years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold mol-style-italic"&gt;My husband was diagnosed with osteoarthritis and the pain has got much worse in recent months. However, he’s been told it will take six months to see a physiotherapist and even longer to see a specialist in hospital. He is 70 – should he go private?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Dr Ellie Cannon replies:&lt;/span&gt; Osteoarthritis is an agonising condition which requires a specialist – but there are also steps patients must take themselves to stay healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is caused by wear and tear of the joints, which is why it is common among older people. Gradually joint tissues are worn down, so do not bend and move as smoothly as before, causing pain and stiffness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Often it occurs in the hands, feet, knees and hips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There is no cure or targeted drug treatments. When it gets severe, patients may be offered joint replacement surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, in the early stages, osteoarthritis is usually treated with painkillers and lifestyle changes, the most important of which is exercise because it prevents joints from stiffening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;NHS physiotherapists provide tailored exercises to improve mobility and hopefully reduce the pain of the affected joints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But any exercise will help, especially swimming and tai chi. There is great advice on the website of the charity Versus Arthritis. Unfortunately, waiting times to see NHS osteoarthritis physiotherapists and specialists are very long at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some patients waiting for scans pay for them at private clinics and then opt back into NHS care. This can save waiting time, but can also be costly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another option would be to see a private physiotherapist while waiting for an NHS expert. They can provide a full assessment and training sessions, which will hopefully make things bearable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead"&gt;Have slimming jabs helped you quit booze?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;At present, these drugs are not being offered as anti-addiction treatments, but there are several big studies looking into the link&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I’m fascinated by the growing evidence that weight-loss drugs appear to help patients overcome unhealthy habits such as drinking and smoking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It’s something I’ve heard from many of my patients. They tell me that along with cutting out the food ‘noise’ which makes them feel hungry, the injections, Mounjaro and Wegovy, also reduce their compulsion to have a glass of wine or a cigarette.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At present, these drugs are not being offered as anti-addiction treatments, but there are several big studies looking into the link. I think it will only be a matter of time before they are used in this manner too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Did weight-loss jabs help you to quit alcohol or cigarettes? Please write in and let me know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead"&gt;An end to the hell of hay fever&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There is exciting news for hay fever sufferers – scientists say they have developed a vaccine-like nasal spray that could slash the symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The experimental treatment creates a shield inside the nose that blocks the effects of pollen particles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It has so far only been tested on mice but researchers are confident it could be ready for human use in five years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For many, hay fever leads to nothing more serious than itchy eyes and a running nose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But for some who suffer severely, it can be a life-limiting issue which stops them enjoying time outdoors during certain months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are several hay fever medications available over- the-counter or by prescription, but none of them are particularly effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It’s an issue that is close to my heart, as my teenage son has a particularly acute form of hay fever. So I know first-hand just how desperately patients need a better treatment option. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mol-bullets-with-font"&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Do you have a question for Dr Ellie Cannon? Email DrEllie@mailonsunday.co.uk&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="mol-bullets-with-font"&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Dr Cannon cannot enter into personal correspondence and her replies should be taken in a general context&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 10:54:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5AFBVV95cUxNaWpfT2ZyTmRTS2NTSWQ4dHpLZlNXNENjbkZOZnNIMHdqMlJKMEdXNUFKcXkyVTJCUjI3Nm1xSl9CR1Fxc2dGOXY2WDFfMTRBZlRETUkzaW53LVdOX2JXS0hDQmdLWlVteE9Gbi1jaFBqRlFyZnZMbXRoUVRjUWo4cHk0ZHVYUGlCZnhNdmRKaGh2QkVmRlBIN0RnSU9nNkpsaFA1OGdqbGZjMzd2TEtwV2xBNm14RnFTU1RzRHVqNFppYmU0dDFpdXZLbEQ5SkdibXJsaWtUUUJaZ1dXMVVXa0dTZ0Q</guid></item><item><title>医生说这是服用低剂量阿司匹林的正确方法- AOL.com | Doctors Say This Is the Right Way to Take Low-Dose Aspirin - AOL.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMicEFVX3lxTE4zRHh4d2ZROW5WMlVWdkxDZ1RqVktETnJ3eHlCTXJnU20xN2IyR19paWNaMWlISzctWVBiNGREcjE4MW1IQ1pPZmlScURUcVd2TE51Vy1ZdWJscE5NVDdzMVJnS1ZRZkRVZE1Jdm1TN2Y?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;The Right Way to Take Low-Dose Aspirin&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;Doucefleur&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Hearst Magazines and Yahoo may earn commission or revenue on some items through these links."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may have heard that taking &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/medicines/low-dose-aspirin/about-low-dose-aspirin/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:a low dose of aspirin;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;a low dose of aspirin&lt;/a&gt; every day can boost your heart health. Last year, the American Heart Association &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/CIR.0000000000001209" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:reported;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; that more than 48% of U.S. adults age 20 and up have some form of cardiovascular disease, so it makes sense that you should take a daily aspirin, right? Not so fast. &lt;strong&gt;If you don't have heart problems, taking a low dose of aspirin might not be right for you. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why do some people take low-dose aspirin?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Typically, low-dose aspirin is for patients who have established &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/atherosclerosis" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:atherosclerotic disease;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;atherosclerotic disease&lt;/a&gt;,” says &lt;a href="https://medicine.duke.edu/profile/nishant-shah" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Nishant Shah, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Nishant Shah, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, an associate professor of medicine in cardiology at &lt;a href="https://medschool.duke.edu/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Duke University School of Medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Duke University School of Medicine&lt;/a&gt; in Durham, NC. “Atherosclerotic disease means there’s evidence of cholesterol plaque in your arteries. Many patients with atherosclerotic disease have had prior heart attacks or strokes. Other patients can have atherosclerotic disease without having had a heart attack or stroke, but are still at risk of having either. Low dose aspirin can help in the prevention of cardiovascular events like heart attack or stroke in patients with atherosclerotic disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mayoclinic.org%2Fdiseases-conditions%2Fheart-disease%2Fin-depth%2Fdaily-aspirin-therapy%2Fart-20046797&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.goodhousekeeping.com%2Fhealth%2Fa65448814%2Fwhen-to-take-low-dose-aspirin%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mayo Clinic;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;, aspirin acts as a blood thinner. Any clots that build up inside a heart artery could block blood flow, leading to a heart attack or stroke, and aspirin can help stop a clot from forming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’ve had a procedure, like &lt;a href="https://www.ctsnet.org/jans/x-aortic-valve-replacement-patients-treated-low-dose-warfarin-and-low-dose-aspirin" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:a heart valve replacement;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;a heart valve replacement&lt;/a&gt;, you may also be prescribed a low-dose regimen for a period of time. Beyond the cardiovascular system, though, a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39825684/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:new study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;new study&lt;/a&gt; from the University of Hong Kong found that using low-dose aspirin for 10 years could cut a person's risk of lung, breast and colorectal cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're curious, take a deeper dive into the specifics of taking low-dose aspirin below, including the best time to take it if your doctor does recommend it for you. Just don't start an aspirin regimen on your own. &lt;strong&gt;“You should consult with your doctor about whether or not low-dose aspirin is right for you,” stresses Dr. Lindley. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is a low-dose aspirin regimen?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technically, any dose of aspirin that is 100 mg or less is considered to be a low dose. However, in the U.S., 81 mg is the most commonly prescribed low dose. The United States Preventative Task Force has made the following &lt;a href="https://www.uspreventiveservicestaskforce.org/uspstf/recommendation/aspirin-to-prevent-cardiovascular-disease-preventive-medication" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:recommendations;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;recommendations&lt;/a&gt; regarding aspirin use to prevent cardiovascular disease:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adults 40-59:&lt;/strong&gt; A daily low-dose aspirin regimen may be recommended if a patient has 10% odds or higher of developing heart disease in the next decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adults aged 60 or older:&lt;/strong&gt; A daily low-dose aspirin regimen isn’t recommended to prevent heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;All decisions regarding an aspirin regimen should be tailored to the individual patient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you know if you should take low-dose aspirin?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s all about your medical history. &lt;strong&gt;“People who have previously experienced a heart attack, a stroke, or an intervention for coronary artery disease, such as a &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/heart-attack/treatment-of-a-heart-attack/stent" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:stent;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;stent&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/coronary-artery-bypass-grafting/who-needs" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:bypass surgery;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;bypass surgery&lt;/a&gt;, may have an indication for aspirin therapy&lt;/strong&gt; for secondary prevention,” says &lt;a href="https://profiles.mountsinai.org/matthew-i-tomey" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Matthew I. Tomey, MD, FACC, FAHA, FSCAI;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Matthew I. Tomey, MD, FACC, FAHA, FSCAI&lt;/a&gt;, an interventional and critical care cardiologist at the &lt;a href="https://www.mountsinai.org/locations/mount-sinai/care/heart" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mount Sinai Fuster Heart Hospital;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Mount Sinai Fuster Heart Hospital&lt;/a&gt; in New York City.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Your doctor will determine whether you would likely benefit from aspirin based on your risk factors such as age, blood pressure, cholesterol and diabetes history, as well as other factors like your family history,”&lt;/strong&gt; says Dr, Lindley. “Sometimes additional testing such as &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mayoclinic.org%2Ftests-procedures%2Fheart-scan%2Fabout%2Fpac-20384686&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.goodhousekeeping.com%2Fhealth%2Fa65448814%2Fwhen-to-take-low-dose-aspirin%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:a coronary calcium score;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;a coronary calcium score&lt;/a&gt; may be performed to help understand your risk for a heart attack.” &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2666667725000881" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:A new study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;A new study&lt;/a&gt; points out that genetic testing may also play a helpful role in determining whether certain patients can benefit the most from an aspirin regimen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who should NOT take low-dose aspirin? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because aspirin is a blood thinner, anyone at higher risk for bleeding should not take it. According to &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/wellness-and-prevention/is-taking-aspirin-good-for-your-heart" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Johns Hopkins Medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Johns Hopkins Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, you should refrain if:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You already take blood thinners, or you take &lt;a href="https://www.hss.edu/health-library/conditions-and-treatments/steroid-side-effects-how-to-reduce-corticosteroid-side-effects" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:corticosteroids;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;corticosteroids&lt;/a&gt;. (Check with your doctor regarding ALL medications you take to avoid any interactions!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You have or have had ulcers, GI bleeding or gastritis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You have kidney failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You have serious liver disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You have any bleeding disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You have any clotting disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you have a history or increased risk of bleeding or frequent falls, it's crucial to discuss this with your physician to weigh the benefits against the bleeding risks,” says &lt;a href="https://manhattancardiology.com/team/dr-bhavna-suri/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Bhavna Suri, M.D;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Bhavna Suri, M.D&lt;/a&gt;., a cardiologist at &lt;a href="https://manhattancardiology.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Manhattan Cardiology;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Manhattan Cardiology&lt;/a&gt; in New York City.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/eurheartj/article/45/27/2362/7688448" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:A recent Italian study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;A recent Italian study&lt;/a&gt; found that &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK547742/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:NSAIDs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;NSAIDs&lt;/a&gt; like aspirin can irritate the GI tract, and that serious GI complications like bleeding, perforation and obstruction happens in 1 to 2% of users. &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2807630" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Additional research;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Additional research&lt;/a&gt; has shown that low-dose aspirin may also increase the risk of bleeding in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do doctors prescribe low-dose aspirin to prevent a heart attack or stroke?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a rule, not for most people.&lt;/strong&gt; “It’s important to know that routine use of aspirin for primary prevention of heart disease is no longer recommended,” says Dr. Tomey. “By primary prevention, we mean preventing events like heart attack and stroke in individuals with no history of atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease. Selectively, physicians may recommend use of low-dose aspirin for prevention in some people at higher than average risk, such as those who are found to have evidence of plaque in their arteries on a diagnostic test, but who have not yet experienced a clinical event.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Age is also a key factor. “Currently, aspirin for primary prevention — meaning that you don’t have known cardiovascular disease — is not recommended for patients over age 70, due to the increased risk of bleeding in older patients,” says Dr. Lindley. “Also, it’s not recommended for patients aged 40 to 69 who are considered low risk of heart attack, stroke and colorectal cancer, and patients under age 40 without known cardiovascular disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Should you take low-dose aspirin with food or drink?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You don’t have to, but it could make it easier for your body to digest the medication.&lt;/strong&gt; “Taking aspirin with food or drink helps protect your stomach lining by reducing irritation, acid reflux, ulceration and a higher risk of bleeding,” says Dr. Suri. “A full glass of water also helps the tablet dissolve and be absorbed properly.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When’s the best time to take low-dose aspirin? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Through the years, there’s been no clear evidence to date that a particular time of administration is superior for prevention of heart attack and stroke,” says Dr. Tomey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, if your doctor gives you the green light for a daily low-dose aspirin, it’s important to stick to a schedule. &lt;strong&gt;“Try to be consistent and take it at the same time every day,” says Dr. Suri.&lt;/strong&gt; Pair your aspirin with an “automatic” daily activity, like brushing your teeth or sitting down to breakfast with the family, and the less likely you’ll be to forget to take it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The bottom line&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a low-dose aspirin regimen is right for you, follow your doctor’s instructions to the letter and don't be afraid to ask questions. &lt;strong&gt;“I encourage any patient who has been prescribed aspirin by a doctor to take a moment to learn about the reason for their aspirin prescription, and always to ask their doctor before starting or stopping aspirin therapy,” Dr. Tomey sums up.&lt;/strong&gt; “It can also be quite helpful to consult with a preventive cardiologist to take a broader, personalized look at options beyond aspirin.” The more you learn about other potential treatment strategies, the better you’ll feel in every way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 10:44:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE4zRHh4d2ZROW5WMlVWdkxDZ1RqVktETnJ3eHlCTXJnU20xN2IyR19paWNaMWlISzctWVBiNGREcjE4MW1IQ1pPZmlScURUcVd2TE51Vy1ZdWJscE5NVDdzMVJnS1ZRZkRVZE1Jdm1TN2Y</guid></item><item><title>补充剂可以减少炎症并延长寿命。以下是一位心脏病专家为降低心脏病风险而采取的措施。- Business Insider | Supplements can reduce inflammation and boost longevity. Here's what one cardiologist takes to lower his risk of heart disease. - Business Insider</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirAFBVV95cUxPdXhBNmUyZGo4Q1lURDRCS2tyWDJxc3RwVzNxOE04Yi1vVnNYZVE0MEVoSVo0S0tadTNqV0g4VWZyT3A1ekUyR093ZnI4c29zVGN6STh3RWxnbFdqbW1sR3hKdldGSjJkZ2lxclJ2bWIwbk9Ubld4YjdINFpmeWV5NVllMmQtSTFCbllKVll2OHJ6eF9kd2o4VVd5LWxwUFpPNngzb3ZnSmNEdjVt?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="post-body-content post-story-body-content" data-component-type="post-body-content" data-load-strategy="exclude" data-track-content="" data-post-type="story" data-track-marfeel="post-body-content"&gt;
            
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Welcome back!&lt;/strong&gt; Apparently, there's a hot new summer cocktail, and it's called &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/hugo-spritz-cocktail-st-germain-recipe-explained-2025-7" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;the Hugo Spritz&lt;/a&gt;. Find out why everyone is jumping on this bubbly's bandwagon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On the agenda:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But first: &lt;/strong&gt;Let's talk about matters of the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If this was forwarded to you, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/subscription/newsletter/insider-today-sunday-edition" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;&lt;em&gt;sign up here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Download Business Insider's app &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="" href="https://www.insider.com/app" data-track-click='{"click_type":"other","element_name":"body_link","event":"outbound_click"}'&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;here.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3 id="2d2d81c1-e984-4ab1-b11e-26ada0d3da0b" data-toc-id="2d2d81c1-e984-4ab1-b11e-26ada0d3da0b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This week's dispatch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Omega-3 can be found in fatty fish like salmon and anchovies.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              carlosgaw/Getty Images
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;h2 id="ef84679e-5101-4303-beb5-fc75bc92b8c0" data-toc-id="ef84679e-5101-4303-beb5-fc75bc92b8c0"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And the (heart)beat goes on…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We know supplements can reduce inflammation, boost strength training, and strengthen your immune system. But did you also know that the right stack can also protect you from heart failure?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Dmitry Yaranov, the director of the advanced heart failure program at Baptist Memorial Hospital in Memphis, Tennessee, told BI senior reporter Julia Pugachevsky that &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/supplements-cardiologist-takes-for-heart-health-omega-3-magnesium-2025-7" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;he takes three supplements to reduce his risk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here's what's in his medicine cabinet:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Omega-3&lt;/strong&gt;: Yaranov said he takes this supplement because he's "not getting enough fresh, fatty fish in my diet." Pugachevsky notes that taking omega-3 "helps to support healthy blood cells, reducing the risk of blood clots" and can reduce the risk of strokes and heart attacks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Magnesium&lt;/strong&gt;: Pugachevsky said that this supplement, typically found in black beans and spinach, "supports heart, bone, brain, and muscle health" and helps with controlling blood pressure.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin D: &lt;/strong&gt;Yaranov said he spends "a long time indoors," which contributes to his lower levels of this essential vitamin, so he started supplementing it. Research shows that Vitamin D is also associated with a lower risk of heart disease in adults over the age of 60.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2 id="cc30e20d-acf4-4a4e-ad8f-02c3a04a9dbb" data-toc-id="cc30e20d-acf4-4a4e-ad8f-02c3a04a9dbb"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skip the jet lag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      To bounce back from jet lag more quickly, get your internal clocks back on schedule with strategic exposure to light and darkness.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Getty Images
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Jet lag, which can cause brain fog, fatigue, and digestive issues, could derail your entire travel experience. It happens when your local time zone is misaligned with your internal clocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who fly regularly — from pro athletes to CEOs — told BI how they beat jet lag, including the supplements they take and the adjustments they make before traveling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/fight-jet-lag-pro-tips-better-focus-and-energy-2025-6" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;From diet changes to light therapy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2 id="f3efdf5d-fcfc-4813-9e6c-8e3b9040c25d" data-toc-id="f3efdf5d-fcfc-4813-9e6c-8e3b9040c25d"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ultimate finance bro flex&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-only "&gt;
                    
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Getty Images; Tyler Le/BI
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;In the realm of posh sports, not much ranks higher than golf, and its elitist nature often manifests in fashion. Donning a logoed golf polo from the course you play has become a subtle status symbol among Wall Street golf bros.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many men described the logoed gear to BI's Emily Stewart as a "head nod," but there's a hierarchy associated with it, too. Just don't get caught wearing a golf polo from a course you've never played.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/wall-street-status-symbol-men-golf-courseshirt-club-masters-2025-7" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;If you know, you know&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also read:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2 id="4e812ecf-a060-401e-9848-be206a63cddb" data-toc-id="4e812ecf-a060-401e-9848-be206a63cddb"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A class dedicated to boosting your VO2 max&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      VO2 max is a buzzy fitness metric that's said to be a strong predictor of longevity.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Kim Schewitz
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;VO2 max has become the latest fitness craze that measures cardiovascular fitness among runners, fitness competition bros, and more. People are obsessed with the metric because it's said to be a strong predictor of longevity. A high VO2 max is also linked to a longer life and a reduced risk of certain health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So when London's GymBox came out with a new VO2:MAXED cardio class, BI's Kim Schewitz, who said she doesn't do cardio, tried it out. She found out her VO2 score was low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/increase-vo2-max-fitness-class-review-make-cardio-fun-2025-7" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;But it made cardio fun for her&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2 id="483172dd-9e06-415f-8357-1bdb6f813f7b" data-toc-id="483172dd-9e06-415f-8357-1bdb6f813f7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Five-star faux pas&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-only "&gt;
                    
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Joey Hadden/Business Insider
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;BI's travel reporter Joey Hadden has stayed at 10 five-star hotels across the Americas and Europe. She shared six mistakes she's made during these swanky stays, so you won't have to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For instance, Hadden learned you should always pack a swimsuit, but you won't need to bring toiletries. Plus, turndown service is a must — you never know what treats you'll get.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/five-star-hotel-mistakes-to-avoid" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;She recommends booking more than one night&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2 id="5fef756b-4b6b-4037-8f33-9635854b9d8b" data-toc-id="5fef756b-4b6b-4037-8f33-9635854b9d8b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're watching this weekend&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-only "&gt;
                    
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              saravuth-photohut/Getty, Tyler Le/BI
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"Miley Cyrus: Something Beautiful":&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/miley-cyrus-daring-outfits-photos-2021-5" rel=""&gt;The chart-topping artist&lt;/a&gt; turned her 2025 album of the same name into a stunning visual companion that's now available on Disney+ and Hulu.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"The Amateur": &lt;/strong&gt;Now on Hulu, this thriller stars Rami Malek as a CIA decoder who is out for vengeance after the death of his wife. Rachel Brosnahan, Laurence Fishburne, and Jon Bernthal also star.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"Billy Joel: And So It Goes":&lt;/strong&gt; This two-part documentary on HBO Max looks at the legendary life and career of The Piano Man, Billy Joel.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-only "&gt;
                    
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              iStock; Rebecca Zisser/BI
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;h2 id="a09a70ef-5e7e-4bf4-80b2-3731f70bdc6e" data-toc-id="a09a70ef-5e7e-4bf4-80b2-3731f70bdc6e"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to shop&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TV on wheels&lt;/strong&gt;: This touchscreen on wheels is like a smart‑TV‑tablet hybrid that lets you stream or scroll wherever you roll it. Its portable convenience makes it a delightful, lifestyle‑first gadget that &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/guides/tech/lg-stanbyme-review" rel=""&gt;editor Sam Crozier loves for her small Brooklyn apartment&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A shirt to do it all&lt;/strong&gt;: Public Rec's Go‑To Polo is crafted with a cooling, stretchy cotton‑blend that is so comfortable our men's style editor, Amir Ismael, swears you can work out in it. Here's &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/guides/style/public-rec-go-to-polo-review" rel=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;why we recommend it for your closet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A heated hand massager&lt;/strong&gt;: Social media fiends, rock climbers, and desk jockeys with carpal tunnel all have one thing in common: they need a hand massage. &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/guides/home/comfier-hand-massager-review" rel=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This handy device&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; isn't a cure-all, but its gentle heat and snug fit make it a great self-care accessory that senior associate editor Gabrielle Chase swears by.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2 id="3a2e4b99-8063-4f80-8653-d1ec4a2af89a" data-toc-id="3a2e4b99-8063-4f80-8653-d1ec4a2af89a"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More of this week's top reads:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The BI Today team:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/author/lisa-ryan" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Lisa Ryan&lt;/a&gt;, executive editor, in New York. &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/author/akin-oyedele" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Akin Oyedele&lt;/a&gt;, deputy editor, in New York. &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/author/grace-lett" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Grace Lett&lt;/a&gt;, editor, in New York. &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/author/amanda-yen" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Amanda Yen&lt;/a&gt;, associate editor, in New York.&lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            &lt;/section&gt;
            
            
            
            
              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Business Insider</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 10:44:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxPdXhBNmUyZGo4Q1lURDRCS2tyWDJxc3RwVzNxOE04Yi1vVnNYZVE0MEVoSVo0S0tadTNqV0g4VWZyT3A1ekUyR093ZnI4c29zVGN6STh3RWxnbFdqbW1sR3hKdldGSjJkZ2lxclJ2bWIwbk9Ubld4YjdINFpmeWV5NVllMmQtSTFCbllKVll2OHJ6eF9kd2o4VVd5LWxwUFpPNngzb3ZnSmNEdjVt</guid></item><item><title>这种古老的做法胜过睡眠药片–科学支持它-SciTechDaily | This Ancient Practice Beats Pills for Sleep – And Science Backs It - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxOYmhOZE5rZmlMY24wYV95SkpncUJVQW5HMzVQdzQxOUxWdGZKQTF1WTVZZzdRSUt3U09Sb2p4a2lJQjduVWJSV1ZBSnJJMFlZckl5a1UwbUl3Z3k0STNsczJGeVRyaW5zaDNLMXpONUNnQ3gxaS1FeURBSlptNHo3QURXZU9DTjdKR2JPUUU0TlhHX1It?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 10:05:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOYmhOZE5rZmlMY24wYV95SkpncUJVQW5HMzVQdzQxOUxWdGZKQTF1WTVZZzdRSUt3U09Sb2p4a2lJQjduVWJSV1ZBSnJJMFlZckl5a1UwbUl3Z3k0STNsczJGeVRyaW5zaDNLMXpONUNnQ3gxaS1FeURBSlptNHo3QURXZU9DTjdKR2JPUUU0TlhHX1It</guid></item><item><title>我通过什么遇见了我的女儿-新闻自由 | What I Went Through to Meet My Daughter - The Free Press</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigwFBVV95cUxPaTRxNkF0ZVNiVDJ4b191bTlOWE4xOXQwbVRwUWJnc0VzVXBSYlRCd3dfemx2dS05THNjTjNkTG5tTG9OdWJTaEdKVHZQSGRzSHVtMjlzajllUUhLZ3Z1Nm5uWEZDN3ZnYmdsOXZxOFd1RndqMm5Md1VWUTBFbmV5eXpidw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div dir="auto" class="body markup"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You’re in the right place,” said Vicky, the receptionist, smiling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I believed it, though it seemed almost absurd that I’d flown all the way to St. Louis, Missouri. I grew up in the United Kingdom, where healthcare is supposed to be free and equal for everyone, and spent the last eight years in New York City, home to some of the best teaching hospitals and research centers in the world. And yet, here I was, at a niche clinic a thousand miles from home, because I was hoping to do the most ordinary thing in the world: become a mother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I sat in the waiting room with my husband, Nick, and my mum, who’d flown in from Scotland for moral support. On the wall were cards from patients, beautiful photos of newborn babies, heartfelt notes of thanks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at them felt bittersweet. I wondered what each mother’s journey had been like. Would I, like them, be a success story? Or might I be the exception—a particularly hopeless case?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had known for years that I likely had a gynecological disorder that is impossible to diagnose without a surgeon cutting holes in the abdomen and examining the inside of the pelvis with a camera. A doctor had told me it might affect my fertility. But after I’d gotten married, in 2023, I got pregnant. Then I lost my baby to miscarriage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In America, around 13 percent of women struggle with fertility issues. Up to half of couples &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38716407/" rel&gt;seeking treatment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; for them are labeled as having “unexplained infertility” by doctors—and therefore go untreated. Many of them will try IVF, which risks being unsuccessful, because the underlying cause of their infertility has not been addressed. Revolutionary though it has been, IVF does not restore a would-be mother’s body to optimal health; in fact, IVF is often a profoundly uncomfortable experience for women, not to mention an expensive one. It’s no wonder that many women with “unexplained infertility” are left feeling that mainstream medicine &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1877575623000691" rel&gt;has failed them&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, subjecting them to stressful, painful interventions, while leaving them in the dark about the mysteries of their own bodies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there is another way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Free Press</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 10:01:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxPaTRxNkF0ZVNiVDJ4b191bTlOWE4xOXQwbVRwUWJnc0VzVXBSYlRCd3dfemx2dS05THNjTjNkTG5tTG9OdWJTaEdKVHZQSGRzSHVtMjlzajllUUhLZ3Z1Nm5uWEZDN3ZnYmdsOXZxOFd1RndqMm5Md1VWUTBFbmV5eXpidw</guid></item><item><title>以下是佛罗里达州四人死于食肉细菌后面临风险的人- NBC新闻 | Here's who's at-risk after four die from flesh-eating bacteria in Florida - NBC News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipAFBVV95cUxNSTFyZGgtUHhWLWhLT1pZX2QxTmtLdEdyNlI5TmpQZnBoWHQ4NkJFdFJqNE5fdWpCaFVPdVFYbkpBUmV3X3pxMXk4MnZNTGdUdGg0SHB5VGZjOXoyQVM5QnlmTjd1dnN5X0VDYUI1b0N1bldGUDZlNTRiZi16dllReGw0aFgyOEtIbDRaa1dzOWNoUlZvTEVqb2xubXp5eXRVdmwtLdIBVkFVX3lxTFBqb2EyX05aVUJTNDhubXpDbGgxeEdVNlZYR2Y4NGota1VpSVV6QXF4c3J1UFozeGc4elQyUzk3ZmJxdXpRdHJ6TU5MY2h3ZjZLMGtSNk13?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-74b45e" class="body-graf"&gt;Four people in Florida have died this year from bacterial infections that can cause “flesh-eating” wounds, the &lt;a href="https://www.floridahealth.gov/diseases-and-conditions/vibrio-infections/vibrio-vulnificus/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;state’s health department&lt;/a&gt; reported this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bc1782" class="body-graf"&gt;The culprit, the bacteria Vibrio vulnificus, thrives in warm seawater. The deadly cases were seen in counties spread around Florida’s extensive coastline, from Bay County in the Panhandle and Hillsborough County, where Tampa is located, on the Gulf Coast, to Broward County in southeastern Florida and St. Johns County just south of Jacksonville.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c35e06" class="body-graf"&gt;Florida has seen 11 Vibrio vulnificus cases so far this year, the state’s health department says. The bacteria can get into the body through open wounds in the skin and cause the surrounding tissue to die, a condition known as necrotizing fasciitis, or flesh-eating disease, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vibrio/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. People can also get Vibrio vulnificus from eating contaminated foods, particularly raw oysters. It’s unclear how the people in Florida were infected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-17648c" class="body-graf"&gt;About 1 in 5 people with a Vibrio vulnificus infection die, the CDC says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f2d2fe" class="body-graf"&gt;Antarpreet Jutla, an engineering professor at the University of Florida who researches Vibrio bacteria, said Vibrio vulnificus infections are still rare, though they tend to &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/hurricane-idalia-concerns-flesh-eating-bacteria-rcna102181" target="_blank"&gt;increase after hurricanes&lt;/a&gt;. Last year, Florida saw a total of 82 cases, which may have been exacerbated by the &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/weather/hurricanes/hurricane-season-ends-rcna181808" target="_blank"&gt;“extremely active” hurricane season.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-a50f4b" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Vibrio vulnificus? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-810fd0" class="body-graf"&gt;Vibrio vulnificus is one of over 200 species of Vibrio bacteria, said Rita Colwell, a professor emerita of microbiology at the University of Maryland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4ffa7d" class="body-graf"&gt;The majority of Vibrio infections aren’t harmful to humans, Jutla said. Some only affect other animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-dfa96b" class="body-graf"&gt;But Vibrio bacteria do cause about 80,000 infections in people each year, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/24884-vibrio-vulnificus" target="_blank"&gt;according to the Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. Most of those cases are gastrointestinal. Only a small handful — 100 to 200 cases — are due to Vibrio vulnificus. Other Vibrio species, including Vibrio parahaemolyticus and Vibrio alginolyticus, are often the cause of those stomach illnesses. Another type of Vibrio, Vibrio cholorae, causes the diarrheal disease cholera.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d72eef" class="body-graf"&gt;Because Vibrio bacteria prefer warm water, they are typically found along the southeastern shores of the U.S., but are also found on the West Coast as well. &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/science/environment/fear-warming-oceans-flesh-eating-bacteria-rcna75935" target="_blank"&gt;As ocean temperatures warm&lt;/a&gt;, more cases have been found further north in recent years, Jutla said, including some in &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/3-people-die-flesh-eating-bacteria-infections-new-york-connecticut-pro-rcna100364" target="_blank"&gt;New York, Connecticut and Maryland&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-1021e7" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who is at risk?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bcd450" class="body-graf"&gt;Vibrio bacteria can creep in open wounds after spending time in salty or brackish water, said Dr. Norman Beatty, an infectious disease doctor at University of Florida Health. Most cases he’s seen have been associated with spending extended time in the water, but he says that a brief exposure could be the “only thing needed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-767532" class="body-graf"&gt;Visible signs of an infection can start in just a few hours, Beatty said, and include redness, swelling and “bull’s-eye” blisters. The site will also be painful. If infection progresses, it can get into the bloodstream and cause sepsis, which can be deadly. Symptoms of sepsis include fever, chills and dangerously low blood pressure, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d34a99" class="body-graf"&gt;People with liver cirrhosis, weakened immune systems and those over 65 are most at risk for infection, Jutla said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-df6724" class="body-graf"&gt;Vibrio vulnificus infections can be treated with antibiotics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-af371a" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to prevent Vibrio infections&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0d1f0e" class="body-graf"&gt;Beatty said he recommends covering up any open wounds before going into the ocean. Even a waterproof Band-Aid does the job, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-50fd5d" class="body-graf"&gt;If people think they have an infection, they should seek care immediately, Beatty said. Delaying can be the difference between developing severe complications and a more mild infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1c4947" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“A delay in presenting to health care is truly the likely reason why most people have a more serious outcome than others,” he said. “People who present within the same day with signs and symptoms of early infection, who receive antibiotics, can do well and can avoid a lot of these serious complications.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxNSTFyZGgtUHhWLWhLT1pZX2QxTmtLdEdyNlI5TmpQZnBoWHQ4NkJFdFJqNE5fdWpCaFVPdVFYbkpBUmV3X3pxMXk4MnZNTGdUdGg0SHB5VGZjOXoyQVM5QnlmTjd1dnN5X0VDYUI1b0N1bldGUDZlNTRiZi16dllReGw0aFgyOEtIbDRaa1dzOWNoUlZvTEVqb2xubXp5eXRVdmwtLdIBVkFVX3lxTFBqb2EyX05aVUJTNDhubXpDbGgxeEdVNlZYR2Y4NGota1VpSVV6QXF4c3J1UFozeGc4elQyUzk3ZmJxdXpRdHJ6TU5MY2h3ZjZLMGtSNk13</guid></item><item><title>高蛋白零食值得大肆宣传吗？以下是评估方法- NPR | Are high-protein snacks worth the hype? Here's how to assess - NPR</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxPWG5Ld0pidFlST3VjeG0tVkFOWE1EZU9PdVNtcTFfMGpkV3pfd2VfOFhNT2J2YTFtWURTaDdkMkFUUExBVVA2X1pRWWFBUlpsU3JsUndsSi1rRjJFeWljSWo5RVd2SUpyWGxMaUJMTHJEd0NqbkdIcEpqc3pqQ3VDU1BoYV9ZVjgzbmt2TENn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-77996" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Protein has taken over the packaged-snack aisles at the grocery store. But do you need extra protein in your chips and muffins?
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    winterling/iStockphoto/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        winterling/iStockphoto/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Protein has never gone out of style. While fat was demonized as the nutrient causing weight gain in the 1990s, followed by carbs in the 2000s, protein sat by the sidelines as the official people pleaser of the macro-nutrient world.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"You need essential amino acids in the diet in order to sustain life," says Stefan Pasiakos, director of the Center for Human Performance Optimization at the Pennington Biomedical Research Center. Protein is needed for building and repairing muscle and tissues and helps support your immune system.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Protein stepped into the spotlight in recent years as keto and other high-protein diets took off. Health and fitness influencers started to push everyone to eat more muscle-building foods in every meal (deep-fried &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sdQFw-_vKpY" target="_blank"&gt;cottage cheese Doritos&lt;/a&gt; anyone?) The nutrient is so ubiquitous online that one influencer asks whether &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DFWBepuNApm/?hl=en" target="_blank"&gt;protein can leave him alone for five minutes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;And it has now taken over the snack food aisles, with "high-protein" or "protein-packed" labels on the front of products as diverse as sweet rolls, chips and pretzels. There's even a &lt;a href="https://www.walmart.com/ip/SNICKERS-HI-PROTEIN-BAR-ORIGINAL-4CT/3988040815?" target="_blank"&gt;high-protein version&lt;/a&gt; of a Snickers bar.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Leaning into protein claims on packaging&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Of course, these claims don't always mean the food is good for you or even a good source of protein.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"You'll see chips labeled high protein," says Pasiakos, who is a former director of the National Institutes of Health's Office of Dietary Supplements. "In reality, they're probably not, but people are now trying to jump all over it."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The global protein-snacks market alone is projected to grow from $50 billion in 2024 to $101 billion by 2032, according to &lt;a href="https://www.fortunebusinessinsights.com/protein-snacks-market-110937" target="_blank"&gt;Fortune Business Insights&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Snack-makers often market protein front and center on their packaging without mentioning the food's sugar content, says Pasiakos.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;For instance, a candy with 1 gram of protein may have a high-protein marketing claim on the front of the package and to the maker, "it may not even be a false claim because they're thinking, 'If you looked at another candy, it's not going to have a gram of protein in it,'" he says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Among many examples, Smash Foods' cashew butter and blueberry jam Snack Bites, sold at Whole Foods, advertises 5g of protein, yet it has 16g of sugar, more than triple its protein amount. 365 Chewy Protein Bites aren't much better, with various flavors having about 20g of sugar to 10g of protein.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;The Food and Drug Administration regulates marketing claims on packaged foods, restricting manufacturers from making big, overarching health claims without proof. For instance, companies can't claim their food prevents heart attacks or cures cancer, Pasiakos says. They also &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2024/12/19/nx-s1-5234143/fda-healthy-food-labels-diet" target="_blank"&gt;can't use the word "healthy"&lt;/a&gt; or derivatives of the word without meeting the FDA healthy standards of providing a specific amount of a nutrient within a food group.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So saying something is "high protein" can be a way of working around the regulations while signaling to consumers that a food might be good for them.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to judge? Try a little math&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So how do you determine whether a snack making protein claims is worth eating? Pasiakos offers this simple calculation to get a sense of what share of the food's total calories is derived from protein.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Take the number of grams of protein in the product and multiply it by 4 — that's the number of calories &lt;a href="https://www.nal.usda.gov/programs/fnic" target="_blank"&gt;per gram of protein&lt;/a&gt;. Now you know the calories from protein in the food. Then take the protein calories and divide by the total calories in the food. That gives you the share of calories in the food that comes from protein.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;For instance, let's say a protein bar has 20 grams of protein and 200 calories. You'd multiply 20 × 4 to get 80. Then you'd divide 80 by 200 and get 40%. "Anything that was high in protein would have 30% or more of protein by calorie count," says Pasiakos.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Another option would be to check the percentage of the daily value (listed as DV) of protein listed on the Nutrition Facts label on the package. Anything 20% or above can be seen as high protein, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/food/nutrition-facts-label/daily-value-nutrition-and-supplement-facts-labels#:~:text=5%25%20DV%20or%20less%20of,per%20serving%20is%20considered%20high" target="_blank"&gt;FDA&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But even if a snack is high in protein, is it automatically healthy? Not necessarily.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Protein's important, but it's not the only nutrient we should be looking at," says Clare Parme Miller, a New York-based registered dietician for &lt;a href="https://lifewaysnutrition.com/clare-parme-miller/" target="_blank"&gt;Lifeways Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;. It's equally important to get enough of other nutrients like fiber and to avoid foods high in added sugars or highly processed ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"Look for snacks with added sugars of less than 10 grams that are less processed than most protein bars," she suggests.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;And, you may not need your snacks to be high protein, she notes.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The federal government suggests adults get at least 0.8 grams of protein per kilogram of body weight (or 0.36 per pound), which is 51 grams for a 140-pound woman who isn't pregnant or breastfeeding. Some nutrition and fitness experts recommend more, especially for those seeking to build muscle and for older people.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So when it comes to snack time, says Parme Miller, "especially if you're getting 20 to 30 grams of protein at mealtime, snacks only need to provide 10 to 15 grams."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;(The &lt;a href="https://www.nal.usda.gov/human-nutrition-and-food-safety/dri-calculator" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. Department of Agriculture has a handy nutrient calculator&lt;/a&gt; that takes into consideration your age and activity level.)&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Whole foods snacks can pack in protein too&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;It's not hard to meet protein minimums with whole foods, says Parme Miller, instead of reaching for packaged snacks with protein claims.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Greek yogurt or small cups of cottage cheese will fulfill your protein requirement and also provide calcium," says Parme Miller. Add berries for a boost in fiber and antioxidants.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Nuts without other added ingredients and roasted chickpeas, in single-serving sizes, provide less protein than Greek yogurt but can be paired with other items to get to 10 grams. For instance, you could add whole grain crackers to boost protein a bit and get another food group in. An ounce of cheese plus a few whole grain crackers also gives you protein and whole grains, which are high in fiber and contain calcium and several B vitamins.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Other whole grain plus protein snacks include smearing a nut butter on whole grain crackers or doing the same with hummus, says Parme Miller. Adding broccoli or another vegetable for dipping slightly ups the protein value and adds fiber and calcium.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"Whatever you do, don't eat gobs and gobs of protein, even if it says high protein on the label," says Parme Miller. "Protein foods, especially ones that also contain fats, are not calorie free."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Reyna Gobel, MPH, MBA, is a health writer, author and nutrition educator who created the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://courses.bestnutritionclassever.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;30-Day Precision Nutrition Challenge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxPWG5Ld0pidFlST3VjeG0tVkFOWE1EZU9PdVNtcTFfMGpkV3pfd2VfOFhNT2J2YTFtWURTaDdkMkFUUExBVVA2X1pRWWFBUlpsU3JsUndsSi1rRjJFeWljSWo5RVd2SUpyWGxMaUJMTHJEd0NqbkdIcEpqc3pqQ3VDU1BoYV9ZVjgzbmt2TENn</guid></item><item><title>佛罗里达州有四人死于食肉细菌。谁有风险？ -雅虎主页 | Four people have died from flesh-eating bacteria in Florida. Who is at risk? - Yahoo Home</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMie0FVX3lxTE9mdW5GakptVzdQMTF4VUpNc1dzQmFOdzFJV1RhdjZBazNRLUlXQ0lObWd0Xy12RFdKbVJfNTk5dWZhck42ODR6UWg1M2dlaVpYU05zMmdyTTQwVTZBWXVQUGpTU0E4eFN2Z29ORWVJU1N6S0dUMlNyUWdycw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Four people in Florida have died this year from bacterial infections that can cause “flesh-eating” wounds, the &lt;a href="https://www.floridahealth.gov/diseases-and-conditions/vibrio-infections/vibrio-vulnificus/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:state’s health department;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;state’s health department&lt;/a&gt; reported this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The culprit, the bacteria Vibrio vulnificus, thrives in warm seawater. The deadly cases were seen in counties spread around Florida’s extensive coastline, from Bay County in the Panhandle and Hillsborough County, where Tampa is located, on the Gulf Coast, to Broward County in southeastern Florida and St. Johns County just south of Jacksonville.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Florida has seen 11 Vibrio vulnificus cases so far this year, the state’s health department says. The bacteria can get into the body through open wounds in the skin and cause the surrounding tissue to die, a condition known as necrotizing fasciitis, or flesh-eating disease, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vibrio/about/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Centers for Disease Control and Prevention;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. People can also get Vibrio vulnificus from eating contaminated foods, particularly raw oysters. It’s unclear how the people in Florida were infected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;About 1 in 5 people with a Vibrio vulnificus infection die, the CDC says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Antarpreet Jutla, an engineering professor at the University of Florida who researches Vibrio bacteria, said Vibrio vulnificus infections are still rare, though they tend to &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/hurricane-idalia-concerns-flesh-eating-bacteria-rcna102181" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:increase after hurricanes;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;increase after hurricanes&lt;/a&gt;. Last year, Florida saw a total of 82 cases, which may have been exacerbated by the &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/weather/hurricanes/hurricane-season-ends-rcna181808" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:“extremely active” hurricane season.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;“extremely active” hurricane season.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Vibrio vulnificus? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Vibrio vulnificus is one of over 200 species of Vibrio bacteria, said Rita Colwell, a professor emerita of microbiology at the University of Maryland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The majority of Vibrio infections aren’t harmful to humans, Jutla said. Some only affect other animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But Vibrio bacteria do cause about 80,000 infections in people each year, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/24884-vibrio-vulnificus" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:according to the Cleveland Clinic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;according to the Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. Most of those cases are gastrointestinal. Only a small handful — 100 to 200 cases — are due to Vibrio vulnificus. Other Vibrio species, including Vibrio parahaemolyticus and Vibrio alginolyticus, are often the cause of those stomach illnesses. Another type of Vibrio, Vibrio cholorae, causes the diarrheal disease cholera.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Because Vibrio bacteria prefer warm water, they are typically found along the southeastern shores of the U.S., but are also found on the West Coast as well. &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/science/environment/fear-warming-oceans-flesh-eating-bacteria-rcna75935" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:As ocean temperatures warm;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;As ocean temperatures warm&lt;/a&gt;, more cases have been found further north in recent years, Jutla said, including some in &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/3-people-die-flesh-eating-bacteria-infections-new-york-connecticut-pro-rcna100364" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:New York, Connecticut and Maryland;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;New York, Connecticut and Maryland&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who is at risk?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Vibrio bacteria can creep in open wounds after spending time in salty or brackish water, said Dr. Norman Beatty, an infectious disease doctor at University of Florida Health. Most cases he’s seen have been associated with spending extended time in the water, but he says that a brief exposure could be the “only thing needed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Visible signs of an infection can start in just a few hours, Beatty said, and include redness, swelling and “bull’s-eye” blisters. The site will also be painful. If infection progresses, it can get into the bloodstream and cause sepsis, which can be deadly. Symptoms of sepsis include fever, chills and dangerously low blood pressure, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;People with liver cirrhosis, weakened immune systems and those over 65 are most at risk for infection, Jutla said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Vibrio vulnificus infections can be treated with antibiotics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to prevent Vibrio infections&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Beatty said he recommends covering up any open wounds before going into the ocean. Even a waterproof Band-Aid does the job, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If people think they have an infection, they should seek care immediately, Beatty said. Delaying can be the difference between developing severe complications and a more mild infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“A delay in presenting to health care is truly the likely reason why most people have a more serious outcome than others,” he said. “People who present within the same day with signs and symptoms of early infection, who receive antibiotics, can do well and can avoid a lot of these serious complications.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This article was originally published on &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/florida-flesh-eating-bacteria-risk-who-what-area-rcna219586" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:NBCNews.com;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;NBCNews.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Home</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE9mdW5GakptVzdQMTF4VUpNc1dzQmFOdzFJV1RhdjZBazNRLUlXQ0lObWd0Xy12RFdKbVJfNTk5dWZhck42ODR6UWg1M2dlaVpYU05zMmdyTTQwVTZBWXVQUGpTU0E4eFN2Z29ORWVJU1N6S0dUMlNyUWdycw</guid></item><item><title>男性正在遭受“夏季长球”的折磨，这可能会对他们的健康产生重大影响- LADbible | Men are suffering with ‘summer long balls’ that could have big impact on their health - LADbible</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxPWGZPME9XWHVHbHlFWmdzZi1uUTRaZzFQXzUtNDJtMl9WdjAwRzhnTVFQLVYybWdEdVF3NG81bmNJQm8tWWRDcTJWdlA2ekItWENnd3daWDdHb1pQWnR0QUZtNF9GZlFQMnB5UWU5bUtFNGMxQng5UENRbGZyWnI2amFhOUNmQjA4aWlqbk44cndralN1SXlmaWhlTjM?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;There have been three heatwaves in the UK this summer already, and it seems men are struggling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Last summer, we told you about '&lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/health"&gt;summer penis&lt;/a&gt;', a term used to describe the impact of warm weather on a man's private parts. Apparently, the penis can appear bigger or fuller during the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/weather"&gt;heat&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;At the time, GP Dr Chun Tang, from private healthcare clinic &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.pallmallmedical.co.uk/"&gt;Pall Mall Medical&lt;/a&gt;, explained what can happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“So ‘summer penis’ is a term people use to describe when a male's penis seems a bit bigger or fuller during hot weather," the doc &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.thesun.co.uk/health/29835169/summer-penis-truth-doctor-explains-hot-weather/"&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; The Sun. “It’s not an official medical thing, just something people have noticed and talked about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“The idea is that in warmer months, especially when it’s hot and humid, the heat causes your blood vessels to expand a bit, which can make things down there look a bit different.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Dr Tang explained that the penis can look larger, especially when flaccid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Some men are suffering with 'summer long balls' (Getty Stock Photo)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“Some men notice that their penis looks a little larger, especially when it’s flaccid," he added. “Because of the increased blood flow, it might feel a bit softer or more relaxed than usual.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Turns out it's not just the penis that is susceptible to changes, but the testicles can also suffer from their own summer-induced 'condition' too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;'Summer long balls' - a term coined by The Cut - refers to men experiencing an increase in ball size during the hot weather. And apparently, it's causing a lot of discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“It sucks,” an unnamed person &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.thecut.com/article/mens-testicles-bigger-summer-long-balls.html"&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; the publication. “I wish I could wear sluttier shorts in the summer. But I can’t do so comfortably.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;And another said: “You have to make sure no one sees you grab your crotch to rearrange if you’re in public."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Some men are struggling in the hot weather (Getty Stock Photo)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The Cut reporter E.J. Dickson explained: "A man told me something a few years ago that haunts me to this day: Every summer, his balls get bigger. Not to the extent that he has to purchase new underwear or anything, but enough to make a noticeable difference when he wears trunks or loose boxers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"... Another told me he experiences a variation on summer long balls in which sweat causes the skin from his scrotum to stick to his leg, creating what he dubs a 'bat wing' effect."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Experts have since spoken out about the phenomenon, explaining that men with enlarged veins within the scrotum could be more likely to experience 'summer long balls'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“What you’re describing as summer long balls is, I suspect, really the varicocele becoming more pronounced as a result of the elevated temperature,” said urologist and surgeon, Yaniv Larish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Last year, men were contending with 'summer penis' (Getty Stock Photo)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“When you have a varicocele, the blood is not moving around efficiently, so instead of circulating around the testicle and pulling the heat away, it’s pooling up and actually insulating the testicle at an elevated temperature.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Varicoceles impact around 15 percent of men and according &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2658802/"&gt;to research&lt;/a&gt;, can decrease fertility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;They can be treated with surgery, but if you are suffering this summer, doctors recommend keeping as cool as possible and wearing snug-fitting underwear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Cleveland Clinic explain: "Varicoceles can contribute to about 40% of all cases of male infertility. However, many people with varicoceles have no problems achieving pregnancy."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 09:37:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPWGZPME9XWHVHbHlFWmdzZi1uUTRaZzFQXzUtNDJtMl9WdjAwRzhnTVFQLVYybWdEdVF3NG81bmNJQm8tWWRDcTJWdlA2ekItWENnd3daWDdHb1pQWnR0QUZtNF9GZlFQMnB5UWU5bUtFNGMxQng5UENRbGZyWnI2amFhOUNmQjA4aWlqbk44cndralN1SXlmaWhlTjM</guid></item><item><title>研究警告：常见甜味剂与发育影响有关- SciTechDaily | Study Warns: Common Sweeteners Linked to Concerning Developmental Effects - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinwFBVV95cUxPVVp2Zmg4dUtwZm9OcDhlTlJ0ZWVtejJTaGk0bmNhQzdKQ1BkUkU3c21VTXpyYWt4NW9yTW4zb29hcDdmMHFPYVlQYWpDNzBGWDZNSFc2T0d2aVItVG5qVnl0TVZWNnExcTQ5SzB1aktGNVE4VDJnbld5OE9wSE42VWVWT25TdHROU25NRjZaWEFrZWJLdHNpWTBkZ1JtY0E?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 09:30:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxPVVp2Zmg4dUtwZm9OcDhlTlJ0ZWVtejJTaGk0bmNhQzdKQ1BkUkU3c21VTXpyYWt4NW9yTW4zb29hcDdmMHFPYVlQYWpDNzBGWDZNSFc2T0d2aVItVG5qVnl0TVZWNnExcTQ5SzB1aktGNVE4VDJnbld5OE9wSE42VWVWT25TdHROU25NRjZaWEFrZWJLdHNpWTBkZ1JtY0E</guid></item><item><title>根据美国顶级胃肠病学家的说法， 7种可以改善消化和促进肠道健康的食物-印度时报 | 7 foods that can improve digestion and boost gut health, according to a top US gastroenterologist - The Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogJBVV95cUxPTFNmalRyRnM2ck5tVEdYSXRybmZNbWNGYXZaT2p5Qy15c3NSbXN1SUVEQXBrRnZnU21faG9DbnVPaE1HeUZoN0lDSlZoM1hoZ0FFWTlzb19TSGNNWjlnRngwdVV6dlZfdDBRaDc2X0d3N2VBS3Z2SDZ2end6VG9jT0k5Sk4ybW82LVYtd1dxVkk1U0ZEelFqdFJtYXZPZ2tKODlqN0xnTVRjMzhxR0xuZGR3bUhiVlVfN0ZkNG9JX3BFaE56dEN5VHQyQlRlTld6RTE5dUY2cFBYdUgtSUlnekw2WXZqM1FEZ1BzbXNuRVdITF9EdmJLbU9qX1M1aDdlZXZFUnVXMmpfbWJDa2RKZmJNVW9qek9oZ093X1RPUzNzZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you struggling with digestive issues such as bloating, constipation, or poor gut health? Well, then it's time to think about your diet. What you eat plays a significant role in your gut health. Dr. Saurabh Sethi, a California-based gastroenterologist trained at Harvard and Stanford, with over 25 years of clinical experience, has shared a list of foods that will boost gut health and improve digestion. Let’s take a look. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Lentils&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Improving gut health does not necessarily mean that it costs you an arm and a leg. You can improve your gut health without breaking your bank account. Case in point, lentils. Lentils are an affordable food, and Dr. Sethi emphasizes their high fiber and prebiotic content. These legumes support smooth digestion, stabilize blood sugar, and nourish beneficial gut microbes. You can add them to soups or salads and improve your gut health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Kefir&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;We all know that yogurt is great for &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/diet/simple-diet-changes-profound-impact-what-your-gut-wants-you-to-eat/articleshow/122580014.cms" rel="noopener" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;gut health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. But Dr. Sethi says Kefir is even better. He says it has “more diverse probiotics than yogurt.” Pick plain, unsweetened kefir for its digestive benefits. Kefir not only aids digestion but also supports mood and skin health through the gut-skin axis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adding kefir into smoothies or consuming it straight can provide a potent dose of gut-friendly bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-type="in_view" class="  "&gt;&lt;div class="EEW3_ timeline_pollWrapper_as " data-scrollga="scroll#poll_view"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="hLnAH"&gt;Poll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="KEEGr"&gt;Which gut health food would you like to try the most?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Chia seeds&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chia seeds are a nutritional powerhouse. They are packed with fiber, omega-3s, and prebiotics. The gastroenterologist calls them ‘tiny but mighty’! Their gel-forming fiber soothes the gut lining and improves stool quality, thereby improving your digestive health. Just a tablespoon soaked in water can make a big difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Red or purple cabbage (fermented or raw)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sethi recommends adding cabbage, either red or purple, to the diet for its microbiome-boosting properties. You can consume them either fermented or raw. Fermented cabbage, like sauerkraut, delivers natural probiotics, while raw cabbage provides sulforaphane, which protects the gut lining. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Green bananas or cooked, cooled potatoes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even common vegetables in your kitchen can provide good gut health. Green bananas and cooked, cooled potatoes are a great addition. They are rich in resistant starch, a prebiotic that feeds beneficial gut bacteria without spiking blood sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Bloated tummy woes? Common remedies to get rid of gas and bloating&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Seaweed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seaweed, often overlooked, is a prebiotic-rich food. They are also loaded with minerals essential for gut health. Dr. Sethi emphasizes its potential to rebuild microbiome diversity, particularly after antibiotic use. You can add seaweed to soups or consume it as snacks to support your gut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Flaxseeds (ground)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ground flaxseeds are great for gastrointestinal (GI) motility. It has fiber and lignans, which enhance gut motility and improve microbial diversity. However, Dr. Sethi &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DMOEodAuRB6/?img_index=1" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;reminds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; us to consume them ground, and not whole. You can sprinkle them on oatmeal or yogurt for a hormone-balancing, gut-friendly boost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and does not constitute medical advice. Consult a qualified healthcare professional before making dietary changes or addressing health concerns. Individual results may vary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 08:53:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogJBVV95cUxPTFNmalRyRnM2ck5tVEdYSXRybmZNbWNGYXZaT2p5Qy15c3NSbXN1SUVEQXBrRnZnU21faG9DbnVPaE1HeUZoN0lDSlZoM1hoZ0FFWTlzb19TSGNNWjlnRngwdVV6dlZfdDBRaDc2X0d3N2VBS3Z2SDZ2end6VG9jT0k5Sk4ybW82LVYtd1dxVkk1U0ZEelFqdFJtYXZPZ2tKODlqN0xnTVRjMzhxR0xuZGR3bUhiVlVfN0ZkNG9JX3BFaE56dEN5VHQyQlRlTld6RTE5dUY2cFBYdUgtSUlnekw2WXZqM1FEZ1BzbXNuRVdITF9EdmJLbU9qX1M1aDdlZXZFUnVXMmpfbWJDa2RKZmJNVW9qek9oZ093X1RPUzNzZw</guid></item></channel></rss>