<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>威斯康星大学的研究：研究人员强调了与慢性大麻使用相关的新诊断- KIRO 7 News西雅图</title><link>https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/uw-study-researchers-highlight-new-diagnosis-tied-chronic-cannabis-use/LUPADHUMVVHYHIIC4GBTERQ7SI/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="default__ArticleBody-sc-tl066j-1 jPcFTl article-body-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;SEATTLE  — &lt;a href="https://newsroom.uw.edu/blog/disabling-cannabis-condition-gets-formal-clinical-identity" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://newsroom.uw.edu/blog/disabling-cannabis-condition-gets-formal-clinical-identity"&gt;The University of Washington says&lt;/a&gt; that a condition that has been connected to chronic cannabis use has been recognized as a formal diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;Cannabis hyperemesis syndrome is a condition tied to long-term cannabis use that can cause severe stomach pain, vomiting, and nausea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;On October 1, the World Health Organization added an official diagnosis code for the syndrome to its medical manual. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;That update now gives doctors a clear way to diagnose the condition — something especially helpful for addiction researchers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more" class="taboola-read-more"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;It also lets providers spot the condition more easily by reviewing a patient’s medical history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;“It helps us count and monitor these cases,” said Beatriz Carlini, a research associate professor at the University of Washington School of Medicine who studies the health effects of cannabis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;Because the syndrome is still relatively new, many doctors aren’t familiar with it, and they’re not entirely sure why it affects some cannabis users and not others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;For treatment, doctors have found that home remedies like hot showers help with symptoms when other treatments don’t work. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more-8" class="taboola-read-more-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;Medications like Haldol, and even over-the-counter options such as capsaicin cream, can help ease symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph body-copyright"&gt;©2025 Cox Media Group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KIRO 7 News Seattle</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 01:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiywFBVV95cUxNR3U1RjZCeFREaWVrTGVuLUpBd2JkMFBpSGUydW5HY0Y3THhtZFNnbHdkY0xZUWY0WjBNalN4dzNWa3lYdnZvanNMX1NVaXFVcW1jVFlQQmdvX0xrZjcyZzBveEsySHpQT1pRdGVQN21weE5pVVRkUjE1V3BnN21BbU5mUVN5N3RNN05YNldKclpIVkNOQVlfcXVoeXNqNWQzR2dJblRiV0NfVUdtMnJFWEpDQVp4ekhsMmItWVQwMnZoN1lOX01JY1Iwb9IB3wFBVV95cUxQWE1weTlxNTVHZjlORXNaTWZfcW92bDR1ZVVRWmtKQVNvbzJZNS1sYVJYeXdmZ3E4ZnprdGpncHVNelFyakgzTXEtcXFBVUFFUFRkRHY3QXQxMU9nN2lFdHROZ0pOUkdQSHFBLV94QXBrOVRwZkZNMDdWNDk3N3NEclFNc3ZTemlHUFRMQW11NVR2ODRLLWNhQzBPbDA0ZVhBWG1wLWIwU2JyS3E4ZXJVSGZfVm5NOTIzcVRDbVdxSVZpZGtJQUlSQ3Vjb3pKTWwzVXVmQzFrNVpBZlRLNkNN</guid></item><item><title>官员确认5例麻疹病例，所有Wasatch高中学生- FOX 13 News Utah</title><link>https://www.fox13now.com/news/local-news/northern-utah/officials-confirm-5-cases-of-measles-all-wasatch-high-school-students</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="RichTextArticleBody-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;HEBER, Utah — Officials have confirmed 5 cases of Measles in Wasatch County from Wasatch High School students Saturday. Two more cases are still being evaluated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials have also confirmed that one or more of these students did attend school or school activities while infectious during school hours on November 14, 17 and 18 and a school play on Saturday on November 15.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We did have a wastewater test indicate the presence of measles in the community on November 6, and with cases existing in other parts of the state, we weren’t surprised to see cases here," said health department director Jonelle Fitzgerald. “The cases we have confirmed at the high school are not connected to each other, and because of that, we suspect that other cases may start to pop up in the community."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are the first confirmed cases of Measles in Wasatch County.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials also state that immediate action is being taken to investigate the circumstances and to limit further spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles vaccine recommendations:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="rte2-style-ul"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Children&lt;/b&gt; should receive two doses of measles vaccine: one dose at 12 to 15 months of age and another at 4 to 6 years. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adults born before 1957&lt;/b&gt; generally do not need to be vaccinated because they are likely already immune to measles due to widespread infection and illness before the measles vaccine became available in 1963. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adults who were vaccinated before 1968&lt;/b&gt; should have a second dose because the vaccine used from 1963–1967 was less effective than the current vaccine, which became available in 1968. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adults who were vaccinated in 1968 or later&lt;/b&gt; are considered fully protected whether they have one or two doses, though certain higher risk groups (college students, healthcare workers, international travelers) should have two doses.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>FOX 13 News Utah</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:16:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPNm5kYWV5WVBfb1FUNVpZUUhQWnotVzFkVkhETzlZWG1yeDltSGhXMGR0d09IcVMyTVRzRjRFdnZqczJBekRwRHpuVjZ5N3hPcVZFZ1VWa2VNQlNSRVhFQWdxSmJBOUd5bExGWWh1end0SkZid0NHMW9nUjFNdER0X19GcDVlT1dZRElEdjdsdWNyVkxkZk4zaVVBWlJ6YUJlMWloMXozNzRaTEFYel92aGpkUnN6YUJxSlh5emhhbjRCUQ</guid></item><item><title>我儿子关于无法实现这种常见身体功能的评论似乎是无害的—直到我在谷歌上搜索它的含义- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/son-remark-not-being-able-135349637.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;It all started at the dinner table one night when my 17-year-old son Gavin said, “You know what? I never burp.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Never?” I asked. He shook his head. “Nope. Never.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/lonely-not-married-happily-single-peace_n_6919e26de4b0b43a45c0cc95?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:I Was Eating Alone When A Man Came Up And Said 4 Words That Have Haunted Me Throughout My Life;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;I Was Eating Alone When A Man Came Up And Said 4 Words That Have Haunted Me Throughout My Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Of course you do,” I nearly replied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Everyone burps... don’t they?&lt;/em&gt; I thought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, I asked, “Well, does that bother you?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Sort of,” he said, shrugging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Family: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/toddler-tantrums-speech-pathologist-advice_l_68111524e4b0188fc5dab6b0?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:3 Surprisingly Simple Tricks for Deescalating And Preventing Toddler Tantrums;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;3 Surprisingly Simple Tricks for Deescalating And Preventing Toddler Tantrums&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We returned to our dinner, but his comment remained in the back of my mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Is it even possible that a person just &lt;/em&gt;can’t &lt;em&gt;burp?&lt;/em&gt; I wondered. &lt;em&gt;And, if so, does it even matter?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m not usually a worrier, and I have been guilty of trying to wait things out rather than take my kids to the doctor, not always with good results. One child turned out to have terrible strep and another one was experiencing a bad bout of pneumonia. But, in this case, because it was such an unusual comment, my mom instincts instantly kicked in. I wanted to know if this was a serious issue and, if so, what could be done to fix it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I decided to see what Google had to say on the subject, and it turns out that yes, it is possible that people can’t burp, and yes, it most definitely matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;The author with Gavin at his college graduation in 2025. &lt;span class="copyright"&gt;Courtesy of Gretchen Scherer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Columbia University Irving Medical Center, the medical name for the inability to burp is &lt;a href="https://www.columbiadoctors.org/news/what-happens-when-you-cannot-burp" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:retrograde cricopharyngeus dysfunction;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;retrograde cricopharyngeus dysfunction&lt;/a&gt; (R-CPD), which is informally known as no-burp syndrome. The diagnosis did not exist before 2019, and instead sufferers were often incorrectly diagnosed with acid reflux, irritable bowel disease or other digestive problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When most people need to let a buildup of air escape from their stomach, the cricopharyngeus muscle relaxes and allows the air to vacate. For reasons that are still somewhat mysterious, some individuals’ cricopharyngeus muscle stays tensed, so they never burp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/son-picky-eater-arfid-therapy_n_68791c50e4b09816d316744f?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:I Couldn't Get My Son To Eat Anything. I Thought He Was Just Picky — But The Truth Was Much More Serious.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;I Couldn't Get My Son To Eat Anything. I Thought He Was Just Picky — But The Truth Was Much More Serious.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The more I thought about it, the more I realized all of the ways in which Gavin’s inability to burp had impacted him throughout his life. He was a terrible spitter-upper as a baby, and he was always more of a snacker than an eater. When he was older, he rarely drank soda, especially out of a can. He also had a reputation in our family for being able to clear a room with his farts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was the smallest of our three boys, and even at the peak of his growth spurt, while he was logging endless miles as a cross-country runner, he only ever ate a small amount of food at each sitting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was common to hear Gavin say he was full after eating only half his meal. No matter how much he loved cheeseburgers, half of it would sit on his plate uneaten. Then, two hours later, he would ask me for another dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If I’m being honest, I didn’t always hide my frustration with those requests. But, luckily for both of us, I was always willing to at least make him a peanut butter and jelly sandwich (otherwise I would be wracked with guilt right now).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/dating-men-women-bisexual-lesbian_n_68e7c3d9e4b0b4458cb74288?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:When Straight Women Find Out I'm Bisexual, There's 1 Big Misconception I Often Have To Clear Up;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;When Straight Women Find Out I'm Bisexual, There's 1 Big Misconception I Often Have To Clear Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although no-burp syndrome is considered relatively rare, people who suffer from it often deal with significant symptoms. Severe bloating, throat gurgling, and terrible flatulence are some of the persistent issues, and they often become worse as a person gets older. The side effects of R-CPD can cause social anxiety and significantly impact quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few weeks after Gavin made that offhanded comment at dinner, he had his annual checkup with his pediatrician. I made sure he raised the burping issue, and Gavin described his symptoms. Unfortunately, his doctor said he’d never heard of R-CPD. Since Gavin was leaving for college the next week, we let it go.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, when Gavin came home at Christmas several months later, he brought it up again. The coping methods he had used before — frequently eating small portions and avoiding carbonated beverages — weren’t as easy to maintain at college. Along with experiencing severe bloating, he now found himself occasionally throwing up. He wanted the problem solved, and I was becoming increasingly concerned about how R-CPD could impact him as he got older, so I kept researching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you google the condition today, an AI overview will tell you everything you need to know. But even just a few years ago, it was incredibly difficult to find a solution, and some of the articles and videos I did find made me worry that it could be doing severe damage to Gavin’s health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/megyn-kelly-epstein-pedophile-grooming-assault_n_691b4443e4b0023259f639c4?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:I Was 16 When A Grown Man Groomed And Sexually Assaulted Me. I've Kept This Secret For 30 Years — Until Now.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;I Was 16 When A Grown Man Groomed And Sexually Assaulted Me. I've Kept This Secret For 30 Years — Until Now.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luckily, a friend of Gavin’s told us about a clinic near Chicago that had pioneered an experimental treatment designed to treat R-CPD by injecting Botox into the throat. We learned that the drug releases the cricopharyngeal sphincter and allows the patient to retrain the sphincter as the injectable slowly wears off. The success rate for a single procedure, which involves three shots, is over 80%, with nearly 20% needing a second procedure in order to be cured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Armed with that information, I wasted no time trying to find a doctor in Minneapolis that could perform the procedure. Before Gavin returned to the University of Wisconsin for his second semester, I had found a local physician trained to do the throat injections, and I was able to get him evaluated. The doctor numbed Gavin’s throat and performed an endoscopy. Based on that and an evaluation of Gavin’s symptoms, the doctor determined that Gavin most likely did have R-CPD and would be a great candidate for the Botox procedure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gavin headed back to college, and we began the process of getting the injections approved by the insurance company. Our hope was to have the procedure done in Minneapolis, but our insurance rejected the request because the FDA has not approved Botox for this purpose. I made many calls over the next several months to our insurance company, the Minneapolis clinic, and the clinic in Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I finally found a workaround by paying out-of-pocket for the Botox (around $600), so it wasn’t submitted as part of our insurance claim. The rest of the procedure was approved, and, in our case, was 80% covered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two days after finishing his spring exams, Gavin was on his way to the clinic in Chicago because they could see him almost immediately. Once he was there, Gavin underwent another endoscopy, watched a video that explained the procedure, and consulted with a doctor. The next morning, Gavin was put under with general anesthesia and was given three injections of Botox in his throat. Everything went smoothly, and Gavin and his dad were on their way home by 11:30 a.m. that day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;The author's son, Gavin, chugging orange soda. &lt;span class="copyright"&gt;Courtesy of Gretchen Scherer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The worst side effect from the treatment was some temporary discomfort. For the first couple of months, the esophageal sphincter is completely open, and Gavin initially described the feeling in his throat as “a little weird.” Within 24 hours, he started experiencing “micro burps,” which is the first step in retraining the cricopharyngeal sphincter. Some people also experience occasional regurgitation as they practice burping during that first week.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Patients are encouraged to burp as much as possible, so we gave Gavin full permission to burp anytime, anywhere. For most of that summer, burping was his new party trick for friends and family.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Three years after the procedure, Gavin is still burping strong, although he hasn’t quite mastered the alphabet yet. His sphincter is now completely retrained. Gavin said the procedure has been life-changing. Almost immediately, he was able to wolf down entire cheeseburgers for the first time, and the ability to drink carbonated beverages at college parties is a definite plus. I notice that he is happier in general and more energetic because he is not distracted by the discomfort that often came with eating.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I am relieved that we were able to find a solution. My Google searches had turned up stories of the extreme discomfort that some people have to live with on a daily basis. Fortunately, Gavin’s symptoms fell more on the mild to medium side of the spectrum.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The more I tell people about Gavin’s story, the less “rare” R-CPD seems. In fact, it may be more common than originally thought; at least two of my son’s friends have the same issue and one also had the procedure in Chicago. However, very few doctors are familiar with the condition and may not know enough to ask the questions that could lead to a diagnosis. Parents&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; may not even notice that a child who burped fine as a baby stopped burping as they got older.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This journey has reminded me of several important truths about being a parent. &lt;span&gt;First, don’t ignore complaints your kids make about their health — even those that seem small or nonchalant. I could have easily shrugged off Gavin’s initial comment, and I’m so glad I didn’t. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Second, doctors don’t know everything. Gavin’s pediatrician is fantastic, but he was even less familiar with no-burp syndrome than I was. I felt a little sheepish questioning him about it, but I’m really glad I kept looking for information and pushing for an answer. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Finally, don’t automatically take no for an answer from your insurance company. It took time and persistence to get an approval for (most of) Gavin’s procedure, but it was absolutely worth it in the end. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are a lot of things I’ve gotten wrong as a parent, but thankfully, this is one of the times I got things absolutely right — and Gavin would love nothing more than to take a big swig of beer and show you himself. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gretchen Scherer is a mother, English teacher, and sometimes writer living in Minneapolis, Minnesota. Her essays and travel articles have appeared in Salon.com, The St. Paul Pioneer Press, Minnesota Monthly Magazine, and a few anthologies. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Do you have a compelling personal story you’d like to see published on HuffPost? Find out what we’re looking for &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/static/how-to-pitch-huffpost" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:here;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="mailto:pitch@huffpost.com" data-ylk="slk:send us a pitch at pitch@huffpost.com.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;send us a pitch at pitch@huffpost.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Related...&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/son-no-burp-syndrome-treatment_n_68e7ce84e4b0b4458cb74b0f?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read the original on HuffPost;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Read the original on HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 22:52:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE5PRHdBck9GR1VzQWMxTi1sM1psVEdIS1FDSW95RXpUeXNlcmJFeU12bDBfQnIwY2hTZ3dZZ1U1aGN3djBETHVEZEZGdVZ2RjRjWUl3R0NZOWlhc1FIM1VMaEk0SXBmWC0zRmdvdDFPc2JWMnBOX1Mzeg</guid></item><item><title>WTOP的Neal Augenstein ： 4期肺癌诊断3年后，下一步是什么- WTOP</title><link>https://wtop.com/inside-wtop/2025/11/wtops-neal-augenstein-3-years-after-stage-4-lung-cancer-diagnosis-whats-next/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="schema-summary"&gt;During the first three years of Augenstein's lung cancer journey, he's been happy to be able to share things he has been learning along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;div id="Entry-content" class="entry-content Entry-content "&gt;
                                                
                                
                &lt;div class="paragraph-with-figure"&gt;
&lt;figure class="article_featured_image right" data-fancybox data-src="#modal-post-featured-image"&gt;
                            &lt;span class="zoom_icon"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
                            &lt;img src="https://wtop.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/IMG_1972-480x320.jpg"&gt;
                            &lt;figcaption&gt;WTOP's Neal Augenstein was diagnosed with Stage 4 lung cancer in 2022. (WTOP/Neal Augenstein)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
                        &lt;/figure&gt;
                        &lt;div id="modal-post-featured-image" class="reveal-modal" data-reveal aria-labelledby="modalTitle" aria-hidden="true" role="dialog"&gt;
                            &lt;figure class="article_featured_image modal"&gt;
                                &lt;img src="https://wtop.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/IMG_1972-780x520.jpg"&gt;
                                &lt;figcaption&gt;WTOP's Neal Augenstein was diagnosed with Stage 4 lung cancer in 2022. (WTOP/Neal Augenstein)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
                            &lt;/figure&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In my first 25 years at WTOP, my reports about lung cancer were primarily stories about famous people who died from the deadliest and second-most common cancer in the U.S. — until I was diagnosed with Stage 4 lung cancer exactly three years ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then, most of my lung cancer stories have been about living.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within six months of being diagnosed with Stage 4 non-small cell lung cancer just before Thanksgiving 2022, after great results with one-pill-a-day targeted therapy that shrank cancerous tumors and lymph nodes in both lungs, I became eligible for a robotic-assisted lung lobectomy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then, I’ve had no evidence of disease, and have remained cancer-free since May 2023, while continuing to take my daily pill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Giving thanks? Indeed.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;During the first three years of my journey, I’ve been happy to be able to share things I’ve been learning along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, is the importance of &lt;a href="https://wtop.com/health-fitness/2025/07/why-newly-diagnosed-lung-cancer-patients-should-get-this-test-done-before-starting-treatment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;newly diagnosed cancer patients getting biomarker testing&lt;/a&gt;, and waiting for the results before beginning treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biomarker testing involves testing biopsied lung tissue — often taken during a bronchoscopy — to try to learn the exact cell mutation that caused a patient’s cancer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The importance of testing is if they have that mutation, then the treatment is very different, and the patient outcomes are also much better,” thoracic medical oncologist Ram Subramanian with Inova Schar Cancer Institute in Fairfax County, Virginia, told me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my case, I was diagnosed with EGFR-positive lung cancer, which has several targeted treatments available, and generally limits the side effects of treatment compared to chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite having no evidence of cancer now, I (and my doctors) wouldn’t say that I’m “cured,” since I was originally diagnosed after cancer had spread from the original site in my left lung.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2025, life with lung cancer can be similar to life with other chronic diseases, including diabetes or heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key is aggressive surveillance, which in my case involves low-dose CT scans every four months, as well as brain MRIs and liquid biopsies twice a year. If something suspicious were to show up on one of these scans, it would likely be early-stage, which could be removed with surgery or targeted by radiation.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, while the  American Lung Association’s&lt;a href="https://www.lung.org/research/state-of-lung-cancer" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; 2025 State of Lung Cancer&lt;/a&gt; report shows the five-year survival rate for lung cancer in the U.S. has risen to 29.7%, which represents a 26% improvement over the past five years, research continues to enable earlier detection, including the&lt;a href="https://wtop.com/local/2025/11/how-ai-helps-detect-lung-cancer-sooner-improving-survival-rates/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; use of artificial intelligence&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lung cancer patients in the D.C. region are lucky — there are a &lt;a href="https://wtop.com/health-fitness/2025/04/what-cancer-patients-families-should-know-about-clinical-trials-in-the-dc-area/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;large number of clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; in Virginia, Maryland and the District, offering new options and hope for patients and their families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, while I’ve been lucky to not have any recurrences in my first three years living with cancer, I often discuss trials with my thoracic oncologist Amin Benyounes, who is the co-leader at the&lt;a href="https://www.inova.org/our-services/inova-schar-cancer/treatment-options/phase-I-program" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; Inova Schar Cancer Institute’s Phase One Program&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Benyounes said many patients considering enrollment in a clinical trial worry about the unknown: “Will this make me feel worse, will it make me feel sick, could it hurt more than it would help? Will my kids or my partner have to bear the burden of me feeling sick?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With clinical trials affording the possibilities for longer survival with fewer side effects, some patients ask, “What if I get my hopes up, and it doesn’t work?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Benyounes: “My answer to that is usually, ‘We have to take things one step at a time.’”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the same guidance he gave me when I began my cancer journey, three years ago.&lt;/p&gt;


                
                
                &lt;p class="After-content"&gt;
                                    &lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;p class="single-page__signature bottom"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Get breaking news and daily headlines delivered to your email inbox by signing up &lt;a href="https://wtop.com/newsletter-signup/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="single-page__signature bottom"&gt;© 2025 WTOP. All Rights Reserved. This website is not intended for users located within the European Economic Area.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WTOP</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 19:32:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxQVklfOU0yblJYcWVfR1psV2h5ZVF3TlZrbF9haUF4T3RnWlVjM1FqcC1aSXVIUHNsX2dQV09HSFNXYmltb1Q2azVNV1JIUk1YZnNQRmZPNDIxVVVNYWJ6aXdCbWxlQjRZUWc0MjZYWTNQdm5GWS1wQ01pMWhKX3ZPSl9qdkR0ZXhtRHJqc2pMYUJNZXM3eHpHeGR6d3l0dThsQWYtY2NIdndQT2U3LWlDRFdJa2o</guid></item><item><title>助听器可将痴呆风险降低61% ，研究称- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51409291/hearing-aids-may-reduce-dementia-risk-by-61-study-says</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;SALT LAKE CITY — Only about one in five adults who could benefit from hearing aids actually uses them. But new research shows that treating hearing loss early may do more than improve hearing — it could also protect your brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 20-year &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaneurology/fullarticle/2837714?guestAccessKey=a1f9c4ab-a0ae-4ca9-afa5-cb8c5e77afc3&amp;amp;utm_source=For_The_Media&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=ftm_links&amp;amp;utm_term=081825#xd_co_f=OWUxNzI0Y2UtNzczMi00Y2JlLTg4YWItNDQyNzVmZmZkYzc2~" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published in the Journal of the American Medical Association found that adults who started using hearing aids before age 70 had a 61% lower risk of developing dementia. The study followed thousands of people and found the strongest benefits in those who treated their hearing loss early, before it became severe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hearing loss can be gradual or it can be quickly overnight," said Richard Phillips, a hearing instrument specialist with House of Hearing in Moab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said untreated hearing loss forces the brain to work overtime, which can speed up cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott Patterson has lived with hearing loss for 20 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was always a little concerned about, well, I don't want people to see that I have hearing aids, I don't want to look older," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He recalled the moment he first received his hearing aids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I still remember getting back in my car and turning on the music and almost coming to tears because I could actually hear the full sound," Patterson said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts say hearing aids won't prevent every case of dementia, but they may be one of the simplest tools to improve communication, reduce isolation and support long-term brain health. They can even help with balance issues, reducing the risk of falls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What we've noticed is the ones that wear them all the time, you can just tell, their cognitive skills seem to be sharper, more alert," Phillips said. "It improves your life and makes the people around you a lot happier, also."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health providers recommend getting a hearing test starting around age 60 — and many clinics offer free screenings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:22:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPam5fb0V2NXZVc1VncWV2YUdTNmR1N2E4dGt3eHduODlyLXRwY0NQUDhFa3Zvalg2d1dXbE04N0NWb1U1SnJYaUV3a3hmeU9HRVZ2aGt1ZVNYbDVFTzlyWmtUMTBRSEdrRnZQQU1CQlE2U2c2ajA1ekVPc0pZeGc1b2VsOXI3N0Rrc3U3NDV6MlRBQ18yVHc</guid></item><item><title>在新泽西州城镇， “异常友好”的臭鼬狂犬病检测呈阳性- NJ.com</title><link>https://www.nj.com/mercer/2025/11/unusually-friendly-skunk-tests-positive-for-rabies-in-nj-town.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WHPLVJKOYNCBTJBF2DLP2CWKZE"&gt;A skunk reported in West Windsor Township earlier this month has tested positive for rabies, according to local officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NRS6BTTQRJD5NBLOXRDE7ZK5QI"&gt;A resident alerted police after seeing the skunk exhibit abnormal behavior near Quaker Road and University Way on Nov. 14, West Windsor Township’s Department of Human Services said in a public health advisory. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HIUY4C2QJNEM5C5DCBDMLRA2CY"&gt;The skunk did not appear injured or ill, but was acting “unusually friendly,” officials said. An unusual lack of fear is a symptom of rabies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="D2NHJZAQLBGMRDEEQ2GNVTGOVQ"&gt;According to local officials, an animal control officer promptly responded to investigate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TFHUTBOKIVCJDFDGITIZ6BB75Y"&gt;Residents are asked to notify police if they notice wildlife acting strangely, or if nocturnal animals — including opossums, raccoons and skunks — are seen during the day. They can also contact the &lt;a href="https://www.westwindsornj.org/departments/health-division" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.westwindsornj.org/departments/health-division"&gt;West Windsor Township Health Department&lt;/a&gt; for additional information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XGN2PT7WQFDQNAQCONISJ66GSQ"&gt;Officials encourage residents to keep their pet vaccinations up to date and avoid contact with wildlife. Children should be cautioned about avoiding contact with stray animals and wildlife, officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OWMNSXXPRBETJLSB4FICGJY6PQ"&gt;Residents are encouraged to also take preventative measures, such as securing trash cans, bat-proofing homes and securing pets after dark, according to officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:JHLWHQOEWFGR5IIHUBUXT2CG4A" data-fusion-component="JHLWHQOEWFGR5IIHUBUXT2CG4A"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:JHLWHQOEWFGR5IIHUBUXT2CG4A" data-fusion-component="JHLWHQOEWFGR5IIHUBUXT2CG4A"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NJ.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOa2lYV2hSQ1UzX0wtNmFEMElTVk9uRXR3MUQyZ01ORnFiODhCWXpFNTFPamxUdUF4RjBaNm1hMVlxLS1WY05wMnE0azl3Ni03eWY3aVllY3R1OFJwUUozNFdLeFZEbDZnNFNoa3FDR3FaOHVzbGRtRlpSdUk2T2FVZzA5b3hCc3kySHhfeEY4VjBfMW1kaHd3N2x6QlNVRmx3OGfSAbYBQVVfeXFMTkJIZjN6ckhuczVNSllQTFo1RFFxbDlzS041YzNPOXlUNDJYdWxuX2w2VEhIQkxlVzR0aFhSNVRTcGstY3BNNU8tcS0tZ3NnYVQzdzdhMkR2OTFNaERsTWVxMGg2WHBReTdrRFlma3Q4VXRYQTY3S0pGOWdiSi1BTUhXeDhBVFhqeG1YQjF6SWZTRmc4YVJDNEdmaTZCNkhjX040M1lxSEYxRXJTenJQNTlTbzAtSHc</guid></item><item><title>7种科学支持的方式，让您在60天内变得更年轻- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/fashion-and-beauty/r-t-7-science-backed-ways-to-be-younger-looking-in-60-days/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;A couple of years ago, after a long week of travel, I caught my reflection in a hotel elevator mirror and thought, “Wow… when did I start looking this tired?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not older. Just tired.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And if you have ever had a similar moment, you know the feeling. Aging is not something we control, but how old we look is a different story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Science says we have more influence over that than most people realize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, I want to break down seven science-backed strategies you can use over the next 60 days to look fresher, healthier, and yes, younger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ready to turn back the clock a little?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1) Improve your sleep quality&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the funny thing about sleep: you do not notice how much it affects your face until you are not getting enough of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But dermatologists do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sleep is basically your body’s overnight anti aging treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Growing up in the restaurant world, I used to believe that pushing through exhaustion was just part of the hustle. But when I finally cleaned up my sleep routine, my dark circles faded within weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A 60 day upgrade you can try: Set a &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/m-if-you-were-taught-these-5-things-growing-up-your-parents-were-more-intelligent-than-most/"&gt;consistent bedtime&lt;/a&gt;, keep your room cool, and avoid screens at least 45 minutes before bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are like me and sometimes read nonfiction before sleep, switch to a physical book. Your skin will thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2) Boost hydration (from the inside and out)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever looked at yourself after a salty meal, long flight, or a few glasses of something fun and noticed your face looked puffier? I have, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hydration is one of those unsexy tips we all know, but it is also one of the fastest ways to &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/nat-if-you-want-to-be-younger-looking-in-60-days-start-practicing-these-8-daily-habits/"&gt;look more youthful&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Higher water intake increases skin hydration and improves overall appearance, especially in people who previously drank less than the recommended daily amount.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moisturizing topically also makes a noticeable difference within days. When the outer layer of skin is well hydrated, it reflects more light. That means you literally glow more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A quick 60 day fix: Add one extra liter of water to your day and use a moisturizer with hyaluronic acid. It holds up to 1,000 times its weight in water and naturally plumps the skin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3) Eat more antioxidant rich foods&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is something I learned working in luxury food: you can enjoy incredible meals without sacrificing your health or your skin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And when it comes to looking younger, antioxidants matter. Oxidative stress accelerates skin aging, while antioxidants like vitamins C and E help neutralize that damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Foods high in antioxidants include berries, &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/food-and-drink/k-if-someone-refuses-to-eat-these-8-foods-as-an-adult-you-know-they-grew-up-spoiled-and-undisciplined/"&gt;leafy greens&lt;/a&gt;, nuts, dark chocolate, tomatoes, olives, and coffee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my favorite parts of traveling is sampling different local foods. Whether I was eating street market papaya in Thailand or an incredible tomato salad in Italy, I noticed the same thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People with diets full of colorful produce tend to have that naturally vibrant, youthful look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Try this for 60 days: Add at least two more servings of antioxidant rich fruits or veggies to your daily meals. Your skin tone can noticeably improve in as little as eight weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4) Use sunscreen daily (yes, even indoors)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-81052" src="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973.png" alt="" srcset="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973.png 1600w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-300x158.png 300w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-1024x538.png 1024w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-768x403.png 768w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-1536x806.png 1536w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-1200x630.png 1200w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-857x450.png 857w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-900x473.png 900w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-420x221.png 420w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-840x441.png 840w" sizes="(max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nobody loves hearing this, but UV exposure is responsible for up to 80 percent of visible skin aging according to the World Health Organization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And here is the surprising part. Indoor light sources, including the blue light from your computer or phone, can contribute to pigmentation and collagen breakdown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/fashion-and-beauty/a-10-subtle-beauty-habits-of-women-who-age-gracefully/"&gt;Daily sunscreen use&lt;/a&gt; not only protects skin but can actually reverse existing signs of aging over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I grew up thinking sunscreen was only for the beach. Now it is the first thing I put on each morning. It is like brushing your teeth. If you skip it, you will eventually see the consequences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A simple 60 day commitment: Wear a broad spectrum SPF 30 or higher every day, even when it is cloudy or you are staying inside. You will start noticing more even skin tone and less dullness faster than you think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5) Strength train 3 to 4 times a week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one might sound like it is about your body rather than your face. But the connection is real.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10290068/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;study found&lt;/a&gt; that resistance training actually changes gene expression in skin cells, making them behave more like younger cells. Participants saw improvements in skin structure and thickness within 16 weeks, with visible changes even earlier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strength training also boosts circulation, helping nutrients reach your skin more efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working out has always been my reset button. But once I learned it helps skin function like it is younger, it became a non negotiable part of my routine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your 60 day plan: Include at least two full body strength sessions per week. Even 20 minute routines count. Think push ups, squats, dumbbell presses. Simple movements with big impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your posture improves, your muscle tone improves, and your overall vitality becomes visible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6) Reduce added sugar&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know. This one stings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love pastries. I love crafted desserts. I love exploring bakeries when I travel. I am not giving any of that up and I am not telling you to either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But added sugar, especially in excess, ages your skin faster through a process called glycation. Glycation damages collagen and elastin, the proteins that keep your skin firm and youthful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/387242540_The_Impact_of_Excessive_Sugar_Consumption_on_Skin_Health_Analysis_of_Biological_Mechanisms_and_Dermatological_Effects" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;A study in&lt;/a&gt; Clinical Dermatology links high sugar intake to accelerated skin aging and deeper wrinkles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is what I noticed when I cut back, not eliminated but reduced. My skin stopped looking inflamed. The puffiness around my eyes dropped. Even my jawline looked a little sharper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A realistic 60 day challenge: Reduce added sugar Monday through Friday. Enjoy your treats on the weekend. It is flexible, sustainable, and your skin will show the difference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7) Manage stress intentionally&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stress eventually shows up on your face. That is not poetic. It is biological.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cortisol breaks down collagen and increases inflammation. Chronic stress does not just make you feel older.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7400286/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Research from&lt;/a&gt; the International Journal of Molecular Sciences confirms that it literally makes you look older faster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The real question is how do you lower stress without disappearing to a beach in Bali for two months?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me, it comes down to tiny, daily habits. Five minute breathing sessions. Short walks with my phone left behind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saying no more often. Reading a chapter of something interesting instead of scrolling endless feeds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Little moments that help my nervous system settle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Try a 60 day approach: Pick one simple stress relief ritual and practice it daily. Meditation, breathwork, journaling, even cooking something nourishing can work. It does not need to be complicated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will feel better and people will start asking why you look so refreshed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking younger in 60 days is not a miracle. It is a byproduct of stacking small, evidence based habits that improve your health &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/r-7-rules-to-live-by-if-you-want-to-glow-from-the-inside-out-in-your-70s-and-beyond/"&gt;from the inside out&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Better sleep. Better hydration. Better food. Better protection. Better movement. Better balance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing extreme. Nothing trendy. Just science and consistency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you stick to even a few of these habits for the next two months, you will not just look younger. You will feel younger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that is the real goal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-2917581504"&gt;&lt;p&gt;				 &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong data-start="380" data-end="431"&gt;If You Were a Healing Herb, Which Would You Be?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="380" data-end="651"&gt;Each herb holds a unique kind of magic — soothing, awakening, grounding, or clarifying.&lt;br data-start="521" data-end="524"&gt;This 9-question quiz reveals the healing plant that mirrors your energy right now and what it says about your natural rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="653" data-end="734"&gt;✨ Instant results. Deeply insightful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 			&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 17:02:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOYTZlTlRGeWt0Y1Ruc2FqdmpCQ1hiUFRSY1dDUWhVVTJVbEN6TVJBNXJoYUdlWkhzM1pQVWJDN3l0b3Q4c2dpUUY4N0VRb3Zmck82Y3B2ZWlQcDU2Zzl1RDV2X3RoRVpkV21jRmQ5ekhrajVsLUxwc3p1UFlqSHBCUURzN2xDRXhacVNVc3pOQm0tRDRNaEplbFZhSzlXdExIMnc</guid></item><item><title>医生解释慢性饮酒对肝脏的影响： “您的肝脏将酒精代谢成有毒物质……” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/doctor-explains-what-chronic-alcohol-consumption-does-to-your-liver-your-liver-metabolises-alcohol-into-a-toxic-101763825596996.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/doctor-explains-what-chronic-alcohol-consumption-does-to-your-liver-your-liver-metabolises-alcohol-into-a-toxic-101763825596996.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you drink alcohol regularly and have noticed your belly starting to bulge, it may be more than just &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/udaipur-dietician-shares-5-healthy-breakfast-habits-that-may-actually-be-unhealthy-and-cause-bloating-or-fatigue-101763270272792.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="bloating"&gt;bloating &lt;/a&gt;- it could be a warning sign from your liver. While most people know &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fitness-trainer-warns-against-working-out-after-drinking-alcohol-or-without-rest-shares-7-worst-times-to-work-out-101763796483753.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="alcohol"&gt;alcohol &lt;/a&gt;isn’t great for the body, few realise how quickly regular drinking can trigger cell damage, scarring, and serious liver dysfunction. In some cases, that expanding belly can signal fluid buildup caused by advanced &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/liver-disease" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="liver"&gt;liver &lt;/a&gt;injury, a condition that demands immediate medical attention.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/22/550x309/beer_1763826073421_1763826073638.jpg" alt="Find out the various stages of liver damage caused due to alcohol!(Unsplash)" title="Find out the various stages of liver damage caused due to alcohol!(Unsplash)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/22/550x309/beer_1763826073421_1763826073638.jpg" alt="Find out the various stages of liver damage caused due to alcohol!(Unsplash)" title="Find out the various stages of liver damage caused due to alcohol!(Unsplash)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Find out the various stages of liver damage caused due to alcohol!(Unsplash)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/hepatologist-says-drink-coffee-first-thing-in-the-morning-even-on-an-empty-stomach-debunks-5-myths-about-coffee-101763807975245.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Hepatologist says ‘Drink coffee first thing in the morning, even on an empty stomach…’; debunks 5 myths about coffee"&gt;Hepatologist says ‘Drink coffee first thing in the morning, even on an empty stomach…’; debunks 5 myths about coffee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Kunal Sood, an anaesthesiologist and interventional pain medicine physician, has explained what really happens to your body when you drink alcohol. In an Instagram video posted on November 22, the doctor explains how chronic alcohol consumption affects the liver and highlights the various stages of liver damage.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Effects of chronic alcohol consumption&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to Dr Sood, when you drink alcohol, your liver breaks it down into a toxic compound that can damage liver cells. Regular alcohol consumption can lead to liver scarring and even cause liver cells to die. The doctor explains, “When you drink, your liver metabolises alcohol into acetaldehyde, a toxic substance that can damage your liver cells. With chronic alcohol consumption, your liver cells will become overwhelmed, leading to scarring and cell death.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;First sign of liver damage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Sood emphasises that chronic alcohol consumption can cause serious liver damage, with the earliest signs often appearing as fat buildup in the liver. He states, “The first sign of this damage is fatty liver or fat building up in the liver. If drinking continues, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/nhs-surgeon-explains-real-reason-you-cant-shake-off-inflammation-simply-the-types-of-foods-that-you-are-101763622363895.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="inflammation"&gt;inflammation &lt;/a&gt;will occur, leading to alcoholic &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/world-news/us-news/trump-trolled-for-misspelling-hepatitis-while-talking-about-womens-health-won-t-be-taking-medical-advice-from-101761547207044.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="hepatitis"&gt;hepatitis&lt;/a&gt;. Over time, scarring develops leading to liver cirrhosis which will severely impact normal liver function.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Advanced liver damage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Sood notes that in the later stages of liver damage, fluid can accumulate in the abdomen, causing a visibly distended or bulging belly - a sign that requires urgent medical attention.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; He explains, “At this advanced stage, complications like ascites, which is fluid buildup in the abdomen, can occur. Ascites happens because &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/gastroenterologist-warns-liver-cirrhosis-can-affect-your-brain-leading-to-symptoms-like-personality-changes-tremors-101755491343083.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="cirrhosis"&gt;cirrhosis &lt;/a&gt;reduces blood flow to the liver, which will increase pressure in nearby blood vessels causing fluid to leak into the abdominal cavity. This will usually require immediate medical attention.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. It is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 15:44:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAJBVV95cUxOWnFiVTdwaHZaYXZkcm0wd0w4OHg1azY4MGpxc3hndi1YX2hxVG51eDhwRXJQS3NDRjdQRGk5TnI5Y3FuR2Jlenh5R3ZIaWFNVzVuMGpNU0hud2loek05MGh1NzltTVQtbjlIcFlvaXdJS1JwT1B2NXlMME1IMkdHVmlpVHN2dWhYMkNmeGVZWUZsMUptNWxSeTZ6WUtYbmlZZk5EVExJREhqalZDMkR1cFVjVVBfeWdRTl9VcTFUTDhRbmpLNHppRkRla3YxZTdPc2xkT3hLX3ZuS05Dbk1OdEZIVUY2ZjNkVWk3UEMyQ3E0Rmh6OW5Ka0JQYnk3VTVFeV81c1dNV0pyZXlD0gGSAkFVX3lxTE8ycDBvWkVWZTltZFNmZTkyMUNwTTc0TmlnUnJHOEhhQ3B2dXhOVUR6cjdlbnVTdHFzVTFnOWFyNE11NWFoOWRrdHZXNEI2TVlMSWs3NDFIMzFyTzFwWG1qUkktSUpRMU9iYmMxLVN3WW5ROGxWbnNiaXk3cUJpbVM5TU8xcTBkc3BzR284Zy03WVE3bGk5R1NQTnJ0bDJuQUhITXpHSkJsNVJrdXBJVHc3aERNNGNPb3RwVmhmTlhGSDc0djV0d0xtQVFnN3NXbmhkYkYxenlYMWdXTklQbkFwenl3MjdpdkpPQlhjNG9tSFRSQlE5YzcwQUpIeXo5a2ZqWm9waU9MYjBzR1ZIX2xkVHc</guid></item><item><title>排名：美国十大主要死亡原因-视觉资本家</title><link>https://www.visualcapitalist.com/americas-leading-causes-of-death/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Visual Capitalist</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 15:36:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTE9KeU1kLUFJMkVrV2lzalVkVEJtbURQeERMVTdCSmVxeFJnV1JFM1ZEYmFFeEtXUnhLWFhNVENRODByR214U192cERBbF94OFY4VDZ5eWRMZFdDd3M4WjF1TENSLWxGVG55cmFRMnd5R0QzZWlz</guid></item><item><title>西海岸卫生联盟，卫生部敦促对疫苗的信任，反对疾病预防控制中心的声明- KOMO</title><link>https://komonews.com/news/local/vaccines-and-autism-robert-f-kennedy-jr-president-trump-tylenol-washington-state-department-of-health-statement-on-vaccine-safety-and-autism-claims</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;OLYMPIA, Wash.  — &lt;/span&gt;The Washington State Department of Health (DOH), along with the West Coast Health Alliance, continue to strongly recommend vaccines to protect children, despite the Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) statement "Vaccines do not cause autism." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the CDC, scientific studies have not ruled out the possibility that infant &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccine-safety/about/autism.html" target="_blank"&gt;vaccines contribute to the development of autism.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Washington state health officials note that rigorous research of millions of people in multiple countries over decades provides high-quality evidence that vaccines are not linked to autism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The West Coast Health Alliance said they are "deeply concerned about inaccurate claims to the contrary recently posted on the federal Centers for Disease Control and Prevention website." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;READ MORE | &lt;a href="https://komonews.com/news/nation-world/cdc-updates-page-to-say-vaccines-do-not-cause-autism-isnt-an-evidence-based-claim-health-and-human-services-robert-f-kennedy-jr-donald-trump" target="_blank"&gt;CDC updates page to state 'vaccines do not cause autism' isn't an evidence-based claim&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We join health agencies and associations across the country, including the American Academy of Pediatrics and the Autism Science Foundation, in confirming that there is no credible scientific evidence linking vaccines to autism. Claims suggesting a link between vaccines and autism undermine public confidence, reduce immunization rates, and contribute to outbreaks of vaccine-preventable diseases. " DOH said in a statement Friday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US Health &amp;amp; Human Services Department Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. announced in April that the agency would be launching an investigation into autism and potential causes of the disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy has been a vaccine skeptic for years and has linked some vaccines to autism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In September, during a press conference, &lt;a href="https://thenationaldesk.com/news/americas-news-now/despite-autism-warnings-from-trump-doctors-say-pregnant-women-can-safely-take-tylenol#" target="_blank"&gt;President Donald Trump advised pregnant women not to take Tylenol &lt;/a&gt;because it could be linked to a spike in autism. Health professionals pushed back on Trump's assertion that pregnant women should avoid taking Tylenol or risk having an autistic baby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Washington state health officials, Autism is a complex condition with multiple contributing genetic and environmental factors. Attributing it to any single cause is inaccurate and misleading, DOH said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Decades of research and large-scale studies consistently show no association between vaccination and an increased risk of autism, according to DOH. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Vaccines are thoroughly tested and remain one of the most important tools we have for preventing infectious diseases. They represent one of the greatest public health achievements in history, having saved millions of lives and prevented illness and lifelong disability," DOH said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KOMO</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 15:01:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwJBVV95cUxNMVA2ZDZKYnVxTko1ZjlHMXF5LVhiMC1RV1NrN1JLdzZfVUswRVBHVzU2WGppNVJpZHJpYUExU0NaV2t2TllKbnNqUU1GZVNWcEIwVGlvTXJJRzBKUUhtR3N0eTQ1SXVoeE1XM1FfQmZtVHM2Qmd1bWZNSm1MSjR5RGVNQ1gza2ZwWVMzNXB6dmFLMTNuZTFVNUljdFZRZUZyaEs4MFMwaGxIVFAtSm5VSE9wTklyUVdaVWlJUlNzWVFzQ0xHUGFraVNWZmZHc1FPYWdQNF9JNnFYUWNsa0JTc1FzeFhEaHhHc1l3UFRCVnhJT1BOblJhRDQ3cmpZbXg0c0Y2d3J3ZU9CV1k</guid></item><item><title>专家警告“严重”的流感季节，担心新的流感病毒-独立报</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/h3n2-virus-flu-season-new-strain-b2870479.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 bxpovR sc-jbiisr-1" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 dFpFuY"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 iBibVd"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 jVZWGn"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 juUDRT"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 cqPbFA"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 rAFIl sc-hez36s-16 jZSKtc"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 PdmgT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 eZqxmv"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 tawua"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 gZmYS"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 cglitp"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 keLMOw sc-aja53j-7 eMEmGu"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 dHXFkr"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 gyGWOu"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 hUgQwJ sc-culv3z-0 eifaJK sc-a5wy94-0 hyKPon"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US flu season has begun slowly, but health experts are concerned following the emergence of a new viral strain, according to U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) data released on Friday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An early analysis suggests current vaccines may still be somewhat effective against this new version, which is driving recent infections. However, many scientists and medical professionals are more worried about disappointing vaccination rates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These low rates were a main reason for the unusually high flu hospitalisations and deaths last winter, making it one of the deadliest seasons this century.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think we’re going to see a really severe season," said Asefeh Faraz Covelli of the &lt;a href="/topic/george-washington-university"&gt;George Washington University&lt;/a&gt; School of Nursing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last winter, the overall flu hospitalization rate was the highest seen since the H1N1 flu pandemic 15 years ago. &lt;a href="/topic/flu"&gt;Flu&lt;/a&gt; was the underlying or a contributing cause of more than 18,000 deaths, and one seven-day stretch early this year saw more than 1,800 deaths — the highest one-week spike in at least a decade. Child flu deaths also were far higher than usual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CDC data posted Friday showed low flu activity so far, with only one state — &lt;a href="/topic/louisiana"&gt;Louisiana&lt;/a&gt; — reporting moderate activity. Most of the reported infections have been in children, said the CDC's Alicia Budd, who tracks flu infections for the &lt;a href="/topic/atlanta"&gt;Atlanta&lt;/a&gt;-based agency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most also have been a new version of the type A H3N2 virus that historically has caused the most hospitalizations and deaths in older people. That type is responsible for most flu infections so far this year, and more than half have been a new subclade K variant that is different from the strain this year's flu shots were built to fight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 lkuiwY"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/20/16/25/GettyImages-1237727981.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/20/16/25/GettyImages-1237727981.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/20/16/25/GettyImages-1237727981.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="A woman arrives at a CVS pharmacy past a sign about free flu and Covid-19 vaccines on January 14, 2022 in Monterey Park, California." class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-244129"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;A woman arrives at a CVS pharmacy past a sign about free flu and Covid-19 vaccines on January 14, 2022 in Monterey Park, California.&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (AFP/Getty)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A preliminary analysis from the &lt;a href="/topic/united-kingdom"&gt;United Kingdom&lt;/a&gt; suggests the shots do provide at least partial protection, although it will take some time for scientists to know exactly how effective they are. Experts say any protection that softens the blow of a flu infection is important to get.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flu seasons tend to get bad between December and February, and illnesses likely will accelerate as people travel and gather for Thanksgiving, Covelli said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think it’s going to start picking up here,” she said. “This is the ideal time to get vaccinated.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers this year have been facing an unusual struggle to get a handle on how respiratory infection and vaccination rates have been trending.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They usually rely on the CDC for data, but a recent government shutdown halted data collection and reporting just as respiratory infections started ramping up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, government efforts to promote disease-preventing shots have been more limited since U.S. Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. was put in charge of the CDC and other federal health agencies. Kennedy, a leading anti-vaccine activist, has fostered uncertainty about the safety of vaccines, including flu shots that contained a preservative called thimerosal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 hcSZFO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/20/15/CDC_Autism_16106.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/20/15/CDC_Autism_16106.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/20/15/CDC_Autism_16106.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="US Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr." class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-244130"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;US Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr.&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (AP)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, vaccination rates against COVID-19 clearly continue to plummet, with about 6% of children and 14% of adults up to date on their shots, according to other CDC data posted Friday. Each figure is about 3 percentage points less than it was at this point last fall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the flu, vaccination trends are a little muddier. Some sources have suggested flu vaccinations are down. Over two million fewer flu shots were given at U.S. pharmacies through the end of October compared to last year, according to data from IQVIA, a health information and research company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the latest CDC data indicates that for children, the vaccination rate this year is about the same as it was at this point last fall, at 34%. And the vaccination rate for adults is up a few percentage points to about 37%, according to the CDC data, which relies on survey information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-iii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is early in the season and too early to know if the increase will be sustained or what is causing it, CDC officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of the beginning of November, the U.S. flu hospitalization rate is about the same as it was at the same point in 2024. Hospitalization rates for COVID-19 and another respiratory virus, RSV, are lower so far this season, according to another set of CDC data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPdXRHcFdibHRLZ192WndlRUROTS1TMzVfM0VqNmtwbDNwSVhGOEZFT0ZBSXRndUJlZ2txcmUxSlQydlRXTWRGM1l4djdWdXZpZ1M2VUtnTGFwTTJfaDdJTFdDS2pnZjFyRWJFZDJqU1YwVER3b0MyUXBMc1RqMkFwejdJOHRCNjNqR25RRjR0Z1ZNUQ</guid></item><item><title>糖尿病前期可以在2年内逆转：当你继续欺骗时，你的身体会产生安静的新陈代谢变化-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/prediabetes-can-be-reversed-within-2-years-the-quiet-metabolic-changes-your-body-makes-when-you-stay-consistent/articleshow/125500852.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prediabetes has become an increasingly important area of focus in public health, largely because it sits at a crossroads between normal metabolic function and type 2 diabetes. It is defined by raised blood glucose levels that fall short of the diagnostic threshold for diabetes, yet indicate a shift in how the body processes sugar. This stage often develops quietly, particularly in urban populations where dietary habits, long work hours and reduced movement are common. Although the condition signals an elevated risk, emerging evidence shows that it remains a phase in which the body can still respond positively to sustained lifestyle improvements. Understanding how reversal occurs and why it often takes around two years helps clarify both the biological process and the practical steps that support long-term change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How metabolic flexibility helps the body reverse prediabetes&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prediabetes develops when the body begins to lose its usual glucose handling efficiency, yet retains enough metabolic flexibility to recover with time and effort. Many people at this stage still show partial insulin sensitivity, particularly in muscle cells, which means that healthier behaviours can help the body use glucose more effectively. By reducing excess calorie intake, improving sleep and incorporating moderate movement across the week, glucose fluctuations become less severe and insulin production faces less pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; These shifts allow the pancreas and liver to adjust gradually rather than react to constant metabolic stress. Recovery is often subtle and may involve extended periods where progress feels slow, although the internal changes accumulate steadily over months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What this means for metabolic recovery:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prediabetes involves impaired but still responsive glucose regulation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Partial insulin sensitivity helps the body react positively to lifestyle adjustments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improvements in diet, sleep and activity reduce the strain on insulin production.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recovery unfolds slowly, which explains why noticeable change takes time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Long term evidence showing &lt;keyword id="28344744" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="prediabetes-reversal" source="Orion"&gt;prediabetes reversal&lt;/keyword&gt; in two years&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A decade-long retrospective cohort study from an urban Indian community &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s40200-025-01790-7" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;published in Journal of Diabetes and Metabolic Disorders&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, examined how prediabetes progressed in real-world conditions. The results demonstrated that many individuals reverted to normal glucose levels within roughly two years when they maintained routine screening and reasonable lifestyle improvements. The study highlighted that dramatic changes were not essential. Instead, the most influential factor was consistency, even when actions were modest. Regular checks kept individuals informed, which helped them stay engaged with their progress, while simple adjustments such as reducing portion sizes or adding short walks had measurable metabolic effects. The study’s timeline of around two years reflects the period needed for pancreatic function, body weight and glucose processing to adapt to healthier patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Key insights from the long-term evidence:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regular screening helps people track gradual shifts in blood sugar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Steady lifestyle adjustments deliver significant metabolic benefits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Biological changes in glucose control align with a two-year adaptation period.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Community-based data shows that sustained habits outperform short-term interventions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How urban living affects prediabetes reversal&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Urban environments create a blend of challenges and opportunities for individuals hoping to reverse prediabetes. Long commutes, high stress and sitting for extended hours often contribute to rising glucose levels. At the same time, cities offer health resources that can support recovery, including nutrition counselling, regular medical facilities, fitness centres and organised screenings. People who manage to integrate small changes into their daily routines, such as replacing processed meals with nutrient-rich alternatives or incorporating regular brisk walking, usually show more stable glucose patterns over time. Even modest shifts create a favourable environment for the body to regulate blood sugar more effectively, especially when combined with periodic check-ups that track progress and encourage accountability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How urban factors influence reversal:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;City living contains risk factors such as inactivity and high stress but also valuable health resources.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Small behavioural shifts, like daily walking, help improve glucose management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Access to medical guidance and screening increases the likelihood of reversal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Habit formation across two years helps counter the metabolic effects of urban routines.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How the body adapts slowly during prediabetes reversal&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reversing prediabetes takes time because metabolic function adapts gradually, not instantly. When individuals increase physical activity, their muscles become more capable of pulling glucose out of the bloodstream. Meanwhile, long-term improvements in diet reduce stored fat in the liver, lowering insulin resistance and giving the pancreas the support it needs to produce insulin more efficiently. Fat tissue itself undergoes changes, becoming less inflamed and more responsive to hormonal signals that regulate glucose. These internal adjustments require continuous reinforcement, which is why brief bursts of effort followed by lapses tend to halt progress. Consistent behaviour is the most reliable driver of improvement, and the two-year timeframe mirrors the natural pace at which tissues recover healthier function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Important take-homes about long-term adaptation:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Muscles, liver and fat tissue depend on repeated signals to improve glucose handling.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Long-term behaviour patterns produce more durable results than short, intense efforts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Insulin sensitivity recovers slowly, which aligns with the two-year reversal trend.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gradual biological readjustment makes consistent lifestyle habits essential.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How shared routines and guidance help sustain improvement&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reversal of prediabetes also depends on the environment surrounding an individual, not just personal habits. Access to supportive community networks, group-based wellness activities and culturally relevant dietary guidance can make lifestyle shifts easier to maintain. Many people benefit from social reinforcement, whether through neighbourhood walking groups, workplace health initiatives or family routines that encourage more balanced meals. These forms of support help individuals stay motivated across the long period required for the body to readjust. Health systems that offer regular follow-up visits, early screening and clear communication further increase the likelihood of improvement, particularly in settings where diabetes risk is widespread and long-term prevention is a public health priority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What strengthens the chance of reversal:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Social support helps people maintain lifestyle changes consistently.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Group activities and shared routines create accountability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regular follow-up visits reinforce long-term motivation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Community access to health education strengthens early prevention efforts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for informational purposes only and should not be considered medical advice. Please consult a healthcare professional before making any changes to your diet, medication, or lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/diet/could-a-low-glutamate-diet-help-reduce-migraines-for-people-living-with-frequent-headaches/articleshow/125491500.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Could a low-glutamate diet help reduce migraines for people living with frequent headaches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgJBVV95cUxPNDBoRDFCUVhYeldNZTFWeHVpdGh4akVkNkpreWVLT19uRW9jalRsb2h2NjNMNzU2Q3EyM2hTbXZnQ2I2Skw0ZWhDTGxtQ01xWGpGSDhUMjhrYmVvSzVkSFI0ZkFhYk42V29pZXlSeGg3WG9XeE9kOVF3U1Y0R2hGU0tEcVVZRE1UNFE4cnVlVFBNY2s5LUluNmZDVzB6b3RrWFlXYl9ld05OY3didkZtMHhrdUIwNnhtaU1fUkdBWEF3Q05pSVktTVFUQ2kxcDhTQThaXzI5aXpnT3B5QU1KWGRiS3ZLb19DZ0xxb3VCVkRiaFJFUlZubGFla0JvRVRENkZmc1FYNEo4OVRYa3EtazJXdFNrSHZ5N2dHZ0FJWHZHQ3pXWWxZbDFhN0ktUXVybDVCZEN30gG7AkFVX3lxTE9RS3VnSDE1aEJhLWRaU0c2ZFY4QXpQMHd1eGVLaXdNbTNOdWF6RHc1NWc1UXhqVVNxQ2xKTW51eTlqMkM1Wm5nd0pjUm1uT0ZYUkV1ejVoYmpQejBhZXN2RGxtMW4zd2VIWVJ2LW96em9xVTlucVp4Tmp2NlJBZmhRelktYUFMeW5TbHBFcEtQZlpzSExDVm02UVpEem0zS0RsRTdxb0d1dFQ4X1JiZlpHdERMcTZDb3lDOWVIQ2ZGSl9CdnZvckNaS1JVbzhfRTNxWVRJd0Y4MnI0dmRzaTNpcFpsUDVnam1xUDhwMmc2NEZkUzYtMnE2dm9lNVBDRlRUTDlJd2xjYXpFZUZ4cmtWbm5UOXFyc0VvTUMzV3VFNEtQRjBLWHJMbnZSUW1mVjVMdUotanAxdlRPOA</guid></item><item><title>给予实验性混合治疗的小鼠治愈的1型糖尿病- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/type-1-diabetes-cured-in-mice-given-experimental-hybrid-treatment</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A specially devised hybrid treatment has shown tremendous potential for treating &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/type-1-diabetes-may-be-triggered-by-bacterial-infections-scientists-find"&gt;type 1 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; in mice, scoring full marks at preventing the condition in prediabetic animals and at reversing the condition in animals with fully developed  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="182304" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What makes the new approach stand out is that it successfully combines immune system cells from both the patient mouse and a donor mouse, encouraging them to live in harmony without a need for &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Immunosuppressive_drug"&gt;immunosuppressive drugs&lt;/a&gt; for at least four months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers behind the work, led by a team from the Stanford School of Medicine, are hopeful the same approach could be successful in humans too. The treatment might also have potential for other procedures where &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/uks-first-liver-transplant-for-advanced-bowel-cancer-removes-all-traces-of-the-disease"&gt;transplants are required&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/breakthrough-diabetes-treatment-may-deliver-insulin-through-a-skin-cream"&gt;Breakthrough Diabetes Treatment May Deliver Insulin Through a Skin Cream&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We believe this approach will be transformative for people with type 1 diabetes or other autoimmune diseases, as well as for those who need solid organ transplants," &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/all-news/2025/11/type-1-diabetes-cure.html"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; developmental biologist Seung Kim, from the Stanford School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Type 1 diabetes is caused by the body's own &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/4-out-of-5-autoimmune-patients-are-female-the-x-chromosome-could-explain-why"&gt;immune system malfuncting&lt;/a&gt;, triggering an attack on pancreatic cells called beta islets, which produce insulin. While healthy donor islets can be transplanted into the body, they also risk being attacked, if not completely rejected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_182308" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-182308" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/TransplantAbstract.jpg" alt="Transplant abstract" class="wp-image-182308 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/TransplantAbstract.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/TransplantAbstract-600x520.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-182308" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Animals were given a conditioning treatment to prepare their immune systems for the cell transplant. (Bhagchandani et al., &lt;em&gt;J. Clin. Invest.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this recent experiment, researchers subtly rebooted the mice's immune systems, preparing them before the transplant with an immune system inhibitor, a low dose of radiation, and a few select  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/antibody" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73081" data-postid="182304" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;antibodies&lt;/a&gt;, as well as combining blood  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/stem-cells" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73034" data-postid="182304" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;stem cells&lt;/a&gt; and islet cells from another animal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, the transplanted cells weren't attacked as foreign invaders, and the immune system began &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-have-discovered-a-special-type-of-immune-cell-that-slows-aging"&gt;functioning normally&lt;/a&gt; again. While a small subset of islet cells showed some signs of inflammation, this critical tissue also wasn't attacked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to not only replace the islets that have been lost but also reset the recipient's immune system to prevent ongoing islet cell destruction," &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/all-news/2025/11/type-1-diabetes-cure.html"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Kim. "Creating a hybrid immune system accomplishes both goals."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-181305" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-600x315.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The experiment represents a number of wins. The treated mice had their diabetes prevented or reversed, and none of them developed the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/10255-graft-vs-host-disease-an-overview-in-bone-marrow-transplant"&gt;graft-versus-host disease&lt;/a&gt; that often occurs in humans when cells are transplanted between people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, mixing donor and recipient immune cells has been shown to work for transplants before, including in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/scitranslmed.aax8863"&gt;previous studies&lt;/a&gt; by some of the same research team, which bodes well for human trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of that said, plenty of challenges remain. For example, islet cells can only be donated after death, and must come from the same person as the blood stem cells. It's also unclear just how many of these cells would be needed for the procedure to be successful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers say they're currently looking at ways of getting more of the donated cells to survive, or figuring out ways of producing them in the lab from &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41392-024-02090-x"&gt;pluripotent human stem cells&lt;/a&gt;. We can't &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-treatment-may-cure-severe-type-1-diabetes-study-finds"&gt;cure type 1 diabetes yet&lt;/a&gt; – but &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/first-of-its-kind-cell-transplant-brings-a-cure-for-diabetes-closer"&gt;we're getting closer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The possibility of translating these findings into humans is very exciting," &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/all-news/2025/11/type-1-diabetes-cure.html"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Kim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The key steps in our study – which result in animals with a hybrid immune system containing cells from both the donor and the recipient – are already being used in the clinic for other conditions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1172/JCI190034"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Journal of Clinical Investigation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:04:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPNll2M09GdzREaDNhMkN3TzdlcHFQSGZBelA5RnVYSWZTb0xXZG82Z1NDLWg2amUtTkFJMUVlRTF6dXZGTkV3WFVudEc5alFuYWk5bTUyazM1bDM1RHQ2UEJhRFRYbzZ2MjNldHRTMmtQNThLakZtRS1Hd0VEVjlCQTlsTThlZzh3bnZTR19TNEI4VEozTmRkUlFn</guid></item><item><title>研究人员发现你的大脑“入睡”的确切时刻–从字面上看–印度防御评论</title><link>https://indiandefencereview.com/researchers-exact-moment-brain-falls-sleep/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-entry-content"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A team of researchers from&lt;strong&gt; Imperial College London&lt;/strong&gt; has pinpointed the exact moment when the brain “falls” asleep, marking a sharp drop in brain activity just before sleep sets in. This discovery could improve treatments for sleep disorders and have significant implications for public safety, particularly in high-risk situations like driving.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Until now, sleep was often thought to be a slow transition, much like drifting into a dream. However, according to neuroscientist &lt;strong&gt;Nir Grossman&lt;/strong&gt;, who led the research, the change from wakefulness to sleep happens suddenly, much like falling off a cliff. Using EEG monitoring, the researchers observed a distinct point where brain activity sharply declines, signaling the start of sleep. This shift occurs in the final moments before sleep begins, offering a precise definition of the transition from wakefulness to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A Sudden Drop in Brain Activity&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For decades, scientists believed sleep began gradually, with brain activity slowly fading until sleep took over. But Grossman’s team found that the transition is much more dramatic. By monitoring&lt;strong&gt; EEG data&lt;/strong&gt;, they identified a specific moment when brain activity drops sharply, signaling the start of sleep. This sharp decline happens just before sleep sets in and is a clear, measurable point that had previously been hard to define, reports &lt;a href="https://www.popularmechanics.com/science/a69451485/your-brain-literally-falls-asleep/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Popular Mechanics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This discovery offers a more accurate understanding of how the brain shifts from wakefulness to sleep, providing valuable insight into how we process the transition. Grossman emphasized the importance of this finding, saying, in a study recently published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41593-025-02091-1" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;The tipping point accurately defines the critical time during the transition from a steady wake state into a steady sleep state.&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt="Graphical Illustration Of The Computational Framework" class="wp-image-96261" data-lazy-srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1200x727.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-380x230.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-520x315.jpg 520w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1536x931.jpg 1536w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework.jpg 1980w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" data-lazy-src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1200x727.jpg"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1200x727.jpg" alt="Graphical Illustration Of The Computational Framework" class="wp-image-96261" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1200x727.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-380x230.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-520x315.jpg 520w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1536x931.jpg 1536w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework.jpg 1980w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Graphical illustration of the computational framework – © Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Sleep-Onset Disorders and Public Safety&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The new findings have important implications for people suffering from sleep disorders, particularly &lt;strong&gt;those who struggle to fall asleep &lt;/strong&gt;or stay awake during critical activities. &lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/how-sleep-deprivation-affects-your-brain/" data-type="post" data-id="76260"&gt;Sleep&lt;/a&gt;-onset disorders, where it takes a long time to fall asleep, can severely impact someone’s health and quality of life. By identifying the exact point when sleep begins, this research could lead to more effective treatments for these disorders, helping individuals to fall asleep faster and enjoy better rest.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Moreover, this discovery has public safety implications. &lt;strong&gt;Sleep deprivation &lt;/strong&gt;can be dangerous, especially in situations where alertness is required, such as driving or operating machinery. Understanding when the brain falls asleep could lead to better ways to monitor and address sleep issues, ultimately reducing the risks associated with sleep-deprived individuals.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt=" Fold Bifurcation Of Eeg Dynamics During Falling Asleep Transition" class="wp-image-96263" data-lazy-srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1200x727.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-380x230.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-520x315.jpg 520w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1536x931.jpg 1536w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition.jpg 1980w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" data-lazy-src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1200x727.jpg"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1200x727.jpg" alt=" Fold Bifurcation Of Eeg Dynamics During Falling Asleep Transition" class="wp-image-96263" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1200x727.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-380x230.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-520x315.jpg 520w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1536x931.jpg 1536w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition.jpg 1980w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt; Fold bifurcation of EEG dynamics during falling asleep transition – &lt;em&gt;© Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Role of Brain Nuclei in the Sleep Transition&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The process of &lt;strong&gt;falling asleep &lt;/strong&gt;involves more than just a decrease in brain activity; it is also controlled by specific clusters of neurons called nuclei. Some nuclei promote wakefulness, while others are responsible for initiating sleep. As the brain transitions, certain &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4660253/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;nuclei&lt;/a&gt; are turned off, causing a sudden shift in how neurons communicate. This change in neural activity leads to the rapid drop in brain activity observed right before sleep.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;One key finding from the study was that the&lt;strong&gt; brain’s occipital cortex&lt;/strong&gt;, which processes visual information, reaches the sleep transition point earlier than the frontal cortex, which is responsible for thinking, memory, and emotional regulation. This explains why some people take longer to fall asleep but experience a quicker shift into sleep once they pass the “&lt;em&gt;falling&lt;/em&gt;” phase. By studying this process, Grossman and his team were able to predict when sleep would occur with remarkable accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Indian Defence Review</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQTG11dHhFQUdxbHlTYWVTUGd5WDlnWnYzZnVfMzU3OWdRX2paNGRSVjNOaHRxY2ozRVdhRTNLb3RyMTBQVFJKR0VUZ0RqSFdzZk5TZHpHT3dPQVFqZDFKcjJLeV81MTJkWC1hem5wUjlVRmRiLS1KRnNTNEE1aHBkWg</guid></item><item><title>华盛顿州居民在H5N5感染后死亡- DW</title><link>https://www.dw.com/en/washington-state-resident-dies-after-h5n5-infection/a-74847177</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-tracking-name="rich-text" data-tracking-skip="true" class="c17j8gzx rc0m0op r1ebneao s198y7xq rich-text l1evdo4u blt0baw s16w0xvi rcjjkz7 w128axg5 b1fzgn0z"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A person believed to be the first confirmed case of H5N5 avian &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/influenza/t-71362030"&gt;influenza&lt;/a&gt; in humans has died, health authorities in &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/united-states-of-america/t-19065189"&gt;US&lt;/a&gt; state of Washington said Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The deceased was a Grays Harbor County resident, according to the Washington State Department of Health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote class="fb-post embed" data-facebook="true" data-href="https://www.facebook.com/photo?fbid=1285430896959179&amp;amp;set=a.221538120015134"&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What have health authorities said?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The department said it would not be releasing specific details relating to the deceased's name, gender or age out of respect for the family's privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They did confirm that the person was an older adult with pre-existing health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"The risk to the public remains low. No other people involved have tested positive for avian influenza," state health authorities said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"Public health officials will continue to monitor anyone who was in close contact with the patient for symptoms to ensure that human-to-human spread has not occurred," the department said and added: "There is no evidence of transmission of this virus between people."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the health department statement, the person had a backyard flock of domestic birds which they said was the likely source of infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="vjs-wrapper embed big"&gt;&lt;h2 aria-label="Embedded video — Bird flu wreaks havoc on US poultry farms" class="headline"&gt;&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;path d="M14.114 7.599H13.5l.002 4.706h.601l4.582 3.25-.005-11.11zM11.084 4.444l-9.007.002-1.336.797.002 9.514 1.334.793 9.007.006 1.509-.799-.004-9.516z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;Bird flu wreaks havoc on US poultry farms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;video id="video-72067212" controls playsinline="" preload="none" poster="data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAAEAAAABCAQAAAC1HAwCAAAAC0lEQVR42mNkYAAAAAYAAjCB0C8AAAAASUVORK5CYII=" data-id="72067212" data-posterurl="https://static.dw.com/image/71985603_605.webp" data-duration="02:36"&gt;&lt;source src="https://hlsvod.dw.com/i/dwtv_video/flv/je/je20250328_Superchickens09E_,AVC_480x270,AVC_512x288,AVC_640x360,AVC_960x540,AVC_1280x720,AVC_1920x1080,.mp4.csmil/master.m3u8" type="application/x-mpegURL"&gt;&lt;source src="https://tvdownloaddw-a.akamaihd.net/dwtv_video/flv/je/je20250328_Superchickens09E_AVC_1920x1080.mp4" type="video/mp4"&gt;&lt;p class="vjs-no-js"&gt;To view this video please enable JavaScript, and consider upgrading to a web browser that &lt;a href="https://videojs.com/html5-video-support/" target="_blank"&gt;supports HTML5 video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What is H5N5 avian flu?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;H5N5 is a sub-type of &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/h5n1-bird-flu-spreading-to-poultry-via-migratory-cranes-germany-denmark-netherlands-usa-europe/a-74527770"&gt;avian flu that is not believed to be a greater threat to human health&lt;/a&gt; than the H5N1 virus that has been behind a wave of 70 reported human infections in the US in 2024 and 2025.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of those have been mild illnesses in workers on dairy and poultry farms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The distinction between H5N5 and H5N1 lies in a protein involved in releasing the virus from an infected cell and promoting spread to surrounding cells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the Washington State Department of Health website the first human cases of H5 avian influenza were reported in Washington state in October 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The department says that to date, there is no evidence of person-to-person transmission of avian influenza in Washington state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Health authorities say birds and other animals infected with avian influenza shed the virus in their saliva, mucous and feces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="vjs-wrapper embed big"&gt;&lt;h2 aria-label="Embedded video — German bird flu outbreak sparks fear among farmers" class="headline"&gt;&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;path d="M14.114 7.599H13.5l.002 4.706h.601l4.582 3.25-.005-11.11zM11.084 4.444l-9.007.002-1.336.797.002 9.514 1.334.793 9.007.006 1.509-.799-.004-9.516z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;German bird flu outbreak sparks fear among farmers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;video id="video-74576972" controls playsinline="" preload="none" poster="data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAAEAAAABCAQAAAC1HAwCAAAAC0lEQVR42mNkYAAAAAYAAjCB0C8AAAAASUVORK5CYII=" data-id="74576972" data-posterurl="https://static.dw.com/image/74510479_605.webp" data-duration="02:38"&gt;&lt;source src="https://hlsvod.dw.com/i/vps/webvideos/ENG/2025/BUSI/BUSIENG251103_QWIBirdfluCMS_01SMW_,AVC_480x270,AVC_512x288,AVC_640x360,AVC_960x540,AVC_1280x720,AVC_1920x1080,.mp4.csmil/master.m3u8" type="application/x-mpegURL"&gt;&lt;source src="https://tvdownloaddw-a.akamaihd.net/vps/webvideos/ENG/2025/BUSI/BUSIENG251103_QWIBirdfluCMS_01SMW_AVC_1920x1080.mp4" type="video/mp4"&gt;&lt;track src="https://www.dw.com/media/subtitles/74598849" srclang="en" label="ENGLISH" default&gt;&lt;p class="vjs-no-js"&gt;To view this video please enable JavaScript, and consider upgrading to a web browser that &lt;a href="https://videojs.com/html5-video-support/" target="_blank"&gt;supports HTML5 video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/track&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Edited by: Saim Dušan Inayatullah, Karl Sexton&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>DW</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 13:10:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQSVZRMjUtTWxyejQ1ZU1oRklvTVZvVDA3QTlYeUhvN0tkcnRGMzA2cUFWNkVsVGlONlY3UU1iREphdU9jejhYWkNCLWZfWXZicFpLcDIzLTBpNnk4dXpFS3dGd09HWTBYVGJIRWZBWXIyVDlncEtHdGJzRlRxa0xnY3FCZ08ybmU0TEtoX9IBjAFBVV95cUxQMWR5c3V4OHhGMmlMc1JhUDQ5WEItRmNYYkF3TExvT0tHaGNoYklFN3JiMm9vV3NXdGhwTFBvYjVjRVVVbmhQUDZmZ2ZzaHRNZkJlQnZ0Um00cDZpTlJ4VEh2ak5uTVRaWmNYUnpqXy03Nll4LXRrU1lsR0d4aEFCamtmSzF6OTFLajJreA</guid></item><item><title>“Fish Pedicures”在TikTok上疯传。皮肤科医生恳求您不要买。-今日美国</title><link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/health-wellness/2025/11/22/fish-pedicures-viral/87297573007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"Fish are friends, not food," &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c6mVl6fAxLw" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;animated sharks famously&lt;/a&gt; declare in 2003's &lt;a href="/story/entertainment/movies/2022/07/25/what-kind-of-fish-is-dory-finding-nemo/7829566001/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;"Finding Nemo."&lt;/a&gt; But are they &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2025/11/11/shay-mitchell-kids-skincare-rini/87200918007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;pedicurists&lt;/a&gt;, too?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;On TikTok, &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@sydney.sedrowski/video/7530628992211094814" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;videos have gone viral&lt;/a&gt; of people getting so-called "fish pedicures," often while traveling outside of the U.S. In the videos, people stick their bare feet into tanks of fish, which swarm their toes. The fish then eat away at dead skin cells and calluses, leaving their feet supposedly silky and smooth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7398691/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Originating in Turkey&lt;/a&gt;, the practice has become popular for tourists traveling abroad − and though the videos of their shocked reactions can be entertaining, &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2025/04/14/machine-analyze-skin/83056544007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;dermatologists&lt;/a&gt; encourage travelers not to participate. If not done in a sanitary fashion, these fish pedicures can be seriously dangerous. In the U.S., they've even come under legal scrutiny and are not permitted in multiple states, including &lt;a href="https://simasgovlaw.com/fish-pedicures-are-not-permitted-in-california/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;California&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Plus, there are safer, simpler ways of taking care of your feet that don't involve fish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"I don't know why people would do that instead of just exfoliating," says &lt;a href="https://rossiderm.com/pages/dr-rossi" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Anthony Rossi&lt;/a&gt;, a dermatologist and surgeon who hosts the podcast &lt;a href="https://go.skimresources.com/?id=83224X1595658&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fpodcasts.apple.com%2Fus%2Fpodcast%2F1-how-your-lifestyle-shapes-skin-health%2Fid1773787097%3Fi%3D1000673975435&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.usatoday.com%2Fstory%2Flife%2Fhealth-wellness%2F2025%2F11%2F22%2Ffish-pedicures-viral%2F87297573007%2F" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-v-afl data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;"Give Good Face: Clean Clinical Science."&lt;/a&gt; "If you're on vacation and you see something and it looks interesting, it doesn't mean you should do it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Why viral 'fish pedicures' are dangerous&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Removing dead skin cells from feet isn't a bad idea. Doing so allows fresh, newer skin underneath to shine through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;When people get a fish pedicure, the fish essentially nibble away at this dead layer − basically exfoliating like a scrub would.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="gnt_em gnt_em_img"&gt;&lt;img class="gnt_em_img_i" fetchpriority="high" data-g-r="lazy" data-gl-src="/gcdn/authoring/authoring-images/2025/11/16/USAT/87299356007-getty-images-601153410-1.jpg?width=660&amp;amp;height=419&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp" data-gl-srcset="/gcdn/authoring/authoring-images/2025/11/16/USAT/87299356007-getty-images-601153410-1.jpg?width=1320&amp;amp;height=838&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp 2x" decoding="async" alt='"Fish pedicures" are viral online. Dermatologists beg you not to get one.'&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_em_img_ccw gnt_em_img_ccw__cap gnt_em_img_ccw__crd" data-c-caption='"Fish pedicures" are viral online. Dermatologists beg you not to get one.' data-c-credit="Baona, Getty Images"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The problem is that, often, it's hard to tell if the fish tanks are sanitary. You don't know what kind of bacteria the fish could be carrying. This can prove especially dangerous if you get a fish pedicure while unknowingly having a cut or opening in your skin. The water these fish swim in can be contaminated, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"You can get mycobacterium, which is like a nasty infection," Rossi says. "Vibrio is a nasty infection, and there have been cases of these infectious outbreaks linked to these fish spas."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Oftentimes too, the same fish are used over and over again for different people's pedicures. So, you're not just getting germs and bacteria from them, but also from other people's feet the fish have feasted on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"These fish, they can harbor bacteria, and they can't be disinfected," dermatologist &lt;a href="https://www.brookejeffymd.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Brooke Jeffy&lt;/a&gt; says. "So, if it's exposed to some kind of infection or germ in one person, it's feasible that they could spread something. The fish themselves can also harbor certain bacteria, which can be really pathogenic for humans as well."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Not to mention the possible ethical concerns. Some fish pedicure providers have been accused of intentionally starving fish so they're hungry enough to eat dead foot skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Don't get a 'fish pedicure.' Do this instead.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;What's important to note, Jeffy says, is the same benefits of a fish pedicure can also be achieved through tried-and-true exfoliation techniques.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"Better choices would of course be using typical chemical exfoliants," she says. Physical exfoliators and just good old fashioned moisturizer, she adds, also do the trick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>USA Today</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 13:05:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxON1h0b3FZZmNlR0pqeTdUWFRJRHUteXNlVk5DUlQ5dmJLMWRfdFY3OEFVZzY1amxJMGszWUswa1hwY0hHdkRRZFFLYXdkOGRTQ1BWckhfSTZTdmM4V010eDVEd2Y2b0kycXkwQmloazMxMEZNdnR6RlVYZE5IbTdqYm1pRW0tdlh6SW9GNkdnTXdaa1NYcGFBUzd2eTQ</guid></item><item><title>杀死巨噬细胞的细菌毒素削弱肠道对溃疡性结肠炎的防御- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-macrophage-bacterial-toxin-weakens-gut.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 12:30:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNcDExYi1YN0hVcXd2REhwNGVDY2lmQWNBTFpYeXpiMEFVMS02U3dhVVdRWE1NWExvUW1NdGVQOGVTcXRZenhrSE03SzMxWlVRN2RuT0RKd2pUaVQxamluUFloY0FMdUY0Ui1WQU9jM3ZkWVJ5LXR2TXlhNUZsdDVrUkd4ZlE4ampidHc</guid></item><item><title>“日落”是我们谈论不够的痴呆症症状- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/sundowning-is-the-dementia-symptom-we-dont-talk-about-enough-g_l_691f838ce4b047290e295f4b</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;During certain times of the day, some people with dementia may become more confused and disoriented. Referred to by neuropsychologist &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.braincenterindy.com/drkrowel" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="April Krowel" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.braincenterindy.com/drkrowel" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;April Krowel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;as “a constellation of symptoms rooted in confusion and disorientation,” this condition is called ”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.alz.org/help-support/caregiving/stages-behaviors/sleep-issues-sundowning" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="sundowning" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.alz.org/help-support/caregiving/stages-behaviors/sleep-issues-sundowning" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;sundowning&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Typically, people will start to experience the symptoms in the late afternoon, early evening, the time when the sun is setting,” Krowel, who specializes in assessments of adults with neurological disorders, told HuffPost. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sometimes, the symptoms occur quite late into the evening, said Dr. Victor Diaz, a neurologist at Orlando Health Neuroscience Institute&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/neuroscience/articles/10.3389/fnins.2020.00910/full" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Approximately 1 in 5 people" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/neuroscience/articles/10.3389/fnins.2020.00910/full" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Approximately 1 in 5 people&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; with dementia experience sundowning. It affects people with different forms of dementia, like Alzheimer’s and Lewy body dementia, Diaz said. “Episodes can last anywhere from a few minutes to a few hours, and in some cases, can extend into the night.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sundowning is not something that a person with dementia may notice in themselves, Krowel noted. Rather, it is typically caregivers who pick up on the change in their loved one’s behavior and mental state. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;It can happen at any stage of dementia, though it “tends to peak in the middle stages of dementia and lessens as the disease progresses,” according to the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://alzheimer.ca/en/help-support/im-caring-person-living-dementia/understanding-symptoms/restlessness-or-confusion" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Alzheimer Society of Canada" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://alzheimer.ca/en/help-support/im-caring-person-living-dementia/understanding-symptoms/restlessness-or-confusion" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Alzheimer Society of Canada&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The symptom is distressing for the person experiencing it. “They don’t know where they are, where they live, they don’t feel safe, which creates an anxiety within them, which can lead to restlessness and irritability,” Krowel explained. They may also experience difficulties with sleeping, Diaz said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are ways to manage these symptoms so the person with dementia feels more at ease. Ahead, experts share how to identify sundowning, and how to best support a person going through it:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why does sundowning happen in dementia? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;To date, no clear cause of sundowning has been identified, both experts said. Some &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="researchers" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;researchers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; believe it partly has to do with a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4344830/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="disrupted circadian rhythm" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4344830/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;disrupted circadian rhythm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Almost every tissue in your body follows a circadian rhythm, which is the body’s internal clock. This process follows the cycle of day and night, to prime your body for alertness in the day and sleepiness at night.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When disrupted in dementia, it &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7494756/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="can potentially cause" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7494756/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;&lt;span&gt;can potentially cause&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; a person to have increased physical activity later during the day, or remain awake for longer after the sun sets. A &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7494756/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="2020 paper " data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7494756/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2020 paper &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;noted that circadian rhythms can play a role in influencing emotions and moods. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.uwyo.edu/zoology/people/todd.html" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Researchers" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.uwyo.edu/zoology/people/todd.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Researchers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; are still trying to pinpoint exactly what is happening in the brain to affect the circadian rhythm in dementia. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full#B33" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="In addition to the above" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full#B33" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In addition to the above&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, if a person has afternoon fatigue, pain, hunger, inadequate exposure to sunlight during the day, anxiety, depression, side effects from medications, hearing loss or sight impairment, these may increase their likelihood of experiencing sundowning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the signs of sundowning?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Disorientation and confusion underpin most of the other sundowning symptoms and behaviors. As the day is ending, people may start to be uncertain and confused about what’s going on in their environment. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“For example, if their family is preparing dinner, the patient might be thinking, ‘What are these people doing?’ They don’t understand the activity around preparing the meal,” Diaz said. They may also feel that they are in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dementia.org.au/living-dementia/mood-and-behaviour-changes/restlessness" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="wrong place" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.dementia.org.au/living-dementia/mood-and-behaviour-changes/restlessness" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;&lt;span&gt;wrong place&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Because of this, they may become agitated and restless. “They might pace around or rock in the chair, things like that, where there’s visibility, an inability to relax,” Krowel said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The person may become anxious, irritable, upset or aggressive. They may also have difficulty falling asleep or staying asleep, Diaz said. “Relatives may say they observe the patient wandering at night, because they’re not sleeping at night and reversing the day with the night.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Symptoms “present differently from patient to patient, because there is more than one form of dementia,” Diaz noted. Visual or auditory hallucinations are more common in those with Lewy body Dementia, for example. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It’s important to learn to tell sundowning apart from delirium, though, as symptoms can appear similar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Delirium may mean the person is going through a condition that is critical and in some cases, life-threatening, so being able to identify its root cause is essential. “Disorientation in delirium [may mean] the patient is in a critical condition. It could be a bad infection, sepsis, a severe and sudden spike in blood pressure, very high blood sugar, or a manifestation of stroke in patients who are older,” Diaz said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The main way to distinguish between delirium and sundowning is by remembering that the latter typically occurs around the time the sun is setting or at a specific time of day, whereas delirium occurs abruptly at any time of the day, Diaz explained. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“For the most part, once you find out what is causing the delirium, and treat it or get it under control, the delirium will subside,” he noted. Sundowning tends to recur, though there are ways to ease its symptoms when it does.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you suspect your loved one is experiencing delirium, Krowel advised seeing your primary care physician or going to emergency care, “depending on how severe the symptoms are at the time.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Ippei Naoi via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Ippei Naoi via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Social interaction, especially at night, can help reduce fear and anxiety associated with dementia and reduce sundowning confusion.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What can worsen sundowning? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Below, Diaz and Krowel shared a list of common factors that can worsen sundowning, and their advice to ease it. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Before running through this list with your loved one, it is a good idea to make sure all of the person’s basic needs are met first: Could they be hungry? Thirsty? Uncomfortable? Tired? They may be agitated because of an unmet need, Krowel said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lack of routines and changing the environment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“When you don’t have any routines, move furniture or objects around, change the person’s caregiver, or introduce any other new developments, this disorients the person more,” Diaz said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Krowel and Diaz advise creating a steady daily routine, sticking to it and minimizing changes to a person’s living environment. Take familiar, comforting objects, like photographs of family, along if the person is going somewhere new and out of their usual routine, as these can help to ground them and make them feel more at ease, Krowel said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Certain types of medications and timing of medications.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Narcotics and certain psychotropic drugs can exacerbate sundowning symptoms, Diaz said. In general, psychotropic drugs to stay away from include &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/neurology/articles/10.3389/fneur.2021.644317/full" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="anticholinergic" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/neurology/articles/10.3389/fneur.2021.644317/full" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;&lt;span&gt;anticholinergic&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="benzodiazepine" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="12"&gt;&lt;span&gt;benzodiazepine&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; medications. If the person needs a drug to manage their pain, Diaz recommended staying away from narcotics, and consulting your treating physician for alternatives. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Diaz also said that sometimes the timing and dosing of medications can exacerbate symptoms of sundowning. If you’re noticing symptoms worsening, start to keep track of the person’s medications, “what time you’re giving the medication, what you’re doing differently, and report this to your primary care doctor.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It may be worth having a medication review done by a physician to make sure your prescribed drugs aren’t worsening your sundowning symptoms, Krowel noted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Poor management of pain, stress or anxiety.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Pain, stress and anxiety can worsen the symptoms of sundowning, Krowel noted. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Monitor the person for any signs that they are in pain, experiencing stress or are anxious, and seek the input of the treating physician and neuropsychologist on how to manage these appropriately. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Poorly lit environment and sight impairment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“As we get older, we tend to have problems like cataract or diminished visual acuity, so good lighting is very important. If you have a poorly lit place, patients can have a lot of difficulty seeing objects, which can lead to confusion. If the person has visual problems, make sure that these are addressed as well,” Diaz said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As it gets darker outside, make sure the person’s room is well-lit with artificial lights and lamps so they can see their surroundings clearly. At night, it may be helpful to install a small &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/alzheimers-disease/expert-answers/sundowning/faq-20058511" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="night light" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/alzheimers-disease/expert-answers/sundowning/faq-20058511" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="13"&gt;&lt;span&gt;night light&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overstimulating environments, especially in the late afternoon.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Environments that are too noisy can hyperstimulate the patient and overwhelm them,” Diaz said. “And that can lead to them becoming more agitated, confused, and even afraid.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“After around 5 in the afternoon, it’s important to create an environment that is calm, low noise, and comfortable so the person won’t be overstimulated,” Diaz added. Noise can be everything from music and television to conversations and clattering of cutlery. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lack of exposure to sunlight during the daytime.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sunlight helps to regulate the circadian rhythm and prepares the body to sleep when it turns dark. “Having a lack of exposure to sunlight is something that &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="research" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="14"&gt;&lt;span&gt;research&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; shows might worsen sundowning symptoms,” Krowel said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As much as possible, make sure the person is exposed to sunlight during the daytime, whether it is sitting by a window or &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/opn.12292" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="walking outside" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/opn.12292" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="15"&gt;&lt;span&gt;walking outside&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lack of sleep and fatigue.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Tiredness and sleep difficulties worsen the severity of sundowning. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If the person is having sleep difficulties at night, sometimes introducing a melatonin supplement around 5 p.m. can be helpful for some patients, according to Diaz. Melatonin, a hormone which helps maintain the circadian rhythm and causes sleepiness at night, has been &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="found to be lower" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="16"&gt;&lt;span&gt;found to be lower&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in individuals with Alzheimer’s dementia. Make sure to check with a physician before starting this, however.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He also recommended correcting any issues that can disrupt sleep, like &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/sleep-latency-fall-asleep-quickly-ano_l_66f2d831e4b0199dbefb13f5" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="obstructive sleep apnea" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="66f2d831e4b0199dbefb13f5" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="17"&gt;&lt;span&gt;obstructive sleep apnea&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, and avoiding excessive caffeine or sugar as these can be stimulating.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lack of interaction.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“One way that families might deal with sundowning is by leaving the person alone in their bedroom until they finish having their episode. That is not advisable, because the more isolated the patient is, it feeds into their fear and anxiety and disorientation,” Diaz said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instead, he advised calmly redirecting the person. “When the person becomes agitated or disoriented, say ‘You are in: [insert name of where they are]. This is what we are doing: [insert explanation of what is happening].’ This reassures the person and explains in that moment what is going on, which helps you avoid the cycle of the person becoming disoriented, anxious and agitated.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 12:09:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxNSkdhXzZQT0tlRFAyRVF4ZGgxTDlIVm13UWpNS2JiRmpiS1JvUFN0Z3hFZUFRdVRhek5McjQ1RW5tT2NZVGJxN2N2eTNoeEFUemYxRmdZNVRiaDNaRnlJdXR2cTVQdFdVVkprTUhsTkVQU0hoY1JrWkZBLXVxUXVuZDM3VWhFWlVQa29pc0Rfc1JZZTEwWXpuWjdIWGtsTkd3amxoeDNwN2VZdk1jZk05ZVh4M3VkblRObkRFa9IBwgFBVV95cUxNTVVxYmlJQWcxbG1kMUhZYUhuZ1d1QTFURFRselloNlNSeVp2MldKYktPNEdTT29aVTJvV3czRmtUcmc2ZUZtd2RLR1V3Qk1sUnhvNnY1bDNucmtFTXhWRDJBeWQ4OElxLS12WnNCN09pS09HdTllaHl5QTRKdjlpM3k1M2ZNMms3blYwMGxWaFgxSWMxU19QanI0eGpBSFhRc051aXpFbFZrWDJYS2tuU1oyT0lQZlBpRk9mSW1iNFVudw</guid></item><item><title>长期COVID症状有8种模式。它们是什么- Axios</title><link>https://www.axios.com/2025/11/22/long-covid-symptoms-timeline-how-long</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 12:01:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE53TmRxSFZlTjU5Z2N1SlpSODJGZTBpVmNRbjNlZ3JjdWFlNVBGN2NLX29zZ3Z6cldFZkVLOHlWUjNpREdyaUlkVW9ObkxrUktIdC1XT0duSURSczk4c3BlSGNURjNiekJVWjNPVWd4U09ERjZDZGY4QmtB</guid></item><item><title>我是一名美食医生。这是如果我有胃痛，我永远不会做的一件事。- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/stomach-pain-doctor-advice-goog_l_691de9cde4b073def3ef4c84</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s pretty common to utter the phrase “my stomach hurts.” You’ve probably had stomach pain at some point in your life, whether it’s discomfort after eating, stress-related pain, menstrual cramps or a larger medical issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Abdominal pain, just those two words, is the most common diagnosis we have seen in our ER actually,” said &lt;a href="https://www.vanderbilthealth.com/doctors/sarker-shabnam" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Shabnam Sarker" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691de9cde4b073def3ef4c84" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.vanderbilthealth.com/doctors/sarker-shabnam" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;Dr. Shabnam Sarker&lt;/a&gt;, a gastroenterologist at Vanderbilt Digestive Disease Center in Nashville. “I would think it was something like chest pain or something else, but abdominal pain is [the most common].”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;As anyone with a stomach condition likely knows, it can often take some time to pinpoint exactly what is wrong. Why? Because “th&lt;span&gt;ere are many causes of stomach pain,” &lt;a href="https://www.orlandohealth.com/physician-finder/sunina-nathoo-md#/overview" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Sunina Nathoo" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691de9cde4b073def3ef4c84" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.orlandohealth.com/physician-finder/sunina-nathoo-md#/overview" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;Dr. Sunina Nathoo&lt;/a&gt;, a g&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;astroenterologist at the Orlando Health Digestive Health Institute, told HuffPost via email — like gallstones, ulcers, Crohn’s disease, irritable bowel syndrome, appendicitis and more.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there is one thing doctors say they never do (and you should never do) when it comes to any kind of stomach pain. Here’s what they said:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They don’t ignore pain — especially if it’s sudden.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“If there is stomach pain that just does not feel right, I recommend seeing a primary care doctor and gastroenterologist to figure out what is going on,” Nathoo said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you can’t get in with a gastroenterologist for some time, Sarker said just seeing a primary care doctor is just fine, too. “You don’t really want to delay if you are uncomfortable,” Sarker noted. Stomach issues can be debilitating and can even cause further issues for your bowel movements and eating habits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“The bottom line is all pain is real and should be evaluated,” Nathoo said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But the type of pain you’re feeling should dictate your next steps, as some symptoms are more serious than others ― specifically if you have sudden, new pain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“If people experience severe and acute onset pain, they should go to the ER. The concern would be that the pain could be due to a cause that requires emergent intervention,” Nathoo explained. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain symptoms that can accompany stomach pain should also be addressed as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If it’s a new symptom, then we always say you should probably consult with somebody,” Sarker said. This is especially true if certain GI “alarm factors,” which Sarker says are new abdominal pain, bleeding from the bowels and weight loss, coincide with the pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;While a one-off stomach ache can happen, if you have mild, chronic stomach pain, you should see a doctor if the pain is non-debilitating and continues for more than a week or two, Nathoo said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s also important to take any pain or symptoms seriously if you have a family history of stomach cancer, esophageal cancer or colon cancer, according to &lt;a href="https://profiles.hopkinsmedicine.org/provider/ekta-gupta/2703764" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Ekta Gupta" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691de9cde4b073def3ef4c84" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://profiles.hopkinsmedicine.org/provider/ekta-gupta/2703764" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;Dr. Ekta Gupta&lt;/a&gt;, a gastroenterologist at Johns Hopkins Medicine in Baltimore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colorectal cancer &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/colon-cancer-young-people-symptoms_l_63fcc67de4b0735bf879341f" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="is becoming more and more" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691de9cde4b073def3ef4c84" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="63fcc67de4b0735bf879341f" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;is becoming more and more&lt;/a&gt; common in young people, according to a recent American Cancer Society report. Colorectal cancer diagnoses increased from 11% in 1995 to 20% in 2019 in people under 55, so it’s something everyone should take seriously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abdominal pain, rectal bleeding and blood in your stool are all signs of the disease, making it important to report any and all gut-related symptoms to a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Westend61 via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Westend61 via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Everything from serious diseases like colon cancer to daily stress can cause stomach pain.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bottom line: Don’t dismiss stomach issues or self-diagnose.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;From gallstones to menstrual cramps to colon cancer to appendicitis and more, there are many, many causes of abdominal pain, which means it’s always a good idea to see a doctor; you won’t always be able to tell just from your symptoms alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;And even if you’ve dealt with certain abdominal discomfort for weeks or months doesn’t mean you have to just keep ignoring it. Sarker recommended keeping a log of the characteristics and associations of the pain, which can help you better get the picture across to your provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors say you should also be aware of the lifestyle behaviors that can aggravate stomach pain, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I tend to suggest to my patients that they should stay away from NSAIDs, which are medications that help with pain in general and so commonly used mindlessly, like Aleve, Motrin, Ibuprofen,” Gupta said. These medications are known to irritate your stomach lining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stress is also linked with stomach ulcers, and spicy and acidic foods can also be the culprit for stomach discomfort, Gupta explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suffice to say, there are lots of reasons people have stomach pain, but the pain — no matter how mild or frequent — shouldn’t be discounted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think instead of trying to self-diagnose, seeking care sooner than later is helpful, especially if it is affecting the quality of your life, or it is acute, just like, hit you all of a sudden and this is definitely out of the norm for you,” Sarker said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 12:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxQZDd0VDREdnJRem4wUEhBVjVWRVlRLVVZY3Qyd2pWWC1tanl3bGNkY01aS0V3T0JpZmVGNk9UNzBQRlhjZW5hMTJnUEtSV3Nwa1JxSnZNMVFfTmRoT3pxY3NDTFNWT3JUQWJZajFtQlhCM3dKMUJSUlpXOGR2TUdPUkllODlKcFJWdmFRbG0zb295V1nSAZgBQVVfeXFMUFlYTkhKc3pMV1c5UVZncjl6Yy1oR1ZNcGVBckFIWkJfaXdlUWhZbHhlM2NrMGk1Yzh0c09qcGxuSVNEZWRTeW14SmdmQzhBRUxCdDRQSG40RFE5NVVDSWpGYmVibnNpVlNBREVtd1VOYW0yZVpoaHF3cmtFTGZFS0hRZHE2c0otdXZRdjdodkwyNGh4cnkxM1k</guid></item><item><title>以下是如何判断您生病后是否仍然具有传染性- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/how-to-tell-contagious-sick-goog_l_691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Getting sick leading up to the holidays brings its own set of headaches. If you’re anything like me, you’ll be worried about transmitting your illness to your loved ones for fear of ruining their festive season. It’s a time of gatherings with friends and family ― people generally want to spend it in good health.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When I fall ill and start getting dreaded symptoms, I spend a lot of time researching exactly when I will be recovered enough to catch up with my friends and family again. In other words, when will I stop being contagious? How convenient it would be, I’ve often thought, if there were a “cheat sheet” of this information for the most common winter infections.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you’ve recently gotten ill and are wishing for the same guidance, keep reading. The advice below will help you gauge whether you’re still contagious, and give you tips on how to protect the people around you from catching the sickness too.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flu&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When people contract the flu, they “get sick fairly quickly. They feel fine in the morning, and by afternoon they’re suddenly pretty sick,” said &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://providers.ucsd.edu/details/12013/primary-care-internal-medicine" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Marlene Millen" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://providers.ucsd.edu/details/12013/primary-care-internal-medicine" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr. Marlene Millen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a board-certified internal medicine doctor and primary care physician at UC San Diego Health.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;They’ll be hit with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/signs-symptoms/index.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="a few or all" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/signs-symptoms/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;a few or all&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;of the following symptoms: chills, fever, cough, sore throat, body aches, fatigue and headaches, and runny or congested nose.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once you get flu symptoms, “people are most contagious the first few days of it,” Millen said, and remain contagious for up to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/index.html#:~:text=Period%20of%20Contagiousness&amp;amp;text=Some%20otherwise%20healthy%20adults%20may,for%20longer%20periods%20of%20time." target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="seven days" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/index.html#:~:text=Period%20of%20Contagiousness&amp;amp;text=Some%20otherwise%20healthy%20adults%20may,for%20longer%20periods%20of%20time." data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;seven days&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Stay home while you are symptomatic. Once symptoms start improving overall and the fever has left without the use of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/fever/in-depth/fever/art-20050997" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="fever-reducing drugs" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/fever/in-depth/fever/art-20050997" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;fever-reducing drugs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; — both things must be true for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="at least a full 24 hours" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;at least a full 24 hours&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;— &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;you are &lt;em&gt;less&lt;/em&gt; contagious and can leave your home. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/guidance/faqs.html#:~:text=What%20does%20%22improving%20symptoms%22%20or,to%20normal%20after%20an%20infection." target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Symptoms are considered to be improving" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/guidance/faqs.html#:~:text=What%20does%20%22improving%20symptoms%22%20or,to%20normal%20after%20an%20infection." data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Symptoms are considered to be improving&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; if you’re feeling well enough to perform your daily activities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;For &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="at least five days" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;&lt;span&gt;at least five days&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; afterward or while you have lingering symptoms, wear a mask and practice physical distancing as much as you can.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“You can be contagious for up to two weeks afterwards, if you’re still pretty sick or if you’re immunosuppressed,” Millen explained.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The influenza diagnostic test cannot tell you how contagious a person is, said &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.uclahealth.org/providers/tara-vijayan" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Tara Vijayan" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.uclahealth.org/providers/tara-vijayan" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr. Tara Vijayan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, medical director of the Adult Antimicrobial Stewardship program at UCLA Health.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COVID&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;COVID is caused by the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/coronavirus/symptoms-causes/syc-20479963" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="virus" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/coronavirus/symptoms-causes/syc-20479963" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;&lt;span&gt;virus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; more clinically known as SARS-CoV-2. You &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/covid/signs-symptoms/index.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="may have" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/covid/signs-symptoms/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;&lt;span&gt;may have&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; a fever, cough, sore throat, muscle aches, headache, congestion or runny nose, diarrhea, fatigue, and nausea or vomiting. Losing your sense of taste or smell is another symptom observed in COVID, although that tends to be less common now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you are symptomatic, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/guidance/faqs.html#:~:text=and%20not%20testing%3F-,The%20updated%20Respiratory%20Virus%20Guidance%20recommends%20that%20people%20stay%20home,using%20fever%2Dreducing%20medication)." target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="stay at home" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/guidance/faqs.html#:~:text=and%20not%20testing%3F-,The%20updated%20Respiratory%20Virus%20Guidance%20recommends%20that%20people%20stay%20home,using%20fever%2Dreducing%20medication)." data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;&lt;span&gt;stay at home&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; even if your symptoms are mild, Millen said. Once symptoms start improving overall and your fever has subsided without fever-reducing drugs — again, both things must be true for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="at least a full 24 hours" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;&lt;span&gt;at least a full 24 hours&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;— &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;you are considered less contagious, and can leave your home. Wear a mask and practice physical distancing if there are lingering symptoms or if you continue to yield a positive result on a home COVID test, both experts said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sometimes, COVID symptoms &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/coronavirus/symptoms-causes/syc-20479963" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="worsen" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/coronavirus/symptoms-causes/syc-20479963" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="12"&gt;&lt;span&gt;worsen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; one to two weeks after their initial onset. If this happens, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="stay home again" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="13"&gt;&lt;span&gt;stay home again&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and follow the above protocols to avoid spreading the virus to others.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are people who are asymptomatic even though they have COVID. If you fall into this camp and get a positive COVID test result, wear a mask and practice physical distancing around other people for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="at least five days" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="14"&gt;&lt;span&gt;at least five days&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: ljubaphoto via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;ljubaphoto via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;There are a few key factors that can generally tell you if enough time has passed that you're no longer contagious.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Common Cold&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The common cold is caused by many different types of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/common-cold/about/index.html#:~:text=A%20cold%20is%20a%20viral,for%20missed%20school%20and%20work." target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="respiratory viruses" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/common-cold/about/index.html#:~:text=A%20cold%20is%20a%20viral,for%20missed%20school%20and%20work." data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="15"&gt;&lt;span&gt;respiratory viruses&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/common-cold/about/index.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Typical symptoms" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/common-cold/about/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="16"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Typical symptoms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; include a runny or congested nose, coughing, sneezing, sore throat, fever, body aches and headache. It’s &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/coldflu.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="similar" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/coldflu.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="17"&gt;&lt;span&gt;similar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; to the flu, but one way to differentiate it is that “colds come on gradually, usually over the course of a few days,” said Millen. Flu, on the other hand, is very abrupt and intense.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;After you begin exhibiting symptoms of the common cold, you are contagious for about seven days, Vijayan said. Once symptoms are cleared, you are no longer contagious. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While you are symptomatic, stay home. Once symptoms start improving overall and your fever has subsided without taking fever-reducing drugs for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="at least a full 24 hours" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="18"&gt;&lt;span&gt;at least a full 24 hours&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;span&gt;you are less contagious and can return to daily activities. Masking and physical distancing are strongly encouraged until symptoms are healed or for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="at least five days" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="19"&gt;&lt;span&gt;at least five days&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, to prevent spreading the virus to others.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSV&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;RSV, or respiratory syncytial virus, is a viral infection.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;“I call it the wheezing virus because it makes people wheeze,” Millen said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you are coughing, sneezing or wheezing, or you have a fever or a runny or congested nose, there is a chance it &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/rsv/symptoms/index.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="may be RSV" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/rsv/symptoms/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="20"&gt;&lt;span&gt;may be RSV&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Symptoms tend to pop up in stages instead of all at once.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Once you start showing RSV symptoms, you are contagious for up to eight days afterward, according to the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/rsv/causes/index.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Centers for Disease Control and Prevention" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/rsv/causes/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="21"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are advised to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="stay home" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="22"&gt;&lt;span&gt;stay home&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; while you are symptomatic. Once symptoms start improving overall and your fever has subsided without fever-reducing drugs for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="at least a full 24 hours" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="23"&gt;&lt;span&gt;at least a full 24 hours&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;span&gt;you are less contagious and can cease isolation. While you have ongoing symptoms, or for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="at least five days" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/prevention/precautions-when-sick.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="24"&gt;&lt;span&gt;at least five days&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, practice physical distancing and mask when you’re out and about. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you are &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/rsv/causes/index.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="immunocompromised" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/rsv/causes/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="25"&gt;&lt;span&gt;immunocompromised&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, you can be contagious for four or more weeks after you start developing RSV symptoms. This is true even if you no longer &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/rsv/causes/index.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="have symptoms" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/rsv/causes/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="26"&gt;&lt;span&gt;have symptoms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strep Throat&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/group-a-strep/about/strep-throat.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Strep throat" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/group-a-strep/about/strep-throat.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="27"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Strep throat&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; is a bacterial infection that commonly presents as a sore throat without any nasal symptoms or watery eyes, Millen explained. Your throat may also feel swollen, there may be red spots on the roof of your mouth or white spots on your throat, and you may develop a fever. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When you start getting the symptoms of strep throat, inform your doctor so they can prescribe you &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/group-a-strep/hcp/clinical-guidance/strep-throat.html#:~:text=People%20with%20group%20A%20strep,starting%20appropriate%20antibiotic%20therapyA" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="antibiotics" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/group-a-strep/hcp/clinical-guidance/strep-throat.html#:~:text=People%20with%20group%20A%20strep,starting%20appropriate%20antibiotic%20therapyA" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="28"&gt;&lt;span&gt;antibiotics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; for it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Once you start the antibiotics for strep throat, you’re only infectious for about 24 hours afterwards,” Millen said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/group-a-strep/hcp/clinical-guidance/strep-throat.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Stay at home" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/group-a-strep/hcp/clinical-guidance/strep-throat.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="29"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Stay at home&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; for 24 hours from when you start taking the antibiotics, and until your fever has lifted. Besides reducing your contagiousness, the antibiotics help ease your sore throat quickly, Vijayan noted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Strep throat&lt;/span&gt; “&lt;span&gt;can be contagious for up to three weeks if you don’t get antibiotics,” Millen said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whooping Cough (Pertussis)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Whooping cough, or pertussis, is a bacterial infection with symptoms that mimic those of the common cold in the early stage of the disease, according to Millen. You might have a runny or congested nose, a very mild cough, and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/signs-symptoms/index.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="low-grade fever" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/signs-symptoms/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="30"&gt;&lt;span&gt;low-grade fever&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;About seven to 14 days in, the coughs worsen into violent and uncontrollable &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/signs-symptoms/index.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="coughing fits" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/signs-symptoms/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="31"&gt;&lt;span&gt;coughing fits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. During and after these fits, some people are short of breath or exhausted; they may vomit, or feel like they’re going to; and they may let out the characteristic “whoop” sound after the cough, according to both Vijayan and Millen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/about/index.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="CDC" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/about/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="32"&gt;&lt;span&gt;CDC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, pertussis is contagious from the time symptoms begin until about 14 days after the onset of the cough. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you have symptoms that resemble the common cold, it’s a good idea to stay home and pay attention to whether your cough worsens over time. If it does, see your doctor immediately to confirm whether you have pertussis or another illness. The antibiotic for pertussis is more effective if &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/hcp/clinical-care/index.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="prescribed early" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/hcp/clinical-care/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="33"&gt;&lt;span&gt;prescribed early&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;After taking the antibiotic for pertussis for five full days, you are considered to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/infection-control/hcp/healthcare-personnel-epidemiology-control/pertussis.html#:~:text=Symptomatic%20persons%20who%20receive%20effective,be%20recognized%20as%20pertussis21." target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="no longer be contagious" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691e4c52e4b0b763ab8da218" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/infection-control/hcp/healthcare-personnel-epidemiology-control/pertussis.html#:~:text=Symptomatic%20persons%20who%20receive%20effective,be%20recognized%20as%20pertussis21." data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="34"&gt;&lt;span&gt;no longer be contagious&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 12:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxNSVNQX2pZUzMxRnQ3ZDBHNmlCMzRINXNablR5dnJ4WVo4bW1RUnhTdDJHMkVVSWhobHByMTZ6T3A3ck9ja3Iwdk1uTmhHaVl5MjRQeVdac1IxdDd5bGdKbUJyN3Z5dzJPOC1yUmJxcERyUVF3aW5RN2xTOFprREUtb0twcDBSU0xYWkRJRGswcS1XMzJS0gGaAUFVX3lxTE9DdmVCZ2w1ZWpLZlQ0N3NCZDc4SFpNUHByWndpUnhRaEtvdVZUU3J3XzlSMkozMUViS1VTeWFmNXZKYmFYSzFXZHd2TE5jNHR2Q00yUTRPMkcxZlJMeGctNHBzWnBXS1ZpYVlQNUs2cTFvOTg4eXlWekhkOVliUGxubUZCQmlIMEMtYk5HbWc2eXNvUHFNS2lKb3c</guid></item><item><title>ELLIE医生： “我的口腔溃疡不断复发，我该怎么办？ '-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15315915/How-rid-never-ending-awful-mouth-ulcers-DR-ELLIE-answer.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;I keep getting mouth ulcers. How do I get rid of them as quickly as possible – and prevent them from coming back?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Dr Ellie responds:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Unfortunately, there is no quick fix for mouth ulcers. But there are steps that can be taken to reduce the risk of future sores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mouth ulcers are breaks in the lining of the mouth, on the inner lips, inner cheeks or the tongue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Anyone with a mouth ulcer that has lasted longer than three weeks should see a doctor. In rare cases, it could be mouth &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-21161e30-c789-11f0-b1a8-bddd4a04d7c6"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;. It can also be a symptom of Crohn’s disease, a debilitating inflammatory bowel problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For most patients, mouth ulcers don’t require medical attention. Instead, the sores tend to clear up on their own. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bonjela, a popular ulcer remedy, only dulls the pain of the sores – it does not get rid of them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some patients may benefit from an antibacterial mouthwash, such as chlorhexidine, to keep the ulcer clean and avoid a painful infection. But, again, this doesn’t speed up the healing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Mouth ulcers are breaks in the lining of the mouth, on the inner lips, inner cheeks or the tongue&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Crucially, though, there are ways to prevent ulcers coming back. Many patients find that taking a vitamin B12 supplement reduces the risk of recurrence. Certain foods, such as coffee, chocolate and peanuts, are thought to trigger ulcers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One of the biggest risk factors is a chemical found in many toothpastes called sodium lauryl sulfate, or SLS. But studies show it can also irritate the mouth, leading to ulcers. The good news is that there are SLS-free toothpastes available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;At 84, I recently developed a large bulge just above my pelvis. It’s not painful and the only other symptom I have is an increased need to go to the toilet. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;My GP has requested a scan, but apparently I’ll have to wait six weeks. Should I be worried?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Dr Ellie responds:&lt;/span&gt; Any new lump that appears in someone aged over 80 should be urgently scanned and assessed. Arguably, the most common lump that appears near the pelvis would be a hernia. This is where internal organs push through a hole in overlying muscles, creating a lump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sometimes they hurt, but not always. The main worry is that the bulge may contain internal parts of crucial organs, such as the bowels. This can cause the organ to be blocked, stopping&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;it from functioning properly, which can have dangerous consequences. If someone has a lump like this and their toilet habits have changed, that might suggest the bowels are affected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is possible that a new lump could be caused by swollen glands or lymph nodes in the groin. Lymph nodes are small bean-shaped glands which help the body to filter out harmful substances like bacteria or viruses. A swollen lymph node might be due to an infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But it could also be a sign of cancer. That is why it is crucial that patients with a new lump get scanned, so the risk of a deadly tumour can be ruled out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A new large lump in an 84-year-old should meet the criteria for an urgent NHS scan. If a patient with a new lump also has a change in bowel habits, then this symptom should be mentioned to the GP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;I have diverticulitis and have been in constant pain for two decades. The only relief I get is from cortisone injections but the effect only lasts for a few months. What else can I do?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Dr Ellie responds:&lt;/span&gt; Patients with chronic pain may benefit from daily tablets that GPs can prescribe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Diverticulitis is an agonising condition where small pockets form in the walls of the intestine. This causes inflammation and, often, infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Symptoms include tummy pain, constipation, diarrhoea and bloating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Unfortunately, diverticulitis cannot be cured. Instead, patients are often given laxatives to help with bowel movement issues and medicines which help with stomach cramps, called antispasmodics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lifestyle changes, including eating a balanced diet rich in fruit, vegetables and whole grains, as well as boosting fibre intake, avoiding smoking and maintaining a healthy weight, have all been shown to help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Diverticulitis patients will generally take anti-inflammatory tablets such as ibuprofen and naproxen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For those in severe agony, nerve pain tablets may help. These drugs, which include amitriptyline, nortriptyline and pregabalin, work by dampening pain receptors in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many patients also report that talking therapy and regular exercise help to relieve some of the pain of diverticulitis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;If shingles jab stops Alzheimer’s, would you pay £500 for it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;I am fascinated by growing research that suggests the shingles vaccine can help to prevent dementia.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Some studies have shown the Shingrix jab, which is available on the NHS, can cut the risk of the deadly disease by as much as 20 per cent.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;More research is obviously needed, but it would appear that some people are already getting injected to protect their brain health.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;One example is Lord James Bethell, 58, a former Conservative health minister during the Covid-19 pandemic. Last week he posted on social media that he paid £500 for the Shingrix vaccine for the express purpose of lowering his dementia risk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;It raises a big question: Should the NHS be offering the vaccine for free to young patients to prevent dementia?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Have you received the shingles jab in order to reduce your dementia risk? Write and let me know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Why are so many doctors still missing women’s heart attacks &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Seven years ago I spoke at Parliament’s first-ever women’s health conference. One of the biggest issues that cropped up was the NHS’s poor record when it came to spotting heart disease in women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Heart attacks, in particular, are often viewed as a men’s issue. But the deadly condition affects 35,000 British women every year. It is thought to become much more likely after the menopause, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Despite this, as we discussed at the 2018 conference, heart attacks are often missed in women as doctors don’t expect them to be affected. And,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;when they are spotted, women are less likely to be offered crucial treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Unfortunately, today, it feels like little has changed since that landmark event. Women who suffer heart attacks are still often poorly served by the NHS. It is about time the Government took notice of this issue and acted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Are you a woman who has suffered a heart attack? Did the NHS mishandle your treatment? I want to hear from you. Please contact me using the email on the right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:58:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxOX3ZIVEdDT3ROQm9sTkxsMWNZNHI3Q0xJMk5vcXVfVlpUTHJBcG0tdW1sckZSR0Y4RmNTMENQcTFCUnZkeEJJUkpZYXhNNWhoU3BaUHhrQnlBRHNMdkpMWW1TUi1Wb2J3S005VWRhOGRtSi1NUV9nSVU3OFd5cWlvUE83SHlCY3I5UmNqaWU4Zk1iWE90bFhsbXk5YllUR3FYTkRNNVlhYWVvaGVZSHNHZ2J3</guid></item><item><title>美国有失去麻疹消除地位的风险吗？ - ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/us-risk-losing-measles-elimination-status/story?id=127763508</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;As measles continues to spread across the United States, questions have emerged about whether the country will retain its measles elimination status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The U.S. is currently experiencing the highest number of measles cases reported in more than three decades, in large part due to an outbreak in western Texas that infected more than 700 people and spread to New Mexico and Oklahoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Meanwhile, an outbreak in Arizona and Utah currently shows no signs of slowing down and a separate outbreak in South Carolina has sent dozens of students into quarantine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;If spread of the virus continues into late January, it will mean the U.S. has seen a year of continuous transmission, which could lead to a loss of the country's elimination status. Measles would once again be considered endemic or constantly circulating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The threat of the U.S. losing its elimination status is looming after &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/canada-loses-measles-elimination-status-amid-year-long/story?id=127373379" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;Canada lost its measles elimination status&lt;/a&gt; following a struggle to contain a year-long measles outbreak, public health experts told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"I do think that the likelihood that we're going to lose status, especially if things continue the way that they're going, is I think pretty high," Dr. Tony Moody, a professor of pediatrics in the division of infectious diseases at Duke University Medical Center, told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Signs point the way to measles testing in the parking lot of the Seminole Hospital District across, Feb. 27, 2025, in Seminole, Texas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Jan Sonnenmair/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;State of measles in the U.S.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;As of Wednesday, there have been 1,753 confirmed cases across 42 states this year, according to the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html#cdc_data_surveillance_section_10-measles-cases-in-2025" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; (CDC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;There have been 45 outbreaks, so far this year compared to 16 outbreaks all last year, CDC data shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Additionally, 92% of cases have been among those who are unvaccinated or whose vaccination status is unknown, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;There have been three measles deaths this year -- the first fatalities due to the disease in a decade -- including among &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/child-measles-dies-texas-hospital-officials/story?id=120539137" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;two unvaccinated school-aged children&lt;/a&gt; in Texas and one &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/unvaccinated-new-mexico-resident-tests-positive-measles-after/story?id=119529919" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;unvaccinated adult&lt;/a&gt; in New Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The CDC currently &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/vaccines/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;recommends&lt;/a&gt; that people receive two doses of the measles, mumps, rubella (MMR) vaccine, the first at ages 12 to 15 months and the second between 4 and 6 years old. One dose is 93% effective, and two doses are 97% effective against measles, the CDC says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;However, CDC data shows vaccination rates have been lagging in recent years. During the 2024-25 school year, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/schoolvaxview/data/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;92.5% of kindergartners received the MMR vaccine&lt;/a&gt;. This is lower than the 92.7% seen the previous school year and the 95.2% seen in the 2019-20 school year, prior to the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Even in states with high MMR vaccine uptake, pockets of unvaccinated or under-vaccinated communities can lead to rapid spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;For example, in Texas, 94.3% of kindergartners were up to date on their MMR vaccine for the 2023-24 school year, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/73/wr/mm7341a3.htm#T1_down" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;CDC data&lt;/a&gt; shows. However, in Gaines County -- the epicenter of this year's outbreak -- 17.6% of kindergartners were exempt from at least one vaccine during the 2023-24 school year, one of the highest exemption rates in the state, according to &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.dshs.texas.gov/immunizations/data/school/conscientious-exemptions" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;state health data&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"It's kind of like you have a very dry forest, so any spark that comes in can burn down the entire forest," Dr. Peter Chin-Hong, a professor of medicine and infectious diseases specialist at the University of California, San Francisco, told ABC News. "That's what's happening, which is fewer people being vaccinated, as evidenced by the drop in in people entering kindergarten."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;He said one case of measles is like a spark that quickly turns into a blaze as it spread through an unvaccinated community "and that's why it's hard to put out the fire."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;How loss of status is determined&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The loss of status is determined by the Pan American Health Organization (PAHO, an agency of the U.N. that oversees international health in the Americas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;An independent body of experts established by the PAHO -- known as the Measles, Rubella, and Congenital Rubella Syndrome Elimination Regional Monitoring and Re-Verification Commission (RVC) -- meets at least once a year to monitor and re-verify measles and rubella elimination among countries in the Americas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Instructions for a Measles vaccination is seen outside of the Lubbock Public Health facility, April 9, 2025, in Lubbock, Texas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Brandon Bell/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;A person familiar with how PAHO determines loss of elimination status told ABC News that there would have to be compelling evidence that there has been continuous spread of measles in the U.S. since January, when the first cases were reported in Texas and that other outbreaks may trace back to the Texas outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The person said the committee will get together in mid-2026 to look at the data, write its next report and formally submit it to the PAHO for review. The annual meeting will likely take place in late 2026, unless a previously unplanned meeting is convened beforehand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"The RVC holds annual meetings with all member states, conducts visits to priority countries, reviews national sustainability reports, and issues recommendations to the Director of PAHO," a spokesperson for PAHO told ABC News. "It may also convene extraordinary meetings with member states to provide recommendations on specific topics or to follow up on outbreak situations. At this time, no extraordinary meeting has been scheduled for next year specifically to assess the U.S. or Mexico situation, but such a meeting could be convened if the epidemiological situation warrants."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Between April 2025 and October 2025, Mexico has seen 4,550 cases, according to the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/global-measles-vaccination/data-research/global-measles-outbreaks/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;WHO&lt;/a&gt;, which could also lead to the loss of its elimination status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Moody explained that the U.S. having measles elimination status, which it received in 2000, is less of a formal declaration and more of a statement that a county has a relatively low number of cases and no sustained transmission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Loss of status would similarly be a statement that a country has sustained transmission and that the virus is constantly present, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"What does it mean from a public health perspective, or a parent's perspective, it means that we have a higher risk for seeing transmission, and that if someone goes to a place where there is sustained transmission, there's kind of an increased risk and, truthfully, you can pick it up just about anywhere," Moody said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;Canada's loss of elimination status&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Earlier this month, the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.canada.ca/en/public-health/news/2025/11/statement-from-the-public-health-agency-of-canada-on-canadas-measles-elimination-status.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;Public Health Agency of Canada said&lt;/a&gt; it was informed of the elimination status loss by PAHO after more than 12 months of continuous measles transmission. Canada's outbreak began in late October 2024, and the county has seen more than 5,200 confirmed and probable cases since then, data from the health agency shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;As a result, the Americas region lost elimination status as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Canada can re-establish its measles elimination status if measles transmission related to the current outbreak is "interrupted" for at least 12 months, according to the county's health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;A family supports a young child as he receives the MMR vaccine at a vaccine clinic put on by Lubbock Public Health Department, March 1, 2025, in Lubbock, Texas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Jan Sonnenmair/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Given that we share one of the longest borders in the world with Canada. It's not as if there's some magic barrier between U.S. and Canada," Moody said. "If there's transmission in Canada, we're going to get it in the United States. ...  I'm not saying that Canada has put us at risk. We've kind of put ourselves at risk but ... I do see it as being a highly likely thing that we're going to see continued transmission."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Canada will present and implement an action plan under PAHO's regional framework to increase immunization coverage, reinforce surveillance systems and ensure rapid outbreak response to stop spread. This shows what the U.S. would likely experience if it lost its status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"If we lose our status, it'll be hard to regain it," Chin-Hong said, noting how many workers have been laid off at HHS that might have helped control large outbreaks. "Not only loss of expertise, but just loss of the workforce in general, the people who go out and do the surveillance and contain the epidemic by vaccination efforts and all that. ... It just denotes how fragile public health gains are. In general, it's easy to lose it and hard to get it back."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;How to prevent further spread&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Public health experts told ABC News there are several steps that can be taken to help control the spread of measles in the U.S. including increasing funding to public health for monitoring and surveillance as well as spreading awareness about how dangerous measles can be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;However, they add that the best way to stop the spread is through vaccination, both to protect yourself and the most vulnerable individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"We can't control the people who are unable to get vaccines because they're being treated for cancer, because they are born with an immunodeficiency," Dr. Aaron Milstone, pediatric director of infection prevention at Johns Hopkins Health System, told ABC News. "What we can control is everyone else in the community who is eligible for a vaccine, who does not take it, and that's the reason that measles is spreading, in part, because the herd protection from our community has gone down."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;As an extra step, public health agencies have &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/han/php/notices/han00522.html?CDC_AA_refVal=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Fhan%2F2025%2Fhan00522.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;previously recommended&lt;/a&gt; early MMR vaccination for infants living in outbreak areas or traveling internationally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;This would result in three doses overall: an early dose between age 6 months and 11 months and then the two regularly scheduled doses at age 1 and between ages 4 and 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Milstone said the recommendation to give a child their first MMR dose at age one was under the assumption that they likely would not be exposed to measles before then and that antibodies passed in utero would help protect them during their first year of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Now, with the continuous spread being seen, "are we going to have to rethink our recommendations for when to vaccinate kids in the U.S.?" Milstone said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;ABC News' Youri Benadjaoud contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:07:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQNS1WWGhHbWpHVkQtcEtSUU9wajBldGo5ZzRRdGVKMk83ZU14OGh6cVpiUTcydUVIdTFYNkhwQnJuakN4WnZQN2lPaU9mSENpRmdZdzRnY0pYY0xVVjJhZkZpWkpwVDFSYUZRTXhwZTRib09xWW1IMWNzbEdmNUlmaDZOQjhrWm1sZ0R0TFRUNHBaa1BF0gGaAUFVX3lxTFB0VjFWMGRNSkdRTFFFb1E5OWw2WGlXTzkyTVF6anl0UTFKTHg4RW5la1ZzM3hOdnMydkhhMkxhZmJDbnU3ZFpyM1BNUnBxX041RGV3dHg1RkZnSXk5Rlo3TjhyclhmVHlpVTdTNU5TUnl4ZlRfUzF6ZVNEUEZ5dmRHRTdjTjVKVmpTTTRWdmJvZWdUdndfclY2T2c</guid></item><item><title>与老年人大脑加速衰老相关的促炎饮食- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/pro-inflammatory-diets-linked-to-accelerated-brain-aging-in-older-adults/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent research suggests that the food we eat may influence the biological aging of our brains. A study involving over 20,000 adults indicates that consuming a diet high in pro-inflammatory foods is associated with accelerated brain aging. This effect appears to be most pronounced in older adults. The findings were published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s10654-025-01318-6" target="_blank"&gt;European Journal of Epidemiology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic systemic inflammation is increasingly recognized as a contributing factor to various health issues, including neurodegenerative diseases. As people age, levels of inflammatory markers in the blood typically rise. Elevated levels of these markers often correlate with a higher risk of cognitive decline and conditions such as dementia. Scientists have established that diet is a primary way to regulate inflammation in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain dietary patterns, such as the Western diet, are known to promote inflammation. These diets usually contain high amounts of red meat, processed foods, and high-fat dairy products. In contrast, diets rich in vegetables, fruits, and whole grains tend to lower inflammation. While previous studies have linked pro-inflammatory diets to memory problems and specific brain changes, the impact on overall brain aging remained less clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers behind this new study aimed to fill this gap in knowledge. They sought to determine if a diet that promotes inflammation is linked to a comprehensive measure of brain health known as “brain age.” They also wanted to understand if this relationship varied based on a person’s chronological age or their genetic risk for dementia. Additionally, the team investigated whether systemic inflammation in the body acted as a bridge connecting diet to brain health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There is growing evidence to suggest that diet may play an important role in brain and cognitive health, and specifically that inflammation from an unhealthy diet could be one contributing mechanism. However, whether dietary inflammation is associated with a comprehensive measure of brain health has not been previously examined,” explained study author Michelle M. Dunk, a researcher at the Aging Research Center and Division of Neurogeriatrics at the Karolinska Institutet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One way to measure someone’s overall brain health is by measuring their ‘brain age’ from MRI scans. We can then calculate the “brain age gap” by comparing a person’s brain age to their chronological age. When someone’s brain looks older than their actual age, it may signal an increased risk for cognitive decline or dementia.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data for this analysis came from the UK Biobank, a large-scale biomedical database. The study included 21,473 participants who were between the ages of 40 and 70. None of these individuals had neurological disorders at the beginning of the study. This exclusion helped ensure that the results reflected typical aging rather than the progression of pre-existing brain diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To assess dietary habits, the researchers used a web-based questionnaire called the Oxford WebQ. Participants reported their food and drink consumption from the previous twenty-four hours. This assessment was administered up to five times over a period of several years. The repeated assessments allowed for a more accurate estimation of habitual dietary intake than a single questionnaire would provide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From this dietary data, the investigators calculated a Dietary Inflammatory Index score for each participant. This index is based on the intake of thirty-one specific nutrients and dietary components. The researchers looked at nutrients that either increase or decrease inflammation levels. For instance, components like fiber, omega-3 fatty acids, and certain vitamins are considered anti-inflammatory. Conversely, saturated fats and carbohydrates are often classified as pro-inflammatory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on these scores, participants were divided into four distinct groups. Group 1 consisted of individuals with the most anti-inflammatory diets. Group 4 included those with the most pro-inflammatory diets. This categorization allowed the researchers to compare brain health outcomes across different levels of dietary quality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approximately nine years after the initial dietary assessments, participants underwent magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) scans of their brains. The researchers used these scans to estimate the biological age of each participant’s brain. They employed a machine learning model to analyze 1,079 different structural and functional measures from the MRI data. This advanced technology can detect subtle patterns of aging that might be missed by traditional analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team then calculated a metric called the “brain age gap.” This was done by subtracting the participant’s chronological age from their estimated brain age. A positive gap indicates that the brain appears older than expected for the person’s actual age. A negative gap suggests the brain appears younger and healthier. This metric serves as a proxy for general brain integrity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also utilized blood samples collected at the beginning of the research period. The investigators measured several biomarkers of systemic inflammation, including C-reactive protein and white blood cell counts. These markers were combined into a composite inflammation score. This score allowed the team to test if inflammation in the body explained the link between diet and brain changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results revealed a significant association between dietary habits and brain aging. Individuals who consumed the most pro-inflammatory diets had a larger brain age gap compared to those who ate anti-inflammatory diets. Specifically, those in the most pro-inflammatory group had brains that appeared about half a year older on average than those in the healthiest diet group. This suggests that poor dietary quality may accelerate the biological clock of the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This association was dependent on the age of the participants. The link between a pro-inflammatory diet and older brain age was much stronger in adults aged 60 and older. In this older demographic, a pro-inflammatory diet was associated with an advanced brain age of nearly a full year. This implies that older adults might be more vulnerable to the negative effects of a poor diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also found that systemic inflammation played a measurable role in this relationship. Statistical analysis showed that the composite inflammation score accounted for about 8 percent of the association between diet and brain age. This finding provides evidence that pro-inflammatory foods may harm the brain in part by increasing overall inflammation in the body. The remaining effect is likely due to other mechanisms not captured by the inflammation score.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genetic risk factors were also considered in the analysis. The researchers looked at polygenic risk scores for Alzheimer’s disease and the presence of the APOE4 gene. The association between diet and brain age was generally consistent regardless of genetic risk. However, the link appeared somewhat stronger in individuals who were not carriers of the APOE4 gene. This suggests that diet remains a relevant factor for brain health across different genetic profiles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings align with previous research showing that healthy diets support cognitive function. Diets like the Mediterranean or MIND diet emphasize the same anti-inflammatory foods identified in this study. These include plant-based foods rich in polyphenols and healthy fats. The current study adds to the literature by using a global measure of brain structure rather than focusing on specific regions like the hippocampus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We found that those eating more pro-inflammatory diets had a significantly larger brain age gap – meaning they had an older, less healthy brain than would be expected based on their chronological age,” Dunk told PsyPost. “Those consuming the most pro-inflammatory diets had an advanced brain age by half a year compared to those with the most anti-inflammatory diets. This association was stronger in adults 60 years of age or older, suggesting that older adults may benefit most from an anti-inflammatory diet.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We were also able to confirm that systemic inflammation partially accounted for this association, by using a composite score of several inflammatory markers in the blood. In other words, those consuming more pro-inflammatory diets tended to have higher levels of circulating inflammatory biomarkers, which were in turn associated with older brain age. This finding suggests that an anti-inflammatory diet could potentially support brain health in part by promoting lower levels of inflammation in the body.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there are some limitations to this study. The UK Biobank participants are generally healthier and wealthier than the average population. This selection bias might affect how well the results apply to the general public. The study is also observational in nature. It can show a connection between diet and brain age but cannot definitively prove that diet causes the aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another limitation involves the dietary assessment method. Self-reported data is subject to memory errors and may not perfectly reflect actual intake. Additionally, the Dietary Inflammatory Index focuses on nutrients rather than whole foods. People consume complex combinations of foods, not isolated nutrients. However, the index is a validated tool that generally correlates well with healthy eating patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The Dietary Inflammatory Index is calculated based on a person’s consumption of a variety of macronutrients, micronutrients, whole foods, and spices,” Dunk noted. “Because this index isn’t primarily based on whole foods, it might not be immediately obvious what a pro- or anti-inflammatory diet actually looks like.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Some of the anti-inflammatory components include dietary fiber (found in whole plant foods), omega 3 fats, onion, garlic, ginger, turmeric, green and black tea, isoflavones (soy), polyphenols (especially high in berries), and many vitamins and minerals. On the other hand, foods high in saturated fat, trans fat, or cholesterol tend to be pro-inflammatory.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This scoring is generally consistent with healthy dietary patterns we often hear about – like the Mediterranean, MIND, or whole food plant-based diets. Each of these dietary patterns are high in healthy plant foods (fruits, vegetables, whole grains, legumes, nuts, seeds) and limit foods like red and processed meat, deep-fried and ultraprocessed foods, and other animal-based foods to varying degrees, which are higher in saturated fat and cholesterol.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research is needed to confirm these findings in more diverse populations. It would be beneficial to investigate whether switching to an anti-inflammatory diet can reverse accelerated brain aging. Clinical trials could provide stronger evidence of a causal relationship. For now, the results suggest that choosing anti-inflammatory foods may be a practical strategy for maintaining brain health as we age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s10654-025-01318-6" target="_blank"&gt;The association between a pro-inflammatory diet and brain age in middle-aged and older adults&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Michelle M. Dunk, Huijie Huang, Jiao Wang, Abigail Dove, Sakura Sakakibara, Jie Guo, Adrián Carballo-Casla, David A. Bennett, and Weili Xu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:04:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxORzlWVnRudUMySFNsaFhTSlRrMnlUNE9hdy1BN0RLaDVObFJ0NVhnT1dqeEVORUZmN0d4NjVGUjA0c25mWGNpUnFQaFZNaVpWdld5N0hHTC1NZkFRVHFMN19jblY3SmNFR2l3YUl5OFFiekRVYmdkbjJydUJqZUdUSGc4R1lQbVZRaks5UmdYRHowY0lxTjhDN3FxYTJKUQ</guid></item><item><title>每天步行10000步够吗？健身教练打破了真正的目标-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/is-walking-10000-steps-daily-enough-fitness-trainer-breaks-down-the-real-target/articleshow/125500928.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walking is generally promoted as the most accessible exercise of them all: no equipment, easy to squeeze into daily life, and accessible to just about anyone. Over the years, this number-10,000 steps a day-has evolved into a fitness mantra promoted by apps, wearables, and wellness influencers. While that can be a motivating thing, experts now say that just hitting this number doesn't guarantee weight loss or improved health. Instead, it's about how, when, and why you move that truly matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Our step goals are to be "personalised"&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Celebrity trainer Siddhartha Singh, who trains actress Tamannaah Bhatia, says daily step targets should reflect a person's lifestyle, work habits, and overall activity levels. "Not everyone needs 10,000 steps," says Singh. For someone with a desk job, for example, 8,000-9,000 steps a day may already be sufficient to counteract the effects of prolonged sitting and maintain good metabolic health. At the same time, people whose jobs involve a lot of physical labor may end up logging 15,000 steps or more without even trying, in which case the 10k goal becomes moot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Step targets should not be followed as strict "regime" but used more as guidelines, tailored to meet the needs of the individual. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This way, there is continuity without adding pressure or guilt when trying to achieve a universally set benchmark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Only walking is not enough&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While walking benefits one in terms of cardiopulmonary health, circulation, and stress relief, walking by itself is not a particularly effective way to lose weight. Celebrity trainer-- Siddhartha also states that strength training, flexibility exercises, and high-intensity workouts are an important part of any complete fitness program. Walking alone burns some calories and aids in core fitness, but adding resistance will help boost metabolism, build lean muscle, and enhance body composition in general.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weight loss and fitness, after all, are driven by more than just the movement of one's body; there is a holistic combination of exercise, nutrition, and lifestyle choices. Over-reliance on walking alone may slow progress or create unrealistic expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Daily step count is less important than intensity&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not all steps are created equal. Ten thousand slow, leisurely steps may not confer all the same benefits as 6,000 brisk, purposeful steps or interval-style walking. Adding intensity-such as uphill walking, power walking, or short bursts of faster movement-increases calorie burn, strengthens the cardiovascular system, and improves endurance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;More often than not, the quality of movement outweighs quantity. It's better to do some focused, intense activity for a shorter period of time than to obsess over reaching some generic step count that may or may not challenge the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consistency is another critical factor. Making exercise a regular part of your life, taking brief frequent walks, standing, or stretching during rest breaks at work, and incorporating activity into daily routines is more effective in establishing sustainable movement patterns than being obsessive about reaching 10,000 steps. Step goals can be motivating, but they are part of a larger strategy that will include strength training, aerobics, good nutrition, and proper sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Guidelines by official authorities&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the CDC recommends at least 150 minutes of moderate-intensity aerobic exercise weekly, along with strength training at least twice a week, it shows that overall physical activity and fitness variety are more relevant than step counts alone. Walking is just one tool among many, and focusing exclusively on steps can lead to a false sense of accomplishment. While the 10,000-step rule may be somewhat useful as a motivational rule of thumb- it is in no way a universal prescription for weight loss or health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more important than hitting a number are individual activity levels, movement intensity, and consistency. Long-term results in fitness come from regular walking, challenging one's body with different exercises, and maintaining balanced lifestyle habits. Ultimately, it is not about the number of steps that defines your health, but how you move and how often, and with what intention you build activity into your life. The best formula for long-lasting weight loss and overall wellness will include step goals personalized to you, a focus on movement quality first, and combining walking with strength and high-intensity exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-wFBVV95cUxPSnRVZXowWF9NQkpZLUJwT1ZzMVUxWGRVeXpxS3VTM3FLMHhHcmwwaE5sVU5UQk13RGdTWEZqWnBFeXFRdzNlaU9fRzlselF4ai1KUUlOc3Zad1Rjdkk1NnJ6cHR2ak9QM0g0RTZnM1BtUERuLWtWa2dvZWctRm9rdm9SazdwRDhrNkZtdmN2ZTdMOUpGc08xVUhIOE5oYWFEaG1ubGtJdVJDSTFwRzByR3dCdEJvdmNsOVBXVmMtT1ppQUV2cVhMR2RPRUp6RG5NUVhTSm1VYkg5cjFhc19BNWE4Q05NalhkZExKZm9ON2RwVDRzbHFJRFhhSdIBgAJBVV95cUxOT3RoakRIWE9vakh0NTB6Skd0QTdBdDJ5cEJ1UDFBUHNVTC1XRnhsWUIyN2x0VVQ5SzdmT0t1RXlhR1VZUTlvbGtUUG14dXlub3poR0xUZG9ISzZrdkhhNDBfWW5WR2paQ0RJT1JMZWdTNWF4ZHNBR25STUxqdm10MHhPbkw4eDU4eDA3Wms1REY0LWxPWnVucWFsSld6NW1QSDF1SnNoR0ZpWmpyd3hITHNfb094cG9UU2cxcWxBVk9Zd0JoUDVuaDVYbE9EdVduY2g4WlZhaGRjU05YekVDZUcwaTFYRnBXaktyUzkwbGRxR2pHWFNxc3VFZVgzdDJO</guid></item><item><title>“皮肤癌集群”的Pa.区域部位- PennLive.com</title><link>https://www.pennlive.com/life/2025/11/pa-area-site-of-skin-cancer-cluster.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MBVHZELWMRBXPLZWSGZ53U6DNA"&gt;Researchers at&lt;a href="https://www.pennlive.com/health/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt; the Penn State Cancer Institute&lt;/a&gt; have been analyzing cancer registry data from over the past five years or so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="E2VDW2S37JH3ZIONELXNKK5AQM"&gt;What they found is that there’s a &lt;a href="https://www.pennlive.com/" rel="" target="_blank"&gt;15-county &lt;/a&gt;stretch in Pennsylvania where adults of a certain age have a higher chance of getting melanoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6QKRHVLZSRDAFORAEBZN7WQ5KU"&gt;Published last week, &lt;a href="https://www.psu.edu/news/research/story/skin-cancer-cluster-found-15-pennsylvania-counties-or-near-farmland" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;the report&lt;/a&gt; — published in &lt;a href="https://ascopubs.org/doi/10.1200/CCI-25-00160" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;the JCO Clinical Cancer Informatics&lt;/a&gt; — states that this “skin cancer cluster” is situated in the south central region of the state. This includes Lycoming and York counties, among others. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VRPCFACXGREDTJN5LBUXO2SWGQ"&gt;It’s in this cluster that those over the age of 50 have a 57 percent higher likelihood of developing the disease. It also involves both rural and metropolitan areas, indicating that these cases are not necessarily confined to remote places or those with the most outdoor exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XYPEHTEEYZBURIV2ARJR3X2YX4"&gt;“Melanoma is often associated with beaches and sunbathing, but our findings suggest that agricultural environments may also place a role,” said associate professor of dermatology at Penn State Health and study co-author, Charlene Lam, via press release. “And this isn’t just about farmers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5SARJ3YDSBC2FBGGZAAEUYOZJA"&gt;“Entire communities living near agriculture, people who never set foot in a field, may still be at risk.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TMTEX7S4EFHOLLFAPD42PFIXZM"&gt;As for why this might be happening, sunlight, of course, has been considered as a factor. So, too, have cultivated cropland and herbicide usage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ONFJD5C5FJFGBN33Z2Y5RT3UHM"&gt;“Pesticides and herbicides are designed to alter biological systems,” explained emeritus professor of public health sciences at the school and the paper’s senior author. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="432YZLZYYBEBRLJ2GSBLWEIHQM"&gt;“Some of those same mechanisms, like increasing photosensitivity or causing oxidative stress, could theoretically contribute to melanoma development.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JET2METT2NBH7G3PPJR6AN4EO4"&gt;Lam added that she lops to better understand these factors in relation to public health. And encourages everyone to get their annual skin check. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:VIQEJ3AIPZAN3GX7EWUYVMZ324" data-fusion-component="VIQEJ3AIPZAN3GX7EWUYVMZ324"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:VIQEJ3AIPZAN3GX7EWUYVMZ324" data-fusion-component="VIQEJ3AIPZAN3GX7EWUYVMZ324"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PennLive.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 10:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxPcHgwelRXNllrQmhVZzVwSXpyejgwemxEc1I5SWV1MVMyRm1xYnRmM3VtdlFhallOaE1sc1JMV3ZTdUphblo0YVB3NzBKVzRYVTJEbjFFbGk0NmIxWE5mamswNmlwU2JOQ0Etem5SelVGQXBIdFdzWklZeEJjYl8wWF8wa0jSAZgBQVVfeXFMT0FlbEJNd3BkaVlySTlnQlhCdkhOS1dIamk5Yk55TW9PQnkzZDVFcXU1eVU3MmNXRlc2VmhHY1lzUm9sODc3M2txdUtudUVfbjl6TkhVdXdRakhpRmloQUd2TFJSeW44cXlWNXBLaF9uNEx0RGZEdEVkUEl6T3Z2MkxLb1Fpd3J2VXJfN0FTMW5mYjdreEZ5RFk</guid></item><item><title>注意到流感在四处蔓延？随着季节的增加，路易斯安那州在案件中领先全国- NOLA.com</title><link>https://www.nola.com/news/healthcare_hospitals/louisiana-leads-nation-in-flu-activity-as-season-starts-up/article_ed728d47-5792-4d05-b81b-87e7a576b2cb.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="row text-row" data-breakout="1"&gt;&lt;div class="col-md-8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Louisiana is heading into flu season and the Thanksgiving holiday with the highest flu activity level in the country. And while the number of severe cases of the illness at hospitals remains low, doctors are seeing signs that the respiratory virus season will get into full swing soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New federal data released Friday shows the percentage of medical visits for flu symptoms in Louisiana climbed to 3.9% in the week ending Nov. 15, almost double the national rate and the highest level recorded in any state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each week, the CDC ranks states on a 14-point scale based on the number of people who visit the doctor for a fever, plus a cough or sore throat. Louisiana is at level 7. Almost every other state is under level 3, except for Colorado, which is at level 4.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
    

    
    
    
    
    
    
&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    
    &lt;div class="row text-row" data-breakout="2"&gt;&lt;div class="col-md-8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost 100 people were admitted to the hospital for the flu last week in Louisiana, compared to 39 at the beginning of November.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Michael Bolton, a pediatric infectious disease specialist at Our Lady of the Lake in Baton Rouge, said Louisiana often sees flu activity rise before much of the country. Itâ€™s not always clear why â€” or if a worse flu season will follow as a result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="inline-asset inline-image layout-horizontal  subscriber-hide  tnt-inline-asset tnt-inline-relcontent tnt-inline-image tnt-inline-relation-child tnt-inline-presentation-default tnt-inline-alignment-default tnt-inline-width-default"&gt;&lt;figure class="photo layout-horizontal hover-expand letterbox-style-white"&gt;&lt;span class="expand hidden-print" data-toggle="modal" data-photo-target=".photo-f37fdba6-c10c-4fd7-93f7-bedd658d2ef4" data-instance="#gallery-items-ed728d47-5792-4d05-b81b-87e7a576b2cb-photo-modal" data-target="#photo-carousel-ed728d47-5792-4d05-b81b-87e7a576b2cb"&gt;
                &lt;span class="fas tnt-expand"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;/span&gt;
            
            
                
                
                    &lt;figcaption class="caption"&gt;
                            
                                &lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;
                                    &lt;p&gt;A map from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention shows flu activity across the country.Â &lt;/p&gt;
                                &lt;/span&gt;
                            
                        
                            
                        
                        &lt;span class="clearfix"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                
            
        &lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he said the timing should serve as a reminder to get vaccinated, especially after last yearâ€™s difficult pediatric season. Nearly 300 children died nationally, close to half of them without underlying health conditions. Most of those children had not received a flu shot.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
    

    
    
    
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;â€œThe flu vaccine is a vitally important piece of your health care plan,â€� Bolton said. â€œI can't underscore that enough.â€�&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    
    &lt;div class="row text-row" data-breakout="3"&gt;&lt;div class="col-md-8"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;A new strain&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thereâ€™s also another reason the flu may be spreading faster. One strain of the flu, known as H3N2, picked up new mutations over the summer. Those changes allow the strain to â€œevade immunity a little better,â€� said Bolton. For example, someone who had the flu last year may not have protection against this strain, though itâ€™s unclear if it will spread in Louisiana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This updated H3N2 strain has driven rapid increases in cases in the United Kingdom, Japan and Canada. New CDC data shows it now makes up more than half of flu samples tested in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
    

    
    
    
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;The current U.S. flu vaccine still teaches the body to recognize H3N2 and is expected to provide at least partial protection against the strain and reduce the risk of severe illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    
    &lt;div class="row text-row" data-breakout="4"&gt;&lt;div class="col-md-8"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Thanksgiving gatherings&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Thanksgiving approaching, Dr. Julio Figueroa, infectious disease expert at LSU Health New Orleans, said increases in flu numbers are expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;â€œItâ€™s not going crazy yet, but now is the time to get your flu vaccine,â€� Figueroa said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to state data, children ages 2 to 4 and 5 to 11 make up the largest percentage of visits to emergency departments for flu, making up more than 10% of visits for each group.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
    

    
    
    
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Margot Anderson, a pediatric hospitalist and infectious disease specialist at Manning Family Childrenâ€™s, said her team is already treating hospitalized children with both flu and RSV, another seasonal respiratory virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NOLA.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6wFBVV95cUxNbl80bEpLdG5MVTVDS2ZGX1h1QUVjdDB6THNaYks0S1FNcE5XYXJLLXRqQ1NldUo5MVJDRXhRWDNaWDFmQk9PMmd1ZXIwbnpLb1JDbUtUTExVSW5rX3J1OVVHaUdEbnVnRW1PVkVuR3JmZnc2Q2ZwaGVmNnB5TWw2UDhRY2drdnNXNXN5YWQ1bERWdjdoZlVFVHZaNUFwN09yWWFjanpKYkp4Yk9NX1JvckpFUmlfWDljRUR2QXJ6MUphRFhWZDJBanRSVmttYUJ6eHJmOVE2M1dQQm1QelozS1Q1eU9Dc1lvQ0xv0gHwAUFVX3lxTFBGeDl2SG5fRFQyTkJQNmt2THJib2R0SmZzd3dpZmxLVGhhR1lXTTZFRXJERURkRW01Q3RhR19kNkhYYmpud0ZKdlVLa21mZFAzQndjclBRVGlJOWFSMkJMNWp5SHJOd0lSTGpHNThrZjNzT1E5N09tUHlycWVXQ212bjJsdXRPczVIVm1LeTZtUU96TEZCTnRPVDJxSDJfV2FIYVBhVnRKWEZrLUk2RjVkMk4zMTh1WUppYVRyZ2tNU2pEdEtvNlhJVkUyTXBrTkRLSENtSlVNcDZMSEE0MkZMTXIzZThCV1Y1cGNiTzlwcw</guid></item><item><title>卫生部门称，华盛顿州居民死于首例确诊的H5N5禽流感病例-路透社</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/washington-state-resident-dies-first-confirmed-h5n5-bird-flu-case-health-2025-11-22/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Reuters</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 09:58:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3AFBVV95cUxNQzdhRXBDNmpKdEFwbGp3RGtCWlVlMXRCS3dBMko0Q3FFMy1IVXd6QmJqUE1leFYzSXZNelc2anJDY1o2OGRVbHVMOVNpYkhzZUF1bUllLXhiRThyZDctX2JTR1lYSUlBTnZOTENfWVlsblA3REdYMjE1dXE1RFJfSDdPMVBZWVpLemc0dHgzZlEzVVVJVFVhc3NCcHJLNW9JTmhlMjlpZnV2blpLMmMzZzVXTVE0ZExMOEUtSlEyXzJibHBrRGNSeEJWVmEzNjFNS1VvS3ZWcDQycGhf</guid></item><item><title>拥有18年经验的血管外科医生警告“1万步不会取消10小时的坐姿” ，以下是行之有效的方法|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/vascular-surgeon-with-18-years-of-experience-warns-10k-steps-wont-undo-10-hours-of-sitting-heres-what-works-101763803593521.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/vascular-surgeon-with-18-years-of-experience-warns-10k-steps-wont-undo-10-hours-of-sitting-heres-what-works-101763803593521.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Do you work from home or spend hours sitting at your desk for work or to complete projects? Well, we have news for you: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/sitting-is-the-new-smoking-sitting-for-too-long-could-be-behind-19-diseases-know-easy-lifestyle-tweaks-to-avoid-risk-101735970282806.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="sitting is the new smoking"&gt;sitting is the new smoking&lt;/a&gt;, and completing your daily steps will not reverse the damage done by hours of constant immobility.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/22/550x309/long_hours_of_sitting_1763804597038_1763804597131.jpg" alt="If you’ve been desk-bound from 9 AM to 7 PM, your veins have already taken the damage. (Shutterstock)" title="If you’ve been desk-bound from 9 AM to 7 PM, your veins have already taken the damage. (Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/22/550x309/long_hours_of_sitting_1763804597038_1763804597131.jpg" alt="If you’ve been desk-bound from 9 AM to 7 PM, your veins have already taken the damage. (Shutterstock)" title="If you’ve been desk-bound from 9 AM to 7 PM, your veins have already taken the damage. (Shutterstock)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;If you’ve been desk-bound from 9 AM to 7 PM, your veins have already taken the damage. (Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/aiims-gastroenterologist-shares-5-signs-of-nutrient-deficiency-weak-bones-isnt-first-warning-for-vitamin-d-deficiency-101763777843854.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="AIIMS-trained gastroenterologist shares 5 signs of nutrient deficiency: ‘Weak bones isn't first warning for…’"&gt;AIIMS-trained gastroenterologist shares 5 signs of nutrient deficiency: ‘Weak bones isn't first warning for…’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Sumit Kapadia, &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/texas-vascular-surgeon-shares-3-tips-to-ensure-vein-health-for-a-comfortable-pregnancy-planning-to-get-pregnant-101760168391170.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="vascular surgeon"&gt;vascular surgeon&lt;/a&gt; and varicose vein specialist with over 18 years of experience, highlighted this issue in an Instagram post he shared on November 21. He warned that hours of sitting cannot be reversed by walking 10,000 steps daily. Instead, he recommended real measures you can adopt in your daily lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;10k steps don't undo long hours of sitting&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Kapadia, in the clip titled 'Your &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/prayagraj-cancer-surgeon-shares-how-to-add-10-years-to-your-life-with-these-3-simple-changes-to-your-plate-101763639306813.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="10,000 steps"&gt;10,000 steps&lt;/a&gt; don't undo 10 hours of sitting', revealed, “This is something I tell my patients almost every day. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;You can hit your step goal in the evening…but if you’ve been desk-bound from 9 AM to 7 PM, your veins have already taken the damage.&lt;/span&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;He highlighted that this problem occurs because circulation doesn’t depend on how much you walk. Rather, it depends on how often you move. He explained that prolonged sitting leads to blood stagnation, which causes vein valve weakness, swelling, varicose veins, and an increased risk of blood clots.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Even a healthy step count cannot reverse 10 hours of immobility,” Dr Kapadia warned. So, what can help reverse this issue?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Here's what actually works&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Kapadia, here are the real rules you need to follow to solve the problem of immobility and the health issues that arise with it:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;1. Get up every 45–60 minutes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;2. Stretch.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;3. Walk for 2 minutes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4. Move your calf muscles – They’re your ‘peripheral heart.’&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Lastly, he advised, “Tiny breaks make huge difference. Your veins don’t need marathons. They need movement.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 09:50:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwJBVV95cUxQeTJFVWM2RTQ2Qi1vQVREX2pzQ0NjbnZ3WHc2aFVPR3BZdzdXX1dpdUNfNTlzeG5GaTI4U3hxTFA5R0hNaUY4QUlfTmx1aU1jSUdMMlN6SUdrMUJVdl9kbHlLQ2dYdVlrMVdMUDlTTFp2TUhhN1dBNlI5XzgwS1M2V0lka0tPMzhRYzRkaEJqZFlSOGZPM0dwUTktZ1JfLW9uOVM5YlRMRjRVZnlZbnhReEQzNWNPUWd2S0ZTZmxyTUNkNC0xVmFpdEhkcW5wT2dJazNkOENMaUVlclZxclF3blBpN21GZXlURjhuWDlMUXFHaTY2dlcwTW9iWUh6MGZQeHNkdHR0d9IBjAJBVV95cUxOdTZOaHFfcE1ScmdiY01rbkFDUlkwS2VtY1l3bzRwbUN4R19ONGhWUEx0bEN5UEpUdGdGY0E5T1RCSHlwbk5qallxWlMtWThyT0puZmg1U2liT3E1QWd1eDJ0SkpHUVJmRVhCNC1nX0xoRDFZcnZhaVhvcEhGYXJmbEVZQjJfVEM2QV9ud1NaVXY1UEtGaGxCV0dtVkdpZ2lXTTJEa2RMbl9CQnlPNUlSV0tab1RtM1ZzbUNQSmE4bzdwWml0WUk0ZzJXemZKdFBCclFXVGtZSFRQUTJkV2dMTGlIYU9oam1yTWZ5c1gycmNPWGRROTBTV0NZNVpBVnFWUVNxMjVlME1DS0dN</guid></item><item><title>大便中出现的结直肠癌的4个早期预警迹象-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/4-early-warning-signs-of-colorectal-cancer-that-appear-in-poop/articleshow/125444726.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colorectal cancer is increasingly recognised as a major public health challenge, with rising incidence rates not only in older adults but also among younger populations. Despite its prevalence, early-stage CRC frequently remains asymptomatic, or manifests through subtle gastrointestinal changes that are easily attributed to benign causes. According to a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2819248" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study in JAMA Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, some symptoms are associated with early-onset colorectal cancer. Take a closer look...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Why early detection is crucial&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the American Cancer Society, the 5‑year relative survival rate for colorectal cancer diagnosed when the disease is localized, i.e. has not spread, is about 90%, but this drops sharply when diagnosed at later stages to around 73% for regional spread and around 13% for distant metastases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Cancer is curable if detected early: Signs to pay attention to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early detection of colorectal cancer isn’t just a technical benefit, it massively improves the chances of survival, lowers recurrence risk, and offers a real shot at a cure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are evidence-based early warning signs of colorectal cancer that appear in stool. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;1. Pencil thin or narrow stool&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A sudden and persistent shift to thin, ribbon-like, or pencil-thin stools could be a red flag. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/colon-rectal-cancer/detection-diagnosis-staging/signs-and-symptoms.html" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, a change in stool caliber that lasts more than a few days may indicate a tumour narrowing the passage. Physiologically, as per &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/colon-cancer/in-depth/colon-cancer-stool/art-20586915" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, when a tumour grows on the inner wall of the colon or rectum, it can constrict the space through which stool passes, leading to thinner stools. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;2. Mucus in the stool&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The intestines naturally produce a small amount of mucus to lubricate the colon lining. But a noticeable increase in slime or jelly-like substance coating stool can be a warning sign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical guidelines from &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK279199/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;NCBI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;also list “bleeding or secreting mucus” from the back passage as one of the signs to monitor. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;3. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Blood in stool&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The presence of blood in stool, either bright red or dark, tarry, is one of the most recognized early warning signs of colorectal cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/colon-cancer/in-depth/colon-cancer-stool/art-20586915" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Clinical studies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; indicate that up to 50–60% of early-stage CRC patients present with some form of rectal bleeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, while hemorrhoids, anal fissures, and gastrointestinal infections can also cause bleeding, persistent or recurrent blood in stool, especially when accompanied by other CRC warning signs, warrants immediate medical evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;4. Persistent diarrhoea or constipation &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changes in bowel habits, such as persistent diarrhea, constipation, or alternating patterns, can be an early indicator of colorectal cancer. According to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.moffitt.org/cancers/colorectal-cancer/signs-symptoms/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;MOFFITT cancer center&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, adults over 50 presenting with sustained changes in bowel habits are at higher risk for colorectal neoplasia, making this symptom an important cue for early evaluation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although dietary changes, infections, and irritable bowel syndrome are more common causes, the persistence of these symptoms should prompt timely diagnostic testing such as colonoscopy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Younger adults are facing higher risk of &lt;keyword id="12135154" type="General" weightage="100" keywordseo="Colon-cancer" source="Orion"&gt;colon cancer&lt;/keyword&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A major &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241211190108.htm" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;epidemiological analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;published in The Lancet Oncology shows that early‑onset colorectal cancer rates are increasing in 27 out of 50 countries, between the age of 25 to 49. Lifestyle factors are also implicated. According to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2227-9059/13/7/1572" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;MDPI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, early antibiotic use, consuming ultra-processed diets, and obesity are emerging as important risk contributors. Researchers warn that shifting dietary patterns, reduced physical activity, and rising metabolic disorders may further accelerate this trend if not addressed early.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is intended for general informational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 09:08:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9AFBVV95cUxPTDVRaldMMVJvdnBjUDZENWNpSjFXdXB1bDZtOFJyUE93OWZJdENWNXNvZUNoSFFOY2RxNmJkdHc2dmxuQVkyR0dCeXh1eFRpamM0VUhOZ0pnazdIcWwzSkZQeU5RNGhxREFnOWh2LWN6MVZFQ2FDcC04NWFqUkVqa2xaQldLRW5MY1g2ajRnZFNOUGNaRENfWlNHVGs1bkpVckRvbnF2ZUo1YUxxRF9wMHlIdW16a1dEd2VuV0FraUtEVGFvZEVCM0RKSGhhY2dEYmcyZkhmLXN6WDItYVBrSWk2VllrUVZBMmZ0TGhsMkRSNnlk</guid></item><item><title>最初难以识别的胃癌的5个警告标志-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/5-warning-signs-of-stomach-cancer-that-are-difficult-to-recognise-at-first/photostory/125500687.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first signs of stomach cancer manifest as mild stomach discomfort, which patients experience in their upper abdominal region. The abdominal pain from stomach cancer starts as a dull sensation, which moves between different locations, and feels like pressure instead of sharp pain. People commonly treat this symptom as heartburn, ulcers or muscle strain. Medical studies demonstrate that stomach cancer warning signs include ongoing abdominal pain, which intensifies, while patients experience bloating and feel full after eating. Medical professionals should perform early medical tests to identify stomach cancer before the pain reaches severe or persistent levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These initial warning signs present as mild symptoms, which most people identify as typical digestive issue, thus making their identification challenging. Patients who experience ongoing indigestion, early satiety, nausea, unexplained weight loss or abdominal pain, should seek medical help when their symptoms do not improve or worsen. The detection of stomach cancer at its early stages, leads to better treatment results and increased patient survival rates, so patients need to monitor these hard-to-detect symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: This article is informational only and not a substitute for medical advice&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 08:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi8wFBVV95cUxPWHFjSTVtd1VwQVZHUkhfN3Y0MkNxWndWTkdYekozaWFNT2h3cFlTTEJISzV3RDNVYjlqMGJ1dDdUM3Q4LUtKeUdSSTdSY2dkUkc1aUFjV1hBYks5NnMtRHlHS0Z6aFpDSDN4TXQwLUdIb2RQQjhPZVZyclhkUlZQcHc3TkJjMDkzZG5HRmQ4T3ZyQzZ0b1pyME90WnR4X1JIR1lRUTBtRzVuOGZSUklKQkdwWl82NDcxLWREMThBNXJoN0FEcGdIZkx4YnE4YXVvRVJlenhDN3N0Q0FkZ09KQUxwTk5HWXVUVzlpQnY1X0pKUk3SAfsBQVVfeXFMTWZoMVVPdWd0V3ZjeGhWZXhrUmM2LWlrdzNDTzlFbmkwWW5OZ3hjcmpHeldjWEo4ME90bzFOVTM0TlRReVFHbG5Jc0tkb3Y1WHVlal9DMmhiNGszSnItOF9yeVZscmY5alItLWtNNVY5b3E3a1NPbUxNbFhjcE4xX1JhSWs0X2NPaG8yN0ZYTm1wY1hzTjk5SkhWZC12c3lYMVgtMTM1MzNtOEFEMC1QbV9FYVFfQWdVeGtvN3NpbE5Rai1QZDRSSDNoMEdkRnJKQUE1ZXc2YUlsN1lZTGxWaThZSF9ReUV2MWJ6ekRWVDBFbTN2ckVCLUFrTm8</guid></item><item><title>顶级心脏病专家揭示了导致心脏病发作次数最多的一个早晨习惯-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/top-cardiologist-reveals-the-one-morning-habit-that-causes-the-maximum-number-of-heart-attacks-within-the-first-10-minutes-of-waking-up-not-food-or-stress/articleshow/125386959.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most heart attacks happen in the early morning hours, between 6 and 10 a.m., and the reasons go beyond traditional risk factors like cholesterol or age. Dr. Heigl, a senior cardiologist at Vienna General Hospital, who studied over 12,000 cardiac cases, points to how people start their day abruptly as a key trigger for heart attacks, that includes the science behind morning cardiac events, the role of cortisol and nervous system stress. Let’s see how…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Why morning is the riskiest time&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr. Heigl, most heart attacks happen between 6:00 and 10:00 a.m - not because of breakfast or weather, but because of a single act: abrupt stimulation. He said, “It starts with the first ten minutes after waking-how violently people enter their own day. People wake up and flood their system,” he said. “They reach for the phone, switch on blue light, read stress before oxygen. The body hasn’t even synchronized blood pressure yet-and they shock it with urgency.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;India's Silent Killer: Heart Surgeon Unmasks Root Cause Of Heart Attack Crisis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Why this happens&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.news-medical.net/news/20250423/Researchers-uncover-link-between-heart-attack-severity-and-circadian-rhythm.aspx" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; show a spike in heart attacks in the early morning hours. This period coincides with a natural rise in blood pressure, heart rate, and cortisol (the stress hormone) due to the body’s internal clock or circadian rhythm. These physiological changes increase the strain on the heart and the likelihood of artery blockages, plaque rupture, and cardiac events. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research from diverse populations confirms the highest rates of heart attacks occur between 6 a.m. and 10 a.m., with some studies citing as much as a 40% higher risk compared to other times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Cortisol’s role in morning heart stress&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cortisol, as we know is the stress hormone, that can raise blood pressure and heart during mental or emotional stress. The cortisol surge lowers heart rate variability. Dr. Heigl, showed data from continuous ECG monitors: in patients with cardiac &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/22187-cortisol" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;events&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, heart rate variability dropped sharply within minutes of waking. The trigger wasn’t effort-it was cortisol spikes caused by instant mental engagement. “The nervous system needs five calm minutes to reenter gravity,” Heigl said. “But we hand it a war instead.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What should one do instead&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Heigl says, “Don’t open the day. Let the day open you.” He teaches his patients to stay horizontal for three slow breaths, sit up gradually, drink water before words, and delay screens by ten minutes. After six weeks, 70% of patients showed lower morning blood pressure and improved vagal tone- a direct shield against cardiac stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Heart attacks,” he said, “aren’t just plumbing failures. They’re scheduling errors.” So the next time your alarm goes off, remember: it’s not the day that kills the heart -it’s how abruptly we force it to start running.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Practical tips to protect your heart in the morning&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;• Avoid checking your phone or engaging in stressful mental activities immediately after waking.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;• Take at least 5 minutes to wake gently with slow breathing and gradual movement.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;• Stay hydrated by drinking water before caffeine or food.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;• Follow a calm morning routine that eases your body into activity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;These small, mindful changes can significantly lower early-morning cardiac stress and reduce heart attack risk, especially for people with hypertension, diabetes, or existing heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 06:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3wJBVV95cUxQQVF6WEk2Q1pEeERpWFZheTh5cVBBd3pGMlVBNWw5TzUzWm83TnBsN0VocEJEWDhDRFJxd0R4d2s5eGJJSm0wZFUzVVJyUFVFRDZPSmt3ZkdxbnBmbU5zcHRiSkVZMUt6Vk1iZHFNMFVESmE3MVdRNl9NbjU3ODZoUExDbkFKdVNBaERoT0k1QUZBSkJzdGJoSUhLSkxMNElDQV9aZjU1cVF3R3U3Ul9kN21WR0lSeEM4a3c3NGt5TWtRM3BRdlNyOHd1NXNJdnFvNEJ0Yk1kQ1JzaVpLRHRxblE1dEhrSVAtdDU0UmZHSm9sdnE3bTlEWDFGQUpYRU9HYmtrZjlmOFdTZXFxZzBvdlg4dXVvdzVkR1FHaDk4TUxQX1k4LUNTNXJQbTVXWTdKN3F5TGh0blpzbDJhaGdocGljWU9sTUQyNjVNbkRURU5YYllkZUhISjgwT2NHNkk</guid></item><item><title>华盛顿州居民被认为是第一个死于罕见禽流感的人-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/bird-flu-infection-washington-h5n5-c8148b46cf9cc8a4f1e5562923086298</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;GRAYS HARBOR COUNTY, Wash. (AP) — A Washington state resident is believed to be the first person to die from a &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/bird-flu-infection-washington-h5n5-b8921d13aa7d96330654a960f80453c3"&gt;rare strain of bird flu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, but state health officials said Friday the risk to the public is low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The person, an older adult with underlying health conditions, was being treated for a bird flu called H5N5 after becoming seemingly the first known human infected by the strain, according to a statement from the Washington State Department of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The person from Grays Harbor County, about 78 miles (125 kilometers) southwest of Seattle, had a backyard flock of domestic poultry that had been exposed to wild birds, health officials said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The risk to the public remains low,” the statement from state health officials said. “No other people involved have tested positive for avian influenza.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials said they will monitor anyone who came in close contact with the person, but “there is no evidence of transmission of this virus between people.”&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Earlier this month, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention issued a statement about the infection that said no information would suggest “the risk to public health has increased as a result of this case.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;H5N5 is not believed to be a greater threat to human health than the H5N1 virus behind a wave of 70 reported human infections in the U.S. in 2024 and 2025. Most of those have been mild illnesses in workers on dairy and poultry farms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The distinction between H5N5 and H5N1 lies in a protein involved in releasing the virus from an infected cell and promoting spread to surrounding cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story has been corrected to remove references stating the person who died was a man. Officials have not released the person’s gender.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 05:54:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPZEs3MWNIa255QVE2Q2M0QXM0b0lfdVpSdi01d2xYcnJ1MDNVeUxjWUtOUUk4MDNaTExlc0NLbW11MlJGcFpHR3J4U2gwREtzUkV5cTRaVGk0OXdBTmg1dzUwb1pHUy0yS3VLRXFybGhNU19xbkplS25NS0l6NG1pMGVINkc5dTNiSEpoTnJWTTBEOE5UZDlVeEd3</guid></item></channel></rss>