<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>这是痴呆症最常错过的警告标志- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/signs-dementia-symptoms-goog_l_690cc915e4b027afb3225b8c</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When we think about dementia, we often think of a person experiencing memory loss and confusion. While it’s true that these are certainly symptoms of dementia and Alzheimer’s (the most common form of dementia), missing some of the more subtle signs that aren’t as well-known can lead to a later diagnosis and delay in care. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;With &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.alz.org/alzheimers-dementia/facts-figures" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="an estimated 6.7 million Americans over the age of 65" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="690cc915e4b027afb3225b8c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.alz.org/alzheimers-dementia/facts-figures" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;an estimated 6.7 million Americans over the age of 65&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in the U.S. living with Alzheimer’s, dementia is far from rare. So, what dementia-related signs should someone look out for in themselves and others? And when should they see their doctor for a dementia screening? Here’s everything you need to know: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The biggest early sign is spatial issues along with trouble with speech and directions.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While we all forget a word now and then, if this becomes a pattern, it could signal a problem. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Difficulty with language including word-finding difficulty, incorrect sentence construction or difficulty with self-expression can present well before the loss of memory,” said &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.delraymedicalctr.com/find-a-doctor/detail/arif-dalvi-1659422632" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Arif Dalvi" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="690cc915e4b027afb3225b8c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.delraymedicalctr.com/find-a-doctor/detail/arif-dalvi-1659422632" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr. Arif Dalvi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a&lt;span&gt; neurologist and physician chief of the Movement Disorders Program at Delray Medical Center.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s easy to brush this off, but it’s important to monitor if there’s any frequency with this behavior. Additionally, you may notice a change in your sense of direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Visual or spatial skills can also be affected early,” Dalvi continued. “A common way this presents is difficulty navigating a previously familiar route or needing GPS directions to a route that was previously known.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pay attention to other red flags as well.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Other less commonly recognized symptoms include difficulty completing familiar tasks, noise sensitivity and a change in taste and smell, according to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.houstonmethodist.org/doctor/stanley-appel/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Stanley Appel" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="690cc915e4b027afb3225b8c" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.houstonmethodist.org/doctor/stanley-appel/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr. Stanley Appel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, neurologist and d&lt;span&gt;irector of the Ann Kimball &amp;amp; John W. Johnson Center for Cellular Therapeutics at Houston Methodist.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“An abrupt change in personality or mood without underlying explanation should also raise a red flag,” Dalvi added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;And, more rarely, you might see some symptoms that resemble other neurological issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Some types of dementia, such as Lewy body dementia, can cause hallucinations or delusions,” Appel explained. “It’s crucial to note that hallucinations can also result from other causes, and any unusual symptoms should be discussed with a health care provider.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bring up any concerning symptoms to your doctor ASAP.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sadly, there is no cure for dementia. But both experts emphasized that an early diagnosis can improve quality of life and stop the disease from progressing as quickly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Traditional treatment options, such as medication to manage symptoms, recommendations for lifestyle changes and referrals to support services like occupational and speech therapy are vital in maintaining cognitive function and overall well-being,” Appel said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Plus, in recent years, there has been a significant breakthrough in the treatment of Alzheimer’s disease. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“The FDA has approved two new drugs, Aduhelm (aducanumab) and Leqembi (lecanemab), that target the buildup of amyloid beta plaques in the brain, which is a hallmark of Alzheimer’s disease,” Appel said. “Although the approval of Aduhelm has been controversial, some studies have shown that it can slow cognitive decline in certain patients. On the other hand, clinical trials have shown that Leqembi can slow cognitive decline in certain patients with mild to moderate Alzheimer’s disease.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In addition to lessening the build-up of amyloid plaques, Appel added that some doctors are working on other innovative approaches to treatment. One is to suppress neuroinflammation with regulatory T-cells (Tregs), and other investigations are using advances in gene therapy to develop novel approaches for Alzheimer’s disease. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“These breakthroughs in medical science offer hope for individuals with dementia and their families,” he said. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There is no “official” age to get a dementia screening, but it’s always a good idea to reach out to your doctor if you’re experiencing any symptoms. Dalvi emphasized that since the incidence of dementia rises with age, particularly after 65, that’s a good time to have a simple dementia screening such as a mini cognitive assessment. Physicians can look for reversible causes of memory loss, like a vitamin B12 deficiency or hypothyroidism. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Screening for hearing loss at this age is also important as it is estimated that 1 out of 9 dementias can be explained on the basis of age-related hearing loss,” he said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While there may not be a complete cure for dementia and Alzheimer’s, there is a lot doctors can do once they reach a diagnosis. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“There should be no stigma associated with screening for dementia,” Appel said. “An early and accurate diagnosis allows a plan to be put in place for either treating or slowing the cause of dementia.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 12:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxQUnJYcmhuQjNBU1liaGxMam9iZC1NSXJPQzZGQjctZXRVUzVTaXB6TW1IQmdZWlpUcVc1QWhkbHdwNEFER1d1NTMzaHNxRUJ3dTJicTZKZ0NyaExNS1VBZWJDXzVDSk41V1BTUklTS0V0bWloV0dQX3dPRzRDYUtSbC1Ta2hPbWVHNkMtZ0JSb9IBlAFBVV95cUxPX2xocUVydE5kTGQxaWNGWk1MLU92SUNWZWpUSXpQdE5rS21CcFRKek1qQlQxNWhLZDI4Zk5UTmVmOWtJamxNd2p6SHRYQmNsUjVzbnlzZ1RVbEtnMGZBME1FM1FzSHp2aUpJcHcydGVDZW11X3kwbnBwYWg1ZzkxSzBhckRIX05senZfR0QxczhJZnB6</guid></item><item><title>听音乐对痴呆症风险有惊人的影响，研究表明- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/listening-to-music-has-a-surprising-impact-on-dementia-risk-study-shows</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Listening to music into old age could reduce the risk of dementia by almost 40 percent, a new study has found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's based on data from 10,893 Australians aged 70 or older, who, at the time of recruitment, were living in retirement communities and had no diagnosis of dementia. They were asked about their music listening habits and whether they played an instrument.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/theres-a-surprising-link-between-music-and-brain-health"&gt;There's a Surprising Link Between Music And Brain Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Folks who "always" listened to music (as opposed to never, rarely, or sometimes listeners) were 39 percent less likely to develop dementia after at least three years of follow-up, and were 17 percent less likely to develop &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cognitive_impairment"&gt;milder forms&lt;/a&gt; of cognitive impairments. They also performed better on tests of general cognition and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/neuroscientists-find-two-types-of-brain-cells-that-help-us-make-memories"&gt;episodic memory&lt;/a&gt;, which is important for recalling everyday events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who were regularly picking up an instrument to &lt;em&gt;make&lt;/em&gt; music were 35 percent less likely to develop dementia, but, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/13607863.2019.1699019"&gt;unlike in other studies&lt;/a&gt;, there was no significant improvement for other kinds of cognitive impairments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who both listened to and played music had a 33 percent reduced dementia risk, and a 22 percent reduced risk for unrelated cognitive impairments. Education level seemed to play a role, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Music engagement benefits were strongest in those with higher education (16+ years) but showed inconsistent results in the middle education group (12–15 years)," the study's authors &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/gps.70163"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paper's lead author, public health researcher Emma Jaffa from Monash University in Australia, &lt;a href="https://newshub.medianet.com.au/2025/10/music-can-stave-off-dementia-by-up-to-40-per-cent-monash-study-finds/126069/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; these results suggest&lt;span&gt; "music activities may be an accessible strategy for maintaining cognitive health in older adults, though causation cannot be established."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While we don't know for sure if listening to music can really stave off dementia, hearing loss is a known risk factor for dementia, and research shows hearing aids &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/landmark-trial-suggests-hearing-aids-help-reduce-cognitive-decline"&gt;can reduce cognitive decline&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;. So it can't hurt to keep your favorite tunes on rotation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Listening to music activates a whole range of regions across your brain," Monash University neuropsychiatric epidemiologist and senior author Joanne Ryan &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2025-10-30/listening-to-music-can-delay-onset-of-dementia/105950280"&gt;&lt;span&gt;explained&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in a radio interview, "and so that's really giving you that cognitive stimulation, which is beneficial to help reduce your risk of dementia." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research was published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/gps.70163"&gt;International Journal of Geriatric Psychiatry&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxQWXZfbDc2S1BlSXRSd1dXTjVfYldiZWxGWGhKNy1CLU1RRm5LbU51OGpsQ08wR0JlbFBBTlFxdXdPT0swd1VJbHo1TVVwbHkyeFhGVFRYSXVhSHMyWmw0MXJUQTlVMjFvVW5mcnl5eGhJS2pxdW9ENGFCTGlwbHRVWlFOdk0tSG1Ba3FCUk1GOUNOSmhyS0xHZUloMTZZYlZ6X0E</guid></item><item><title>带状疱疹如何增加痴呆症风险以及哪些因素可能有助于预防痴呆症-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/11/02/shingles-vaccine-dementia-prevention/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FXQ3VKQGQRHXVMYYKP2CKGYHVA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;One of the largest studies ever conducted on the link between the shingles vaccine and brain health offers insight into how the disease increases dementia risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HO4VVENR2JDW3LGCQ6VM2DJQLQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;People who experienced multiple episodes of shingles had a higher risk of dementia for several years after the second outbreak, the study found, compared with those who had it only once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 10:01:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxPa3IxUWtWUGNzbUg1a09oN09kNnNmSjZ1UDJ3WF9LUDJONG1UenFhTjVhNWE5aEdLQjVrTFdVejA2MHl0STlTUnBQMEx0TzBRcFNQd0liLUNCSHRMNnNDSlJnamtfU2IxSDFMMWpOVGJ4MWVyZWVNcGZsTUtpN0Q2MmRpN0hTUFdTWnRkZ1FQdw</guid></item><item><title>自然计划生育的MAHA推动的崛起-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/09/us/politics/maha-natural-family-planning.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 10:00:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQMFFQYkZ5bGpEN0FaV1E3NllhZFY3elNKVy0yMGdTNG5zVWRESGRZMExRVlBybmNBdlF0a3hyZHlDdUR0X1dYMlFoVUx2WE9vVktJRTBaUzFqWkVpSllPTTlscV9hMjdwdG10bEVvQ3RwVVYzbFlaaEtGNksxZlRldHlEaWJnb0U</guid></item><item><title>牙釉质再生：科学家发现突破性凝胶可预防更强的牙齿和蛀牙-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/regrowing-tooth-enamel-scientists-discover-breakthrough-gel-for-stronger-teeth-and-cavity-prevention/articleshow/125199799.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine a world where cavities could be reversed instead of being drilled and filled. That possibility is now closer than ever. According to a&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-024-54785-y" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt; 2024 study published in Nature Communications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, scientists have developed a glycerol-stabilised calcium phosphate gel capable of repairing early enamel damage by mimicking the tooth’s natural mineralisation process. This discovery represents a breakthrough in preventive dentistry. Though still in development, experts believe it could mark a shift from repairing cavities to regenerating enamel naturally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Why &lt;keyword id="30428490" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="regrowing-tooth-enamel" source="keywords"&gt;regrowing tooth enamel&lt;/keyword&gt; matters for &lt;keyword id="20101956" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="oral-health" source="keywords"&gt;oral health&lt;/keyword&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tooth enamel is the strongest material in the human body, yet it cannot regrow once lost. This thin, protective outer layer shields the teeth from acids, bacteria, and wear. When enamel erodes, the inner dentine becomes exposed, causing sensitivity and increasing the risk of decay. Current dental care focuses on patching damaged areas with fillings or crowns, but these are artificial replacements, not true restoration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Nature Communications study explains how scientists aimed to replicate enamel’s natural growth process. Their glycerol-stabilised calcium phosphate (CaP) clusters form a nanoscale coating that can merge seamlessly with existing enamel. This new layer mimics the hardness and composition of natural tooth enamel, effectively rebuilding lost mineral density. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research could fundamentally change the approach to oral health by treating early-stage decay before it requires invasive procedures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How the new enamel-regrowing gel works&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The technology is based on biomimicry, meaning it imitates the natural biological process of enamel formation. During tooth development, cells called ameloblasts secrete proteins that guide calcium and phosphate ions to crystallise into enamel. Once teeth erupt, ameloblasts are lost, making regeneration impossible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers overcame this by developing a glycerol-stabilised calcium phosphate cluster, a material that mimics enamel’s crystalline structure. When applied to a demineralised tooth surface, these clusters bind tightly and rapidly form a protective coating. In controlled lab tests, the gel successfully repaired early-stage enamel erosion within hours, demonstrating mechanical strength and acid resistance comparable to healthy enamel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;What makes this particularly impressive is that the gel integrates with the tooth surface rather than sitting on top of it. This could make it a non-invasive, self-healing treatment for minor cavities and erosion, something no toothpaste or mouthwash can achieve alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Key benefits of regrowing tooth enamel with calcium phosphate gel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If clinical trials confirm its safety and effectiveness, this new gel could transform how dentists manage oral health. The potential benefits include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Early &lt;keyword id="26143070" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="cavity-prevention" source="keywords"&gt;cavity prevention&lt;/keyword&gt;: The gel could halt tooth decay before it progresses, reducing the need for drilling and fillings.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reduced tooth sensitivity: By sealing exposed dentine, enamel regrowth may naturally relieve discomfort caused by temperature or acids.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Long-lasting protection: The new enamel layer closely matches the hardness and resilience of the natural one, improving durability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Accessible preventive care: Applied by dentists or potentially in at-home treatments, it could make enamel protection easier for everyone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Together, these outcomes suggest a future where dental damage can be repaired before it becomes irreversible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What limitations remain before enamel regrowth becomes available&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the promising results, the Nature Communications research is still in its experimental phase. The gel has shown success in laboratory and simulated oral environments, but human clinical trials are still needed. Scientists must confirm how well it performs under real-life conditions like chewing, saliva exposure, and bacterial activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another challenge is scalability. Producing stable, medical-grade calcium phosphate clusters that retain effectiveness over time is complex and costly. It may take several years before the product reaches dental clinics. Researchers are now exploring ways to optimise its composition and shelf life to ensure consistent results in everyday use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The future of dentistry with enamel regrowth&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If successfully commercialised, tooth enamel regrowth technology could mark a major turning point in dental care. Instead of filling cavities, dentists could focus on biological repair and regeneration, preserving the tooth’s natural structure. Preventive treatments might become as simple as a topical application during a check-up, making oral care less invasive and more sustainable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, maintaining enamel health remains essential. Brushing twice a day with fluoride toothpaste, flossing regularly, avoiding acidic foods, and scheduling routine dental visits are still the best defences against enamel erosion. This new discovery adds hope, not replacement, to those habits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea of regrowing tooth enamel was once science fiction, but it is now on the verge of becoming science fact. The 2024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-024-54785-y" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nature Communications study has opened the door to a new kind of dentistry, one where the body’s natural defences can be restored, not replaced. While we may still be a few years away from enamel-regenerating gels appearing in clinics, the progress so far suggests that the future of oral care is regenerative, not restorative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for general informational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the guidance of a qualified healthcare provider regarding any medical condition or lifestyle change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also read| &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/can-you-really-breathe-through-your-butt-inside-japans-surprising-medical-experiment/articleshow/125185298.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Can you really breathe through your butt? Inside Japan’s surprising medical experiment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 09:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwJBVV95cUxQX3FBb2c2SW1SS01ZRENYZG85cHZmaEVqUEVxeXl0NUprb3NPUG1CUUxMQV9UdkxOdi1WLWllcU9jS19lSTRDX0w5UnpSZ1dXUDNMN0VtY1hLVGNhdjdaUEdkX0I0b3FzTnNPSHl2VS04bzlqNzdmd0pEQ1lhOUkzSHFSX3lFSjN5eGpKOUhGRGpFc0dmcHhPU19DZ2RLdGNyZVBEY0pmVXRia2FfTHlxQ3g2VlhkV0F2LVctdDlsSVFNSERoeW1RamJBMGo5RnRYTy1GVTlzM0N2UXFFUktkWVc2eEJRS1dLQlRlS2NqdTlDRWZRaDhxMF84NkxJN1hxRzJaRUJJSFFpVzB3bmVZdWRwaHprVnhQX1RWYmtMaUQxZHp0MDg4</guid></item><item><title>不吃药或节食就能控制心脏病？将坏胆固醇减少一半的单一疗法-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/manage-heart-disease-without-pills-or-diet-single-treatment-to-cut-bad-cholesterol-in-half/articleshow/125196272.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart disease is the world’s leading cause of death across the world but a new scientific chapter may be unfolding. What if managing cholesterol did not always mean daily pills, relentless diet tracking or stressing about missed doses? According to a recent &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2511778" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;trial published in The New England Journal of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, gene-editing technology known as CRISPR has been used in humans to sharply lower levels of “bad” cholesterol and triglycerides in a single treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;What this means for you is that the path to a healthier heart is not only new drugs or stricter diets, it might also be about smarter treatments combined with everyday habits. The results of the study were presented Saturday, November 08, 2025, at the American Heart Association's annual meeting. Here is what the science says and how you can stay in control of your cardiovascular wellness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Why are women more at risk for heart disease?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Science snapshot: One-and-done vs life-long routine&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trial in question involved a small group of adults whose cholesterol remained high despite existing therapies. Researchers targeted a gene in the liver called ANGPTL3 using CRISPR, turning it off in order to mimic rare protective mutations found in some people. In this study, LDL cholesterol and triglycerides dropped by about 50% within weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="Scientists Used Gene Editing to Slash “Bad” Cholesterol by Half: The Next Big Shift in Heart Health" msid="125196667" width="" title="Scientists Used Gene Editing to Slash “Bad” Cholesterol by Half: The Next Big Shift in Heart Health" placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-125196667/scientists-used-gene-editing-to-slash-bad-cholesterol-by-half-the-next-big-shift-in-heart-health.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;Scientists Used Gene Editing to Slash “Bad” Cholesterol by Half: The Next Big Shift in Heart Health&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The takeaway is that a one-time gene edit may help bypass the need for daily medication for some, shifting the paradigm from manage to possibly correct at the root. However, the caution remains that it is early days hence, safety must be monitored long-term and the technology is not yet available to most. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why it matters for everyday life&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might be thinking, “Great but what about me?” Even if you are not a candidate for gene editing, this breakthrough highlights three big messages for your lifestyle -&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prevention continues to matter:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; Technology is advancing but healthy habits still form the foundation. Daily nutrition, movement and stress management remain essential.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your cholesterol story is longer than stat numbers: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;Most people view cholesterol as “numbers on a lab result.” This trial reminds us that there is a genetic and biological upstream, meaning that what you do over the years still counts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hope meets realism: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;Seeing a future where a one-time intervention exists does not excuse today’s choices. It reinforces how powerful prevention really is.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Everyday moves that amplify your heart health&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you ride the wave of optimism around gene-editing, here are daily practices to stay proactive. These are not replacements but just solid support for your heart:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prioritise sunlight and movement:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; Outdoor walks support circulation and enhance mood and both are beneficial for heart health. According to the &lt;a href="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/news/2022/national-walking-day-nih-researcher-available-discuss-heart-healthy-benefits-walking" data-type="tilCustomLink" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;National Heart, Lung and Blood Institute&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, “Studies show that a daily walk can boost &lt;keyword id="20068019" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="cardiovascular-health" source="keywords"&gt;cardiovascular health&lt;/keyword&gt; by lowering the risk of heart disease, stroke, high blood pressure, obesity and Type 2 diabetes.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus on gut-heart connection:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; Emerging science recognises that gut health impacts lipid metabolism. Fibre-rich whole foods, legumes, vegetables and fermented foods support that axis. A &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5390330/" data-type="tilCustomLink" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;2019 review in Physiology &amp;amp; Heart&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; noted that “the gut microbiota can mechanistically impact host lipid levels … independent of body mass index and other metabolic disturbances.” The gut is not just digestion. It is linked to how lipids are handled in your body, which affects heart health. Eating fibre-rich, whole foods and fermented options supports that axis.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitor stress and sleep:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; Chronic stress and poor sleep raise inflammation, which worsens heart risk. Simple mindfulness, screen-free time before bed and regular sleep cycles help. A &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11883-024-01207-5" data-type="tilCustomLink" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;2024 review in Emerging Topics in Life Sciences&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; noted that sleep disturbances raise inflammatory markers like CRP and IL-6, which are linked to higher cardiovascular risk. Poor sleep and high stress both trigger inflammation, higher blood pressure and worse lipid profiles, which are all harmful for your heart. Managing them matters.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Know your numbers and your story: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;Regular cholesterol, triglyceride, blood pressure and BMI check-ups keep you aligned. If you have family history or stubborn cholesterol despite good habits, ask about genetic testing or specialised lipid clinics. The practice of regularly checking cholesterol, triglycerides, blood pressure, BMI etc is supported widely in cardiovascular prevention literature.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Treat it as a long game:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; The gene-editing news is promising but not immediate for most. In the meantime, adopting heart-smart habits now buys you healthier futures.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The bigger picture: Medicine, lifestyle and you&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;As cardiologist experts noted, gene editing for common diseases is a “revolution in progress” but revolutions don’t happen overnight. This means that your best move is not waiting, it is living. Your habits today shape how you age tomorrow. While future treatments may simplify the fight against heart disease, your daily choices remain the most powerful levers you hold. Every vegetable, every walk, every hour of quality sleep builds resilience. In the end, whether you benefit from the gene-editing wave or not, think of your heart health as both legacy and lifestyle. A one-time treatment may be around the corner but until then, every day is your chance to invest in the life you want.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult with a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment and before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 03:47:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgJBVV95cUxQTzZjNEVIam81dzRfUTlsSjEtZG5pUUVrdlM5VGluSkZLeExJaGJKa25CdXh6enF1UHVuTkhGWTN0eDRYMzNka1dlYlRHS0ZpdWdGVkZ2bmxTeXRJSW9VRUFGMVcwSXk3djNaYm9QSUhsbGpIOTk2anowVmxOZVg3bHZqNVRIU0F6UkI5bi1BZEcwSk52SGFRMnZHenFnVzBpZmp6c19PUk1xNkFVSk9jUjRQT0tpVWlRZ05KbEp6SXpCRUdSLTRIUmZwWUstc05rR2REZWJLQnJYS0szcVJDc2hNX01CdUdoQUV5NUJWUWRmTEFrRmlCYTFYME9DTWlhQ05DMFV4cllhR1VLVzJkRnY4aHllU1ZPNVHSAZ8CQVVfeXFMUFZlWkVONW9yZTV6M3M3czJNTGNwNWVzcllNQ1EteTVocG0yMXBUZmNpeVpVbXhBNW9mY0VBRl9LRTB0WDdrRU5wX0hNNjBUVlFVZVBLNGhueHQ5T3pLclBIbDZBVDVHZTFNZkF5WEl6bTNZZzJiSTI1Yk5zcUZwTVhxMnhpdFZlZFJWMHdWUGlLY1VBczMzbjFHcXJfN0VFSFpGb05RNWtpVEhiazIyWk94SEdIRzk1aUZ0eDNPdDVpMGtqUEJCY3laZWNpVlVkNnVIYU5QcVNZTDFVOUFxZlYwOUpFR2dlaVBlcUk1TXE1MTVjNjV1Y0MtQlpYRlZwdjQ0Z2o4QXVucUY3MmtoM1JkY2lid2NNaTJsbHo1dmM</guid></item><item><title>30岁以上的成年人中约有三分之一， 65岁以上的成年人中约有一半会在晚上起床排尿。我们要求专家们权衡一下这种冲动的含义，以及您可以采取哪些措施来遏制这种冲动。- facebook.com</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/nytimes/posts/about-a-third-of-adults-over-30-and-half-over-65-get-up-at-night-to-urinate-we-a/1222890163026778/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;div class="core"&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Sorry, something went wrong.&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're working on getting this fixed as soon as we can.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="back" href="//www.facebook.com/"&gt;Go back&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>facebook.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 02:46:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0wFBVV95cUxPcHl2ellWd0N3RThUbnZhbzh4UWlIY0hXUE9EXzR6VHlabUgzTlUtZFNzdDc3TDlZNjY4Z1E0NHNHN2prbTJGck5rc1FaSWNjdFVEUVQzb2R1SFg1UUdaTkZzNlNDRkRDSGZyMW1rVFo1R04tRmxKdnFZbUJUd1pYY2dJTXFmcEJ6SjBscWQtY3h6TmJTYk04OUhDb21jRWVpOWVpWmk0b09OT1ZMUzlVRUlma3NFeUZOazYyUV94RjV6NmR3dWNKSVZrNXhoeHN1dDJZ</guid></item><item><title>有没有觉得需要关机？您的迷走神经可能是关键- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cy0k9yz5wexo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Ever feel the need to switch off? Your vagus nerve might hold the key&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-0 fYJjWP"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-11 ljQVMv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-5 xGeVU"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-7bfdb3c2-7 djOqvY"&gt;Ruth Clegg&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-8 gvcwmG"&gt;Health and wellbeing reporter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251105-121702-1a3e907763-web-2.33.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/f6f4/live/93b4d8d0-bc00-11f0-8456-eff94716b162.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/f6f4/live/93b4d8d0-bc00-11f0-8456-eff94716b162.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f6f4/live/93b4d8d0-bc00-11f0-8456-eff94716b162.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/f6f4/live/93b4d8d0-bc00-11f0-8456-eff94716b162.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/f6f4/live/93b4d8d0-bc00-11f0-8456-eff94716b162.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/f6f4/live/93b4d8d0-bc00-11f0-8456-eff94716b162.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/f6f4/live/93b4d8d0-bc00-11f0-8456-eff94716b162.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f6f4/live/93b4d8d0-bc00-11f0-8456-eff94716b162.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Alamy Illustration showing brain and active vagus nerve (tenth cranial nerve or CN X) und human organs of a human adult female" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Alamy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It's the body's superhighway that carries information from your brain to your major organs. You might not have a clue it exists - let alone that you might need to train it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But a quick scroll through my social media and there's a whole array of tips on the vagus nerve - how to heal it, stimulate it, even reset it - all to apparently reduce stress and anxiety levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Poking your ear with what looks like a rubber toothbrush, moving your eyes from side to side, tapping your body or gargling water while wearing a weighted vest - these are just some of the techniques being recommended to train that nerve and improve your wellbeing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;With our &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://mentalhealth-uk.org/blog/burnout-report-2025-reveals-generational-divide-in-levels-of-stress-and-work-absence/#:~:text=We've%20published%20findings%20of%2Cpoint%20over%20the%20last%20year." class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;stress levels sky-high, and burnout on the rise among under-35s&lt;/a&gt;, it's no wonder many of the posts on socials have gone viral with millions of hits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Some of these methods might seem a bit absurd. But is it really possible to train your mighty internal messenger, and could that actually bring quick relief to life's stresses?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251105-121702-1a3e907763-web-2.33.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/b6c7/live/9b94ddc0-bbd8-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/b6c7/live/9b94ddc0-bbd8-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/b6c7/live/9b94ddc0-bbd8-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/b6c7/live/9b94ddc0-bbd8-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/b6c7/live/9b94ddc0-bbd8-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/b6c7/live/9b94ddc0-bbd8-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/b6c7/live/9b94ddc0-bbd8-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/b6c7/live/9b94ddc0-bbd8-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="@cariad.connection Eirian Collinge sitting outside in a park" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;@cariad.connection&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Yoga therapist Eirian Collinge uses breathwork, eye movements, and tapping in her practice&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;I decided to find out by coming to small candle-lit studio in Stockport town centre - where I find myself in a small group, humming loudly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Humming, I am told, can help stimulate our vagus nerve and slow down our heart rate. And I do start to feel a bit more relaxed. I can feel the low hum vibrating in my body and my brain seems a bit less busy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;At this somatics class, yoga therapist Eirian Collinge guides us through a session of gentle moves combining deep breathing, rocking and swaying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;While she doesn't buy into all the techniques on socials, Eirian says there are parts of her practice that use breathwork, eye movements and tapping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But, she says, "it's a process" and there's no quick fix. It is rooted in a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12302812/#abstract1" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;theory that suggests we can calm down our nervous system&lt;/a&gt; by connecting with our bodies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Some scientists say this is an over-simplification of our complex internal systems. But &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://journalofpsychiatryreform.com/2023/10/17/polyvagal-approaches-scientifically-questionable-but-useful-in-practice/#:~:text=Conclusion,others%20in%20the%20environmental%20surround." class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;others say it can be effective&lt;/a&gt; in helping us find a snippet of calm in a busy, intense world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Sarah, who is lying down just a few mats away from me,  started coming to this class about a year ago. She says the practice has been life-changing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I actually cried after the first session," she says. "It felt like the first time my brain has ever switched off."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The 35-year-old, who struggles with her mental health, says it feels like she is "flossing her brain".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251105-121702-1a3e907763-web-2.33.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/0aa0/live/c2a539a0-bbdd-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/0aa0/live/c2a539a0-bbdd-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0aa0/live/c2a539a0-bbdd-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/0aa0/live/c2a539a0-bbdd-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/0aa0/live/c2a539a0-bbdd-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/0aa0/live/c2a539a0-bbdd-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/0aa0/live/c2a539a0-bbdd-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0aa0/live/c2a539a0-bbdd-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Xander Xander, a 37 year old man is sat on a on a sofa in shorts and a running top. He's laughing and he's got a muddy leg" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Xander&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Xander says he now knows what to do when he is overwhelmed, like going for a run in the muddy hills &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Sarah's partner, Xander, agrees. It's made him more aware of his feelings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"As a man," he explains, "We are not really programmed to do that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I've struggled with depression for most of my adult life, but now, instead of trying to fix my thoughts I can sit with my emotions and accept them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"If things get a bit much for me I can peel back a little from work. Go for a run, get out in the hills, for example.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Understanding my nervous system is a huge part of that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The vagus - Latin for "wandering" - starts in the brain as two main branches - left and right - that connect to every major organ, constantly relaying vital information back and forth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It's part of the autonomic nervous system, which controls things we don't think about, like breathing, heart rate and digestion. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The system, in part, is made up of:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 diUlgm"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;the sympathetic nervous system - which triggers "fight or flight", preparing us for anything from being chased by a wild animal to that all important job interview, and&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;the parasympathetic nervous system - which relies on the vagus nerve to help put the brakes on and brings the body back into a state of calm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;If one of these is out of sync we start to see problems. But can we really reset the balance ourselves, by attempting to activate the vagus nerve?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Consultant psychiatrist Prof Hamish McAllister-Williams is sceptical. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We have good evidence vagus nerve stimulation can help with neurological disorders like epilepsy and &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0165032720329505" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;mental illnesses like treatment-resistant depression&lt;/a&gt;," he says, "but that comes from a device that is fitted in the body - a bit like a pacemaker which sends pulses of electrical energy to the vagus nerve."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;That device sends mild electrical stimulations through the vagus nerve to the brain, sparking a release of chemicals like serotonin and dopamine which help us regulate our mood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;While vagus nerve stimulation inside the body requires invasive surgery and is available for a small cohort of patients on the NHS, there is now a growing market for wearable - non-invasive - technology. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;These devices, which cost anything from £200 to more than £1,000, tend to be clipped on the ear, worn round the neck or placed on the chest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251105-121702-1a3e907763-web-2.33.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/59c3/live/1f080b30-bc03-11f0-90b3-259a136a1615.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/59c3/live/1f080b30-bc03-11f0-90b3-259a136a1615.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/59c3/live/1f080b30-bc03-11f0-90b3-259a136a1615.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/59c3/live/1f080b30-bc03-11f0-90b3-259a136a1615.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/59c3/live/1f080b30-bc03-11f0-90b3-259a136a1615.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/59c3/live/1f080b30-bc03-11f0-90b3-259a136a1615.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/59c3/live/1f080b30-bc03-11f0-90b3-259a136a1615.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/59c3/live/1f080b30-bc03-11f0-90b3-259a136a1615.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="@lucylambertco Lucy Lambert wearing stimulation device on her neck" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;@lucylambertco&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Lucy was burnt out and felt she had nowhere to turn before discovering these devices&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The are some credible studies that suggest these external stimulators can potentially impact on brain activity," Prof McAllister-Williams explains. "But there is a lot less evidence than for the internal devices."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;With external devices, the electrical impulses need to travel through skin, tissue, muscle and fat so it's not as simple and direct as a stimulator in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;After she experienced burnout, Lucy Lambert says such non-invasive vagus nerve stimulators helped her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The mother-of-three left her job as a primary school teacher because she was so completely "stressed, tired and anxious".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I had been running on empty for so long - I didn't realise," Lucy says. "Then it hit. The to-do list of life became too much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The mental load was so huge I couldn't get out of bed."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;After exhausting various medical routes and feeling like she was getting nowhere, Lisa's brother recommended one of these devices which vibrates, claiming to send low-level electrical pulses to the vagus nerve, often through the skin in the neck or ear area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I noticed that when I started to feel overwhelmed, I would get a headache first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I would then wear a device for 10 minutes twice a day; the pain from the headache would go, and my whole body would calm down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The vibrations, they really do something."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She says the devices didn't fix burnout but they helped her create "conditions where real healing can happen".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251105-121702-1a3e907763-web-2.33.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/6148/live/b5acf100-bbda-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/6148/live/b5acf100-bbda-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6148/live/b5acf100-bbda-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/6148/live/b5acf100-bbda-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/6148/live/b5acf100-bbda-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/6148/live/b5acf100-bbda-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/6148/live/b5acf100-bbda-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6148/live/b5acf100-bbda-11f0-ae46-bd64331f0fd4.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="@lucylambertco Vagus nerve stimulators" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;@lucylambertco&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Lucy has a range of non-invasive vagus nerve stimulators which she uses along with taking time out and slowing down her pace of life&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Chris Barker, who works in pain management, says this area of medicine is still developing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He says there is a growing understanding of the importance of the vagus nerve, but while there is "clear evidence" around the impact an unbalanced nervous system can have on everything from our mental health to our heart rate and our ability to digest food, it does not mean we have the all the answers - yet - on how to correct the problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's really rational to focus on something that's problematic - and try to fix it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Our bodies are, of course, really complex, and sometimes the problem we see may be part of an imbalance in a wider system."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It's not about going to extremes, he says. It's "about figuring out what works for you" - and that can often take time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It's worth noting if you have underlying heart or respiratory conditions you should seek medical advice before trying to rebalance or stimulate your nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Now, several years after experiencing burnout, Lucy, 47, is launching her own business helping others to build emotional resilience and confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She still uses her devices daily, meditates, and regularly checks in with how she is feeling. "The devices make me rest and switch off."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But she agrees it is difficult to know whether it's the devices making the difference or the fact she is taking some much-needed time out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There is a lack of robust scientific evidence behind these devices but for Lucy, they've played an important part in her recovery. Understanding her nervous system and the importance of the vagus nerve has empowered her, she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's helped me take ownership of my own mental health and wellbeing, and that's massive."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 02:04:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5sYnFDQWx2akxVSXRLRHJlTHVVWnNyM3hGR0FXZXFjT3VzM0wtOW11THdFSDRNUFg3cEw2QTVFOEFkX2R3Uy1hdGRNd3BDNU5GMmRqUVJkNWh4QdIBX0FVX3lxTE12OXRpczY1eFlqY1pjZmtySFg3d2lOaTRKbWh2TGFTQ3lWa0pLSjhyTXlwYW11YzQ3SHdaQ1BnMEFscnEtNWFxY2RQQjhJLUhjVV92OHZtSmdHY1o2ZHBn</guid></item><item><title>低血压会秘密损害您的器官：低血压如何导致肾脏、心脏、大脑和肝脏-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/low-blood-pressure-can-secretly-damage-your-organs-how-hypotension-leads-to-kidney-heart-brain-and-liver-failure/articleshow/125092644.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Low blood pressure, or hypotension, is often overlooked because some people tolerate lower readings without symptoms. However, in many situations, particularly during critical illness or acute medical events, hypotension can be dangerous. When blood pressure drops too low, oxygen-rich blood struggles to reach vital organs, which can lead to cellular damage, organ dysfunction, and even organ failure if not addressed promptly. Understanding hypotension involves exploring why adequate blood pressure is essential for organ perfusion, how the body compensates to maintain blood flow, which organs are most vulnerable, and what happens when these compensatory mechanisms fail. Early recognition and treatment are crucial to prevent serious complications from low blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Blood pressure and how low levels affect your organs&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood pressure is the force blood exerts against the walls of blood vessels. It is measured as systolic/diastolic pressure (e.g., 120/80 mmHg). However, for organ perfusion, mean arterial pressure or MAP, the average pressure in the arteries, is more relevant. Organs rely on adequate pressure to ensure continuous blood flow. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When MAP drops below 60 to 65 mmHg, perfusion becomes inadequate, meaning organs no longer receive enough oxygen and nutrients. Without sufficient perfusion, cellular metabolism is impaired, leading to cell injury or death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Improve Low Blood Pressure Naturally: Here Are 4 DIY Home Hacks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if the systolic or diastolic pressures seem mildly low, prolonged hypotension can cause cumulative organ damage because organs are highly sensitive to oxygen delivery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How low blood pressure leads to organ failure&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the study published in the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://janesthanalgcritcare.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s44158-022-00045-8" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Journal of Anesthesia, Analgesia and Critical Care&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; (2022), arterial hypotension during surgery and in the intensive care unit can significantly impact patient outcomes. The authors highlight that maintaining adequate blood pressure is crucial for organ perfusion, as drops in pressure can lead to hypoperfusion and subsequent organ dysfunction or failure. The study outlines common causes of perioperative hypotension, explains its effects on vital organs, and discusses prevention strategies and remedies that clinicians can use to minimise complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;At normal blood pressure, blood flow delivers oxygen and nutrients to tissues. Hypotension reduces this flow. The body attempts to compensate through:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Increased heart rate to maintain cardiac output.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Peripheral vasoconstriction redirects blood to essential organs like the brain and heart.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When hypotension is severe or prolonged, these compensatory mechanisms cannot keep up. Organs experience hypoperfusion, leading to oxygen deprivation (hypoxia). Hypoxia impairs cellular energy production, leading to cellular dysfunction, apoptosis, and necrosis, which can accumulate into organ failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organ-specific vulnerabilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not all organs respond to hypotension the same way. Some are more susceptible due to high metabolic demands or limited autoregulatory capacity:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kidneys: The kidneys filter blood and require a constant supply of oxygen. Low blood pressure reduces renal perfusion, impairing filtration and potentially causing acute kidney injury (AKI).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Liver: Reduced hepatic artery and portal vein flow can cause ischemic hepatitis, sometimes called “shock liver.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Brain: Cerebral perfusion drops in hypotension, potentially causing confusion, syncope, or even coma.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Heart: Low coronary perfusion reduces oxygen delivery to cardiac muscle, increasing the risk of ischemia and arrhythmias.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The severity of organ damage depends on how low the pressure drops and how long it persists. Even short periods of severe hypotension can trigger irreversible cellular injury, particularly in sensitive organs like the kidneys and brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Role of duration and severity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Magnitude: The lower the blood pressure, the greater the risk of organ hypoperfusion. MAP below 60 mmHg or systolic BP below 90 mmHg is considered particularly dangerous in critical care.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Duration: Even moderate hypotension can cause organ injury if sustained over hours. Short, transient drops are generally better tolerated than prolonged hypotension.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both factors interact: a brief but extremely low MAP can be as harmful as a longer, moderate hypotensive episode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Low blood pressure and organ damage: Evidence from clinical studies and ICU data&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clinical studies and ICU data confirm the relationship between low blood pressure and organ damage:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Patients with chronic kidney disease and low blood pressure exhibit higher mortality and worse renal outcomes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Intraoperative hypotension during surgery is associated with increased postoperative organ dysfunction and complications.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;ICU meta-analyses show that hypotension strongly correlates with acute kidney injury, liver injury, neurological impairment, and overall mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mechanistic studies support these observations, demonstrating that prolonged low perfusion directly injures organ tissue. In CKD patients, extremely low blood pressure shows a “J-shaped” relationship with renal outcomes too low a pressure worsens kidney function, even if modestly lower readings might be tolerated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Organ failure patterns in acute low blood pressure&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In acute hypotension scenarios (e.g., shock, major bleeding, sepsis), organ failure often follows a predictable pattern:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kidneys: First to show dysfunction due to high metabolic demand and limited autoregulatory reserve. Early signs include low urine output and rising creatinine.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Liver: Reduced perfusion can lead to elevated liver enzymes and ischemic hepatitis.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Brain: Hypoperfusion manifests as confusion, dizziness, or syncope.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Heart: Low coronary flow may cause ischemia, arrhythmias, or cardiac arrest.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This pattern reflects each organ’s sensitivity to reduced oxygen delivery and its capacity for compensatory adaptation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Conditions that increase the risk of organ failure in low blood pressure&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain conditions exacerbate the risk of organ failure in hypotension:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="73"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pre-existing organ disease such as CKD or heart failure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advanced age or frailty, reducing compensatory mechanisms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rapid-onset hypotension, e.g., from bleeding or septic shock&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prolonged hypotension, which cumulatively damages organs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients with multiple risk factors are particularly vulnerable, and even moderate hypotension may precipitate organ failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="77"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also Read | &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/how-many-dry-fruits-to-eat-daily-nutritionist-reveals-exact-portions-of-almonds-and-walnuts-to-consume-for-maximum-heart-brain-and-overall-health/articleshow/125084988.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;How many dry fruits to eat daily: Nutritionist reveals exact portions of almonds and walnuts to consume for maximum heart, brain, and overall health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="80"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 01:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwJBVV95cUxPZmZxVi1weHZseFlhbWYwNGRZdGJnVFVfcFdoUGtHZE1sQW1fLS15ZnI3TV9YRnFsQUhNcXhnQUdockRmMGRuNmVSSGZpTWJnZkFxS0dXY2hxNTk2X0RITElNX3lvSmZOYTQ4OVJadktTNktZRXYxb2Vhbi00eUxVZGRuU29SNl9MRjhqby1UTFFKR1E5aTBZSkN5MjJkVE93YmZTTWdKMjBIejJwWGllY1JxQnRwLTNMTU1WVEJYczhIUnBlaktITDY1UTlLMG1SR2xzdXczZ2EzeFl0Q1pCcEdZdkZCNkJwdTNIODM2bVd5TGJhaTBxVUlycjk5RzFOOUFGTDBXVkVOdTZqWldOeHZ4M2Q5R1FOazVsRElGWDF4SVZpVTB6WGRLeUtHc2Z4VHFxeEZRVdIBvAJBVV95cUxQOFVCbkN3NzZVRUFidV9VLXV5NnJ2RURXblBKMXJHZzhpTk5vRHNqN1p4ZjV4UVhYaUlDYWNQa3pQNHZsZlhpd0hyNUxhU0g5WDJsb01nRVZYM2J4S2pnUzd1R1ZFZUlUUG4xcjZrdkZNYmN0TV9tZ2VhQ1BKVGFkSjdwVWIxQ0dUcVhRTkc3SEFkUFRIQ2V1akZhbUlVY3o2azFJanFkdm9RV1VRbmg0a1ZWWHNKeGludmxsVWJPTC1yckMtUy1jTDJ2eDJEWmVBQUthcHB3azhvRlBEd05CdXJmX3lKMFFQVHhFUzRMenZma1l0bHJzVUotQTA1RGFsblpGcjZUTmItN0swMTFBNk9TaWE2aGJjZ29iYk5tRF90TUFWTDJkWnR4SUtPcmp0TzNiMENxQjQ3bmIt</guid></item><item><title>新的突变型流感毒株会导致严冬吗？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c2dr8gzdz1wo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Experts say this could be the worst flu season for a decade - here's why&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-0 fYJjWP"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-11 ljQVMv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-5 xGeVU"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-7bfdb3c2-7 djOqvY"&gt;James Gallagher&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-8 gvcwmG"&gt;Health and science correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251105-121702-1a3e907763-web-2.33.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images A woman blowing her nose and sneezing into a handkerchief during a rainy autumn day. She is wearing a yellow rain coat and a red umbrella " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Flu strikes every winter, but something seems to be different this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A seasonal flu virus suddenly mutated in the summer; it appears to evade some of our immunity; has kick-started a flu season more than a month early and is a type of flu that history suggests is more severe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The NHS has now issued a "flu jab SOS" as fears grow that this will add up to a brutal winter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There is a lot of nuance and uncertainty, but leading flu experts have told me they would not be shocked if this was the worst flu season for a decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We haven't seen a virus like this for a while, these dynamics are unusual," says Prof Nicola Lewis, the director of the World Influenza Centre at the Francis Crick Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It does concern me, absolutely," she says. "I'm not panicking, but I am worried." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So what's going on? And what can we do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Scientists track the evolution of influenza viruses because they mutate constantly and the seasonal flu vaccine has to be updated each year to keep up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This evolution happens in a rhythm known as "shift and drift". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Most of the time the virus drifts along making minor changes and then every so often there is a sudden abrupt shift as the virus mutates substantially.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;That happened in June this year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Seven mutations appeared in a strain of H3N2 seasonal flu and led to a "fast increase" in reports of the mutated virus, says Prof Derek Smith, the director of the centre for pathogen evolution at the University of Cambridge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251105-121702-1a3e907763-web-2.33.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images 3D illustration showing spherical object representing the virus. It is covered in green and orange spikes which represent the two key proteins on the surface of a flu virus. There is one flu virus in focus in the bottom right and more in varying degrees of blur in the background. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;H3N2 strain of influenza &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Unusually, this happened outside flu season in the middle of the northern hemisphere's summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It almost certainly will sweep the world, so from that standpoint, it's something that will come up quickly," says Prof Smith.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;By September, as children went back to school, the nights drew in and the temperatures started to drop, there was an uptick in cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Exactly what the mutations are doing is still being explored, but they are probably helping the virus to evade some of the immunity we have built up over years of flu infections and vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The result is the virus is finding it easier to infect people and spread – that is why the flu season is so early in the UK and other countries including Japan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;If the virus can spread more easily then it does not have to wait for more favourable wintery conditions – when we spend more time indoors with the heating on and the windows shut – to start the flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We're miles ahead," says Prof Lewis, "I think it's going to be a strong flu season".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;If you remember your R numbers from the pandemic (that is the number of people each infected person passes the virus on to), they suggest the new mutant has an edge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Seasonal flu usually has an R number of around 1.2, while the early estimate for this year is 1.4, said Prof Lewis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So very roughly, if 100 people had flu, they would pass it to 120 in a typical year and 140 this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Worst flu season for a decade?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's highly likely it's going to be a bad flu season and it's going to happen quite soon, we're already well into it," says Prof Christophe Fraser, from the Pandemic Sciences Institute at the University of Oxford.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"There are indicators that this could be worse than some of the flu seasons we've seen in the last 10 years."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In a typical flu season around one-in-five of us get infected, but that could be higher this year, he warns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But all these predictions are still clouded in uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Some look to Australia for clues as it had the worst flu season on record this year, although it did not face the same mutated H3N2 we have. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;We know the virus is spreading very well in children in the germ-fest that is the school playground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But the immunity a 10-year-old has developed will be very different from that of their grandparents whose immune defences may have been shaped by six times as many flu seasons. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So, experts will be watching closely as the virus starts infecting older age groups in the coming weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;'It's a nastier virus'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;History suggests that the form of influenza we are facing this year is more severe, particularly for older people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There are multiple types of flu and you may have heard some of the names like H1N1 swine flu, which caused a pandemic in 2009, or H5N1 which is the current flu killing birds around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The fresh mutations have happened in a group of H3N2 influenzas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"H3 is always a hotter virus, it's a nastier virus, it's more impactful on the population," said Prof Lewis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It is worth remembering that some of us will get flu and develop no symptoms at all, while others get a sudden fever, body aches and exhaustion, but the virus can be deadly in older and more vulnerable groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Last year, nearly 8,000 people died from flu, and in the 2022-23 flu season there were nearly 16,000 deaths. The NHS is already anticipating a tough flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So what can we do about it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The clear advice is to get the seasonal flu vaccine – the NHS in England issued a "flu jab SOS" saying there were 2.4 million vaccine slots available in the next week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 GunZh"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251105-121702-1a3e907763-web-2.33.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Two people in a bland, white clinic room. One is an older man with grey hair, an incredibly intense grin on his face and his left arm is rolled up. A young woman with shoulder length brown hair, wearing a rich blue set of scrubs is standing over him. She holds a shot of flu vaccine in her medical gloved hands. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Prof Lewis argues this is "absolutely the most important year" to get vaccinated and that "if you have been called by your GP, please get your flu vaccine as soon as possible".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, this year's vaccine is not a perfect match to the mutated virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The decision on the design of the vaccine was made in February to give enough time to produce the millions of doses necessary - and then the new mutant emerged in June.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Some protection is better than no protection, but this year is likely to be one of the years where the amount of protection is less than it is in years when the match is better, it's not an ideal situation," said Prof Fraser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The vaccine will still trigger the body to produce antibodies that can recognise and stick to flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But the biggest benefits are anticipated to be in lessening the severity of the disease rather than stopping you get ill or slowing the spread of the virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Meanwhile, doctors have been sent advice reminding them that &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.cas.mhra.gov.uk/ViewandAcknowledgment/ViewAlert.aspx?AlertID=103269" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;early antiviral treatment&lt;/a&gt; reduces the risk of complications from flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Japan is also going through an early flu season and has closed schools to help contain outbreaks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;These are not Covid-style lockdowns, but short-term measures the country uses to disrupt the spread of the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Nobody knows for certain what will happen in the coming months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It might all go away by next week," says Prof Lewis, "but I don't think it will."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:03:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9sR1ZHNXRKYXFIR09kN1BOTWxNVXRrZTlWLWVRazJOTTVldUpBTW1hNVpBZnU5eERxOVNQU3ViY2dJR21KcDhzLVc3dFRLS0lIaF9FMGozQUFJZ9IBX0FVX3lxTFBsN2p6M2c3aVpFYW16RWFLdnJBVThodU5PYS1xWndIbURZbzNKQ0JHWDc1VXZ4UEY2Z1NiZFo3WGhFZXdqY2NJd1p5bUJHRGV3NXVuQVFzQm42anZ4R2ZN</guid></item><item><title>新的突变型流感毒株会导致严冬吗？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c2dr8gzdz1wo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Experts say this could be the worst flu season for a decade - here's why&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-0 fYJjWP"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-11 ljQVMv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-5 xGeVU"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-7bfdb3c2-7 djOqvY"&gt;James Gallagher&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-8 gvcwmG"&gt;Health and science correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251105-121702-1a3e907763-web-2.33.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images A woman blowing her nose and sneezing into a handkerchief during a rainy autumn day. She is wearing a yellow rain coat and a red umbrella " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Flu strikes every winter, but something seems to be different this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A seasonal flu virus suddenly mutated in the summer; it appears to evade some of our immunity; has kick-started a flu season more than a month early and is a type of flu that history suggests is more severe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The NHS has now issued a "flu jab SOS" as fears grow that this will add up to a brutal winter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There is a lot of nuance and uncertainty, but leading flu experts have told me they would not be shocked if this was the worst flu season for a decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We haven't seen a virus like this for a while, these dynamics are unusual," says Prof Nicola Lewis, the director of the World Influenza Centre at the Francis Crick Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It does concern me, absolutely," she says. "I'm not panicking, but I am worried." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So what's going on? And what can we do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Scientists track the evolution of influenza viruses because they mutate constantly and the seasonal flu vaccine has to be updated each year to keep up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This evolution happens in a rhythm known as "shift and drift". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Most of the time the virus drifts along making minor changes and then every so often there is a sudden abrupt shift as the virus mutates substantially.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;That happened in June this year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Seven mutations appeared in a strain of H3N2 seasonal flu and led to a "fast increase" in reports of the mutated virus, says Prof Derek Smith, the director of the centre for pathogen evolution at the University of Cambridge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251105-121702-1a3e907763-web-2.33.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images 3D illustration showing spherical object representing the virus. It is covered in green and orange spikes which represent the two key proteins on the surface of a flu virus. There is one flu virus in focus in the bottom right and more in varying degrees of blur in the background. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;H3N2 strain of influenza &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Unusually, this happened outside flu season in the middle of the northern hemisphere's summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It almost certainly will sweep the world, so from that standpoint, it's something that will come up quickly," says Prof Smith.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;By September, as children went back to school, the nights drew in and the temperatures started to drop, there was an uptick in cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Exactly what the mutations are doing is still being explored, but they are probably helping the virus to evade some of the immunity we have built up over years of flu infections and vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The result is the virus is finding it easier to infect people and spread – that is why the flu season is so early in the UK and other countries including Japan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;If the virus can spread more easily then it does not have to wait for more favourable wintery conditions – when we spend more time indoors with the heating on and the windows shut – to start the flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We're miles ahead," says Prof Lewis, "I think it's going to be a strong flu season".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;If you remember your R numbers from the pandemic (that is the number of people each infected person passes the virus on to), they suggest the new mutant has an edge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Seasonal flu usually has an R number of around 1.2, while the early estimate for this year is 1.4, said Prof Lewis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So very roughly, if 100 people had flu, they would pass it to 120 in a typical year and 140 this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Worst flu season for a decade?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's highly likely it's going to be a bad flu season and it's going to happen quite soon, we're already well into it," says Prof Christophe Fraser, from the Pandemic Sciences Institute at the University of Oxford.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"There are indicators that this could be worse than some of the flu seasons we've seen in the last 10 years."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In a typical flu season around one-in-five of us get infected, but that could be higher this year, he warns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But all these predictions are still clouded in uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Some look to Australia for clues as it had the worst flu season on record this year, although it did not face the same mutated H3N2 we have. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;We know the virus is spreading very well in children in the germ-fest that is the school playground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But the immunity a 10-year-old has developed will be very different from that of their grandparents whose immune defences may have been shaped by six times as many flu seasons. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So, experts will be watching closely as the virus starts infecting older age groups in the coming weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;'It's a nastier virus'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;History suggests that the form of influenza we are facing this year is more severe, particularly for older people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There are multiple types of flu and you may have heard some of the names like H1N1 swine flu, which caused a pandemic in 2009, or H5N1 which is the current flu killing birds around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The fresh mutations have happened in a group of H3N2 influenzas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"H3 is always a hotter virus, it's a nastier virus, it's more impactful on the population," said Prof Lewis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It is worth remembering that some of us will get flu and develop no symptoms at all, while others get a sudden fever, body aches and exhaustion, but the virus can be deadly in older and more vulnerable groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Last year, nearly 8,000 people died from flu, and in the 2022-23 flu season there were nearly 16,000 deaths. The NHS is already anticipating a tough flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So what can we do about it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The clear advice is to get the seasonal flu vaccine – the NHS in England issued a "flu jab SOS" saying there were 2.4 million vaccine slots available in the next week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 GunZh"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251105-121702-1a3e907763-web-2.33.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Two people in a bland, white clinic room. One is an older man with grey hair, an incredibly intense grin on his face and his left arm is rolled up. A young woman with shoulder length brown hair, wearing a rich blue set of scrubs is standing over him. She holds a shot of flu vaccine in her medical gloved hands. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Prof Lewis argues this is "absolutely the most important year" to get vaccinated and that "if you have been called by your GP, please get your flu vaccine as soon as possible".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, this year's vaccine is not a perfect match to the mutated virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The decision on the design of the vaccine was made in February to give enough time to produce the millions of doses necessary - and then the new mutant emerged in June.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Some protection is better than no protection, but this year is likely to be one of the years where the amount of protection is less than it is in years when the match is better, it's not an ideal situation," said Prof Fraser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The vaccine will still trigger the body to produce antibodies that can recognise and stick to flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But the biggest benefits are anticipated to be in lessening the severity of the disease rather than stopping you get ill or slowing the spread of the virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Meanwhile, doctors have been sent advice reminding them that &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.cas.mhra.gov.uk/ViewandAcknowledgment/ViewAlert.aspx?AlertID=103269" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;early antiviral treatment&lt;/a&gt; reduces the risk of complications from flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Japan is also going through an early flu season and has closed schools to help contain outbreaks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;These are not Covid-style lockdowns, but short-term measures the country uses to disrupt the spread of the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Nobody knows for certain what will happen in the coming months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It might all go away by next week," says Prof Lewis, "but I don't think it will."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:03:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9sR1ZHNXRKYXFIR09kN1BOTWxNVXRrZTlWLWVRazJOTTVldUpBTW1hNVpBZnU5eERxOVNQU3ViY2dJR21KcDhzLVc3dFRLS0lIaF9FMGozQUFJZw</guid></item><item><title>新研究声称大量饮酒与年轻时的严重脑出血有关|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/new-study-claims-heavy-alcohol-use-tied-to-severe-brain-bleeds-at-younger-ages-101762601468694.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/new-study-claims-heavy-alcohol-use-tied-to-severe-brain-bleeds-at-younger-ages-101762601468694.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;A new study from researchers at Mass General Brigham, published in &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.neurology.org/doi/10.1212/WNL.0000000000214348" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Neurology"&gt;Neurology&lt;/a&gt;, has found that heavy &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/i-should-have-been-dead-anthony-hopkins-reflects-on-alcoholism-sobriety-and-his-journey-to-healing-101762153457769.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="alcohol"&gt;alcohol &lt;/a&gt;use could make brain bleeds more severe and happen much earlier in life. The investigation, based on data from Massachusetts General Hospital, also suggests that frequent drinking damages the brain’s small blood vessels over time, increasing the risk of fatal or disabling strokes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/08/550x309/photo-1653697739283-0b741b14c22e_1762602121613_1762602133621.jpg" alt="The study focused on over 1,600 patients treated for non-traumatic brain bleeds between 2003 and 2019(Representative image/Unsplash)" title="The study focused on over 1,600 patients treated for non-traumatic brain bleeds between 2003 and 2019(Representative image/Unsplash)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/08/550x309/photo-1653697739283-0b741b14c22e_1762602121613_1762602133621.jpg" alt="The study focused on over 1,600 patients treated for non-traumatic brain bleeds between 2003 and 2019(Representative image/Unsplash)" title="The study focused on over 1,600 patients treated for non-traumatic brain bleeds between 2003 and 2019(Representative image/Unsplash)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;The study focused on over 1,600 patients treated for non-traumatic brain bleeds between 2003 and 2019(Representative image/Unsplash)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The brain bleed is one of the most lethal and disabling conditions known to human beings. “They come on suddenly, cause severe damage, and often leave patients with life-changing disabilities,” said Dr Edip Gurol, senior author of the study and a clinician investigator at Mass General Brigham’s Department of Neurology, told &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2025/11/heavy-drinking-linked-to-worse-strokes/" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="The Harvard Gazette"&gt;The Harvard Gazette&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to Gurol, only about 20 per cent of patients who suffer an intracerebral haemorrhage - commonly called a &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/world-news/us-news/ace-frehley-brain-bleed-what-to-know-about-condition-that-put-kiss-guitarist-on-life-support-101760648674485.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="brain bleed"&gt;brain bleed&lt;/a&gt; - can care for themselves a year later. Roughly half do not survive the event.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Also read: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/grammy-spotlight-on-indian-talent-anoushka-shankar-shakti-and-charu-suri-among-top-nominees-101762590506903.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Indian musicians dominate Grammy stage with nominations for Anoushka Shankar, Shakti, and Charu Suri"&gt;Indian musicians dominate Grammy stage with nominations for Anoushka Shankar, Shakti, and Charu Suri&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Heavy drinking ill effects: Bigger bleeds, younger patients, higher risk&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study looked at over 1,600 patients treated for non-traumatic brain bleeds between 2003 and 2019. About seven per cent of them reported drinking three or more alcoholic drinks daily. Compared to non-drinkers, heavy drinkers experienced 70 per cent larger bleeds and were, on average, 11 years younger when the event occurred - 64 versus 75.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;CT and MRI scans showed that these patients were also more likely to have deep brain bleeds or ones that extended into fluid-filled spaces around the brain. Researchers noted evidence of chronic damage to small blood vessels - the kind of deterioration often seen in dementia, balance issues, and memory decline. Even moderate drinkers, consuming just two drinks a day, showed signs of earlier onset of brain bleeds.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Heavy alcohol use appears to raise blood pressure and damage the brain’s small vessels,” Gurol told The Harvard Gazette.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Also read: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/hollywood/kill-bill-the-whole-bloody-affair-trailer-released-check-length-release-date-and-other-key-details-101762592274367.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Kill Bill: The Whole Bloody Affair trailer released; check length, release date and other key details"&gt;Kill Bill: The Whole Bloody Affair trailer released; check length, release date and other key details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;The biological toll of alcohol on the brain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study found that heavy drinkers arrived at the hospital with lower platelet counts and higher &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/new-york-cardiologist-with-30-years-of-experience-shares-most-common-high-blood-pressure-symptom-you-should-never-ignore-101762488874679.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="blood pressure"&gt;blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;, a combination that makes the brain especially vulnerable. With platelets reduced, the body struggles to stop bleeding, and high pressure makes vessels more prone to rupture. Together, those factors increase both the likelihood and severity of brain haemorrhage.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Gurol emphasised that even small reductions in alcohol consumption can make a difference. “We now know that heavy drinking leads to larger, earlier brain bleeds,” he said. “Minimising or stopping alcohol use is an important step to lower that risk. Even for people at relatively low risk, limiting alcohol to no more than three drinks per week may help protect brain and cardiovascular health.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The researchers also acknowledged limitations: self-reported alcohol use, a small number of heavy drinkers, and the fact that the study was based at a single hospital with mostly white participants. Future research, they noted, should involve more diverse populations and track long-term drinking habits.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 23:40:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4AFBVV95cUxQSk5vOTBPR1V3Y2RRZVdUY0JKVE90VFFpRDZpQ1pwdlo0Uzd4YjdTbFhzdFZsSFhXVXdiWU9SWG1Cakt2QkxCX3lqc01VT1ZCUGFHVGtPSjZDNEYxV0lhbnhYcmFOTnU1QVZsQzJlOUdNeWhEYm1RaHJhd2Ridl9CSjRYb2NBbmxLaDJEOWYxMVRPTlVpdzRmSnBSeFp4UkxHb2NYMXh0RndlT0YtbmtYaU1TTEpwQmJvQUcteS1sWnVyZllOV3pMWG14LUFjbC0zVUh3dGNpc1VHRi1GWjgxadIB5gFBVV95cUxQeEJNVnhsYWlwZDhJX0lQd3RROU04RktLQ1BQbEFhMkdOMHA0ZnByRl9Qc3drXy1jSWpXTzRkODFscUd6OEN1a205WkNvUmI1bzQ2Ym0zU0pnZ0YzQzdma01Cbzc5TVZHdGZReDNtc0hJMEdESVhHZzUzQWFFckhfVFpxc1NwSzBrZU1DYkxzd01QVmozaGs0bVdhRUtzb0pMc0VWSFNRc25YZS1mMklKX0JsanlYdk9jZWZYWmRqNzAzQnB0Vld0Q0JVYnowamJ2ZEZrNU5IcXpkRmpfa1dTTzNncUFLdw</guid></item><item><title>每天吃腰果如何帮助预防心脏病和支持整体健康-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/how-eating-cashews-daily-can-help-prevent-heart-disease-and-support-overall-health/articleshow/125189655.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart disease continues to be one of the most serious global health issues, but small dietary changes can make a meaningful difference in prevention. Cashews, the creamy and nutrient-rich nuts from the cashew tree, are packed with heart-healthy fats, essential minerals like magnesium and potassium, and powerful antioxidants that support cardiovascular function. Studies suggest that regular cashew consumption may help lower blood pressure, improve cholesterol balance, and reduce triglyceride levels, three vital factors for heart health. When consumed in moderation as part of a balanced diet that includes fruits, vegetables, and whole grains, cashews can play a simple yet effective role in maintaining a healthy, resilient heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Healthy fats present in cashews that protect your heart&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cashews are rich in monounsaturated and polyunsaturated fats, the same “good fats” found in olive oil and avocados. These fats help lower harmful LDL cholesterol while maintaining healthy HDL cholesterol levels. Balanced cholesterol reduces the buildup of plaque in arteries, improving blood circulation and lowering the risk of coronary artery disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Best dry fruits for winter and why you should consume them every day&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike saturated fats found in processed foods and red meat, the fats in cashews support blood vessel flexibility and reduce inflammation. Regularly eating cashews may also help lower total cholesterol and improve the ratio of good to bad cholesterol, which is an important marker for heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benefits of eating cashews for heart health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6573847/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;a study published in Current Developments in Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, regular consumption of cashew nuts was linked to significant reductions in systolic and diastolic blood pressure, as well as lower triglyceride levels, indicating potential heart-protective benefits. While the study found no major changes in total cholesterol or HDL and LDL levels, researchers suggested that adding cashews to a balanced diet may support overall cardiovascular health and help manage blood pressure naturally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Natural blood pressure regulation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cashews are an excellent source of magnesium and potassium, two minerals vital for controlling blood pressure. Magnesium helps relax blood vessels, improving blood flow and reducing strain on the heart. Potassium balances sodium levels in the body, which can prevent hypertension.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies show that people who include moderate amounts of cashews and other nuts in their diet tend to have healthier blood pressure levels. These small daily changes can make a measurable difference in long-term cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improving blood lipid levels&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Triglycerides, a type of fat in the blood, are a major risk factor for heart disease when levels are too high. Cashews have been shown to help reduce triglyceride levels and improve overall lipid profiles. Their combination of healthy fats, fibre, and plant compounds helps the body process fats more efficiently, preventing their buildup in arteries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regular consumption, even in small amounts, may support healthier cholesterol and triglyceride levels, especially when combined with a diet low in processed foods and rich in fresh produce and whole grains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich in antioxidants and anti-inflammatory compounds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic inflammation and oxidative stress damage the lining of blood vessels and accelerate heart disease progression. Cashews contain antioxidants such as polyphenols and tocopherols, which neutralise harmful free radicals in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;These natural compounds protect heart tissue, reduce inflammation, and support the repair of blood vessel walls. The antioxidants in cashews, when paired with other nutrient-dense foods, can enhance cardiovascular protection and slow the effects of ageing on the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Supporting a healthy weight&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maintaining a healthy weight is key to reducing the risk of heart disease, and cashews can play a role here as well. Though calorie-dense, they are rich in protein, fibre, and healthy fats that increase satiety and prevent overeating. Eating a small portion of cashews as a snack may help control cravings for less healthy foods and support steady energy levels throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research also suggests that people who regularly eat nuts tend to have a lower body mass index (BMI) despite their high calorie content, likely due to their positive effects on metabolism and appetite regulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to include cashews in a heart-healthy diet&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eat 5-10 unsalted cashews daily as a snack or part of your breakfast.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Add to salads, smoothies, or stir-fries for extra texture and nutrients.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Choose raw or dry-roasted cashews over salted or oil-fried varieties.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pair with other heart-healthy foods like berries, leafy greens, whole grains, and oily fish.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Practice moderation, one small handful (about 28 g) per day is sufficient for health benefits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Precautions to keep in mind&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While cashews are beneficial, overconsumption can add excess calories, potentially leading to weight gain. Always choose unsalted or lightly roasted varieties to avoid too much sodium, which can raise blood pressure. Those with nut allergies should avoid cashews completely. Additionally, while they support cardiovascular health, cashews should complement, not replace, other healthy habits such as regular exercise and medical treatment where necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and should not be considered medical advice. Please consult a healthcare professional before making any changes to your diet, medication, or lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also read | &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/makhana-vs-singhada-which-is-better-for-digestion-weight-loss-and-blood-sugar/articleshow/125136632.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Makhana vs. Singhada: Which is better for digestion, weight loss, and blood sugar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 22:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-AFBVV95cUxPcmwtZVVqelNrdXNWbXF3VUhENzJ5T3c4QU1JQXJFeHVJSGN6dVduUWh6aXJRT3FtT0NDZ0plLWNiVDJQYV9jRlNiU1c1c3JXN0dsZXpfSGJEU2Z4NkRqaFZTUFRhNS1ZbmZKT2dFN2M4Ny15X21FNHE3ZkFUSWNGVWdWTVMwNldFaGNFVTJmOXFpWVQtMmJiYXRjOW9abWFWeV9tamw0QjRMRnFKRjlzSEJzajlWUjJfMmw4VnlqWDh1ZTQxeElqanFMUTV0ZVhLMGh0M1FyTTJTVnBnSWxIYVJ5b054NncwUXBJaVJTMzZQVU9pRXctX9IB_gFBVV95cUxOZDE2WjV0SmU2d1ZxcGFTUTcxcXFpYmtkb2N3MjJJV1lMRnZoOXN2Y3NQNjgwQTZZTTFfQ0dRWmNhZDhTNlJiQk5PQWlIRF8xUGY5UWVIdTV6eFBqcVcyaHdsMDZtMEdFLUMweUc5dXlLamw1bE9QZWRqWnIxUUlBYUpuUUZzNWk3ckpTNEFwalZsNHZoS0lHOWpUUzE4LUdRdlIyQkRETDJ1cDRwVHUyYXhselNLaHFnQjBqNVhyS3Y4eTlXc0RXdGk0N04talc4azBaNHJnMHNRWS1fNGNUZnNLYzBvVFYzenJEQUpLOTQxdXlnRE13QlRxaWIzUQ</guid></item><item><title>喝绿茶时血压会发生什么变化- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/happens-blood-pressure-drink-green-180000726.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Design elements: Getty Images. EatingWell design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Key Points&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The antioxidants in green tea support healthy blood pressure by helping blood vessels relax.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the longer term, green tea may help protect your arteries by reducing oxidative stress and inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choose regular or decaf brewed green tea over supplements or extracts for blood-pressure benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;High blood pressure, or hypertension, affects nearly half of U.S. adults and increases the risk for heart disease and stroke. Blood pressure is an important indicator of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-tea-for-metabolic-syndrome-8782901" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:metabolic health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;metabolic health&lt;/a&gt; and healthy blood pressure is less than 120/80 mm Hg. The top number (systolic) measures pressure when your heart beats, while the bottom (diastolic) measures it between beats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While lifestyle and medications play the biggest roles in managing it, small daily habits—like &lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/drink-blood-pressure-study-11760522" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sipping green tea;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;sipping green tea&lt;/a&gt;—may also have an impact. We spoke with nutrition experts to find out how drinking green tea affects your blood pressure and who should avoid it, plus tips to add it to your routine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How Green Tea Affects Blood Pressure&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;May Relax Blood Vessels and Improve Circulation&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much of green tea’s heart-healthy blood pressure benefits come from antioxidant compounds called catechins—these polyphenols help blood vessels stay flexible and open. “One compound in particular, epigallocatechin gallate (EGCG), boosts nitric oxide and promotes vasodilation, helping your blood vessels relax,” says &lt;a href="https://www.nutritionbybess.com/old-about" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Bess Berger, RDN;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Bess Berger, RDN&lt;/a&gt;. When your blood vessels relax, or vasodilate, your blood pressure lowers—a short-term effect that supports smoother circulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“While catechins are one type of tea polyphenol, the blood pressure–lowering effects of green tea are probably attributable to a combination of all of the plant compounds it contains instead of an individual few,” adds &lt;a href="https://www.drnutritionchanger.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Qianzhi Jiang, Ph.D., RDN;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Qianzhi Jiang, Ph.D., RDN&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though some research suggests that green tea may lower blood pressure in both healthy individuals and those with hypertension, the results are inconsistent, and further long-term studies are needed to confirm these findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Helps Protect Arteries from Long-Term Damage&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;While green tea may help blood vessels relax in the moment, its bigger advantage may come from how it protects them over time. The same polyphenols that give green tea its antioxidant strength appear to guard arteries against oxidative stress and low-grade inflammation—two drivers of the slow, silent damage that can increase blood pressure with age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Green tea’s catechins support blood vessel health by reducing inflammation and improving how your vessels function,” says &lt;a href="https://www.dieteticseducation.org/about" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Devon Golem, Ph.D., RD, LDN;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Devon Golem, Ph.D., RD, LDN&lt;/a&gt;. Over time, that can translate to more supple arteries that expand and contract more easily, helping your heart pump blood efficiently. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The result isn’t an overnight change in blood pressure but a gradual, protective effect that keeps arteries healthy and resilient in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Caffeine Can Temporarily Raise Blood Pressure&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although green tea generally has less caffeine than coffee—about 30 milligrams of caffeine in an 8-ounce cup of green tea versus 95 mg in the same serving of coffee—it’s still a stimulant that can cause a short-term increase in blood pressure. “If you’re super-sensitive to caffeine, green tea could cause a temporary bump in blood pressure right after drinking it,” says Berger. This effect typically fades within a few hours as your body metabolizes the caffeine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For most people, this short-term spike doesn’t cancel out green tea’s long-term cardiovascular benefits. Research suggests that the long-term benefits of drinking green tea likely outweigh the short-term effect caffeine may have on blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re prone to &lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-to-do-if-you-drink-too-much-coffee-in-the-am-11758446" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:caffeine jitters;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;caffeine jitters&lt;/a&gt;, switching to &lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8030655/does-green-tea-have-caffeine/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:decaf green tea;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;decaf green tea&lt;/a&gt; can be a good option. You’ll still get many of the same beneficial antioxidants, as one review compared caffeinated and decaffeinated green tea extract supplements and found no difference in blood pressure effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How Much Green Tea Should You Drink Daily?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s no official guideline for how much green tea to drink for blood pressure benefits. “The majority of the studies used three to four cups of green tea daily, and greater reductions in blood pressure were observed with longer use—more than three months,” explains Jiang.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brewing matters, too. Jiang says that most of green tea’s polyphenols are released within the first five minutes of steeping, so letting your tea sit for a few minutes can help you get the most benefit from each cup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Overconsumption is very rare from green tea beverages,” says Jiang&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; However, green tea extracts may lead to side effects, including nausea, abdominal discomfort and increased blood pressure. Experts agree: It’s better to drink green tea than to take supplements that contain green tea extracts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How Green Tea Interacts with Blood Pressure Medications&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While brewed tea in moderate amounts is generally safe, concentrated green tea extracts can interfere with how certain drugs are absorbed or metabolized. Studies show that green tea can reduce the effectiveness of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/medications-don-t-mix-with-green-tea-11815448" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:certain blood pressure medications;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;certain blood pressure medications&lt;/a&gt;, including the beta-blocker nadolol. It may also interfere with other heart or cholesterol drugs when taken at the same time. These effects are more likely with high intakes or green tea extracts, but brewed tea can still play a role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you take medication for blood pressure or cholesterol, it’s worth checking with your health care provider to make sure that green tea fits safely into your routine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is Green Tea Safe for Everyone?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For most people, a few cups of green tea a day are perfectly safe—and even beneficial—but there are some exceptions. “Caffeine can negatively affect pregnant and breastfeeding women, children and individuals with anxiety, irregular heartbeats, seizures, sleep issues and irritable bowel syndrome,” says Golem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re pregnant or breastfeeding, keep total &lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8009784/how-much-caffeine-is-too-much/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:caffeine intake;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;caffeine intake&lt;/a&gt; under 200 mg per day (about two cups of green tea, depending on strength), or follow your health care provider’s guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who prefer to limit their caffeine intake can still benefit from drinking decaf green tea, which contains many of the same antioxidants but with less caffeine. While it’s uncommon, concentrated green tea extracts have been linked to liver issues in sensitive individuals, so sticking to brewed tea is the safest way to enjoy its benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Ways to Enjoy Green Tea&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Try It Iced:&lt;/strong&gt; Brew a few cups ahead and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/249466/iced-mint-green-tea/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:chill them;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;chill them&lt;/a&gt; for a refreshing afternoon drink. Add a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/252432/green-jasmine-mint-iced-tea-with-lemon/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:squeeze of lemon;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;squeeze of lemon&lt;/a&gt; to boost flavor and add some vitamin C.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Go for Matcha:&lt;/strong&gt; This &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/matcha-health-benefits-11705379" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:powdered form of green tea;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;powdered form of green tea&lt;/a&gt; offers a concentrated source of antioxidants and a mild caffeine lift. Whisk it into hot water for a traditional preparation, or use it in desserts—think cakes, cookies and pudding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skip the Sugar:&lt;/strong&gt; Opt for unsweetened tea to maximize health benefits. If you prefer a sweeter beverage, try a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/266309/warm-honey-green-tea/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:drizzle of honey;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;drizzle of honey&lt;/a&gt; or sweetener of your choice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Infuse It with Flavor:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/252432/green-jasmine-mint-iced-tea-with-lemon/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Steep your tea with fresh herbs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;Steep your tea with fresh herbs&lt;/a&gt; like mint or basil, or add slices of ginger or orange for a fragrant, spa-like spin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Creative in the Kitchen:&lt;/strong&gt; Green tea can also be used in cooking. Jiang notes that in Japan, green tea is sometimes poured over rice and topped with salmon and scallions—a simple dish called ochazuke that adds subtle flavor and antioxidants to your meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Our Expert Take&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Green tea isn’t a magic fix for high blood pressure, but it can play a small role in supporting heart health—especially when enjoyed regularly as part of a healthy lifestyle. Its polyphenols can help relax blood vessels in the short term and protect them from long-term damage caused by oxidative stress and inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts recommend getting your green tea from the cup, not a capsule. Brewed tea offers the ideal balance of beneficial compounds without the risks associated with concentrated extracts. A few cups a day—paired with other healthy habits like eating a balanced diet, staying active and managing stress—can help keep your blood pressure in a healthy range.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/green-tea-and-blood-pressure-11844020" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:EatingWell;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;EatingWell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 20:03:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxOdDZabzFBX2E1R0luQ3BaZjlJVnRfT2lsTVFhbmdZWW5URVBjMzlJUUdVS0RVX3F4T2xTWVJ0YUh5NkpLQmJPYm8yTVVtLTJiNWoxb2JyY1pBWUdLRXN6NDZPNnY2b2g3R29OcFYxTkJCQW1abE9PT01hMFBnVUhoZXNnaXA</guid></item><item><title>3种类型的脱发和实际帮助的护理-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/11/08/hair-loss-causes-treatments/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3GBHCRG365AHPGNU6EFEE4QPOE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In a clinic north of Baltimore, Myriam Lucia Vega Gonzalez meets patients every day of the week who have all types of hair loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="7GVD7IO4ONBV7AW5WWIDNUKDME" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“It’s a very, very common complaint,” said Gonzalez, an assistant professor of dermatology at Johns Hopkins University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxPejl0T3dhRWNnOF9wTEUwbEpuSzZBZ21mQ21IQUh3cEtzZlZxWDQzVzZJSHlGVmZiUUk0UDV6N1BOd2dhdDE1YzU2b2ROa094Ym9JZFpnMXVuejFDNVRuc3h6c2hSc3BlTFBoMUJXM1BKOWVlMUxGQ0plakZHdTFIS3BERmI1QQ</guid></item><item><title>我的日常能量饮料习惯使我因严重的器官损伤而住院-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15236087/energy-drinks-deadly-kidney-disease.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 21-year-old who had an eight-a-day energy drink habit was hospitalized after the beverages severely damaged his kidneys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The unidentified man from Turkey rushed to his local emergency room with nausea and vomiting that had started the day before. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He had no chronic medical problems, wasn't overweight, didn't smoke and was a 'fit healthy young man' who had never abused drugs or &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/alcohol/index.html" id="mol-481cf7d0-b440-11f0-a2ba-991f13657966"&gt;alcohol&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But blood tests revealed his creatinine, a waste product that comes from normal muscle breakdown, was about five times greater than the normal range, while his phosphorus, a mineral that helps form the structure of cell membranes and bones, was three-fold higher than average. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The concerning levels showed his kidneys were not able to properly filter the materials out of his blood, a sign of injury or organ failure. If these levels get too high, they can damage vital organs and lead to heart attack, stroke or organ failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The man told doctors that he had been preparing to run a race for the past month and was drinking two liters (68 ounces), of unnamed 'energy drink' every day to help him stay alert. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;HIS habit had caused stage three acute kidney injury (AKI), which is considered the 'middle stage' of acute &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15208907/heart-health-condition-affects-Americans-dont-know-it.html"&gt;kidney disease&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A 21-year-old in Turkey suffered stage three acute kidney injury after consuming excess energy drinks (stock image&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The unidentified man said he has been drinking two liters of an unspecified energy drink every day for a month to prepare for a race (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Roughly one in three Americans report consuming an energy drink at least once, and nine percent drink them every day. They are also especially popular among teenagers, with between 30 and 50 percent of 12- to 17-year-olds say they drink them regularly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About one in 10 Americans, 35million, have some form of kidney disease, and just over 800,000 are in kidney failure, according to the American Kidney Fund. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And about nine in 10 people with the condition have no idea they have it, including one in three Americans with severely reduced kidney function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The disease causes the kidneys to be unable to properly filter out waste and excess fluid from the blood, causing them to build up in the body, leading to high potassium, which threatens heart function, brittle bones, a weakened immune system, heart attack and stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Acute kidney injuries are usually caused by slowed blood flow to the organs, damage or blocked urine flow. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the man in the case report had no underlying conditions, his extreme energy drink consumption likely lead to the injury, doctors &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://jmedicalcasereports.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s13256-025-05614-3"&gt;wrote in a case study&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Energy drinks typically contain a mix of caffeine, B vitamins, sugar, artificial sweeteners and additives like taurine and guarana. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;An 8.4-ounce can of a popular energy drink contains 80 milligrams of caffeine, roughly the same as a cup of coffee. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If the man was drinking eight cans, this would add up to 640 milligrams of caffeine, 46 percent more than the FDA's recommended daily limit of 400 milligrams. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Recent research suggests excessive caffeine consumption, which would be more than 500 milligrams daily, may increase the risk of developing kidney stones. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Caffeine is a stimulant that temporarily raises blood pressure, but in excess amounts, that high blood pressure can put extra strain on the kidneys. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors treating the man also wrote that at least once he consumed an energy drink that contained 150 milligrams per liter of caffeine and 800 milligrams per liter of taurine, which may have made taurine that primary culprit. &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Taurine is an non-essential amino acid found naturally in the bone marrow, brain, heart and muscles. It's also found in meat and fish and is used in certain beverages to energize cells and boost mental clarity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Taurine is considered safe in small amounts, but higher levels have been shown to cause vomiting, upset stomach, dizziness, diarrhea and constipation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Along with caffeine, excess taurine can lead to dehydration and high blood pressure, potentially damaging kidneys, though research is limited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Writing in a medical journal, doctors treating the man suggested the combination of taurine and caffeine likely caused his injury. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The patient was admitted to a kidney clinic and told to stop consuming energy drinks immediately. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The most important first step to treat [energy drink]-induced AKI is withholding it,' his doctors wrote.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;His creatinine levels gradually normalized over the course of 16 days, and he did not need dialysis or other long-term treatments.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors continued following him for two years, during which his kidney function remained normal.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 17:49:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNUF9IWDdsVGJPZWJSU2JWaFVXanJ0VHZyaEItR0Y1ODJPTG44NjY3cDNCUXN5QUtENE8zZWtWOXJBdGRIeFFoUFd6TzJpTExTdzVyODJ6amttU0VWbWVVaGp2bjRMZ09sTnZvbUhIanU3WjBlOXVfR3Z0UTYtSWhPOXhIZFFfM3RQNmFtUU1nVFVweUtmUGRj0gGcAUFVX3lxTE1LTDBVOUlWdnZXY1BSZHJQOFo1Rjl5WHkzcS0tSXA4c1hGWXBEbjVVMDNVME9UQVE3TXowWEZkUDdnNWJmazRpRWc0dUxHcXY1YjM1Wl9WWFU0anYtTWRlc3FSQTEtQnlrNVdielFqZ3VyRTNuWnhFMHJobkFlZF9EanByR0VraGxqWWs4eXBZMGFfZU5leDUxazVKRw</guid></item><item><title>124岁的中国妇女分享她健康长寿的秘诀……大米、这道蔬菜汤和…… --印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/124-year-old-chinese-woman-shares-the-secret-of-her-long-healthy-life-rice-this-vegetable-soup-and-/photostory/125182871.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qiu Chaishi credits her longevity to a plain meticulously kept rhythm. She makes sure to have three meals each day, and goes out for a walk after each one, and heads to bed around eight o’clock in the evening. This steady routine not only eases digestion, but also keeps her internal clock in sync. At her age, she remains impressively self‑sufficient, handling everyday tasks such as brushing her hair, tending the fire, feeding the geese, and climbing the stairs all on her own. Even a modest amount of movement keeps her muscles engaged and her body functioning, helping to prevent frailty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAJBVV95cUxPY0xrLXhNekZpV0NZQlJrX1JkQUVNZFNORjVTRUJHSGFKa0JNZHR0R1BsQURXejVNQkF0WTVYNHRwWVNmQnRSQnh5WTRIeHZLdkEwbjBIRDRndHZSSmdRX2diZk83djZfaFZMRHh1VV9IUXROWERTNkVsazdKcDMwOE1mZ3RvWk1vRGJhc2huZ3VVWG9KZkpTdXdpaDlJUjNpQjV1UTlMWmMzNDlXVFFqaHBYODNnZENiMmJ6NEoya25lc3VTS0VITjIyc1dsS0laRnpQLS1Tb1JFWEFqZmZZNUFGOTZmZ0tYZGRtVEk1ZEN5SGp2dmNQYzBVNHB3Z29EV05xZnpVeWhSOE94SjRKYVpsT2vSAZwCQVVfeXFMTmVCS0g4SHZyc21nZUNITV9tQmJkUWtzclFFYksyUC1zUkg1a0kwMnZOd2RyT25IbFVJU01XN3NncXdLQ0F6djdRLV90bFJSQUNjMzVhbzhhSFNPZjJ5dzgtUGNTckxkLXV5T0FYeFpabU12SkNYWnBvTWRCZmVaTmRRd0dFSk4yb2h1YzBvOFBPOXV4UlhIZlFDWlY3Mml6MWNvS09vajVwWTJDZGlfSHB4SVpnT3FKQ2ZHU1BQOVdkMVFCbTZFTHBrR1pmeFVMSE5wd21IOVJlaUFKWWRZaTViaEVVMnZnT1JxbzJGTDhRSnZHekJjNEIwUE55MHd0SDA1dkd2SmxLaWhKMWhIWjNBSmhvZ3Q1aVpNNS0</guid></item><item><title>“一劳永逸”的基因编辑治疗如何降低胆固醇--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2025/11/08/crispr-gene-editing-cholesterol-disease/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GULUNR3RTBFEPB6AGZL3D325TE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In a cutting-edge medical experiment, a small group of people who had high cholesterol despite taking conventional drugs to lower it saw significant reductions in two major risk factors for heart disease after receiving a single gene-editing treatment at the highest dose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:27:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOM2FBVXA0UE9KdTBsUEJOd19QV09aWGJCR2VhS2xDTUE0aXE0V0VTM3A0dm9pc2dnQm9ycmVGbDdFNUtjQThMMmhvWnBDQzFEYlZ3NS1UeWtlUXlHUVMwWWFpb0NlTENPTEdhb3RkVHFHMWJNY1FKbFkzekExU0xvOXpIU2JUckNLOWhBLXZxQTRUOG85</guid></item><item><title>南瓜籽比奇亚籽更健康吗？营养学家称重- marthastewart.com</title><link>https://www.marthastewart.com/pumpkin-seeds-vs-chia-seeds-11844175</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="marthastewart-sc-page_1-0" class="comp marthastewart-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block marthastewart-sc-block-callout--summary marthastewart-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Points&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Both pumpkin and chia seeds are nutrient-rich superfoods that support heart, bone, and digestive health in different ways.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pumpkin seeds offer more protein, zinc, and heart-healthy fats, while chia seeds excel in fiber, calcium, and omega-3 content.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Both seeds are versatile—pumpkin seeds add crunch to meals or make a rich butter, while chia seeds thicken smoothies, puddings, and jams.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; They may be small, but when it comes to enriching your daily diet, seeds are no slouches. Two of our favorite go-tos, &lt;a href="https://www.marthastewart.com/benefits-of-pumpkin-seeds-11816812" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;pumpkin seeds&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.marthastewart.com/benefits-of-chia-seeds-11759791" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;chia seeds&lt;/a&gt;, are tiny titans, supporting the body in numerous ways. We asked nutrition experts to explain the benefits of each, and the best ways to enjoy their superpowers.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-pumpkin-seeds-vs-chia-seeds-which-one-is-healthier"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block marthastewart-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Pumpkin Seeds vs. Chia Seeds: Which One Is Healthier? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The answer depends on what you're looking for from your seeds—and how you plan to use them. "Both are nutrient-dense and complement each other well. They can easily fit into a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.marthastewart.com/best-plant-based-proteins-11710274" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;plant-based eating pattern&lt;/a&gt;," says Melissa Mroz-Planells, DCN, RDN, and spokesperson for the Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Unless someone has specific health goals that we are tailoring nutrient intake for, I typically recommend just cycling through various &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.marthastewart.com/best-nuts-to-eat-8772028" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nuts&lt;/a&gt;, seeds, and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.marthastewart.com/beans-to-eat-11695027" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;legumes&lt;/a&gt; so you benefit from as many different nutrients as possible," says Desiree Nielsen, RD, host of &lt;em&gt;The Allsorts&lt;/em&gt; podcast, and cookbook author.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For boosting your &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.marthastewart.com/what-is-fiber-and-why-you-need-it-11761089" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;fiber intake&lt;/a&gt;, chia seeds stand out. Mroz-Planells says. If getting more calcium for bone health is a priority, Nielsen recommends eating more chia seeds. "If you want more protein and healthy fats, for satiety, pumpkin seeds may be a better fit," Mroz-Planells says.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-benefits-of-pumpkin-seeds"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block marthastewart-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Benefits of Pumpkin Seeds &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A superfood, pumpkin seeds are available with hulls, shelled (known as pepitas), or scooped straight from fresh pumpkins, and offer a host of health benefits.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block marthastewart-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Heart-Healthy Fats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Pumpkin seeds contain unsaturated fatty acids, like the plant-based omega-3, alpha-linolenic acid (ALA), and omega-6 fatty acids, plus monounsaturated fats. Their healthy fats help lower LDL (bad cholesterol), raise HDL (good cholesterol), and regulate blood pressure.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block marthastewart-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Protein and Minerals &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Chia and pumpkin seeds are considered complete proteins and contain all nine essential amino acids, though pumpkin seeds are higher in protein and zinc. "Both are excellent sources of magnesium, phosphorus, and iron, supporting energy metabolism and muscle function," Mroz-Planells says. "Magnesium is important for nervous system function, including muscle relaxation, which is why it's such a heart-healthy mineral," Nielsen explains, adding that zinc is critical for immune function and skin health. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Nielsen regards pumpkin seeds as an energizing food due to their rich mineral content, including iron, manganese, and selenium. Pumpkin seeds provide sustained energy and double as a stress reliever. This plant food is a source of the amino acid &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.marthastewart.com/best-foods-for-better-sleep-11774197" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;tryptophan&lt;/a&gt;; combined with magnesium, zinc, copper, and selenium, it enhances a good night's sleep.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block marthastewart-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Anti-Inflammatory Properties &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Pumpkin seeds contain &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.marthastewart.com/antioxidant-foods-11765686" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;antioxidants&lt;/a&gt; like vitamin E and flavonoids, which complement omega-3s, helping to reduce inflammation in the body.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Pumpkin seeds with hulls have an edge fiber-wise, containing about 5.2 grams of fiber per ounce compared to pepitas with 1.8 grams of fiber, which further increases those anti-inflammatory effects.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block marthastewart-sc-block-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-tips callout--bordered" data-text="Tip" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Keep portions in check since both are calorie-rich," Mroz-Planells says. A one-ounce serving of pumpkin seeds has about 125 calories; a one-ounce serving of chia seeds has around 138 calories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-to-enjoy-pumpkin-seeds"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block marthastewart-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How to Enjoy Pumpkin Seeds &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The unique textures and flavors of pumpkin and chia seeds naturally lend themselves to different uses, Nielsen explains.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Try grinding the seeds into little nutrient "sprinkles" to top your morning cereal, she suggests.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add them to granola bars and muffins, or scatter them over soups, salads, yogurt, oatmeal, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.marthastewart.com/1554311/farro-brown-rice-or-spelt-breakfast-bowl" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;grain bowls&lt;/a&gt;, hummus, and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.marthastewart.com/872700/classic-guacamole" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;guacamole&lt;/a&gt;. "If you're looking for a delicious sauce to boost your meals, a pumpkin seed salsa macha is a staple," Nielsen says. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toss roasted or lightly toasted pumpkin with &lt;a href="https://www.marthastewart.com/soy-sauce-vs-tamari-8727166" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;tamari&lt;/a&gt; or hot sauce for a crunchy snack.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pumpkin seeds make a rich, nutritious butter. "Pop them into a food processor (you can toast them first for extra flavor and to speed up blending) and let them go until a butter forms," Nielsen says.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-benefits-of-chia-seeds"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block marthastewart-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Benefits of Chia Seeds &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As with pumpkin seeds, chia seeds offer a concentrated source of key nutrients in a small package, Mroz-Planells says. They can &lt;a href="https://www.marthastewart.com/1111970/soaked-chia" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;expand up to 12 times their size in liquid&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block marthastewart-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Protein and Minerals &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Chia seeds are loaded with essential minerals, including phosphorus, selenium, and manganese, key for metabolism and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.marthastewart.com/8193876/healthy-recipes-graceful-aging" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;antioxidant&lt;/a&gt; support. Their &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.marthastewart.com/best-foods-for-calcium-11819174" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;calcium&lt;/a&gt; and magnesium content help support bone and nervous system health, Nielsen notes, while zinc and iron are important for sustaining energy and immunity.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block marthastewart-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Gut Health &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Chia seeds offer both soluble (that's why they gel) and insoluble fiber to help improve &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.marthastewart.com/8197882/best-recipes-gut-health" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;gut health&lt;/a&gt;," Nielsen says.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block marthastewart-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Healthy Fats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This superfood is also a unique source of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.marthastewart.com/best-omega-3-foods-to-eat-11815581" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;omega-3 fatty acids&lt;/a&gt;. "Just one tablespoon contains all the omega-3 ALA you need in a day!"&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Nielsen says. Still, there's a caveat, she says: "The bulk of the nutrition in a chia seed is contained in the inner core, so if you want to absorb more nutrition from your chia seeds, be sure to consume them ground."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-to-enjoy-chia-seeds"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block marthastewart-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How to Enjoy Chia Seeds &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A natural thickening agent, &lt;a href="https://www.marthastewart.com/how-to-eat-chia-seeds-8609897" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;chia seeds magically transform everything from yogurt to oats&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chia seeds can &lt;a href="https://www.marthastewart.com/8300996/8-best-egg-substitutes-for-baking" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;replace eggs&lt;/a&gt; in baked goods. "I stir one tablespoon of ground chia with two tablespoons of warm water and let that sit before using," Nielsen says.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chia seeds are perfect for a creamy texture and fiber boost, Mroz-Planells says. For smoothies, add an extra 1/4 cup of liquid to accommodate the thickening action, Nielsen advises.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One or two tablespoons of seeds per serving increases the omega-3s and minerals in &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.marthastewart.com/1524080/no-cook-overnight-oats" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;overnight oats&lt;/a&gt;, she adds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Layer &lt;a href="https://www.marthastewart.com/870097/vanilla-chia-pudding" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;chia pudding&lt;/a&gt; with fresh fruit and nuts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chia seeds can make a quick, fresh fruit jam for breakfast. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>marthastewart.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTE56VTJHVFJvV21mcXVrd3FCUm9VV1VRMmc5YlVxajlfT1Q2R01vWG9aazVaUmxjbHRnSGM4SE5SZjJpeUtuODN6NHJOU0I3SmF5cXdPS3hwYU5meHpXcEtfSVd2bjNxM2owblVGNVhCSFFmUG0y</guid></item><item><title>创新生命支持系统之父Robert H. Bartlett去世，享年86岁--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/08/science/robert-h-bartlett-dead.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:55:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE1wN1ZHcDRRNUs5dnZBcEZnd1NTRUg2OGJTbWFqd1dDbUN2VDdUTnRiYjlrTVRyaS0tNlVxNDN4YTJ1QVc5SnZuMV80ZEhreUNUT2lkd2VLWmVPLWphRFVyRFhHNzNlNi13VnBWVDlOak9mdzVFdUZuUHNR</guid></item><item><title>股票代码：不要死于心脏病-黑客新闻</title><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45857053</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hacker News</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:53:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWEFVX3lxTE5ZSDVKOTdhSjIyaW15Z18wRVdvdDdncEJqN0J2b2ZTWE9BbzQ4Nzk3ZTJ2RGtsdzdtc2dBSVl6YkprUUZnaGdaWG5HOVJISVJrWTRYekNmaTY</guid></item><item><title>咖啡会让你冲进厕所吗？佛罗里达州胃肠病学家解释为什么喝咖啡会刺激肠道运动|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/does-coffee-make-you-rush-to-the-loo-florida-gastroenterologist-explains-why-drinking-coffee-stimulates-bowel-movements-101762614578668.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storyMainDiv" class="fullStory tfStory current videoStory story__detail storyAf101762614578668 " data-vars-storyid="101762614578668" data-story-section="lifestyle" data-story-subsection="health" data-vars-author="Eshana Saha" data-premium-story="false" data-performance-type="not-set" data-story-title="Does coffee make you rush to the loo? Florida gastroenterologist explains why drinking coffee stimulates bowel movements"&gt; &lt;p class="htEchoTopPageBanner dHide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="stickyCard"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;h1 class="hdg1"&gt;Does coffee make you rush to the loo? Florida gastroenterologist explains why drinking coffee stimulates bowel movements&lt;/h1&gt;  &lt;div class="actionDiv flexElm topTime"&gt; &lt;p class="dateTime secTime storyPage"&gt;Published on: Nov 08, 2025 09:20 pm IST &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="googleFollow mHide"&gt; &lt;button class="htEchoShareBarDesk"&gt;&lt;/button&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;h2 class="sortDec"&gt;Do you need to drink coffee in the morning to stimulate bowel movements? Dr Salhab explains the science behind the connection.&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;div class="storyDetails taboola-readmore"&gt; &lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/does-coffee-make-you-rush-to-the-loo-florida-gastroenterologist-explains-why-drinking-coffee-stimulates-bowel-movements-101762614578668.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;We’ve all experienced it: that urgent need to dash to the bathroom right after your morning &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/technology/5-coffee-makers-that-will-instantly-elevate-your-kitchen-101762250675879.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="coffee"&gt;coffee &lt;/a&gt;- or the dread of drinking coffee when you’re out and about. While it might feel like a quirky coincidence, there’s actually a scientific explanation behind it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/08/550x309/coffee_1762616795423_1762616795653.jpeg" alt="Dr Salhab explains the science behind coffee and bowel movements.(Pexel)" title="Dr Salhab explains the science behind coffee and bowel movements.(Pexel)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/08/550x309/coffee_1762616795423_1762616795653.jpeg" alt="Dr Salhab explains the science behind coffee and bowel movements.(Pexel)" title="Dr Salhab explains the science behind coffee and bowel movements.(Pexel)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Dr Salhab explains the science behind coffee and bowel movements.(Pexel)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/can-chewing-gum-ease-heartburn-florida-gastroenterologist-shares-3-easy-hacks-to-relieve-acid-reflux-without-medication-101761387796258.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Can chewing gum ease heartburn? Florida gastroenterologist shares 3 easy hacks to relieve acid reflux without medication"&gt;Can chewing gum ease heartburn? Florida gastroenterologist shares 3 easy hacks to relieve acid reflux without medication&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Joseph Salhab, a gastroenterologist and health content creator from Florida, specialising in &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/digestion" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="digestion"&gt;digestion&lt;/a&gt;, liver, pancreas and &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/deep-cleaning-for-diwali-nutritionist-shares-7-kitchen-items-to-get-rid-of-that-are-silently-harming-your-health-101760186828101.html" data-vars-anchor-text="nutrition"&gt;nutrition&lt;/a&gt;, is explaining what makes you want to run to the loo after drinking coffee. In an Instagram video posted on November 8, the gastroenterologist highlights the role of coffee in stimulating bowel movements and shares three gentler alternatives that won’t leave you running to the loo.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why does coffee make you need to poop?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Salhab states, “Does coffee make you have to go poop? If it does, you're not alone. In fact, 30 to 40 percent of people who drink coffee regularly report that coffee has to make them go to the bathroom in the morning.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He mentions that this happens for a few reasons. He explains, “First is the caffeine content. Caffeine can stimulate movement of the colon within four minutes of ingesting it. Coffee also stimulates contraction of your &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/crash-dieting-living-sedentary-life-cause-gallbladder-stones-physician-warns-of-5-everyday-habits-that-increase-risk-101758705466730.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="gallbladder"&gt;gallbladder &lt;/a&gt;to pump digestive enzymes and bile. And this also stimulates your gastrointestinal tract to start moving.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The gastroenterologist adds that coffee is typically served warm, and consuming warm beverages can naturally stimulate bowel movements - warm water also works the same way. He continues, “Also, the antioxidants within coffee have been shown to promote the growth of beneficial bacteria within the gut and these beneficial bacteria can also influence how often we use the restroom.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Gentler alternatives&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Salhab outlines three effective ways to manage that sudden urge to run to the loo after drinking coffee.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can opt for beverages with lower caffeine content - such as green tea - or simply cut down your usual coffee intake to reduce its laxative effect.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Switching to a cold brew or iced coffee also helps.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If that doesn't work, you can just switch to a decaf version, which still has plenty of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-calls-matcha-tea-science-in-a-cup-shares-top-5-benefits-fat-burn-antioxidant-weight-loss-caffeine-101752815578622.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="antioxidants"&gt;antioxidants &lt;/a&gt;and health benefits, minus the sudden urge to rush to the bathroom.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. It is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="recommendedSliderContextual" id="recommendedSliderContextual-101762614578668" data-vars-story_id="101762614578668" data-vars-story_section="lifestyle" data-vars-author="Eshana Saha" data-vars-story_headline="Does coffee make you rush to the loo? Florida gastroenterologist explains why drinking coffee stimulates bowel movements"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" class="trendTopsSHow" id="trendTopsSHow-101762614578668"&gt; &lt;div class="trendTops"&gt;  &lt;div class="trendInlineSeo"&gt;&lt;p&gt; Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;label class="moreBtn1" for="trendTopsSHow-101762614578668"&gt;&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="followHT trendSeo__1"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="bottomSeoParaEcho1"&gt; &lt;div id="bottomSeoParaEcho"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="mb5 mt5" id="bottomBreadCrumb"&gt; &lt;div class="breadcrumbs"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Home_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/" data-vars-event-cta="News"&gt;News&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Lifestyle_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle" data-vars-event-cta="Lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Health_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle/health" data-vars-event-cta="Health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Does coffee make you rush to the loo? Florida gastroenterologist explains why drinking coffee stimulates bowel movements &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="bottomSeoParaEcho pb0"&gt; &lt;label class="moreBtn" for="trendTopsSHow-101762614578668" id="spanSeeLessEcho"&gt;See Less&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;p class="relatedStoryCricket"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="saranyuPlayer" id="saranyu-player"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="relatedStory2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="us-ad align-center mb10 mt10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="htEchoShortsEntryPoint" data-size="enlarged"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="affiliate-shop-now" id="affiliate-shop-now"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:50:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwJBVV95cUxOWkRYLUFid09SZzdWUWkwWGVlZmJyMFdDQ1dLVGpyU21fMjZwTXhuT1RoWllJaWxhOExOTkVYa1dfM0NNTEN0UVppUmZxdkJtQWVXTXV6V0hlZ1Q4UjNORkwwQlhILUp5b2Mxd3F5eUlQSFB5NzItV28wWE5Hek5vWXF3Vk9oZTNpajdhOXR3aE5udjQwLTY0YXBJb3JGQjhRdW0tbll1b1pPYVFRczA2anBXYmdab05UWG9hc2lERU9rYlFXdWc5blgxajNHQm92Snc5OVpGcG92Tmo3WEw4bEJ2ZEtMU0lYaVpBS3EzVVJLQlRoYjNDSDZVY21iX25DMmlablh3ZnhSTkVod3d3djMxZFFFbGPSAZwCQVVfeXFMTjA0SHdHSmpLSGNrRmpyX0tqUmVsa1gxR1VMUVUxRUdCZlNxQVpRbW5sdUlSb25mUkgtR1VWQjRGcTFVT0thVng2amtlTkJmMzRSM1NnbmhSaUVXYW9MMmhxZ3hUQUZNTVpNemZoeVlZcWR3N3JpdG9XeXhVeUJxRWZ4UnhOb0JXdnhxckhpaVluRk1weThJVHU5bUxuQXBwWDNXMTFIb3N4dEk3UGdGS21JNTY3X093aVcyWXFWZk5kd1ZXWml1cy1YZ0tNS3g1Q0JGMzN6enRUWVNvYjlCcXluNTZnZ2p3RnhBTHo4UWMwY0RtTzRWS2FwVUtCWE1ZSUNnZ1VRWnNOUTl5dHhlU2h3eHAwcUMyWklVOTg</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现可以阻止阿尔茨海默氏症的脑细胞- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/11/251108083902.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;In Alzheimer's disease, the most common cause of dementia, microglia (the brain's immune cells) play a double role. They can protect the brain by clearing harmful debris or, under certain conditions, contribute to damage and inflammation. How these cells behave can strongly influence how the disease unfolds.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientists from the Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai, together with researchers from the Max Planck Institute for Biology and Ageing in Cologne, Germany, The Rockefeller University, The City University of New York, and other international partners, have identified a unique group of microglia that appear to protect the brain. This discovery could pave the way for new treatment strategies aimed at slowing or preventing Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a study published November 5 in &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;, the team found that microglia with lower levels of a transcription factor called PU.1 and higher expression of a receptor known as CD28 help reduce brain inflammation. These specialized microglia also slow the buildup of amyloid plaques and the spread of toxic tau proteins, which are both major hallmarks of Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PU.1 is a protein that binds to specific DNA regions, helping control which genes are activated or silenced. CD28, found on the surface of T cells, acts as a signaling receptor that supports immune cell activation and communication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Protective Microglia Work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using mouse models of Alzheimer's, as well as human brain cells and tissue samples, the researchers showed that reducing PU.1 levels encourages microglia to express immune-regulating receptors typically found in lymphoid cells. Although these protective microglia make up only a small portion of total microglia, their effect is widespread: they suppress inflammation throughout the brain and help preserve memory and survival in mice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the scientists removed CD28 from this specific microglial subset, inflammation worsened and plaque growth increased, confirming that CD28 plays an essential role in keeping these brain-protective cells active.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Microglia are not simply destructive responders in Alzheimer's disease -- they can become the brain's protectors," said Anne Schaefer, MD, PhD, Professor in the Nash Family Department of Neuroscience at the Icahn School of Medicine, Co-Director of the Center for Glial Biology at The Friedman Brain Institute, Director of the Max Planck Institute for Biology of Ageing, and senior author of the paper. "This finding extends our earlier observations on the remarkable plasticity of microglia states and their important roles in diverse brain functions. It also underscores the vital importance of international collaboration in advancing scientific progress."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It is remarkable to see that molecules long known to immunologists for their roles in B and T lymphocytes also regulate microglial activity," added Alexander Tarakhovsky, MD, PhD, Dr. Plutarch Papamarkou Professor of Immunology, Virology, and Microbiology at The Rockefeller University and co-author of the paper. "This discovery comes at a time when regulatory T cells have achieved major recognition as master regulators of immunity, highlighting a shared logic of immune regulation across cell types. It also paves the way for immunotherapeutic strategies for Alzheimer's disease."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genetic Clues Point to Lower Alzheimer's Risk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research expands upon earlier genetic findings by Alison M. Goate, DPhil, Jean C. and James W. Crystal Professor of Genomics and Chair of the Department of Genetics and Genomic Sciences at the Icahn School of Medicine, founding director of the Ronald M. Loeb Center for Alzheimer's Disease at Mount Sinai, and a senior co-author of the study. Dr. Goate's prior work identified a common genetic variant in SPI1 (the gene responsible for producing PU.1) that is linked to a lower risk of developing Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"These results provide a mechanistic explanation for why lower PU.1 levels are linked to reduced Alzheimer's disease risk," said Dr. Goate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A New Path Toward Immunotherapy for Alzheimer's&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The discovery of the PU.1-CD28 relationship offers a new molecular framework for understanding how microglia can protect the brain. It also strengthens the idea that targeting microglial activity through immune-based therapies could alter the course of Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This research was supported by the National Institutes of Health, European Research Council, Stavros Niarchos Foundation, Cure Alzheimer's Fund, Freedom Together Foundation, Belfer Neurodegeneration Consortium Grant, Massachusetts Life Sciences Center, Robin Chemers Neustein Postdoctoral Fellowship Award, Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, Alzheimer's Association, BrightFocus Foundation, National Multiple Sclerosis Society, and Clinical and Translational Science Awards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:44:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE9vdDczaW9DN1RQQ3ItVU5TMzV2UGd3RDRqR0tiN0drZ25MT0o0WTE4bFhqWWRWRERtVkJlLVYzNUU2TVhtc25CeXFtNjR5NVZuNC1iNWtITHR2VWhvczRpc0hmNWlzQzlVME9UTkJMNA</guid></item><item><title>白发可能是您身体的癌症防御秘密- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/gray-hair-may-be-your-bodys-secret-cancer-defense/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:14:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxNTXd1djlOaEJ0TG9MZmdVdVhXMjQ2eHhWUDdPSzBOTXRicklsVEE4cW9EVlFoM1ZPN2ljVUlIeUFBNUJqQlhiWU85LWNqenpocHVRbDNuazZnZW41Z1d5cmZ3TS1hQ1BmRHFEOWstVWJFNVMzbzRpM2Qxb0NVSEVFTQ</guid></item><item><title>基于CRISPR的治疗在早期研究中降低胆固醇和甘油三酯- statnews.com</title><link>https://www.statnews.com/2025/11/08/crispr-therapeutics-cholesterol-lowering-gene-editing-study/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A CRISPR-based gene editing therapy dramatically reduced levels of low-density lipoprotein, often called “bad cholesterol,” and triglycerides in patients with heart disease, a new study found.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Some researchers said that the treatment, developed by the biotech CRISPR Therapeutics and so far tested in just 15 people, pointed to a possible future where some people prevent heart attacks with one-time gene editing. But this research is also at a very early stage, and scientists expressed concerns about the potential liver toxicities of the treatment and those like it. There is also the question of how many patients would want permanent editing for common illnesses that might be treated with a shot or a pill.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The results were published in the &lt;a href="http://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2511778" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;New England Journal of Medicine&lt;/a&gt; and are being presented Saturday at the annual scientific meeting of the American Heart Association in New Orleans.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker article" aria-labelledby="restricted-story-heading" aria-describedby="restricted-story-description" checked&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-bar"&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-text"&gt;STAT+ Exclusive Story&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-login"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;img class="restricted-content-breaker-bg" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-breaker-bg.png" alt="STAT+"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper"&gt;
				&lt;span class="stat-paywall-archive"&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/"&gt;
						&lt;img class="stat-plus-logo" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-logo-white.svg" alt="STAT+"&gt;
					&lt;/a&gt;
				&lt;/span&gt;
				&lt;h2 id="restricted-story-heading"&gt;This article is exclusive to STAT+ subscribers&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;h3 id="restricted-story-description"&gt;Unlock this article — plus daily coverage and analysis of the biotech sector — by subscribing to STAT+.&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper-cta mobile"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta mobile"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-cards"&gt;
					&lt;div class="slider-container" aria-label="Subscription plan toggle"&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="individual" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Individual plans&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;p class="switch" role="switch" tabindex="0" aria-checked="false"&gt;
							&lt;button class="slider"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="group" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Group plans&lt;/button&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
							

		
						&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button view-all" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker view all plans" aria-label="View All Plans"&gt;View All Plans&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="restricted-message-breaker"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-wrapper"&gt;
								
								&lt;div class="restricted-content-message"&gt;
					&lt;p class="restricted-content-text"&gt;
						To read the rest of this story subscribe to STAT+.					&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button restricted-button" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker subscribe cta 1"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
								
							&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPVnFXZzNmeUg1OUM2SlBjbGJnWG9NdDdaXzBxMjZJaWVLYnhadF9BVE40X2xVcnh3Y2EwWklzNHp4WkhBOUlNRkpNWmN4YWJzaDZwWkR4WE55d0podldoMTV6TzJCRndrRUo4enRLSFdDbzBvQm11bnBJbUZQUXYyZWRZNUoyVzRzclVtbTl4RmRMQldHamVtR0ZBejk</guid></item><item><title>在一项新研究中， CRISPR基因编辑有助于降低高胆固醇- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/11/08/nx-s1-5587748/crispr-gene-editing-cholesterol-heart-disease</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-97036" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Patients with high cholesterol often take medicine for years to manage it but a new gene-editing treatment has potential to make a difference.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    TEK IMAGE/Science Photo Library/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        TEK IMAGE/Science Photo Library/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;A single infusion of an experimental gene-editing drug appears safe and effective for cutting cholesterol, possibly for life, according to a small early study released Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The study, which involved 15 volunteers, found one infusion of a drug that uses the CRISPR gene-editing technique could safely reduce cholesterol, as well as levels of harmful triglycerides, by about half.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;"Rather than a lifetime worth of medicine, we have the potential to give people a cure," said Dr. &lt;a href="https://providers.clevelandclinic.org/provider/luke-laffin/4268377" target="_blank"&gt;Luke Laffin&lt;/a&gt;, a preventative cardiologist at the Cleveland Clinic who helped conduct the study. "It's very exciting."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The results of the study were presented Saturday at the &lt;a href="https://professional.heart.org/en/meetings/scientific-sessions" target="_blank"&gt;American Heart Association's annual meeting&lt;/a&gt; and published in &lt;a href="http://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2511778" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The New England Journal of Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;If confirmed by future research, the approach could provide a powerful new weapon to fight &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/heart-disease/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;, the nation's leading killer, freeing people from the need to take statins and other cholesterol-lowering drugs every day.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Laffin and others cautioned, however, that much more research is needed to confirm the findings and make sure the treatment would be safe and long-lasting.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The idea of an inexpensive, one-and-done [treatment], so you don't have to take any of those drugs, right now that's an idea — a fantasy — because gene-editing is expensive, long-term safety is unclear," Dr. &lt;a href="https://www.scripps.edu/faculty/topol/" target="_blank"&gt;Eric Topol&lt;/a&gt;, a cardiologist at Scripps Research in California who wasn't involved in the study.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Other scientists agree.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's a step in the right direction," says Dr. &lt;a href="https://www.med.upenn.edu/cvi/musunuru-laboratory.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kiran Musunuru&lt;/a&gt;, scientific director of the Center for Inherited Cardiovascular Medicine at the University of Pennsylvania Perelman School of Medicine. He was not involved in the research either. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It could be a very important tool," he says. "But to actually prove it's protective against cardiovascular disease you need to do more study."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;And, Musunuru and others note that the bar for safety would be higher to use gene-editing on patients who are otherwise healthy compared to those already suffering from serious illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Doctors infuse the drug into patients' bloodstream so it can travel to the liver and disable a gene called ANGPTL3, which is involved in producing cholesterol and triglycerides. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's a knockout of the gene. It cuts it. And after that, the gene no longer functions," said Dr. &lt;a href="https://providers.clevelandclinic.org/provider/steven-nissen/4268279" target="_blank"&gt;Steven Nissen&lt;/a&gt;, another preventive cardiologist at the Cleveland Clinic involved in the research.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://crisprtx.com/about-us/leadership/dr.-samarth-kulkarni" target="_blank"&gt;Samarth Kulkarni&lt;/a&gt;, chief executive officer at &lt;a href="https://crisprtx.com/" target="_blank"&gt;CRISPR Therapeutics&lt;/a&gt;, which is developing the drug and sponsored the study, says the approach "could potentially impact millions of people around the world."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The findings are consistent with a &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/11/12/1211672034/for-the-first-time-gene-editing-provides-hints-for-lowering-cholesterol" target="_blank"&gt;similar approach&lt;/a&gt; being developed by another company, &lt;a href="https://www.vervetx.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Verve Therapeutics&lt;/a&gt; in Boston.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The fact that we now have more clinical data that there's a 'there there' is of course tremendously encouraging," says &lt;a href="https://vcresearch.berkeley.edu/faculty/fyodor-urnov" target="_blank"&gt;Fyodor Urnov&lt;/a&gt;, who studies gene editing at the University of California, Berkeley. "Having a CRISPR medicine for heart attack would be an extraordinary win."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Neither company has said how much the treatment might cost, but other gene-editing and gene therapies have been very expensive, costing millions per patient.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Millions of people take medicines every day to cut their cholesterol and their risk for having a heart attack or stroke. But heart disease still kills nearly 700,000 people every year in the US. One big reason: A lot of people quit taking their medicine.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"This problem of adherence — that people stop taking their medications — is huge," Nissen says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Researchers are planning larger, longer studies to see whether a one-time gene-editing drug could safely protect people against heart attacks and strokes for a lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxPblE2anJRaEV6S2l5YnZibVFOSlhoMFZRd3hfZ0Y4YUNwWTRuaXNValpnLVRmRzN4V05qdEMwU1h1VFljQmY1ZEV3LWJOZEVvRGNvUzl5dV9QQmpWSEhBMXpXQ3E2NGlFZkxqYXhKZmpCWm42UW81THRrcFVWM3JxMEtHalhiNGI2WHRPVFhUSzNnU0RD</guid></item><item><title>基因编辑疗法将胆固醇水平降低一半</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/a-gene-editing-therapy-cut-cholesterol-levels-by-half/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="lead-in-text-callout"&gt;In a step&lt;/span&gt; toward the wider use of gene editing, a treatment that uses &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/tag/crispr/"&gt;Crispr&lt;/a&gt; successfully slashed high cholesterol levels in a small number of people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;In a trial conducted by Swiss biotech company Crispr Therapeutics, 15 participants received a one-time infusion meant to switch off a gene in the liver called &lt;em&gt;ANGPTL3.&lt;/em&gt; Though rare, some people are born with a mutation in this gene that protects against heart disease with no apparent adverse consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The highest dose tested in the trial reduced both “bad” LDL cholesterol and triglycerides by an average of 50 percent within two weeks after treatment. The effects lasted at least 60 days, the length of the trial. The results were presented today at the American Heart Association’s annual meeting and published in &lt;a href="http://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2511778"&gt;The New England Journal of Medicine.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The Nobel Prize–winning Crispr technology has mostly been used to &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/a-baby-received-a-custom-crispr-treatment-in-record-time/"&gt;address rare diseases&lt;/a&gt;, but these latest findings, while early, add to the evidence that the DNA-editing tool could be used to treat common conditions as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“This will probably be one of the biggest moments in the arc of Crispr’s development in medicine,” Samarth Kulkarni, CEO of Crispr Therapeutics, tells WIRED. The company is behind the only approved gene-editing treatment on the market, &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-worlds-first-crispr-drug-gets-a-slow-start-sickle-cell-beta-thalassemia-vertex/"&gt;Casgevy&lt;/a&gt;, which treats sickle cell disease and beta thalassemia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The American Heart Association &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/epub/10.1161/CIR.0000000000001123"&gt;estimates&lt;/a&gt; that about a quarter of adults in the US have elevated LDL levels. A similar number have high triglycerides. LDL cholesterol is the waxy substance in the blood that can clog and harden arteries over time. Triglycerides, meanwhile, are the most common type of fat found in the body. High levels of both raise the risk of heart attack and stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The Phase I trial was conducted in the UK, Australia, and New Zealand between June 2024 and August 2025. Participants were between the ages of 31 and 68 and had uncontrolled levels of LDL cholesterol and triglycerides. The trial tested five different doses of the Crispr infusion, which took about two and a half hours on average to administer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“These are very sick people,” says Steven Nissen, senior author and chief academic officer of the Heart, Vascular and Thoracic Institute at Cleveland Clinic, which independently confirmed the trial’s results. “The tragedy of this disease is not just that people die young, but some of them will have a heart attack, and their lives are never the same again. They don't get back to work, they develop heart failure.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;One trial participant, a 51-year-old man, died six months after receiving the lowest dose of the treatment, which was not associated with a lowering of cholesterol and triglycerides. The death was related to his existing heart disease, not the experimental Crispr treatment. The man had a rare, inherited genetic form of high cholesterol and previously had several procedures to improve blood flow to his heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 14:56:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxPcVRpeFc3TkdfNEkxaV9GN283NnR6UFlIY09nSUk2M2xDT0NqR0dvbmIybXBteGNDVHJ6Uk1LOEt1ekdTNDY4MmhUc2VURXh3c1A2YVJsWjdrQUhGUGw2MWlIM2toZWNhNnlkQzhrMmRKMFNkY1BWWk1aZG1LazRYQUU5UUVMVzdsZ1E</guid></item></channel></rss>