<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>疫苗专家组的紧张局势暴露了RFK Jr.领导下的科学更广泛的冲突。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/09/20/acip-vaccine-cdc-criticism-rfk/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AXAY47Q7H13V1D9VNT1268CTD0" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The chair of a new panel of federal immunization advisers selected by Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. said Friday that the group’s “enormous depth and knowledge about vaccines, about science” should be obvious to anyone listening to them work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 10:17:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQanZ0UjlmMkI3VnNQZVVVVnBkN296X3ZqaTF4aGd6emhNQ1NuZVhHNzFvU3dPLThxNDZmZFlidVU1bVh3TVFuMTJ5ZnVvN3NVWDc4aFdLeFV1YWFZTU82OXU3Mi1EaFNsUFRUeEpNMUlfRVA0ZlpaM1Y2RDczX2V6U0kxZ0RlWUU</guid></item><item><title>阳光对健康的好处可能大于患皮肤癌的风险-黑客新闻</title><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45298034</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hacker News</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 06:03:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWEFVX3lxTE1tR0pQUG1WeFhfdTVIczRJV01VNUJpZEJ5UTdUc0JCOW94SzRkN2lGc1NfZDFkR1hYbmJHcWxxTzZZQXRPRDFycFJZek9oVkdFVkpfNHFoQlU</guid></item><item><title>我无法治愈的病情是一种潜在的Ozempic副作用。相信我—减肥不值得。- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/laurieyarnell/ozempic-side-effect-gastroparesis-stomach-paralysis</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-1
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="skincare" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139329371" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;In case you’ve been living under a rock and missed the hype, Ozempic is an injectable diabetes drug that’s become popular as an off-label medication for weight loss. It mimics GLP-1, a naturally occurring hormone, to suppress appetite and delay the passage of food in the stomach, making many feel fuller after eating less.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if I wanted to, I couldn’t take drugs like Ozempic because I have a stomach condition called gastroparesis, also known as paralysis of the stomach. Recently, media outlets have reported that in rare instances, taking &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/07/25/health/weight-loss-diabetes-drugs-gastroparesis/index.html" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7941202" data-affiliate="true"&gt;these drugs might be linked&lt;/a&gt; to the development of gastroparesis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unless you’re related to me, you’ve probably never heard of the condition, but gastroparesis is thought to affect about &lt;a href="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/digestive-diseases/gastroparesis/definition-facts#:~:text=symptoms%20and%20complications.-,How%20common%20is%20gastroparesis%3F,the%20United%20States2%2C%203." target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7941202" data-affiliate="true"&gt;10 men and 40 women&lt;/a&gt; out of 100,000 people. In addition to nausea and vomiting, the condition also causes gas, acid reflux, distension and other equally fun symptoms. As my gastroenterologist explained it to me, the muscles in the stomach react too slowly in people with gastroparesis, causing food to sit there until it starts to ferment. The resulting symptoms, particularly the severe nausea and vomiting, mean that eating will be the last thing on your mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But no matter how much weight you may lose, you do not want gastroparesis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My condition is officially listed as idiopathic — that is, it has no known cause. In the spring of 2015, I started to feel nauseous all the time. After months of morning sickness-like nausea and vomiting, followed by a misdiagnosis and an unnecessary surgery to remove my gallbladder, my gastroenterologist mentioned an unusual medical condition that could only be diagnosed with a special test at the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the radioisotope gastric-emptying test, I had to ingest egg salad containing a small amount of tasteless radioactive material that allowed a mini camera to follow the food through my digestive system. Scans of my stomach were then taken over several hours. Afterward, it was official: I was diagnosed with gastroparesis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another reason why you don’t want gastroparesis? There is no cure. Ondansetron, the drug of choice for the nausea, does nothing for me. The preferred drug for delayed stomach emptying, domperidone, was available in the U.S. when I first developed the condition but I now have to get it from Canada. And the cost of domperidone, about $1,000 annually, is not picked up by insurance. I also have to take pantoprazole and sucralfate, twice a day each, to prevent painful acid reflux and ulcers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are surgical treatments like one I had last year at a gastroparesis clinic in Ohio to help manage symptoms, but again, they are not a cure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though some cases of gastroparesis do go away on their own, the longer you’ve had the condition, the greater the likelihood that it won’t. Gastroparesis is not life-threatening, but it has definitely been life-altering for me, as any chronic medical condition can be. It literally affects every aspect of my life; I never know when I will wake up feeling nauseous, so having to cancel plans is an unfortunate side effect of gastroparesis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best way for me to manage the condition is by being hypervigilant about what I eat and drastically limiting fiber and fats. No meat, no more fresh veggies or most fruits, no lettuce, and no oil or fried foods that slow down digestion. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I eat lots of small, bland meals and I am constantly monitoring my symptoms. If I don’t eat enough, I get nauseous. If I eat too much, I get nauseous. If I eat something that actually tastes good, I will probably get nauseous. I am afraid to try a dish when when I don’t know exactly what’s in it, since accidentally eating a food that’s isn’t “safe” can lead to extreme nausea that has me curled up in the fetal position for days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I often bring my own food when I travel, even for a day, and I am always thinking ahead about my meal options. I always carry my meds, as well as snacks that don’t require refrigeration, like oyster crackers, saltines and mints. Big events like weddings can be particularly challenging; I’ve had to sneak away to eat my yogurt or plain turkey wrap, which I bring in an insulated lunch bag. I carry a plastic bowl in my car, just like I did when I was pregnant, in case I have to vomit. In short, I am never not thinking about gastroparesis or worrying about its potential symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 03:16:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxPa2lKVTRKYnpuX0dmSWlkMjF4T2FHbThZb3FrMVJhNmg1U0k3aVBIaktVSHQxc3pDTVBQUDRpMXBYYUhWOXpUbHB0anV0MFhscmxqYUVBTTFNUUMzUFJtSmh6MVlQV2VVWGJ0V3JTWmVoMTNobFpvMUlJcFNFVkJaNHYwVDRRRjBJdWtPWXVzQlcyWk1a</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr.的疫苗顾问为接种新冠疫苗增加了障碍-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/09/19/cdc-covid-vaccine-vote-acip/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="U2LVQKJXEZGQDACAVFNY3C7L44" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;ATLANTA — A federal vaccine advisory panel unanimously voted Friday on a more restrictive approach to coronavirus vaccines by recommending that everyone consult a clinician before getting a shot. The shift creates a complication for Americans who for years were able to get a free shot without having to justify it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 01:49:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNeERZUlRfenhZWjVfMW9nX1ZTb0IwNXBTcm91QXhudWNLUHg5S3VSejNxY0JHckhvRXg3WVBQWkVRRE1kVVdEbFNsblVMZ194Ti1GUFkyLU5FYzNNUW1LbjBtMnJETDEyNmpBeVdVWWpsRUk1bVozT2JzcG16U2FMNWhYTQ</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr.精心挑选的CDC咨询小组如何对新冠疫苗等进行投票- PBS</title><link>https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/how-rfk-jr-s-hand-picked-cdc-advisory-panel-voted-on-covid-vaccines-and-more</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-text"&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kennedy made what he called &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/hhs-restore-public-trust-vaccines-acip.html"&gt;“a clean sweep”&lt;/a&gt; in June when he fired the entire committee and replaced them with his handpicked selections. These new members included &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/anti-science/rfk-announces-new-acip-members-including-vaccine-critics"&gt;noted vaccine skeptics and conspiracy theorists&lt;/a&gt;. Some members &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/hhs-cdc-announce-new-acip-members-sept-2025.html"&gt;joined the committee as recently as this week&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The advisory committee’s performance appeared “sloppy” and highlighted how “medicine is an art and a science,” said Dr. Georges Benjamin, executive director for the American Public Health Association. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You have a committee, and you bring one new person in, that changes the whole dynamics,” Benjamin said. “A lot of these folks are on a very steep learning curve because they’re not vaccine specialists – most of them.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are four takeaways from the meeting and how the panel’s decisions will affect health policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The committee tried to fight its image&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Committee chair Martin Kulldorff opened the meeting by rejecting criticism that panel members were anti-vaccine and challenging previous directors of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention to a debate about vaccine science. Other committee members pushed back at the characterizations they have faced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Joseph Hibbeln, a psychiatrist and Omega-3 fatty acid researcher who serves on the committee, said the members did not enter the conversation with “pre-determined attitudes or pre-determined opinions,” but instead were respectful of others, even during disagreements: “We are not, as a committee, anti-vaxxers.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the manner in which the ACIP was reshaped in recent months, and Kennedy’s statements and actions on vaccines, has worked to undermine public health workers and institutions, said Jennifer Nuzzo, an epidemiologist who directs the Pandemic Center at the Brown University School of Public Health. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nuzzo specifically pointed out how many of the committee members had criticized research about infectious diseases, including COVID-19, at the meeting and demanded more research. During the proceedings, their arguments often relied upon personal stories, such as their own experiences getting vaccine information at their local pharmacy, rather than data and evidence. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Water cooler conversations [do] not amount to epidemiology,” Nuzzo said. “There’s a lot of reasons why anecdotes may be misleading. Sometimes, they do suggest something else is going on, but you have to do rigorous studies to figure it out.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;COVID-19&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Much of Friday’s discussion was consumed with a technical review of COVID-19 infection rates, and deliberations grew tense. During public comments, health experts said the committee’s proposed recommendations for COVID-19 vaccines created more confusion and erected more barriers at a time when people are losing health care coverage and communities are experiencing worsening health outcomes on multiple fronts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Retsef Levi, a professor at the MIT Sloan School of Management, chaired the committee’s COVID-19 working group. According to his presentation of the group’s findings, assessed levels of protection from COVID-19 vaccines against hospitalization, death and long COVID “are based on very low-quality data and analyses,” he said. “That is a major uncertainty we all have to acknowledge.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We feel the vaccines should be prescribed,” he said, adding that the group recommended that state and local authorities should require prescriptions for COVID-19 vaccines. The outcome for that measure was up in the air through the vote itself on Friday, which resulted in a 6-6 tie. Kulldorff cast the deciding “no” vote as the committee’s chair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dozens of medical societies, including the American Medical Association, the American Academy of Pediatrics and the American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists, have touted the safety and efficacy of COVID-19 vaccines and have &lt;a href="https://www.ama-assn.org/public-health/prevention-wellness/open-letter-american-public-respiratory-virus-vaccines"&gt;recommended their use&lt;/a&gt; to prevent severe health outcomes and death linked to the disease. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trade association AHIP, formerly known as America’s Health Insurance Plans, which represents health insurance companies, &lt;a href="https://www.ahip.org/news/press-releases/ahip-statement-on-vaccine-coverage"&gt;issued a statement Tuesday&lt;/a&gt; saying that companies planned to cover vaccines based on recommendations that already were in place as of Sept. 1 until the end of 2026. They did not wait for this week’s ACIP meeting before deciding to extend coverage. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“While health plans continue to operate in an environment shaped by federal and state laws, as well as program and customer requirements, the evidence-based approach to coverage of immunizations will remain consistent,” the group said. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Tom Frieden, former CDC director during the Obama administration, &lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/show/cdc-panel-overhauled-by-rfk-jr-changes-childhood-vaccine-recommendations"&gt;told PBS News Hour’s Ali Rogin&lt;/a&gt; that the insurer association’s decision marked “a huge vote of no confidence” in the vaccine advisory panel’s process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And that’s unfortunate,” Frieden said. “I think, stepping back, you have to look at what this administration, and particularly Secretary Kennedy, is doing, rather than what he is saying. He’s saying he wants to restore trust. He just destroyed trust of the insurers.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even as vaccine uptake rates decline nationwide, physicians and public health experts urged the committee to protect access to vaccines for people who still wanted to acquire that level of protection for themselves and their families. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Low uptake should not limit access to those who want to be vaccinated and reduce their risk for severe outcomes,” said Dr. Robert Hopkins, Jr., medical director of the National Foundation for Infectious Diseases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What actually happens in reality is “hard to say,” said Dr. Sean O’Leary, an American Academy of Pediatrics fellow, who pointed out during a call with reporters that Kennedy’s committee has “sown confusion.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Hepatitis B&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, after hours of deliberation, the committee attempted to vote, then postponed and ultimately tabled a vote that would have delayed dosage of the hepatitis B vaccine for newborns until a month after they are born. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hepatitis B, an infectious disease that weakens the liver and is transmitted through blood and bodily fluids. It often takes months for symptoms to become obvious, heightening the risk of subsequent transmission to others. People who engage in intravenous drug use with shared needles are at higher risk of contracting the disease. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As few as &lt;a href="https://www.hepb.org/what-is-hepatitis-b/what-is-hepb/facts-and-figures/"&gt;1 in 4 people in the U.S.&lt;/a&gt; who are estimated to be sick with hepatitis B are diagnosed, meaning many people are unaware they have been infected. Testing is possible, but stigma often inhibits people from asking for the test or having more candid conversations with their health care providers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because the disease can be passed from a pregnant person to their fetus,  the vaccine for hepatitis B has been available and administered in the United States to newborns within their first hours of life, a practice that has been in place since 1991. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The vote to change the timing of when infants receive the vaccine began to unravel as presentations began. Leading up to the committee’s decision to ultimately table the vote, a feeling of uncertainty persisted among ACIP members who seemed increasingly unconvinced that their vote on hepatitis B vaccines was necessary at this time, given its benefits. The vaccine has been deemed safe and effective in controlling the disease’s spread. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The optimal approach seems to be to have a standard recommendation,” said Dr. Cody Meissner, a committee member. “It’s very hard to identify people who are most likely to be exposed and infected to hep b, such as IV-drug users, sex workers, homeless people. You can’t find them. It’s hard to get them vaccinated.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parents and families “don’t understand the discussion of the subtleties that we’re going through,” said Hibbeln. “If we make a major change in what has been a successful vaccine campaign, we have to have a darn good reason.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Multiple experts asked why the committee was pushing this vote at all and given the vaccine’s  long-running track record of safety and effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I would urge the committee to follow the methodical process of an evidence-based science,” said Dr. Amy Middleman, a professor of pediatrics at the University of Oklahoma’s College of Medicine. “Please, please do that for public confidence and in order to make sure the science is adequately and appropriately vetted.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Experts later praised the decision to table the hepatitis B vote as being the correct choice because of the implications of delaying its administration on newborns, families and public health. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Measles, mumps, rubella and varicella&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also on Thursday, ACIP members voted to remove the option for a combined vaccine that boosts protection against measles, mumps, rubella and varicella (MMRV) for kids under age 4. Instead, the committee voted 8-3 to recommend that toddlers up to age 3 receive an MMR vaccine with a separate dose to protect against varicella, also known as chickenpox. This option already exists and some physicians already recommend it to caregivers.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/watch-live-rfk-jr-s-hand-picked-vaccine-panel-meets-to-consider-covid-shots-and-more"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WATCH:&lt;/strong&gt; RFK Jr.’s hand-picked vaccine panel recommends new restrictions on MMRV vaccines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“HHS will examine all insurance coverage implications following today’s ACIP recommendation, prior to a final decision on adoption” by CDC Acting Director Jim O’Neill, according to a statement issued by HHS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During their discussion, committee members expressed concern about a slightly increased risk of febrile seizures in young children who receive the MMRV vaccine. But O’Leary said these cases are rare and “benign.” He said health care providers had preferred to deliver the combination vaccine “because it’s less pokes for children.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The American Academy of Pediatrics stands by its recommendation to “offer parents the choice,” O’Leary. “Now, what they’ve done is take away the choice for parents” of children under age 4, he said. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The AMA is concerned that this change not only reduces parental choice, but also reflects ACIP’s reliance on selective data in forming its guidance,” said Dr. Sandra Fryhofer with the American Medical Association. &lt;/p&gt;

                                            &lt;div class="inline-invite inline-invite-type__funding inline-invite-style__default"&gt;
        
                    &lt;div class="inline-invite-funding__box"&gt;
                &lt;figure class="invite__logo"&gt;
                    &lt;svg class="svg"&gt;&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#pbs-newshour-horiz-refresh"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
                &lt;/figure&gt;
                &lt;p class="invite_heading"&gt;
                    We're not going anywhere.
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p class="invite_body"&gt;
                    Stand up for truly independent, trusted news that you can count on!
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://give.newshour.org/page/85597/donate/1?ea.tracking.id=nh_july_2025_rescission_article&amp;amp;supporter.appealCode=N2507QW07000AA" class="donation-link ga-click-funding ga-click-ender-funding"&gt;
                    &lt;button class="donate-button"&gt;Donate now&lt;/button&gt;
                    &lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="#000000" class="bi bi-arrow-right-short" version="1.1" id="svg1" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:svg="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;
                    &lt;defs id="defs1"&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;
                    &lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" d="M4 8a.5.5 0 0 1 .5-.5h5.793L8.146 5.354a.5.5 0 1 1 .708-.708l3 3a.5.5 0 0 1 0 .708l-3 3a.5.5 0 0 1-.708-.708L10.293 8.5H4.5A.5.5 0 0 1 4 8z" id="path1"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
                    &lt;/svg&gt;
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;


                                    &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PBS</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:08:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxOZEFNOVB0ZUlOcmlXRndJeDJQQ0pZRkFoSUUyYmRKdTZTaDNkNXBYTUNxOHhUWDRjdWRrSGZJREkzRC1iX0VkLXVITy1MY05FRlFwVXJyVzdEZmdRQml6Wlc0MnRmUjZ1SjFDWjRJb2s4VERLbkZJWDRpcnJjOFhpdG1FekJhZU9RUm5Db0lhV2lxbmo4X2RkRDFzVDRueEtEblZoeTRlRHpjTWwzdGhoUS130gG3AUFVX3lxTE9rVkoxQjNhUmhQZ1J3dnBMUEdXeEFQME5PcWVja0hxRGxFeE4wZndhNHpwZV9FeFBsdFk3Wl9GSTZuaG9YaU9lU2F3aExKUXl6aEZjaTRZU1MxSXdsRjFVaGVOcEVvS3otajYzSjFkbHhfYjZfeG1YMEdKcEU5d2MzQXJkQ2toZk9Pc2ZRMGhaS25MMGg1UWFZMXZVWEtZVEdJX285dWs3QmRoekZ6dzA4dHVCb2szaw</guid></item><item><title>研究：阿司匹林将结直肠癌复发率减半- NewsNation</title><link>https://www.newsnationnow.com/health/aspirin-colorectal-cancer/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>NewsNation</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 23:41:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTFB5UFlyX0JUSzl2eWYyTG9zeC1IOWZCNzhjMFM5d2hnYkEtM3V4R1dyUzVWOVIycXU1ZzZzWlM0MnZtZFlnelhJaXN1bndabTUxSlh2S180RU5fa0pNaENEZFF0N0FPMFc4SU8wckZwV0bSAXZBVV95cUxPdjlwQ3I4M1BwdEtiWXg1Yzl4alI0Y01UZkx2SEM3eFlEZXIwdUowMHJCR0hBV2NubGVwR1l6elRoZEl3R3NpNXdPaUI3eUZRcEhNclhJMjhkM2IyVDNHZVl6WWxyeEhaQS01SnFpR0ZObTRqRnBn</guid></item><item><title>CDC疫苗小组在混乱中推迟了一次投票并推翻了另一次投票-纽约时报</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/19/health/cdc-vaccines-mmrv-hepatitis-b.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 22:15:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxNb1FXYXhpWHR1RkNCMVVJelUyNXd3LVhJTF9idDFDa2VNMkI0VjBSQW1YMU1fdmVXa3lyNlJzcHhrdm5mdE1yMGRLT1VzU2dzUndualMwdWZ3c0ZralRuUF9fYlZHMXE4VjJPa21IS0hpUVd5N1poVlJ0TWpKV2tKczZn</guid></item><item><title>孕妇不应该使用大麻，新的医疗指南说-纽约时报</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/19/health/pregnancy-cannabis-marijuana-guidelines.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 20:15:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxQRlJWTVRhWlY4TEoxMmVRQUhoV2xyTUJKMG1yTTZpNU5hUEhNb0VzSzBPN1liYnVQSEtHcGJ3akhmSVRLNDNwQldrd0U4WWlPbERzaFhrbl9DUkFnSlRvbGFLY3ViNkgxaGNzVEhHTGR2ODhpYURlQXIzODFWMVMwbnd0cXJyUFd5dGZyenpXMA</guid></item><item><title>美国疾病控制与预防中心（ CDC ）顾问投票决定增加新的新冠疫苗规则，以阻止疫苗接种- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/09/19/nx-s1-5545946/cdc-covid-vaccine-acip-recommendations</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-89631" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                ACIP member Retsef Levi points to a slide while speaking during a meeting of the CDC's Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices on September 18, 2025 in Atlanta, Georgia. The federal vaccine advisory group, recently appointed by Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., made recommendations Friday on the COVID vaccine.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Elijah Nouvelage/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Elijah Nouvelage/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;A panel of vaccine advisers to the federal government debated several changes to COVID-19 vaccine access in a chaotic meeting Friday, marked by confusion over processes, technical difficulties and passionate disagreement among members and other experts in attendance.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Ultimately, the committee backed away from its most controversial proposal that called for states to require those who want a COVID-19 vaccine to get a prescription.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The committee voted to recommend vaccination for adults 65 and older and younger people subject to a process called shared decision making. Their recommendations would not prohibit anyone over six months from getting the shot, but they do call for patients to speak with a clinician about the risks and benefits.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;For people 64 and younger the conversation should emphasize that benefits are greatest for people with the most risk of serious disease and lowest for people without increased risk.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The advisers also voted that the CDC should add information about the possible risks and uncertainties related to COVID vaccine effectiveness to information sheets about the shots. Many of the risks were speculative or already known to be unfounded.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;While the CDC generally adopts the recommendations of the panel, the votes are not final until acting CDC director Jim O'Neill signs off on them.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The gathering underscored the turbulent and highly politicized nature of vaccine policy under the leadership of Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., which is now at odds with positions held by major medical organizations.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Over the course of the meeting, many clinicians in attendance raised concerns about how ACIP had sidelined expert input, elevated questionable or preliminary data, and broken from the established process for developing these recommendations, which influence insurance coverage.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's troubling to see the erosion of the committee's integrity," said Dr. Sandra Fryhofer, who spoke on behalf of the American Medical Association on Friday, "We're concerned about how vaccine recommendations are being developed by this new panel, data is being selectively used to justify specific conclusions&lt;em&gt;." &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;The recommendations on COVID-19 come on the heels of Thursday's vote to restrict access to the MMRV vaccine in children under 4, and represent the latest push in Kennedy's ongoing campaign to reshape vaccine policy in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;However, some proposals that would have more dramatically reshaped the vaccine schedule did not make it through. A vote to remove the recommendations that infants get the hepatitis B vaccine at birth failed to pass on Friday morning.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;And the recommendation that a prescription be required for anyone to get a COVID vaccine – which could have been a new hurdle in many places, if states adopted the recommendation – ended in a tie. ACIP chairman Martin Kulldorff voted no, breaking the tie. The motion failed.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;This was the second meeting of the vaccine panel since Kennedy fired &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/06/09/nx-s1-5428533/rfk-jr-vaccine-advisory-committee-acip" target="_blank"&gt;the existing roster&lt;/a&gt;, chosen during the Biden administration, and installed his own choices. Some on the panel have a history of criticizing vaccines, particularly the COVID-19 shots which have been an animating force for many of Kennedy's supporters.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;One member, Retsef Levi, an MIT professor of operations management, drove much of the discussion leading up the votes on COVID-19, which were not shared publicly until Levi presented them at the end of the meeting. Several outside medical groups in attendance requested that the voting topics be shared to have transparency.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In his comments, Levi emphasized safety concerns about the vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"I don't think that the public currently believes the narrative of safe and effective," he told the panel.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There has been considerable confusion around the availability of COVID-19 shots since late August when the Food and Drug Administration only &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/08/27/nx-s1-5515503/fda-covid-vaccines-restricted" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;approved&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the fall boosters for people who are 65 and up, or have high risk medical conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 20:05:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxQU0ZMaGNwYlVnWVlQd2FKYTVGN2p1eHU4YXpXRnhzTmlwZDFTb1VBWmtQTHd3SGdHWThTczVuejM4RkxnZlZ4R1praVZ0UE4wLVg2NXdQRElIZVowU0wtY2l0UldJb0VpQUhHM0NUZkszeVRBV2xZa3JNWnViSHdXdUtVQXNFUUFpSGRjYldfeGJNTHJTZUdRNGtSazBuOWtzYmtQMjd5N01XOWRfbHk0</guid></item><item><title>科学家找到纹身-癌症链接-但这不是您所期望的- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-find-a-tattoo-cancer-link-but-its-not-what-youd-expect-2000661419</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-lg lg:leading-[29px] font-serif max-w-none "&gt;
              
              
              &lt;p&gt;You may have heard lately that tattoos can potentially raise your risk of skin cancer. Recent research might complicate that narrative, however, suggesting that tattoos aren’t as harmful to our skin as assumed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Scientists at the University of Utah led the study, &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/jnci/advance-article/doi/10.1093/jnci/djaf235/8239343?login=false"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; last month in the Journal of the National Cancer Institute. Contrary to their expectations, they found that people who had multiple tattoos actually had a lower associated risk of melanoma. That said, the findings don’t provide conclusive proof that tattoos can prevent skin cancer, the researchers caution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-4 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Further investigation is warranted to clarify these relationships,” they wrote.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;An unexpected finding&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Several recent studies have indicated that tattoos could pose a unique cancer risk. Just this March, for instance, a study of twins living in Denmark &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/tattoos-could-be-a-hidden-cancer-risk-study-of-twins-finds-2000578684"&gt;found&lt;/a&gt; that people with a tattoo had greater odds of being diagnosed with skin cancer (and lymphoma) than their non-inked siblings.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tattoo ink can contain &lt;a href="https://tattoo.iarc.who.int/background/"&gt;potential carcinogens&lt;/a&gt;, such as certain metals, and some researchers have speculated that the ink can agitate our body’s cells in harmful ways, causing inflammation or other changes that fuel cancer formation. By that logic, people with large or multiple tattoos should have a greater risk of skin cancer. And indeed, the Danish study did find that people with a larger tattoo had a higher risk than others.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;With the help of cancer registry data, the researchers behind the new study attempted to survey as many Utah residents as possible who had been diagnosed with melanoma between January 2020 and June 2021, conducting the surveys by phone. All told, they obtained responses from 1,167 melanoma cases. They then compared these cases to controls matched in age, ethnicity, and other factors (this data was collected from a representative survey of Utah residents regularly conducted by the state health department).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As with the earlier Danish study, the researchers expected that the more tattoos someone had, the greater their odds of having skin cancer would be. But to their great surprise, they found otherwise.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;People with two or more tattoos had a lower associated risk of both invasive and localized (also called &lt;em&gt;in situ&lt;/em&gt;) melanoma, the results showed. The most apparent lower risk was seen in people who had four or more tattoos and in people with three or more large tattoos.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;What to think about your tattoos&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The researchers certainly aren’t ready to declare that tattoos will keep people safe from skin cancer just yet.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In their paper, they argue the lower observed risk in people with multiple tattoos is likely a sign of “unmeasured confounding”—meaning they might have failed to control for other important risk factors that could differ between people who get tattooed a lot compared to people who don’t. People who get multiple tattoos may be more vigilant about their skin care in general, for instance, and opt to wear sunscreen or stay out of the sun more often.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The researchers also point out that they still observed a small increased risk of skin cancer associated with only having one tattoo, further muddying the implications of their work.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="s1"&gt;“This isn’t a black and white case of ‘get more tattoos, and you could lower your risk of melanoma,’” said lead study author &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="s1 s3"&gt;Rachel McCarty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="s1"&gt;, a former doctoral student at the University of Utah’s Huntsman Cancer Institute, in a &lt;a href="https://healthcare.utah.edu/huntsmancancerinstitute/press-releases/2025/09/study-finds-melanoma-less-common-individuals-several-tattoos"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; from the institute. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="s1"&gt;“Instead, we need to do more research to understand what we are seeing and if this decreased risk is simply due to behavioral or physical factors, or if there could be beneficial immune responses associated with tattooing which lower melanoma risk.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting at least one other recent study &lt;a href="https://aacrjournals.org/cebp/article-abstract/29/10/2093/124436/Tattoos-and-Hematologic-Malignancies-in-British?redirectedFrom=fulltext"&gt;failed&lt;/a&gt; to find a link between potentially relevant cancers like lymphoma and tattooing. So at least for the time being, the jury is still out on whether people should be concerned about their tattoos and to what extent.&lt;/p&gt;
              
                          &lt;/div&gt;

            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 19:25:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxOanFkSmRrY21OSUZ4NFVYdldrVTdfSzBYSUllZER5ajFiUUtjRVBsb2FHdFJMMWtSc3BpUmRvRGNqWHJLclM5cDJYN2xTRDNnMUJrOGdpWXlCdWRxSUIxMnV2OTNHX2s5NVhuSVJpM2pkcU45RXJFM1ppVW53U1hkM2JfT0FyVFNaa01hZ1lpdkkwWjViNTE5QlFiZHI</guid></item><item><title>路易斯安那州报告在沿海水域发现五例食肉细菌死亡-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/sep/19/louisiana-flesh-eating-bacteria-deaths</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Five people in &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/louisiana" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Louisiana&lt;/a&gt; have died in 2025 from a flesh-eating bacterium found in warm coastal waters, substantially exceeding the annual average on such deaths, state officials have said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Those who had died from contracting Vibrio vulnificus as of Wednesday were among at least 26 to be infected with the bacterium, with each case resulting in hospitalization, according to &lt;a href="https://ldh.la.gov/news/vibrio-seafood-safety" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Louisiana’s department of health&lt;/a&gt;. Most of those cases – 85% – involved wounds being exposed to seawater, and 92% of the infected had one underlying health condition, the health department said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Over the previous decade, &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/louisiana" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Louisiana&lt;/a&gt; has registered an average of 10 Vibrio infections and a single death, state health department officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The higher numbers in Louisiana come after scientific researchers have &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-023-28247-2" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;warned&lt;/a&gt; of evidence that Vibrio infections are becoming more common amid rising sea surface temperatures associated with the climate crisis – which has primarily been spurred by human emissions of greenhouse gases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Vibrio bacteria flourish in warm coastal waters and proliferate between May and October. Infections can result from exposing an open wound to seawater or from consuming seafood that is either raw or undercooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;About one in five people who contract Vibrio vulnificus in particular die – occasionally within two days of feeling sick from the infection. Those who do survive such an infection on occasion require limb amputation or intensive care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The story of one man who grew up in New Orleans, and died after contracting Vibrio vulnificus in July in nearby Bay St Louis, Mississippi, vividly illustrated the dangers of the bacterium to the public in the region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Basil Kennedy, 77, evidently contracted the bacterium after scraping his leg on a boat trailer, his daughter told the Louisiana news station &lt;a href="https://www.fox8live.com/2025/08/12/mississippi-man-with-new-orleans-ties-dead-flesh-eating-bacteria/?fbclid=IwY2xjawMIJmBleHRuA2FlbQIxMABicmlkETFiWHRIU0s4a3JKSzlEVnF4AR4JF8LK9Y54BiehiI1D2POkhtUW-W1YaB6A7tX7tTSHMpz-UqfKNzquUUcBFA_aem_Jlk9wK-fDHfZz4cxZ-24MA" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;WVUE&lt;/a&gt;. Kennedy reportedly cleaned and bandaged the wound, and he avoided getting into the water, thinking nothing more of it. But in about three days, his health sharply declined, and he died, his daughter said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Kay Kennedy Regimbal told the station “there doesn’t need to be fear of the water” despite her father’s death – but she added that “there really needs to be an education and an understanding of how to be prepared for a situation where you may be exposed or there is a potential risk”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Symptoms of Vibrio infection can include gastrointestinal illness, an unusually severe wound or – as associated with bloodstream infection – fever, blistering and dangerously low blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The US usually reports about 150 to 200 cases of Vibrio vulnificus a year. About half of those cases occur in Texas, Louisiana, Mississippi, Alabama and Florida. Louisiana officials said the most cases and deaths have been in their state and Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOOGJoRUk3N0lPam9lUDV4NXdUWEduN0F4ODVuMVc4dGhoak9qeW9Yb1JxN0tjUjBIS2VsLTB2eGZESkJuZUpCUjk0VE1IcVJNWGRFdFNoV3B4SEw2UWhHQTNqSG9haVI3WVViV2RwbERmemF5Tm8yX0VrbkREYzIxOW1BTlhJaWVtVkxhYVRVOA</guid></item><item><title>密歇根州的顶级文档提供新冠肺炎疫苗资格说明- MLive.com</title><link>https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/09/michigans-top-doc-offers-covid-19-vaccine-eligibility-clarification.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GXOI6EIDS5BT3KYL6SAIX2KI2A"&gt;Michigan’s chief medical executive has issued guidance to clear up confusion for vaccine providers and residents alike regarding this year’s COVID-19 booster. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="M4NZWKAIHVH7VLA4X6RGZH5F5Y"&gt;Anyone older than 6 months and without contraindication, who has not yet received the 2025-2026 vaccine, can be considered to have an underlying condition that makes them eligible to be vaccinated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4UH2R5A3J5HB3NGXTRDDAFL76I"&gt;Not being vaccinated in and of itself is an underlying condition, explained Dr. Natasha Bagdasarian, citing studies that found last year’s booster reduced risk of severe illness leading to emergency room visits by 33% and hospitalization risk by 45%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QWRZQJBCZVH43OWFBPCW4ZSIW4"&gt;“National medical organizations and scientific experts continue to recommend routine COVID-19 vaccination for those at high risk, but also recommend vaccines be made available for all those who want them, ages six months and older,” Bagdasarian said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VDCNOUFZ2VHR7AKXIL6HQALKMI"&gt;“As the state’s chief medical executive, it is my duty to protect and promote public health, and everyone deserves the opportunity to access COVID-19 vaccine if they desire one.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="H64CD5XN4RBXZOUMNW2WCZFFQU"&gt;Bagdasarian issued a “&lt;a href="https://links-1.govdelivery.com/CL0/https:%2F%2Fwww.michigan.gov%2Fmdhhs%2F-%2Fmedia%2FProject%2FWebsites%2Fmdhhs%2FCME-Standing-Recommendation-Regarding-2025-COVID-19-Vaccines-FINAL-436pm_09182025.pdf%3Futm_campaign=%26utm_medium=email%26utm_source=govdelivery/1/0100019962494de1-47cbff9c-7d68-4ef1-96f2-f947163035e4-000000/mLX4bn_G0H3VQAxu2OE4ZINzsfAerHgwn9hFw9a5PnY=423" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://nam10.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Flinks-1.govdelivery.com%2FCL0%2Fhttps%3A%252F%252Fwww.michigan.gov%252Fmdhhs%252F-%252Fmedia%252FProject%252FWebsites%252Fmdhhs%252FCME-Standing-Recommendation-Regarding-2025-COVID-19-Vaccines-FINAL-436pm_09182025.pdf%253Futm_campaign%3D%2526utm_medium%3Demail%2526utm_source%3Dgovdelivery%2F1%2F0100019962494de1-47cbff9c-7d68-4ef1-96f2-f947163035e4-000000%2FmLX4bn_G0H3VQAxu2OE4ZINzsfAerHgwn9hFw9a5PnY%3D423&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7Cjhicks3%40mlive.com%7C42522d753d4c45f3731108ddf78547de%7C1fe6294574e64203848fb9b82929f9d4%7C0%7C0%7C638938874327223509%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=VfgYs%2Fnl4aw1jfyHz%2Bqt6im%2BvquOOP44Zh6VoUc71M8%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0"&gt;standing recommendation&lt;/a&gt;” on the vaccine Friday, Sept. 19. It was not a mandate to anyone. Rather, it was meant to offer clarity and support. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YER4LE5CWVBCFJL6LMUAFR5WLE"&gt;“This gives (providers) support to interpret the FDA label and say ‘Yes, you’re at higher risk and we feel comfortable because this is best practice in Michigan as outlined by this standing recommendation,’” she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QF6S6325P5CS3L7GGZYKT7CDWE"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/08/2025-covid-vaccine-eligibility-what-michigan-residents-need-to-know.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/08/2025-covid-vaccine-eligibility-what-michigan-residents-need-to-know.html"&gt;&lt;b&gt;2025 COVID vaccine eligibility: What Michigan residents need to know&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UIT26ASVYZA5NMCSZ4MRLEOWRU"&gt;U.S. Health Secretary Robert Kennedy Jr. said vaccines will remain available for “all patients who choose them after consulting with their doctors.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UPHFZKAAGJHWNBQFZUD6GCIUCY"&gt;However, in late August federal regulators imposed new eligibility restrictions when they approved the latest round of COVID vaccines. They limited shots to people 65 and older or who have health conditions that increase their risk of severe illness from coronavirus infection. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WGYOYRD5NJDWNPJZWBHYDRSEVQ"&gt;Regulators didn’t provide a complete list of underlying conditions and referred to a list from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) which was also not exhaustive. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="N7FDNN6SY5D4ZIPDVKQLIGSREA"&gt;The conflicting federal messages and ambiguous eligibility guidelines created confusion among vaccine providers and those who want to get a booster this fall. That confusion sparked Bagdasarian’s official recommendation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HXEAZPBQGNDUNCNDHHXHDUTDNI"&gt;The Michigan Department of Health and Human Services (MDHHS) continues to support COVID booster shots for anyone older than 6 months, with exceptions for those with a vaccine allergy or condition that prevents them from being vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3HC3TZLZRFGJ5DH2NVOF3VGUOQ"&gt;State guidance aligns with the American Academy of Pediatrics (AAP) and the American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UGD4FJODC5ETLJYSB2NHVGXIEY"&gt;“As we enter respiratory virus season, any barrier to COVID-19 vaccination creates a dangerous vulnerability for children and their families,” said AAP President Dr. Susan Kressly in a statement. “Respiratory illnesses can be especially risky for infants and toddlers, whose airways and lungs are small and still developing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RGGSHZLCTJB5TJRSHGWHW6ROC4"&gt;On Wednesday, Gov. Gretchen Whitmer &lt;a href="https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/09/gov-whitmer-instructs-agencies-to-remove-barriers-to-covid-vaccine-access.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/09/gov-whitmer-instructs-agencies-to-remove-barriers-to-covid-vaccine-access.html"&gt;ordered state agencies to remove barriers&lt;/a&gt; to vaccine access for any resident who wants a shot. That included ensuring all health insurance plans under state regulatory authority cover vaccines, to the extent possible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ITJ5K52HNFH5VCQSQSYJ3DMVPI"&gt;For more information about COVID vaccines, including access, contact your primary care physician or visit &lt;a href="https://www.michigan.gov/coronavirus/resources/covid-19-vaccine" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.michigan.gov/coronavirus/resources/covid-19-vaccine"&gt;Michigan.gov/coronavirus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:YD3VSZSNJFBK5JCBXBEHYRZ3UY" data-fusion-component="YD3VSZSNJFBK5JCBXBEHYRZ3UY"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:YD3VSZSNJFBK5JCBXBEHYRZ3UY" data-fusion-component="YD3VSZSNJFBK5JCBXBEHYRZ3UY"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>MLive.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxNSjZYTnJnWEh0bEVRMlIwZy1OOFZ1UExXN2dxd3FveGJ4QmZGbFVHUDQxX2FPZzhUNEltaThVSlNXakRnZjVNakE5LWpvODVEc0NWY2FuU3J4RWxDLUdiMkpINkFSbG9MczN2V2tTZGFsWWpFU0dkZlNkRUVDQWpRS3h1V3lPU3hVVGdvRW5PT3hUNDIwOURiSlRDNWRJRXpOOTBCb0JUNFJkOWfSAb8BQVVfeXFMTlN1Rjd5X0MxYURSS0FPTTVMc3ZBeVVVdEEtS1ZDMEgzMkVBeEVjazdOQmxpbkRfdi1uWExsWUM1NGYta0ZKbzBVMndrMnBZZk1qQ01uVDhqWTlOZTJiNUVzLXhoaGtMUlNtWjdvZHdkVVlQa3piT0lmUmFqQ1lWYWhsVHJ6RkxpM1k3OFN1dnZCNUNFdEtWT1owZ2JJenYyaGo1SDBpR0xTSjJvdnp3LVQ2X1AyS1lHeU83SVBvZnM</guid></item><item><title>纽约数十人住院治疗的致命肺部疾病现已在1000英里以外的州被发现-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15114971/lung-disease-legionnaires-Iowa-deadly-pneumonia.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A bacterial infection that plagued &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/new_york/index.html" id="mol-7aa01310-9562-11f0-93eb-5da462fdacf7"&gt;New York City&lt;/a&gt; for weeks has traveled nearly 1,000 miles to two more states. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rates of Legionnaires’ disease cases in Marshall County, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/iowa/index.html" id="mol-7a9f28b0-9562-11f0-93eb-5da462fdacf7" class=""&gt;Iowa&lt;/a&gt;, have doubled in about a week, reaching a total tally of 68 cases since a cluster was first announced on Thursday, Sept 4.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Iowa Department of Health officials still do not know the source of the declared outbreak in the county, home to around 40,000 people, and have launched an investigation into its origins. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They are urgently focused on testing 12 cooling towers, large air conditioning units for big buildings, in the north-central part of town, believing these to be the most likely origin of the &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14972215/outbreak-deadly-lung-disease-legionnaires-new-york-city.html"&gt;contaminated aerosolized&lt;/a&gt; water droplets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Legionnaires’ disease is spread &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15039397/new-york-deadly-lung-legionnaires-disease-spread.html"&gt;through aerosolized droplets&lt;/a&gt; containing the bacterium Legionella. Legionella can survive in airborne water droplets for several hours, although this timespan is highly dependent on factors such as relative humidity and the specific bacterial strain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The disease causes &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/pneumonia/index.html" id="mol-7a9abbe0-9562-11f0-93eb-5da462fdacf7"&gt;pneumonia&lt;/a&gt;, a severe lung infection that often begins with a high fever that can rocket past 104 degrees Fahrenheit (40 degrees Celsius). A relentless, dry cough and profound shortness of breath quickly follow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The illness wages a full-body attack, bringing muscle aches, headache and a confused mental state as well as severe gastrointestinal symptoms like nausea, diarrhea, and abdominal pain. In some of the most severe cases, the infection can even lead to coughing up blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sydney Grewell, the county's health department director, said the scale of the outbreak is unlike anything the community or the state has experienced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The recent outbreaks mirror a major incident in Manhattan, where tainted cooling towers sickened 114 people and resulted in seven fatalities throughout Harlem and Morningside Heights&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Earlier this month, it was announced that a deadly outbreak of Legionnaires' disease, which first tore through New York City neighborhoods, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14954791/Legionnaires-disease-death-Michigan-cases.html"&gt;has now spread&lt;/a&gt; to the city's northern suburbs, claiming new lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Health officials in Westchester County announced two fatalities, one in White Plains and another in New Rochelle, and confirmed 35 additional cases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The outbreak echoes a recent crisis in Manhattan, where 114 people were sickened across Harlem and Morningside Heights, leading to seven deaths traced to contaminated cooling towers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the source of the Westchester cluster remains under investigation, Health Commissioner Dr Sherlita Amler pointed to the summer's prolonged stretch of 90-degree days as a key factor, creating the warm, stagnant water conditions in which the lethal Legionella bacteria thrive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Meanwhile, in Michigan, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14954791/Legionnaires-disease-death-Michigan-cases.html"&gt;a deadly outbreak&lt;/a&gt; of Legionnaires' disease at a retirement community claimed the lives of two residents this summer, prompting an urgent investigation by health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The deceased, both residents of Allegria Village in Dearborn, contracted bacterial pneumonia in June and July. While their identities have not been released, officials confirmed they had recently moved into separate units within the continuing care facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Wayne County Health, Human and Veterans Services department is leading the investigation, which is still in its early stages, to determine the source of the contamination and ensure the safety of other residents and staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Up to 18,000 people are hospitalized with Legionnaires’ disease each year in the US, and about one in 10 die. It’s more common between June and October, in part because air conditioners run more than any other time of year and cooling towers are typically the cause of outbreaks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The number of Legionnaires' disease cases in Marshall County, Iowa, has surged to 68, doubling the total in just over a week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Despite launching an investigation, health officials in Iowa have not yet identified the source of the outbreak in the county, which has a population of approximately 40,000 people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Legionella bacteria thrive in warm water. Summer weather creates ideal conditions for it to multiply to dangerous levels in human-made water systems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Iowa health officials have not said how many of the 68 patients in that state have been hospitalized. In Marshall County, one death has been recorded: Father Bernard ‘Bernie’ Charles Grady, 82.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The retired Catholic priest, described by his brother Peter as a ‘remarkable’ and ‘incredible’ man, became the outbreak's first and, so far, only fatality according to &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.siouxlandproud.com/news/iowa-news/legionnaires-cases-in-iowa-community-grow-as-one-family-grieves/"&gt;SiouxLand Proud&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Specialized testing confirmed he had been infected by the bacteria. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;His illness began suddenly with dizziness during dinner on August 22nd. A week later, after suffering from congestive heart failure, he passed away in a Waterloo hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The extremely high fevers associated with Legionnaires' disease drastically increase the body's metabolic rate. This means the heart has to work much harder and faster to deliver oxygen and nutrients to fight the infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Infections are more likely to be severe in seniors, who have weaker immune systems than younger populations.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In severe cases, the bacterial infection can spread to the bloodstream, leading to sepsis, which in turn can cause a dramatic drop in blood pressure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;in Michigan, a deadly outbreak of Legionnaires' disease at a retirement community has claimed the lives of two residents this summer, prompting an urgent investigation by health officials&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To compensate, the heart must pump even more vigorously, which can overwhelm a heart that is already weakened or has pre-existing conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the US, an estimated 250 to 800 people die from Legionnaires' disease each year, based on reported case data, which represents only a fraction of actual cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The symptoms of Legionnaires' disease are indistinguishable from those of many other types of pneumonia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Without a specific reason to suspect Legionella, a doctor will often diagnose and treat it as community-acquired pneumonia, without ever identifying the exact cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Health department director Grewell said: ‘This is something I’ve never experienced. I don’t think this is something that Marshall County has experienced, and I don’t think this is something the state has experienced as well, especially of this magnitude.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘We have seen some trends in the patients that we are seeing, which is why we narrowed the focus to northcentral Marshalltown. Those people have visited the area, traveled to the area, and that’s where our cooling towers are primarily located.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:31:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxOd1FDbHZ5T2d0azFNamJBRkkzZVBOYVhnRjlzby1nYWd3UldRR0pxWlVIRTFpMXpPUXU0VHRNQUFqSDVOZnB6M3p0OEl0c05PbzdaVWxZaktXdmVZdVFETVpOanRpOXUyRl8wRXBLYXBhU3FsQnkzTVczOGJsOGF1dGt5clpEOTB6X0NwbVBoUzRpNm9IZzRWVDh3Rll6a0pEWXBpRkNNUdIBrAFBVV95cUxNWGp6OWxyRmNwWjZLRng5aHBMQjB5YzBYLWhDOVk4LXR5czlVdHVnTndOdDRVU3dHUHJMYTRMS1ducUxVV3VfRjdzRmhyRGw3d09jMHI0bHF0N3hCdmlYT3ZEa2RER3FmdTRrMTdTMXJ0dGxVWkRqbE41R2hTajBnZ1U4RmRtQkdnbVZzUUR1TTZlX1hwQmwzRHV6S0tGaVhscEt6azF1WTg2ZURU</guid></item><item><title>每年对数百万人进行的“过度使用”医学检查使癌症风险增加三倍-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15115371/overused-medical-test-triples-children-cancer-risk-ct-scan.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Radiation exposure from 'overused' medical scans may triple the risk of cancer in children, a government-funded study suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Every year, about 18 percent of Americans, 61million, undergo imaging tests like CT scans, which use radiation to create detailed pictures from inside the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the tests are crucial for detecting injuries, chronic diseases and cancer, repeated scans can cause &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14482065/Over-used-medical-test-given-millions-year-causing-explosion-tumors.html"&gt;small amounts of radiation&lt;/a&gt;, a known carcinogen, to accumulate in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With these risks in mind, researchers in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/california/index.html" id="mol-250d97a0-9577-11f0-a15e-b9099f259218"&gt;California&lt;/a&gt; examined data from nearly four million children in the US and Canada to examine radiation's effect on cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They found about one in 10, adding up to 3,000, cases of blood cancers such as leukemia and lymphoma in children could be attributed to radiation exposure from tests like CT scans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In fact, getting just one or two head CT scans was linked to nearly twice the risk of developing cancer. But as children got more scans over time, they were over three times more likely to be diagnosed than children who didn't have the tests. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers suggest about one in 10 blood cancers in children and teens could be prevented entirely by cutting out unnecessary imaging tests and lowering radiation doses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Using other methods like ultrasound or MRI, they said, could provide a feasible alternative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A new study from researchers in California found regular scans using radiation could increase a child's risk of cancer by 3.5 times (stock image) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Rebecca Smith-Bindman, first study author and radiologist at the University of California San Francisco, said: 'Children are particularly vulnerable to radiation-induced cancer due to their heightened radiosensitivity and longer life expectancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'While medical imaging can be lifesaving, our findings underscore the critical need to carefully evaluate and minimize radiation exposure during pediatric imaging to safeguard children’s long-term health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This involves ensuring that imaging is performed only when it provides essential information for the child’s care and, in cases such as CT scans, using the lowest possible radiation doses.'  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 15,000 children in the US are diagnosed with cancer every year, with the most common form being leukemia, accounting for around 30 percent of US diagnoses per year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Roughly 1,600 American children die of cancer each year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Recent research also shows childhood cancers have &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14267083/doctors-warning-toxic-chemicals-cause-childhood-cancers.html"&gt;increased by about 35 percent&lt;/a&gt; over the last half-century, which experts have suggested could be due not only to better diagnostic tools but also increased environmental exposures like radiation and pollution. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The new study, published Wednesday in the &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2502098"&gt;New England Journal of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, followed a cohort of 3.7million children born between 1996 and 2016 across six US healthcare systems and Ontario, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/canada/index.html" id="mol-151c01a0-9573-11f0-a15e-b9099f259218"&gt;Canada&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The participants were followed from birth until they either: were diagnosed with &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-151990a0-9573-11f0-a15e-b9099f259218"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; or a benign tumor, ended healthcare coverage, turned 21 or until the study's end date of December 31, 2017. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above shows the relative risks for blood cancers in children according to cumulative radiation exposure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Half of the participants were male, and the largest group (43 percent) were born between 1996 and 2004, and 4,916 (0.1 percent) died before the end of the study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Of the participants, 2,961 were diagnosed with blood cancer during the study period. Eight in 10 cases were lymphoma, while leukemia and bone marrow cancer accounted for 15.5 percent. The remainder were rare cancers of the white blood and immune cells. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 58 percent of cancer patients were males, and just over half the cancers were diagnosed in children under five years old.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers found for children who underwent a head CT, about 25 percent of their cancers could be attributed to radiation exposure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Additionally, getting one or two CT scans of the head was associated with a 1.8-fold increased risk of blood cancer, and receiving repeated scans increased the risk 3.5 times. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers wrote: 'In our cohort of children and adolescents, we estimated that medical imaging was associated with 10.1 percent of hematologic cancers.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The risk comes from the unregulated radiation exposure that varies widely machine-to-machine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;CT scans can be life-saving tests, catching disease or bleeding early enough to be treated. They also used to diagnose and monitor diseases like cancer and bone injuries, as well as to assist in surgeries and evaluate efficacy of certain treatments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, experts say they are sometimes overprescribed and performed unnecessarily, potentially because of the money-making opportunities for the hospitals, as the tests are very expensive, or out of doctors' fears of missing a diagnosis and being sued. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above shows the risk of blood cancers after exposure to radiation &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Radiation is a known carcinogen found to damage the DNA molecules within cells, causing them to multiple out of control and form cancer cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It also generates free radicals, toxic molecules that attack DNA and other compounds within cells, and induces inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Radiation from tests like CT scans is easily absorbed by the bones, where it travels to bone marrow and increases the risk of blood and bone marrow cancers.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers urgently urged clinicians to only use scans with radiations when necessary instead for an MRI or ultrasound, neither of which use radiation.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Diana Miglioretti, study author and professor at UC Davis Health and chief of the Division of Biostatistics, said: 'This study provides robust, directly observed evidence of a clear dose-response relationship between radiation from medical imaging and hematologic malignancy risk in children and adolescents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Our findings align with international research highlighting that children are especially radiosensitive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It’s crucial for clinicians to weigh the immediate benefits of imaging against potential long-term health risks and to optimize imaging protocols to minimize radiation exposure.'  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The research was funded by the National Cancer Institute (NCI) and grants from the Ontario Ministry of Health and Long-Term Care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Previous research from Dr Smith-Bindman estimated that more than 100,000 new cancers will have been caused by CT scans from exams done in 2023 alone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The research, published in April, estimated 'CT-associated cancer could eventually account for five percent of all new cancer diagnoses annually.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:22:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxNWE0xay1iVGZoN2xEMnlUQWJ6M3pzcndoNWUzak50cU5xal9jQmtPX3I1Z2RDSk14dUh3eVN4QTR2TGpsbExHTDhuVElPWjdSTTg0ZjhmSHZONExpbXltMmZSMjg2TEs5TVNrZkRNTk1aN3BpS0FheXpPTS0yMmh5elI4OWtadmlEUUZGbkZEYmJQYzRQTEJKaXhHMmZXenJZR0M1RkV3bnpCMmUyZUhoOG5qWnVWZ9IBuwFBVV95cUxNYUUxdHQ4dUtoQlhkWlJIS0EtWEdPaFNueEdCRFpKeXRQVmMtNk9VSnNfSHFXVXdHNFl1cDdnWGpoRXJVRXpVNU45S25rLVlZdE5GOFlXWTVHQjNOYkQ2U0xpNEoySUM2RV95YkN6Zlc2dG9pT2JVRHBBQ29hNDVZZ2NuUktkM0dtWHFNd2hNUnNMX1l3eGg2Mk1RY1hMRDdNVnRCMFNmSmJQeXlPakVRWmJiN2N1V0p4OTlz</guid></item><item><title>新的研究表明，这种夜间习惯可能会增加您的痴呆风险- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/dementia-risk-habit-study-11813296</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new study in &lt;em&gt;Neurology&lt;/em&gt; links chronic insomnia with a 40% higher risk of later cognitive impairment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;People with insomnia who also slept less than usual, were more likely to have markers tied to memory problems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Starting a nightly routine and advice from a health care professional can help with quality sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Sleepless nights aren’t just exhausting—they may carry implications for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/worst-habits-for-brain-health-11773249" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;long-term brain health&lt;/a&gt;. While many of us experience occasional rough patches, chronic insomnia has been increasingly connected to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/everyday-habits-hurting-your-memory-11804198" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;memory and thinking changes&lt;/a&gt; as we age. Now, new research published in &lt;em&gt;Neurology&lt;/em&gt;, the medical journal of the American Academy of Neurology, adds weight to that concern: older adults with chronic insomnia had a 40% higher risk of developing cognitive impairment (a category that includes MCI and dementia) during follow-up.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; What’s especially notable is that the investigators also looked inside the brain. Among people with insomnia who reported sleeping less than usual, imaging at baseline revealed more white matter changes (often a sign of small blood-vessel stress in the brain) and higher amyloid burden (a protein that can accumulate in Alzheimer’s disease). Together, the clinical and imaging findings help explain why &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/exercise-sleep-insomnia-risk-new-study-8628457" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;persistent sleep problems&lt;/a&gt; might track with later cognitive issues.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-was-this-study-conducted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Was This Study Conducted? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Researchers drew on data from the long-running Mayo Clinic Study of Aging, which follows older adults over time. They compared participants with and without chronic insomnia and tracked annual cognitive testing alongside brain imaging. Cognitive outcomes included global cognitive scores and diagnostic status (normal, MCI or dementia). 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Imaging focused on white matter hyperintensities (WMH) on MRI. White matter hyperintensities are bright spots linked with small-vessel changes. The imaging also included amyloid-PET, which visualizes amyloid accumulation. The team used established statistical models to estimate both the risk of developing cognitive impairment and how cognition and imaging markers changed over time, while adjusting for many health and lifestyle factors.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-did-the-study-find"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What Did the Study Find? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In this study, chronic insomnia was linked to a 40% higher risk of developing cognitive impairment over the study period. Second, among those with insomnia who also slept less than their usual amount, baseline testing and scans painted a less favorable brain-health picture—poorer cognitive performance, more WMH and higher amyloid at the outset. Importantly, insomnia was not tied to faster accumulation of WMH or amyloid across follow-up. In plain terms: having insomnia, particularly with less sleep, was linked to greater risk. It wasn’t linked to a faster pace of brain damage later on.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To help interpret the magnitude, the authors note this elevated risk is meaningful—large enough to deserve attention—yet still observational. The study cannot prove that treating insomnia would prevent cognitive impairment; other factors may contribute despite careful adjustments.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This study has some notable limitations. Insomnia was identified from medical records rather than overnight sleep studies. Changes in sleep duration were self-reported and not always measured at the same time as the insomnia diagnosis. And because participants are from a single region, the results might not be generalizable to everyone.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-does-this-apply-to-real-life"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Does This Apply to Real Life? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re wrestling with ongoing sleep trouble, there’s a lot you can do, starting tonight. Anchor a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/i-tried-a-doctor-recommended-sleep-routine-for-2-weeks-8763725" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;consistent wake-up time&lt;/a&gt; every day (weekends included) to steady your body clock. Build a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/things-women-over-50-should-do-before-bed-11757559" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;wind-down routine&lt;/a&gt; 30 to 60 minutes before bed: dim the lights, step away from email and doomscrolling and switch to quiet, low-stimulation activities. Get bright outdoor light soon after waking and keep evening light low to reinforce your natural rhythm.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Protect your sleep by reserving the bed for sleep and sex. If you're awake and frustrated for about 20 minutes, get up and do something calm in dim light until you feel sleepy again. Cut off caffeine by early afternoon, and avoid alcohol for three to four hours before bed. Daily movement, like walking, helps build healthy sleep pressure and brief stress-management practices (slow breathing, progressive muscle relaxation, a short mindfulness session) can reduce nighttime arousal.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For chronic insomnia, ask a health care provider about cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia. If you snore, wake up gasping or feel excessively sleepy in the day, consider getting screened for obstructive sleep apnea. Talk to a health care professional if your sleep problems persist for three months or more, if you routinely sleep less than six or seven hours despite your best efforts or if sleepiness makes driving unsafe.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A large study in &lt;em&gt;Neurology&lt;/em&gt; reports that chronic insomnia is associated with a 40% higher risk of developing cognitive impairment, and that people with insomnia who also slept less than usual showed more white matter changes and higher amyloid at baseline. While the research doesn’t prove causation, it’s a clear nudge to take &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/habits-that-can-disturb-your-sleep-8551851" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;persistent sleep problems seriously&lt;/a&gt;. Prioritize a consistent routine, smart light exposure, movement and talk with a health care professional if insomnia sticks around.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:14:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibkFVX3lxTE5ubWY2OGhPcncwbnRwTTV5VWc3Q1VRaE80Yk9RV0Zqcnh4ZXMwVUFDaHA2ck1LaVdFbDBlUXFXUzMteDkyd1BZMm9LRjQ0NTM2alBlNTJHMko1S0ZpLUFvWDlqbUMzMnpYRlJIZnpB</guid></item><item><title>您需要了解的关于美国“接吻虫”病的所有信息- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/19/health/video/gupta-kissing-bug-chagas-endemic-us-digvid</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="video-resource__details--leaf"&gt;
                    &lt;p data-editable="headline" class="video-resource__headline inline-placeholder"&gt;Everything you need to know about ‘kissing bug’ disease in the US
                &lt;/p&gt;
                        &lt;p class="video-resource__showlink"&gt;
                              
                        &lt;/p&gt;
                              

                        
                        &lt;div data-editable="description" class="video-resource__description inline-placeholder"&gt;&lt;p&gt; Experts say “Kissing bugs” are now endemic in the US and spreading Chagas. CNN’s Dr. Sanjay Gupta walks us through how the disease is diagnosed and treated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                    
                &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:29:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOSWpGRnNEdm1SZjNzRlM3V3l5bThFTnduajlVcjFCbEV3OUhZSTdEckdZcGtHVDhSR3VXdHYxYmFUQ3NDXzJqc3BCSE9UdDg0d2ZOZ0czblpGZ2N3cS1CUVFYNTIxRHVQTFIzTjN2SDhiV2ZjV0czLUl3RHhqazFrRDJ2QkZfQ1g2d1N3eXEzbw</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心疫苗顾问决定不推迟婴儿乙型肝炎疫苗注射的更改- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/rfk-jr-cdc-vaccine-panel-hep-b-babies-data-rcna232394</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f65185" class="body-graf"&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is not expected to change recommendations for hepatitis B vaccines in newborns, after its panel of advisers tabled Friday a much-awaited vote on the issue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-386654" class="body-graf"&gt;The panel had been expected to recommend delaying the use of the vaccine in babies, currently administered shortly after birth, but some members expressed frustration over a lack of evidence about side effects and said more discussion was needed. One member also said the voting language wasn’t clear and could lead to confusing guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0e1c88" class="body-graf"&gt;The unorthodox decision follows a chaotic, unconventional voting process for the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP), whose 12 members were all appointed under Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. in the last few months. Many have expressed skepticism about the safety and efficacy of vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-db5bab" class="body-graf"&gt;The members were due to vote Friday on whether to delay the first dose of the hepatitis B vaccine until a child is at least 1 month old, provided the mother tests negative for the virus. Currently, the first dose is given within 24 hours of birth because hepatitis B — an incurable infection that can lead to liver disease, cancer and death — can be transmitted from mother to child during delivery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-258047" class="body-graf"&gt;The hepatitis B vaccine has become a target of Republican legislators, including Rand Paul of Kentucky, who question the medical necessity of protecting newborns if their mothers have tested negative for the virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bccfe3" class="body-graf"&gt;ACIP member Dr. Robert Malone said Thursday that the committee took up the subject because “a significant population” in the U.S. has concerns about vaccine policy, including giving the hepatitis B vaccine at birth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5d513e" class="body-graf"&gt;However, many public health experts questioned the need for a vote without new data to analyze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-27e0cd" class="body-graf"&gt;Minutes before tabling the subject, the ACIP voted unanimously to recommend testing all pregnant women for hepatitis B. A spokesperson for the Department of Health and Human Services said the test is covered across insurance programs and the goal of the vote was to encourage providers and health systems to increase testing rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-776e8d" class="body-graf"&gt;At the meeting on Thursday, CDC staffers &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://www.cdc.gov/acip/downloads/slides-2025-09-18-19/02-langer-hep-b-508.pdf__;!!PIZeeW5wscynRQ!oU4Q9e_38wyod3qsCKl_7D82SjN7OstS2ldBmu3EqyV-o31SM2XBkZiE0YK48MAU2QrYje_19WDXlAWPDKUJwPrXjHrd$" target="_blank"&gt;summarized the results of 17 studies&lt;/a&gt;, which found that the hepatitis B vaccine is overwhelmingly safe and has helped to virtually eliminate hepatitis B infections among newborns. The agency also noted that many pregnant women aren’t screened for hepatitis B in the U.S., making it hard to rely on testing to decide which children to vaccinate. According to the CDC, 12-16% of pregnant women in the U.S. are never tested for hepatitis B during pregnancy — and even if they are, some cases can be missed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3cafe7" class="body-graf"&gt;Several ACIP members pushed back on what they said were omissions in the CDC’s presentations, pointing to individual studies and anecdotes that they said raised questions about neuro-developmental side effects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e064ba" class="body-graf"&gt;Two committee members, Malone and Vicky Pebsworth — both of whom have a history of sharing misinformation about vaccines — said the CDC presentations omitted a &lt;a href="https://nap.nationalacademies.org/read/13164/chapter/10" target="_blank"&gt;2012 report from the Institute of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;. The report said it couldn’t determine whether hepatitis B vaccines were associated with brain inflammation because no studies had properly looked at that research question. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c60234" class="body-graf"&gt;“The absence of data that statistically proves lack of safety does not mean that the product is safe,” Malone said on Friday morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7afc72" class="body-graf"&gt;Pebsworth also raised concerns about CDC data showing irritability or fussiness in some infants who received the hepatitis B vaccine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f59d79" class="body-graf"&gt;“These are not trivial reactions,” Pebsworth said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-cd9b05" class="body-graf"&gt;However, such symptoms are hard to attribute to vaccines because infants can be irritable or fussy regardless of vaccination. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f1ec3e" class="body-graf"&gt;Dr. Cody Meissner, a pediatrician and the only current ACIP member who has previously served on the committee, pushed back on Pebsworth’s concern, noting that irritability or restlessness “are certainly not objective parameters that should be used to assess safety.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f81574" class="body-graf"&gt;He added that no vaccine is 100% safe or effective, but that the committee was meant to decide whether protection from vaccines outweighs any possible risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a2cb0b" class="body-graf"&gt;“When you apply that to a newborn hepatitis B vaccine, I don’t think there’s any question whatsoever that the benefit far outweighs any adverse side effect,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4e4e0a" class="body-graf"&gt;Cases of acute hepatitis B infections among children plummeted after the CDC &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/preview/mmwrhtml/mm5730a3.htm" target="_blank"&gt;began recommending a universal dose&lt;/a&gt; at birth in 1991. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-896a09" class="body-graf"&gt;It's unclear whether ACIP will revisit the subject in the future. If they do, liaisons from the National Foundation for Infectious Diseases, the American College of Physicians and the Society for Adolescent Health and Medicine called on the committee to return to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/media/pdfs/2024/09/ACIP-Evidence-to-Recommendations-Framework-cdc.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;a framework for vaccine recommendations&lt;/a&gt; that has long guided the advisory panel's decisions. The framework considers a vaccine's risk and benefits, whether a recommendation is feasible and how it would impact health equity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3bbc2a" class="body-graf"&gt;Dr. Amy Middleman, a liaison for the Society for Adolescent Health and Medicine, said it's easy to be distracted by conflicting studies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-86845c" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“I would urge the committee to use the methodical, scientific method to weigh the risks and benefits appropriately,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:06:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxQN2J1QU1MSGIzX0o2TWRjQWFFcnBETE9FQ2k0ZmZsWHppeFhPM1J4OUdPTTRBV3YtcWh4akxfNThpM2J2Z3RSZG84a0M5RHRBRzl2Wl9feFByX2M2djhZZUQ1cnRqelhFYjJLNEpGNkRqX1Nzd0lDSm5QMjlfSHFUd2RrYmVQMVljNVhOSjZWdHVYU05RZmVQX0FOcUXSAVZBVV95cUxQNnpaeGFKeFhxLW5aNjd1Q3JHUnA4V0hoM1RFeEU5NTE0dm95dEV4UVJVdUk5QVRDUTRTWHpwYlhDWXRwX05EQzk0Njlsc3Z3Q0QtOEZpZw</guid></item><item><title>观看直播：疾控中心咨询小组讨论COVID-19疫苗风险，与外部专家就流程进行争论- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/cdc-vaccine-advisory-panel-covid-19-hepatitis-b-vaccines/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-update__bodytext"&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;After the tabled hep B vote, some liaison members from top medical organizations shared their agreement for holding off on making changes to the current recommendations. Some also urged more transparency in how decisions will be made on future potential recommendation changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I would urge the committee to use the methodical scientific method to weigh the risks and benefits appropriately," said Dr. Amy Middleman, a liaison for the Society for Adolescent Health and Medicine. She added, "This is important for all vaccine decisions, and this is what I think some of us are really concerned about in terms of the absence of it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ACIP member Retsef Levi said he appreciated the desire to keep scientific methods but took issue with the liaison member's comments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have to say that one thing that puzzles me is that many of the speakers that push for the scientific approach are speaking very confidently in the absence of the gold standard evidence of robust long-term clinical trials against placebo," Levi added, who has been pushing for more research beyond what the CDC has presented during the meetings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When ACIP chair Kulldorff began to move on from the hep B discussion, Dr. Jason Goldman, president of the American College of Physicians, chimed in asking for more explanation and to call out the committee for muting him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That is disrespectful. You want debate and discussion, but you're muting people and silencing them," Goldman said. "Please provide to the public so they can have trust, faith and confidence in vaccination as to what process we are going to be using to properly vet and discuss all future vaccines. … Tell the public how you are going to be analyzing all of these vaccine decisions so we can have confidence in this committee."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kulldorff responded that he previously responded to that comment already before moving on to the next agenda matter.&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/div&gt;
            
            

          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:23:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxQREsycTlXTG5mU0VGcmc3cHE5cjhldDFQTXlaTUFKMExBSl8tb1lDVmVYSnRXa0VoRF96WDRqbVp2ZEFCOXI3TFkxOFdTOThMYXE3WGl1Q0tERkxYckZMTXhfSHBreU1lSTNLb0RlY3F0ZjZfdnNYSE9lX0lYcUl0TXhYQ0o3VmcwTTlOLTVmT1VXbmlTMldXWHRB0gGfAUFVX3lxTE1mWjNOZ3I4MTFjdGFVSzF4dFl2QUx5ZW05NEd2RGEzUjJOQXVCMktJYnVUbW92N09sUGFUMzNWWWtaNDBUUWRjVXM1V3J5N01pd294QnpSNWVRRmt6MWc4ZDl3VGR6Q1EwRHRXQzRHbXE4UEQyVWw4MWRJcE56a3VJbUtXMzEwdjFrcUdOU1JhV0RHb0hxX1padkZJSGR4aw</guid></item><item><title>8有助于减少多余腹部脂肪的家庭锻炼-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/fitness/8-home-exercise-that-help-reduce-excess-belly-fat/photostory/124000375.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belly fat is a&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/belly-fat-linked-with-higher-heart-disease-risk-2018072614354"&gt; serious health concern&lt;/a&gt; and can lead to the risk of heart disease, type 2 diabetes and metabolic disorders. The good news is, some simple exercises, when incorporated with a healthy diet and consistency, can significantly lead to a leaner and healthier body. &lt;br&gt;Excess belly fat is associated with serious health issues, including the dangerous visceral fat. A study conducted by Harvard University explains how visceral fat is strongly linked with a higher risk of heart disease. The good thing is, studies have concluded exercising can significantly reduce belly fat. A recent study conducted in the US found that &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29127602/"&gt;high-intensity interval training &lt;/a&gt;significantly reduces total fat mass, abdominal fat and visceral fat mass. &lt;br&gt;Visceral fat is metabolically active and tends to respond faster to lifestyle changes. Below are suggested 8 home exercises that are supported by scientific studies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3AFBVV95cUxQZE4xbzBMVEJOM2tZblRjOWRiUnRVbFgwazF0MWI5Rm5acTRDbzczbGtnMWgzWDItNzRjdko2SW4yU2h2VGJrdmtnbDVvZnh4a25yQTNoQkRRTnp2ZzROa1p0aW9VSWhXQnFOLXZFRWZVS1dQTWZSc3hROUJfWEhRejFkOV9kaDVQRmV2TEtrN3NDYjQ4SEV0dlFRZlBGYld3WTZKeGNhRVl4RzdyQ2lEYjZGd3BPZ1FISDZqeUlodkxCSGZZWWhWTmd0c0poY1BaWWswYTczZjFzX3Ru0gHkAUFVX3lxTFA3eUpWSTZRUjlvNjNHazNsMUNkWF93dWwxQ1BpakN4cVp1Unl4dlVjcVdJWHExMVVRRHJPZTE4T0U5bzI1Y2FVY0NXZVN5TjdQVGFUOURyeS1pNkYwWDA3NFpGbWxfV2I2SGR5QVc1MWRqY2VGVmtMb2I4akNRQWRGU3FVbDF6SnZxU0tsYnlBZUhFc0w3VU96TzRIdWhqeC1jVlJzMjFwNE5NbVZ6YUZjcDh5UGhPcTdEelRZdGstQ1JQVXJZTFBYbVhHY0lpcUFaOC1fVkdReUdnR3EycXQyNDIwUw</guid></item><item><title>与小鼠阿尔茨海默病症状恶化相关的微塑料- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-linked-to-worsening-alzheimers-symptoms-in-mice</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;If you're already genetically predisposed to  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="174203" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease, consuming microplastics could trigger cognitive decline, according to a new study in mice from researchers at the University of Rhode Island.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers wanted to see how microplastics might interact with &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-diet-can-lower-genetic-risk-for-alzheimers-scientists-discover"&gt;genetic Alzheimer's risk&lt;/a&gt; to make brain dysfunction more likely – a combination of both the genes we're born with and the environment we live in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two groups of mice were used, one with the APOE4 gene variant that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-figure-out-how-an-alzheimer-s-disease-risk-gene-actually-does-its-damage"&gt;increases Alzheimer's risk&lt;/a&gt;, and one with the APOE3 variant that doesn't affect risk. In each group, some of the mice had microplastics added to their drinking water, and some didn't.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/unexpected-link-between-menthol-and-alzheimers-found-in-mice"&gt;Unexpected Link Between Menthol And Alzheimer's Found in Mice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There are modifiable factors we're studying related to Alzheimer's – diet, exercise,  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-are-vitamins-and-do-we-really-need-to-take-them" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73116" data-postid="174203" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;vitamins&lt;/a&gt;, and especially environmental toxins like microplastics," &lt;a href="https://www.uri.edu/news/2025/09/uri-study-links-microplastic-exposure-to-alzheimers-disease-in-mice/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; neuroscientist Jaime Ross.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you carry the APOE4, and you happen to consume a lot of microplastics, will this contribute to Alzheimer's disease?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using tests designed to measure cognition, the researchers found that mice with APOE4 that consumed microplastics did begin showing signs of cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mice with the APOE3 gene, and APOE4 mice that hadn't been &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-seem-to-be-in-every-kind-of-animal-except-one"&gt;exposed to microplastics&lt;/a&gt;, behaved normally, suggesting that the combination of genetic risk and microplastics was driving the changes in the animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intriguingly, the researchers noted sex differences in affected mice. The male APOE4 mice given microplastics showed signs of cognitive decline through apathetic behavior, while the female APOE4 mice given microplastics seemed to have &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-name-new-type-of-memory-loss-often-mistaken-for-alzheimers"&gt;impaired memories&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This actually matches what we see in humans with Alzheimer's: men with the disease often show &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/geriatrics8040075"&gt;signs of apathy&lt;/a&gt;, while women often experience &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s00415-022-11541-w"&gt;issues with memory&lt;/a&gt;. That makes the microplastics link worth investigating further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When you expose animals that are carrying the largest known risk factor in humans for developing Alzheimer's disease to micro and nanoplastics, lo and behold, their behavior changes in a sex-dependent manner similar to the sex-dependent differences we see with Alzheimer's patients," &lt;a href="https://www.uri.edu/news/2025/09/uri-study-links-microplastic-exposure-to-alzheimers-disease-in-mice/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Ross.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_174207" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-174207" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/MouseDiagram.jpg" alt="Mouse experiment" class="wp-image-174207 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/MouseDiagram.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/MouseDiagram-600x271.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-174207" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The researchers looked at the influence of genes and microplastic exposure on mice. (Gaspar, et al., &lt;em&gt;Environ. Res. Commun.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also found that some signs of inflammation in the APOE4 microplastics mice matched what would be &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/brain-autopsies-reveal-a-potential-culprit-behind-alzheimers"&gt;expected from Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;. The mice didn't develop the disease itself, but did show some changes associated with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While a single APOE4 gene does raise the risk of Alzheimer's in people &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-gene-doesnt-guarantee-dementia-heres-what-you-can-do-to-reduce-risk"&gt;quite considerably&lt;/a&gt;, it's still not a guarantee of the disease developing – many people with this genetic risk don't get Alzheimer's. That points to other factors being involved too, and scientists are making progress in understanding what those factors are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on these study results, it seems as though exposure to plastic pollution could be one of these additional factors. We know microplastics can potentially &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-are-infiltrating-your-brain-what-are-the-effects"&gt;get into the brain&lt;/a&gt;, but it's still not clear exactly how harmful this exposure could be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As is often the case with Alzheimer's, it's tricky to work out &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-may-start-at-the-brains-borders-scientists-discover"&gt;which brain alterations&lt;/a&gt; might be happening as a result of the disease, and which might be driving it in the first place. While this study only involved mice, it could be significant that Alzheimer's-like changes were seen in a short period of time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's interesting that what we're seeing in mice is similar to what we're seeing in the real world," &lt;a href="https://www.uri.edu/news/2025/09/uri-study-links-microplastic-exposure-to-alzheimers-disease-in-mice/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Ross.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We want to encourage further research into the scourge of micro and nanoplastics."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1088/2515-7620/adf8ae"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Environmental Research Communications&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:01:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQTXNseFZMNGM1OHBtMXl5UzUwUmt2YUVOR3FvdUtxZUlCQ3R0eTRmc2g2RnQxdlVzaF84bmhrLVM1LTVSYnRvWlF5YTY1LWZ1anR1aV8zNktBWFNfVExVOTl4YlIzZlZVUmVsR1BXRVpQY3RWajVIZVYwVWh5Vjc4S2xoREhleVhpSzhJeU1pem01bUl5</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr.的反疫苗小组意识到它不知道自己在做什么，跳过投票- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/health/2025/09/rfk-jr-s-anti-vaccine-panel-realizes-it-has-no-idea-what-its-doing-skips-vote/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
          
          
&lt;p&gt;He summed up the discussion succinctly: "The only thing that we're discussing here is if there's some benefit or removal of harm that comes from waiting a month. And I have not seen any data that says that there is any benefit to the infant of waiting a month, but there are a number of potential harms to the infant of waiting a month."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Panel member Robert Malone, who has falsely claimed that COVID-19 vaccines cause a form of AIDS, explained that the proposed change for the hep B vaccination was not due to any safety concern or evidence-based reason, but about trust among parents who have been exposed to vaccine misinformation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The signal that is prompting this is not one of safety, it is one of trust," Malone said yesterday. "It is one of parents uncomfortable with this medical procedure being performed at birth in a rather unilateral fashion without significant informed consent at a time in particular when there has been a loss of trust in the public health enterprise and vaccines in general."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Dashed decisions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the questions and uncertainties of the proposed recommendation and the data behind it dogged the committee again this morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This morning, the voting language was put on a slide and immediately drew criticism. The language was:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a mother tests [hepatitis B]-negative:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The first dose of the Hepatitis B vaccine is not given until the child is at least one month old.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Infants may receive a dose of Hepatitis B vaccine before one month according to individual based decision-making. *&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Also referred to as shared clinical decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hibbeln, the psychiatrist, again pushed back, this time noting that the language of the change is confusing. "You can't say don't give it and then give an opportunity to give it," he said, arguing that shared clinical decision-making is, essentially, all or nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discussion quickly spiraled, with another member questioning whether there was any data presented at all on the proposed recommendation. There was a fast motion to table the vote indefinitely, and the motion to table passed in a speedy vote of 11–1, with the ACIP chair, Martin Kulldorff, being the only holdout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the rest of the day, the panel is discussing COVID-19 vaccines. Stay tuned.&lt;/p&gt;


          
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                  
          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 14:54:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxNb0pmMGNKSm04RzBuVXdCSWJQYVYxT0JCalFyQkJpeHhVQjgyRWFTZl81QTNsa0RUQlVSS1ptQlNHWG9JMTh1emlZYzVZNF94c25sTzBMa2xzMjNqeURMWURTdzhNa1I3NXRxU3NhUEVjSklCS3JTbzBkVDJkS1QtS2Q5dUhtakNrNl91V3JLYTByZnVQVWFMSzhCeldHeXBiZHFnX0JNUHdLckFyc1F4bXRBYmhOUHc1</guid></item><item><title>胰腺癌的突破，因为专家发现关键的生活方式因素与致命疾病有关-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15110035/pancreatic-cancer-oral-bacteria-gum-disease.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Harmful bacteria and fungi living in your mouth could triple your risk of developing pancreatic &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-a1f245d0-955a-11f0-88b6-e3beff13fbc8" class=""&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;, a study has suggested. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts have long believed that people with poor oral hygiene are more vulnerable to a host of diseases—including cancer—than those with healthier mouths. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But now scientists from NYU School of Medicine, have discovered which bacteria could increase the risk, theorising that the harmful bugs originating in the mouth can be carried by saliva into the pancreas. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Writing in the journal &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaoncology/fullarticle/2839132"&gt;JAMA Oncology&lt;/a&gt;, Dr Richard Hayes, expert in population health and study co-author, said: 'It is clearer than ever that brushing and flossing your teeth may not only help prevent periodontal disease but may also protect against cancer.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The oral microbiome—the community of bacteria and fungi that live in the mouth—is increasingly being studied for its potential role in disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the current study, researchers found for the first time that a type of yeast called candida—which naturally lives on the skin and throughout the body—may play a role in pancreatic cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the largest study of its kind, researchers examined data from two ongoing investigations tracking 900 American participants to better understand how lifestyle factors, such as smoking, and medical history are involved in cancer development. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At the beginning of the study, participants—from the American Cancer Society Cancer Prevention Study II and the Prostate, Lung Colorectal and Ovarian Cancer Screening Trial—rinsed with mouthwash and provided saliva samples. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Yixuan Meng, PhD, study lead author, said: 'Our findings provide new insight into the relationship between the oral microbiome and pancreatic cancer.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers then followed the participants for around nine years to record any presence of cancerous tumours. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers then compared the bacterial and fungal DNA from saliva samples of 445 pancreatic cancer patients to that of another 445 randomly selected cancer-free participants. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After accounting for confounding factors known to increase the risk of the disease, such as smoking, age and race, the researchers identified 24 species of bacteria and fungi that either increased or slashed pancreatic cancer risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another three bacteria linked to the cancer were already known to cause a nasty gum infection that can eat away at the jawbone and soft tissue surrounding the teeth, known as periodontal disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Altogether, the entire group of harmful microbes increased the risk of developing the cancer by more than threefold. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;By assessing the makeup of each participant's oral microbiome, the researchers were able to develop a tool that could estimate individual cancer risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Professor Jiyoung Ahn, study co-author, said: 'By profiling bacterial and fungal populations in the mouth, oncologists may be able to flag those most in need of pancreatic cancer screening.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, the researchers emphasised that at this point, their findings cannot confirm a direct cause-and-effect link, but rather a correlation between cancer risk and certain microbes in the mouth. &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pancreatic cancer remains one of the least survivable forms of the disease and worryingly its on the rise. Source for data: Cancer Research UK &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They now plan to explore whether oral viruses—like oral thrush—could contribute to cancer and how the mouth's microbiome could affect a patient's' prognosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Pancreatic cancer—dubbed a 'silent killer' due to its subtle symptoms—kills just over 10,000 patients every year, about one death every hour. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And by 2040, cases are expected to hit record highs with 201,000 cases of the deadly cancer expected to be diagnosed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Pancreatic cancer is typically caught at late stages, as warring signs are easily mistaken for other problems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When spotted early, before it has spread throughout the body, around half of patients will survive at least a year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But if the cancer has already spread beyond the organ—as happens for the majority of patients—only one in 10 patients will survive. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While pancreatic cancer is most likely to strike people over the age 75—younger groups can also get the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Last year the Daily Mail highlighted a '&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-13033795/Huge-spike-cancer-sparks-alarm-experts-baffled.html"&gt;frightening&lt;/a&gt;' explosion of young women developing the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rates of pancreatic cancer have soared by up to 200 per cent in women under the age of 25 since the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Whilst numbers remain low, oncologists cannot explain the surge in young women, with no such spike noted in men of the same age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Overall, incidences of the disease have increased by around 17 per cent in Britain over the same timespan, with soaring obesity rates and environmental factors suspected to be behind the trend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Potential symptoms of pancreatic cancer include jaundice, where the whites of the eyes and skin turn a yellow hue, alongside itchy skin and darker urine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other possible signs include loss of appetite, unintended weight loss, constipation or bloating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While these symptoms are unlikely to be cancer it is important that they are checked out by a GP early just in case, especially if people have had them for over four weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The pancreas is a tadpole-shaped organ that forms part of the digestive system and also performs a crucial role in hormone regulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is located just behind the stomach and is about 25cm in length.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In its digestive role, it helps produce enzymes that help the body break down food into the nutrients it needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Charity, Cancer Research UK, estimates 22 per cent of cases of the disease are caused by smoking, known to increase the likelihood of gum disease, and 12 per cent by obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 14:41:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxNelhHZEdCUWdEWUNZNzZtNjBrUWZzWHdwYTdUWUVyMzViQU9lR2ZUODJRbHRLMmlkaU9fRi1UN0RDMkNLMVZCbXB5UGJsMUtCaFBpWnpWZkM4MjRtS2d6T0ZQT09zckdjNFU3S3Z0ZmpJVTFoOGNJZTg2T0k4YjVYbW1YOTBjUDA3amlXOWpxTDY2TnVXSlp4UEtOdjFENFp1cEE</guid></item><item><title>密歇根州首席医疗官Natasha Bagdasarian博士就COVID-19疫苗提出长期建议-密歇根州（ .gov ）</title><link>https://www.michigan.gov/mdhhs/inside-mdhhs/newsroom/2025/09/19/standing-rec</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="news-item__section-content"&gt;
                            &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Determines not receiving a dose of COVID-19 vaccine to be an underlying condition&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            &lt;p&gt;LANSING, Mich. - In response to &lt;a href="https://content.govdelivery.com/attachments/MIEOG/2025/09/17/file_attachments/3390509/ED%202025-7%20Access%20to%20COVID-19%20Vaccines.pdf" class="off-domain-link"&gt;Gov. Gretchen Whitmer’s Executive Directive&lt;/a&gt; to state agencies to ensure Michigan families can access COVID-19 vaccines, the state’s Chief Medical Executive Dr. Natasha Bagdasarian has issued a &lt;a href="https://www.michigan.gov/mdhhs/-/media/Project/Websites/mdhhs/CME-Standing-Recommendation-Regarding-2025-COVID-19-Vaccines-FINAL-436pm_09182025.pdf"&gt;Standing Recommendation&lt;/a&gt; for the COVID-19 vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;
                            &lt;p&gt;“National medical organizations and scientific experts continue to recommend routine COVID-19 vaccination for those at high risk, but also recommend vaccines be made available for all those who want them, ages six months and older,” said Bagdasarian. “COVID-19 vaccines have been proven to reduce the likelihood of emergency department or urgent care visits, as well as hospitalizations and severe outcomes. They are one of our best defenses against the virus. As the state’s chief medical executive, it is my duty to protect and promote public health, and everyone deserves the opportunity to access COVID-19 vaccine if they desire one. This Standing Recommendation will help to protect vaccine accessibility and availability in our state.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            &lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, Aug. 27, the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) approved the 2025-2026 vaccine for those 65 years of age and older and those ages 5 through 64 years with at least one underlying condition that puts them at high risk for severe outcomes from COVID-19. However, the FDA did not define the list of underlying conditions. The &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/covid/hcp/clinical-care/underlying-conditions.html" class="off-domain-link"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention’s list&lt;/a&gt; includes conditions such as obesity and physical inactivity and states it is “not exhaustive” and “should not be used to exclude people with underlying conditions from recommended measures for prevention or treatment of COVID-19.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            &lt;p&gt;In her recommendation, Bagdasarian stated, “Any person over the age of six months without contraindication who has not received a dose of a Food and Drug Administration (FDA)-approved or -authorized 2025-2026 COVID-19 vaccine may be considered to have an underlying condition that puts them at high risk for severe outcomes from COVID-19 and is thus eligible to receive an age-appropriate dose.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            &lt;p&gt;The Michigan Department of Health and Human Services (MDHHS) continues to recommend the COVID-19 vaccine in alignment with the &lt;a href="https://publications.aap.org/pediatrics/article/150/3/e2022058700/188297/COVID-19-Vaccines-in-Infants-Children-and?_gl=1*1btcx64*_ga*MjA2NTMzODkyNC4xNzUyODUyNjUz*_ga_FD9D3XZVQQ*czE3NTMzNjk5MzgkbzIkZzAkdDE3NTMzNjk5MzgkajYwJGwwJGgw*_gcl_au*MTI5NDQyMjA2LjE3NTI4NTI2NTI.*_ga_GMZCQS1K47*czE3NTMzNjk5MzkkbzIkZzAkdDE3NTMzNjk5MzkkajYwJGwwJGgw?autologincheck=redirected" class="off-domain-link"&gt;American Academy of Pediatrics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aafp.org/family-physician/patient-care/public-health-emergencies/recent-outbreaks/covid-19/covid-19-vaccine.html" class="off-domain-link"&gt;the American Academy of Family Physicians&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://www.acog.org/womens-health/videos/get-your-recommended-covid-19-vaccine-during-pregnancy" class="off-domain-link"&gt;American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists. &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
                            &lt;p&gt;To help ensure insurance coverage and availability of COVID-19 vaccines as outlined in the Executive Directive, MDHHS is working with the Department of Insurance and Financial Services and the Michigan Department of Licensing and Regulatory Affairs.&lt;/p&gt;
                            &lt;p&gt;To learn more about COVID-19 and seasonal respiratory illnesses and how to protect yourself, visit &lt;a href="https://www.michigan.gov/mdhhs/keep-mi-healthy/chronicdiseases/seasonal-respiratory-viruses" class="off-domain-link"&gt;Michigan.gov/COVIDFluRSV&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;
                            &lt;p&gt;# # #&lt;/p&gt;
                            &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
                            &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>State of Michigan (.gov)</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 14:24:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxOZ01Eek5FeHduUW9zLXpxbXYxZGxsWkJYSzJOWEJDSmlQanhIeWd1RFNyVFBqZDJCODJhS1pUbW9zOU9fWnQ4MVFXVVBuQ0JsakZ2bGxrLUZBR2kyRGEwMm1fcUVLLU83anpxYnpFTTF1SENvS3I4TWd2SFNWWVE1dHBB</guid></item><item><title>肯尼迪的疫苗小组投票推迟乙型肝炎投票- Politico</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2025/09/19/kennedys-vaccine-panel-votes-to-throw-out-the-hepatitis-b-universal-birth-dose-vaccine-recommendation-00572740</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Politico</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 14:13:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5gFBVV95cUxNbGhmb0JxRDlWSEt2Q1JoX3RmdlJ3V2EycUNaYmpUZTdYUlU5cm5MQmpjbl9tVWlMRHhYTmRBd2pMY2xzelMxSkRrVkc2NTFtVzFYU0JVb3pwSHk5d1Z4QUY5MGVpQ3VTaGpROGxXT2hkeUN1QmEybEZKVFpkMkV6cUpfYk9Cc2ZSRWtRc1NEYmJrRnJhY3pCWk5kbXJFWWxWYnRxVXpxYUZablVFVl9FNGFqZm5PdXVtcWhOTHpJSlpSTkJZMWN2WUJKN1V6US15MDd3ZWFFN01KdHRBYi1WZVgtMDRQUQ</guid></item><item><title>它被认为是“女性的状况。“不应该。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/technology/2025/09/pcos-symptoms-men-children-weight-gain-baldness.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="21" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmfpwlf77000w3b79gzxnlquw@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://slate.com/theslatest?utm_source=slate&amp;amp;utm_medium=article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=article_plain_text_topper"&gt;Sign up for the Slatest&lt;/a&gt; to get the most insightful analysis, criticism, and advice out there, delivered to your inbox daily.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="86" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmfpwl4le003hqgkvga57xg5i@published"&gt;Look up polycystic ovary syndrome, or PCOS, and every definition you find will state that the hormonal disorder manifests in women and people with ovaries of reproductive age. There’s much that scientists still don’t know about PCOS, including how to cure it. But if you &lt;em&gt;do &lt;/em&gt;know one thing about the condition, I’d guess that it’s the fact that it occurs in women. Unfortunately for the rest of the spectrum of ages and genders, there’s more to the story. PCOS can affect men and children, too.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="95" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmfpwv1um001u3b79l61qcyju@published"&gt;PCOS is a hormonal condition that affects roughly &lt;a href="https://womenshealth.gov/a-z-topics/polycystic-ovary-syndrome"&gt;1 in 10 women&lt;/a&gt; between the ages of puberty and menopause. It’s marked by an imbalance of reproductive hormones: Women with PCOS often have elevated androgens, the sex hormone responsible for&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;“masculine” traits&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;like excess body hair, acne, and male-pattern hair loss. The hormonal imbalance then disrupts ovulation. Despite its name, women diagnosed with PCOS don’t always have ovarian cysts. But some symptoms are highly suggestive of PCOS, including irregular or missed periods, excessive hair growth on the face and body, acne, weight gain, and difficulty conceiving.&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="72" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmfpwv1un001v3b799mnm8k85@published"&gt;Some researchers are &lt;a href="https://answers.childrenshospital.org/rethinking-polycystic-ovary-syndrome/"&gt;studying&lt;/a&gt; the emerging understanding that PCOS isn’t just a women’s condition, but a metabolic disorder affecting people of all genders—and one that could be detected as early as childhood.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;“For decades, we’ve seen that first-degree male relatives of women with PCOS are also affected,” says Jia Zhu, a pediatric endocrinologist at Boston Children’s Hospital. There are broader metabolic mechanisms at play that aren’t limited to ovarian function, Zhu says.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="78" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmfpwv1un001w3b79wm0xrlwf@published"&gt;While people without ovaries can’t technically be diagnosed with PCOS, research shows they can inherit the same genes that cause PCOS in women, leading to what scientists call the “male equivalent of PCOS.” When men inherit these PCOS genes, they don’t develop reproductive problems like their female relatives would. Instead, they may have &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2666379123001490?via%3Dihub"&gt;metabolic problems&lt;/a&gt; like obesity and insulin resistance, which increase their risk of diabetes and heart disease. Early male-pattern baldness is also associated with PCOS genes.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="54" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmfpwv1un001x3b79rz4aizfy@published"&gt;Given how common obesity, diabetes, and heart disease are, how can physicians be sure these metabolic problems in men are related to PCOS genetics? It’s all about specific patterns (like early baldness &lt;em&gt;and &lt;/em&gt;metabolic dysfunction) and not isolated symptoms. And there’s one particular genetic research tool, the polygenic risk score, which proves especially helpful.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="80" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmfpwv1un001y3b79cte94ibr@published"&gt;The risk score helps physicians&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;understand how PCOS genetics work in both women and men. It measures how much a person is inherently prone to a disease based on the combined effect of multiple genes, considering hundreds or thousands of tiny differences across the entire length of a person’s genetic material. In their &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8947237/"&gt;2021 study&lt;/a&gt;, Zhu and her team observed a 9 percent increase in the odds of obesity in men for every meaningful increase in the polygenic risk score.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="92" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmfpwv1uo001z3b79tj83rogq@published"&gt;Research also shows that the condition is less age-dependent than previously thought. Children who have a mother, sister, or other close relative affected by PCOS can develop symptoms themselves, Zhu says. “The clinical risk factor is the early development of pubic or [armpit] hair growth before the age of 8 in girls,” she explains. Boys who have genetic exposure to PCOS tend to reach puberty at an earlier age as well. Kids of all genders with higher polygenic risk scores have been shown to have &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37690116/"&gt;higher body mass index and increased fat mass&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="74" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmfpwv1uo00203b79mpqtnpu3@published"&gt;For now, no standardized approach exists for diagnosing or treating the PCOS equivalent in men and children. Though PCOS is a lifelong disorder with noticeable symptoms, clear-cut diagnosis can only be made in women of reproductive age who have irregular cycles and high androgen levels, says Andrea Dunaif, an endocrinologist at Mount Sinai. “We don’t have really good contrasting traits to make a diagnosis in anybody other than women of reproductive age,” Dunaif notes.&lt;/p&gt;

  



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="52" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmfpwv1up00213b79mzdnogs3@published"&gt;Without available tests, Dunaif says parents whose children may have genetic exposure to PCOS should monitor them closely for symptoms, especially rapid weight gain. Obesity can make the other metabolic and reproductive symptoms of PCOS worse, Dunaif says, and it’s more effective to prevent weight gain than to treat high body weight.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="51" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmfpwv1up00223b79idizrj58@published"&gt;Zhu hopes we won’t have to rely on that type of symptom-spotting for long. “My ultimate goal is to be able to identify children who have genetic predisposition to PCOS and provide targeted and personalized counseling, and potentially even provide therapeutic options that can be tailored to their genetics,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="57" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmfpwv1up00233b79q1jhxm3k@published"&gt;There might come a day when the definition of PCOS will be unrecognizable from today’s ovary-centric view. What we now call a women’s reproductive disorder may be reframed as a metabolic condition that affects entire families, with treatments guided by genetics and not just gender. Until then, at least people with ovaries aren’t in the fight &lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;alone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="The Slatest" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmfpwl4le003kqgkvmu8gij64@published"&gt;


    &lt;div class="newsletter-signup__intro newsletter-signup__intro--centered"&gt;
          &lt;img alt="" class="newsletter-signup__img" hidden data-src-light="https://dot.cdnslate.com/static/media/components/newsletter-signup/the-slatest.49f353b.png" data-src-dark="https://dot.cdnslate.com/static/media/components/newsletter-signup/the-slatest-dark.ca73d21.png"&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Get the best of news and politics&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Sign up for Slate's evening newsletter.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxONDNzX1FTdmhzclhMWDNzQkNYd25ZT1RLLVdBaGdhc1E0SG5UR05qUFRrY1J6UndMZ0lGTGU5VTRSWFU1dU92V0ZXVEF1Z0FFT2FsMFVkQWlHbUQ1bTZVdW02c2xJTjNaV3hyZllPZk85UXd0dDJnOHVuTzVqTFQ3TGVnT044ZVVSWWJHeE8tZExMYVU</guid></item><item><title>在混乱的开始会议中， CDC疫苗顾问推迟了乙型肝炎疫苗的投票，投下了新的MMRV疫苗投票- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/19/health/cdc-acip-hepatitis-mmrv-covid-vaccine</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/action-bar/instances/cmfqut05t003w26p759ome792@published" data-label-id-prefix="action-bar-start-of-article" class="action-bar" data-dynamic-breakpoint-placement='{"extraLarge":{"placement":".layout-article-elevate__left"}}' data-expand-conditions='{"follow":{"extraLarge":{"alwaysExpand":true}},"shareOptions":{"large":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"medium":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"extraLarge":{"withAction":"follow","maxNumOfActions":2}}}'&gt;
    &lt;p class="action-bar__overlay"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet" tabindex="-1"&gt;
        
            &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet--action" data-title="follow"&gt;
                

  
&lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/follow-topics-bar/instances/cmfqut05t004026p72rug4o6j@published" data-unauth-redirect="/account/register/follow" data-embed-max-topics="" class="follow-topics-bar follow-topics-bar_overlay follow-topics-bar--hide"&gt;
    &lt;div class="follow-topics-bar_overlay__inner"&gt;
        &lt;p class="follow-topics-bar_overlay__scroll-wrapper" tabindex="-1"&gt;
                  &lt;button data-unselectable="true" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/chip/instances/cmfqut05t004126p7bzus91v3@published" class="chip follow-topics-chip " data-component-variation="follow-topics-chip" data-component-name="chip" data-zjs="click" data-enable-interstitial="true" data-override-success="" data-label="Vaccines" data-id="617c0361-7001-4fd9-87cb-f147c812ab03" data-reset-on-log-out="true"&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__label"&gt;Vaccines&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__icon"&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--check"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--add"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/button&gt;

                  &lt;button data-unselectable="true" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/chip/instances/cmfqut05t004126p7bzus91v3@published" class="chip follow-topics-chip " data-component-variation="follow-topics-chip" data-component-name="chip" data-zjs="click" data-enable-interstitial="true" data-override-success="" data-label="Federal agencies" data-id="874fe3a3-ab02-4ed7-8d3b-417b95049613" data-reset-on-log-out="true"&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__label"&gt;Federal agencies&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__icon"&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--check"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--add"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/button&gt;

                  &lt;button data-unselectable="true" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/chip/instances/cmfqut05t004126p7bzus91v3@published" class="chip follow-topics-chip " data-component-variation="follow-topics-chip" data-component-name="chip" data-zjs="click" data-enable-interstitial="true" data-override-success="" data-label="New in medicine" data-id="24c5535c-fbd9-44e1-874d-d8ff9577aaa4" data-reset-on-log-out="true"&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__label"&gt;New in medicine&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__icon"&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--check"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--add"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/button&gt;

                  &lt;button data-unselectable="true" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/chip/instances/cmfqut05t004126p7bzus91v3@published" class="chip follow-topics-chip " data-component-variation="follow-topics-chip" data-component-name="chip" data-zjs="click" data-enable-interstitial="true" data-override-success="" data-label="Children's health" data-id="87ea547e-9c19-45e7-9908-15728272141c" data-reset-on-log-out="true"&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__label"&gt;Children's health&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__icon"&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--check"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--add"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/button&gt;

        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p class="follow-topics-bar_overlay__fade follow-topics-bar_overlay__fade--hide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;a class="follow-topics-bar_overlay__explore-more-link" href="/follow"&gt;
            See all topics&lt;svg class="icon-ui-caret-right" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M17.218 11.522c.28.261.28.685 0 .946L7.2 21.794c-.242.225-.632.28-.91.093a.613.613 0 01-.088-.975l9.579-8.917-9.538-8.878c-.242-.225-.3-.589-.1-.847a.721.721 0 011.048-.082l10.027 9.334z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

          &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet--action" data-title="share options"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/social-share/instances/cmfqut05t003z26p7alnw5y66@published" class="social-share_labelled-list"&gt;
    &lt;div class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links vossi-social-share_labelled-list" data-type="share-links"&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.facebook.com/dialog/share?app_id=80401312489&amp;amp;href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F19%2Fhealth%2Fcdc-acip-hepatitis-mmrv-covid-vaccine&amp;amp;display=popup" data-type="facebook" aria-label="share with facebook" title="Share with Facebook"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-facebook-circle" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.04139 1.33301C11.7458 1.33301 14.7488 4.33601 14.7488 8.04042C14.7488 11.3884 12.296 14.1632 9.08943 14.6663V9.97928H10.6523L10.9497 8.04042H9.08943V6.78225C9.08943 6.25182 9.34934 5.73475 10.1825 5.73475H11.0283V4.08409C11.0283 4.08409 10.2607 3.95309 9.52685 3.95309C7.99476 3.95309 6.99336 4.88165 6.99336 6.56269V8.04042H5.29031V9.97928H6.99336V14.6663C3.78677 14.1632 1.33398 11.3882 1.33398 8.04042C1.33398 4.33601 4.33699 1.33301 8.04139 1.33301Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Facebook&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F19%2Fhealth%2Fcdc-acip-hepatitis-mmrv-covid-vaccine" data-type="x" aria-label="share with x" title="Share with X"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-x-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.99386 8.11503L0 0.666992H4.74756L8.44753 5.27039L12.4004 0.687719H15.0151L9.71175 6.84331L16 14.667H11.2666L7.2603 9.6887L2.98317 14.6532H0.354296L5.99386 8.11503ZM11.9565 13.287L2.91105 2.04698H4.0571L13.0912 13.287H11.9565Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Tweet&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;a class="social-share_labelled-list__share" href="mailto:?subject=CNN%20content%20share&amp;amp;body=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A%0Ahttps%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F19%2Fhealth%2Fcdc-acip-hepatitis-mmrv-covid-vaccine" data-type="email" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="share with email" title="Share with email"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-email-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 24 24" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M2 6C2 4.89543 2.89543 4 4 4H20C21.1046 4 22 4.89543 22 6V18C22 19.1046 21.1046 20 20 20H4C2.89543 20 2 19.1046 2 18V6ZM4 6H20V9.11604L12 11.9396L4 9.11604V6ZM4 11.237V18H20V11.237L12.3328 13.943C12.1174 14.019 11.8825 14.019 11.6672 13.943L4 11.237Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Email&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/19/health/cdc-acip-hepatitis-mmrv-covid-vaccine" data-type="copy" aria-label="copy link to clipboard" title="Copy link to clipboard"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-hyperlink" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.64373 10.3574C5.38338 10.0971 5.38338 9.67496 5.64373 9.41461L9.88637 5.17197C10.1467 4.91162 10.5688 4.91162 10.8292 5.17197C11.0895 5.43232 11.0895 5.85443 10.8292 6.11478L6.58654 10.3574C6.32619 10.6178 5.90408 10.6178 5.64373 10.3574Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M4.22952 8.94321L5.64373 7.52899C5.90408 7.26865 5.90408 6.84654 5.64373 6.58619C5.38338 6.32584 4.96127 6.32584 4.70092 6.58619L3.28671 8.0004C1.98496 9.30215 1.98496 11.4127 3.28671 12.7144C4.58846 14.0162 6.69901 14.0162 8.00075 12.7144L9.41497 11.3002C9.67532 11.0399 9.67532 10.6178 9.41497 10.3574C9.15462 10.0971 8.73251 10.0971 8.47216 10.3574L7.05795 11.7716C6.2769 12.5527 5.01057 12.5527 4.22952 11.7716C3.44847 10.9906 3.44847 9.72426 4.22952 8.94321Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.94356 4.22916L7.52935 5.64338C7.269 5.90373 6.84689 5.90373 6.58654 5.64338C6.32619 5.38303 6.32619 4.96092 6.58654 4.70057L8.00075 3.28635C9.3025 1.98461 11.4131 1.98461 12.7148 3.28635C14.0165 4.5881 14.0165 6.69865 12.7148 8.0004L11.3006 9.41461C11.0402 9.67496 10.6181 9.67496 10.3578 9.41461C10.0974 9.15426 10.0974 8.73215 10.3578 8.4718L11.772 7.05759C12.553 6.27654 12.553 5.01021 11.772 4.22916C10.9909 3.44812 9.72461 3.44811 8.94356 4.22916Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Link&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__open" data-type="open" aria-label="open social share" title="Open social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-share-os" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19 12c.394 0 .714.32.714.714v8.572c0 .394-.32.714-.714.714H4.714A.715.715 0 014 21.286v-8.572a.715.715 0 011.429 0v7.857h12.857v-7.857c0-.394.32-.714.714-.714zm-7.664-9.79a.73.73 0 011.024 0l.076.075 4.916 4.854c.183.18.27.449.188.69a.734.734 0 01-1.216.314L12.57 4.5v11.786c0 .357-.357.714-.714.714s-.714-.359-.714-.714V4.5L7.372 8.143a.73.73 0 01-1.102-.091c-.21-.289-.149-.694.106-.946l4.884-4.821z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__close" data-type="close" aria-label="close social share" title="Close social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-close" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19.787 18.758l-6.792-6.781 6.746-6.735a.728.728 0 00-1.028-1.03l-6.747 6.737-6.711-6.7a.728.728 0 00-1.028 1.03l6.71 6.698-6.723 6.712a.727.727 0 101.027 1.03l6.725-6.714 6.793 6.782a.725.725 0 001.028 0 .727.727 0 000-1.03"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfqut05t003y26p7gi94hn5z@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Vaccine advisers to the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention voted 11-1 to delay a vote on changes to a newborn hepatitis B shot. It was a surprise twist after a lengthy discussion on the hepatitis B vaccine typically delivered to newborns shortly after birth.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfquz52a00093b6q58dg3aic@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The committee had planned to consider a new recommendation that would wait to give newborns a dose of the hepatitis B vaccine until they are at least a month old. Currently, babies are given this shot at birth, usually before they leave the hospital.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfquz52a000a3b6q1sejok4r@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The birth dose of hepatitis B vaccine has been recommended in the United States since 1991. After it was implemented, hepatitis B infections in infants dropped from an average of 18,000 per year to around 20 reported cases of hepatitis B in babies per year now. Children infected with hepatitis B nearly always develop longterm infections which can damage the liver, increasing the risk for liver scarring, transplant and cancer.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfquz52a000b3b6qti091qup@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            After an abrupt and confusing end to Thursday’s meeting, vaccine advisers also cast new votes on Friday on the combined measles, mumps, rubella and chickenpox vaccine in the Vaccines for Children program. ACIP members voted Thursday to recommend against using the combined measles, mumps, rubella and varicella vaccine for young children. The new vote on Friday brought the Vaccines for Children program in line with that new recommendation. Nine voted in favor and three members abstained.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfquz52a000c3b6q2xe34tqu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The advisory group’s recommendation isn’t final. HHS said in a statement Thursday that it “will examine all insurance coverage implications following today’s ACIP recommendation, prior to a final decision on adoption by the Acting Director.” Kennedy deputy Jim O’Neill is serving as acting CDC director after Dr. Susan Monarez was ousted abruptly as head of the agency last month.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfquz52a000d3b6qezxtgvbp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Jason Goldman, president of the American College of Physicians and a non-voting ACIP liaison member, told the members on Friday he was concerned about the conflicting MMRV votes case on Thursday, which would have created different recommendations for people of lower socioeconomic levels.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfquz52a000e3b6qwsiiing4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It suggests, Goldman said, that the second vote “actually revealed the truth that you do not have the data or evidence to challenge the current standing and that there is that there is no associated harm.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfqut3mv00003b6qx9wsj3qu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;em&gt;This is a breaking news story and will be updated.&lt;/em&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:18:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQMEoyQl9IeUVNOGxqLXk2Z3dsb3FWcWlDakVrd1NWekszS0tJVnBmTjh3bm5wMUhpaEw2RFFEMUxXNHRXbDNJclZVQ2pad0J0V2lMR2xkT1NTUGwwRUZXM2JIZ0x1cXRRLU5LUUQybXBlTGJsb3paYW03bnBPY1EtTg</guid></item><item><title>令人震惊的常见损伤与痴呆风险增加有关- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/shockingly-common-injury-linked-with-increased-dementia-risk</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Older adults who experience injurious falls are more likely to develop dementia within a year of their accident compared to people of the same age who have other kinds of physical injuries, according to a large study published in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings from a team of researchers in the US do not prove falls contribute to dementia (although this can't yet be ruled out either), but they do suggest that falls could be an early indicator of deteriorating brain conditions that lead to  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="174879" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease and&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-isnt-the-only-form-of-dementia-an-expert-explains-the-differences"&gt; other dementias&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below for a summary of their research:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is possible that falls serve as a sentinel event that marks a future risk for dementia,"&lt;a href="https://www.doi.org/10.1001/jamanetworkopen.2024.36606"&gt; explain&lt;/a&gt; physician Alexander Ordoobadi from Brigham and Women's Hospital and colleagues in their paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This study's findings suggest support for the implementation of cognitive screening in older adults who experience an injurious fall."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/an-early-signal-of-dementia-could-be-hidden-in-how-we-read-faces"&gt;An Early Signal of Dementia Could Be Hidden in How We Read Faces&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Falls are the&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.15585/mmwr.mm6927a5"&gt; most common way&lt;/a&gt; adults over 65 are injured. Nearly one-third of this age group experiences injury from a fall each year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One of the biggest challenges we face is the lack of ownership in the process of follow-up screening for cognitive impairment," Ordoobadi&lt;a href="https://www.brighamandwomens.org/about-bwh/newsroom/press-releases-detail?id=4814"&gt; says.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Because there may not be adequate time for these screenings in an emergency department or trauma center setting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each year,&lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/dementia"&gt; almost 10 million new cases of dementia&lt;/a&gt; are diagnosed, leaving more of us to confront frightening cognitive decline either personally or in our loved ones.&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newly-identified-proteins-may-explain-devastating-effects-of-alzheimers"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newly-identified-proteins-may-explain-devastating-effects-of-alzheimers"&gt;Despite decades of &lt;/a&gt;effort, we're still&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/brain-waves-can-be-manipulated-while-we-dream-and-it-could-help-treat-dementia"&gt; without a cure,&lt;/a&gt; leaving patients only with&lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/article/S0140-6736(20)30367-6/fulltext"&gt; strategies to stall&lt;/a&gt; the debilitating conditions' progression, so the earlier dementia can be identified, the better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ordoobadi and team analyzed a year's worth of US Medicare claims from those who had experienced a traumatic injury. They identified 2 ,453 ,655 patients over the age of 65 who sought medical assistance for an injury in 2014 or 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_149075" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-149075" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/SupportWorkerNurseHelpsSeniorManIntoWheelchairDementiaAlzheimers642.jpg" alt="Nurse helps senior man into wheelchair" class="size-full wp-image-149075" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/SupportWorkerNurseHelpsSeniorManIntoWheelchairDementiaAlzheimers642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/SupportWorkerNurseHelpsSeniorManIntoWheelchairDementiaAlzheimers642-592x415.jpg 592w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/SupportWorkerNurseHelpsSeniorManIntoWheelchairDementiaAlzheimers642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-149075" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Falls could be an early indicator of deteriorating brain conditions that lead to Alzheimer's disease and other dementias. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAC5vszdMNw/"&gt;Kzenon/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;After excluding people with known dementia diagnoses, the researchers then compared patients that had injured themselves in a fall with those who had experienced other types of physical injuries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They found older adults who experience injury from a fall were over 20 percent more likely to develop dementia within a year of their accident, compared to the other sorts of physical injuries the patients attended a medical clinic for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_149074" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-149074" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/DementiaFallsGraph.jpg" alt="A graph comparing cumulative incidence of dementia to days from injury" class="size-full wp-image-149074" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/DementiaFallsGraph.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/DementiaFallsGraph-600x291.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-149074" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Cumulative incidence curve of dementia diagnoses after a fall. New diagnoses occurred gradually over the course of the year, although there was an initial sharp increase in new diagnoses in the first 1 to 2 weeks after the injurious fall. (Ordoobadi et al., &lt;em&gt;JAMA&lt;/em&gt;, 2024)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The relationship between falls and dementia appears to be a two-way street,"&lt;a href="https://www.brighamandwomens.org/about-bwh/newsroom/press-releases-detail?id=4814"&gt; says&lt;/a&gt; injury epidemiologist Molly Jarman from Brigham and Women's Hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Cognitive decline can increase the likelihood of falls, but trauma from those falls may also accelerate dementia's progression and make a diagnosis more likely down the line."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This study can only determine if one factor follows the same pattern as another, so it can't tell if falls and dementia are directly related. Due to a lack of prescription data, the researchers could not account for medication effects, which may have skewed their results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However,&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1093/ageing/afs012"&gt; previous studies&lt;/a&gt; have found people with known cognitive impairments are at increased risk of experiencing falls, also supporting the idea that falls may be an early indicator of these devastating brain conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other potential earlier warning signs of the cognitive impairments that lead to dementia include&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-vision-can-predict-dementia-12-years-before-diagnosis-study-shows"&gt; loss of visual sensitivity&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/these-15-factors-are-linked-to-early-dementia-risk-a-major-study-found"&gt; poor mental &lt;/a&gt;health, and&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/an-early-warning-sign-of-dementia-risk-may-be-keeping-you-up-at-night-says-study"&gt; increased nightmares&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But cognitive declines can be an indication of&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/up-to-13-of-dementia-cases-may-be-a-misdiagnosed-treatable-condition"&gt; other treatable conditions too&lt;/a&gt;, so it is critical that potential dementia patients are thoroughly assessed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our study highlights the opportunity to intervene early,"&lt;a href="https://www.brighamandwomens.org/about-bwh/newsroom/press-releases-detail?id=4814"&gt; says&lt;/a&gt; Jarman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If we can establish that falls serve as early indicators of dementia, we could identify other precursors and early events that we could intervene on, which would significantly improve our approach to managing cognitive health in older adults."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research was published in&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.doi.org/10.1001/jamanetworkopen.2024.36606"&gt; JAMA&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in October 2024&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:01:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxQbXpNZC1KUmRMNGpwYzMwSWZtR1h1TkkzT0RMemNGU1RMeGhMMUI0OUFGclh3V0g3Wkg2b1lHVDgwWWdhNFdxb0hRVmRWN1BTTHZQZmVEU0x5Y2V4WU9HYkFDSndhWFF4M0JmSlZValZGNFRSdGltLU44bXBxdElpT3AyMzdYWHZ3R20zNWZ4Vkg5SG8</guid></item><item><title>我将普通感冒症状归咎于压力……但当我的学生强迫我去看医生时，他们挽救了我的生命-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15114505/blamed-cold-symptoms-stress-students-saved-life-forced-doctor.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A teacher who blamed her chest soreness and coughing on stress and a recent move has her students to thank for saving her life after they urged her to go to the doctor. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Aurora Lucas, 32, from &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/chicago/index.html" id="mol-922f6850-9553-11f0-929d-f5972bed8a75"&gt;Chicago&lt;/a&gt;, said she first started experiencing chest pain while she was moving houses in August 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lucas tried to brush-off the symptoms in an attempt to avoid paying $250 for a doctor's appointment. However, when her symptoms didn't subside, she visited a doctor in September who Lucas said told her she 'looked good' and sent her home to 'drink hot water and honey.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She continued to have chest pain and was feeling very tired, which she continued to blame on moving and the stress of working a busy teaching schedule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But while teaching, Lucas said she 'couldn't finish her sentences without coughing'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her students and colleagues encouraged her to return to the doctors and, after her symptoms worsened, Lucas went to the emergency department on several occasions between September and November 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Eventually, Lucas couldn't walk because she was coughing so much and after months of back and forth, was referred for a PET scan for detailed medical imaging at the end of November.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One month later, Lucas was &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14695689/colon-cancers-doctors-alarmed-rise-sharply-young-people.html"&gt;diagnosed with stage three lung cancer&lt;/a&gt; after scans revealed she had three lime-sized tumors in her lungs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Aurora Lucas had just moved houses when her symptoms of chest soreness and coughing began&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;In December 2021, after months of doctors and hospital visits, she was diagnosed with stage 3 lung cancer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lucas said: 'I hit a big milestone in August 2021. I bought my first home and instead of celebrating, I was feeling very fatigued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'That's when the first chest pain showed up and I thought it was because the whole process was so stressful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I even called my sister who's a nurse and she thought maybe it was anxiety.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Because Lucas had just spent so much money moving, she didn't want to pay to see a doctor, and she was eager to return to teaching in person in 2021 after being virtual during the Covid pandemic.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, Lucas said: 'I could barely do my job. I was very fatigued and I was coughing a lot. I could barely even drive myself home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I would almost fall asleep at the wheel - that's how bad the fatigue was and my husband started picking me up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We both thought it was me overworking and being overstressed.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lucas was urged to visit the doctor by both her students and fellow staff members, but claims she was told by doctors that she 'looked good'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lucas said: 'It was my students and colleagues that noticed that I could barely finish my sentences without coughing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Lucas continues to take targeted therapy tablets, and continues to have check-up scans every four months&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Lucas underwent two rounds of chemotherapy which started in January 2022, followed by a month of radiotherapy treatment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I was tired all the time, I had chest pain and I would wake up in the middle of the night with sharp back pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The cough would not go away even with cough drops and medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The doctor was like "You look so good, you should go home, boil some water and add some honey."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I was too stunned to speak.'  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After months of back and forth, Lucas was eventually sent for a PET scan in November 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lucas said: 'I was in and out of the emergency room with those symptoms between September and November.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I was coughing so much, there was a point where I could barely walk.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In December 2021 Lucas received the diagnosis of stage 3A lung cancer. The five-year survival rate is approximately 36 percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Lucas was diagnosed with stage three lung cancer after scans revealed she had three lime-sized tumors in her lungs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Overall, lung cancer affects about 226,000 Americans per year and about 124,000 are expected to die from the disease in 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Stage 3A lung cancer is a type of non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC) that indicates a tumor has grown to larger than 5cm and spread to nearby lymph nodes in the chest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;NSCLC specifically accounts for about 85 percent of lung cancer cases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The special educator teacher admits she was 'relieved' that she'd finally been given a diagnosis after months of back and forth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lucas said: 'When the doctor walked in the room I said "it's cancer isn't it?" and he was like "yes it is."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'On the X-ray I had three tumors on my right lung, which were the sizes of limes and the cancer had engulfed the middle part, which were the lymph nodes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I felt so relieved. I was so restless of not having any answers and so many doctors kept telling me it was nothing.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lucas underwent two rounds of chemotherapy which started in January 2022, followed by a month of radiotherapy treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Lucas was a newlywed at the time of her diagnosis and had just moved houses and started teaching for the 2021-2022 school year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Since March 2022, she has been taking daily targeted therapy pills, and continues to have check-up scans every four months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lucas said: 'I only had to do two rounds of chemo. I opted out of surgery and suggested we go straight to targeted therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The targeted therapy pill, even with side effects, lets me live a pretty normal life. I have been taking that since 2022 and it's still really working for me now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'They haven't declared me cancer free yet. They want to scan me for two more years but I still have to go to scans every four months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The tumors have shrunk [and] the doctors described it like ice melting under the sun.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:00:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxNZmxjZEhoUHNCNWZscTVmNXJXTUkzbmlLODBqa2trVnpwdHpzSEhyM0hQUmo3RnZsSlJDSmh4eHE5R1VuUnFBeVV4TkZqWmo4SUgwb01NZXhpM1ZiU3p0ZjZWVUtBbjV5ZjlyYS11SzR0clp6c0s3ZGhTMnc1TmlCbzJDSE5pYnQ2d2FwV1RHRkxvSmREZmlxdDA5cjd3aVpjZ0JMUm5mSHpBbERjdWRTbUktYl80RzZScVHSAb8BQVVfeXFMTjJJWE5kOVZpa3pLU21kMnBZZ3dZUmlQRTItSXQtdm9QcFVCbHFJUHREWU9jNWZId0lnWTBpUE1wZFZoY1lhNDhjZzMxSzhib254X2cyZjVkNzhzb2RyRFFkcXZoMldrU2MyaXEwUHBocmxDejBlbmF3eDlKZUtXOFpDNE5PYWJFS0RWY1RueW9YM2Z4dk5pUHZOV3UzY0hLSzUzOVU1b19SUDlZbklPMXQzTHVfZ0NHZE9USVZISzQ</guid></item></channel></rss>