<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>首次注射阻止人类免疫缺陷病毒批准- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c803egy217xo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;'Game-changing' HIV protection jab approved in England and Wales&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-c4820dd1-0 cYDsPh"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-c4820dd1-11 bxdaHR"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;Michelle Roberts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;Digital health editor&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 ERpRj"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/b86c/live/cdc0d600-a837-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/b86c/live/cdc0d600-a837-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/b86c/live/cdc0d600-a837-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/b86c/live/cdc0d600-a837-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/b86c/live/cdc0d600-a837-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/b86c/live/cdc0d600-a837-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/b86c/live/cdc0d600-a837-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/b86c/live/cdc0d600-a837-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images A scientist draws liquid medicine through a syringe from a vial" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;An injection to prevent HIV is to be offered to patients on the NHS in England and Wales for the first time, bringing the policy in line with Scotland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The long-acting shot, given six times a year or every other month, is an alternative to taking daily pills to protect against the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Experts hope the cabotegravir (CAB-LA) injections will help meet the ambition of ending new HIV cases by 2030 in the UK. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Meanwhile, early results for a different injection called lenacapavir suggest it may even be possible to move people on to &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cewk4qlrd4po" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;an annual HIV prevention jab&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;'This represents hope' &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Wes Streeting, the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, said: "The approval of this game-changing injection perfectly embodies what this government is determined to deliver - cutting-edge treatments that save lives and leave no one behind. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"For vulnerable people who are unable to take other methods of HIV prevention, this represents hope."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;HIV prevention therapy, known as PrEP (pre-exposure prophylaxis), is taken by HIV-negative people to reduce the risk of getting HIV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Pills have been available for years and are still extremely effective at stopping HIV infections, but are not always easy for some to take. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It can be hard to access, not practical, or feel embarrassing. For example, people might worry someone like parents or housemates could find their pills. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Homelessness and domestic violence can make it difficult to take oral PrEP every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;An injection which lasts for months offers convenience and discretion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;HIV is a virus that damages the cells in the immune system and weakens the body's ability to fight everyday infections and diseases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It can be caught during unprotected sex or through sharing needles. Mothers can also pass it to their baby at birth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Cabotegravir should be used in combination with safer sex practices, such as use of condoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The NHS has an undisclosed discount from the manufacturer for the treatment that has a list price of around £7,000 per patient per year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The jab will be considered for adults and adolescents with a healthy weight who are at high risk of sexually acquired HIV and eligible for PrEP, but for whom taking oral tablets would be difficult. It’s thought around 1,000 people will be offered it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;They will be able to get it from NHS-operated sexual health clinics "in coming months" says &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nice.org.uk/" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence&lt;/a&gt; (NICE). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Charities say some people face long waiting times for appointments at clinics and the rollout must happen quickly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Richard Angell, of the Terrence Higgins Trust, said it was time to explore delivering the "transformative therapy" in other settings, not just sexual health clinics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It's highly effective and acceptable for patients, and a vital tool for tackling inequalities – with the potential to reach those who are not currently accessing other HIV prevention."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.gov.uk/government/statistics/hiv-annual-data-tables/hiv-testing-prep-new-hiv-diagnoses-and-care-outcomes-for-people-accessing-hiv-services-2025-report" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;Official figures&lt;/a&gt; for England show the number of people taking PrEP in sexual health services is increasing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Last year,146,098 HIV-negative people accessing sexual health services had a PrEP need because they were at substantial risk of acquiring HIV. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Of those, about 76% (111,123) began or continued PrEP - a 7.7% rise from 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;PrEP need is not being identified and met equitably though. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Access to the treatment varies significantly by group, with uptake highest among white (79.4%) and ethnic minority (77.8%) gay, bisexual and all men who have sex with men, but much lower among black African heterosexual women (34.6%) and men (36.4%). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;At the same time, HIV testing has expanded across hospital A&amp;amp;E departments in England. Currently, 89 routinely test anyone who has blood taken, specifically in cities and towns with high HIV prevalence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:27:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9PRVFUZkp3V1prV1RYTXAyeHpPVERON3dFSWFGSW1kS3Qxb2MyWG5wOVhHalI5OGpXeEd5WnJXekxYRENvUVRkeTZMUmFzaEhYSG9iUVdOQXhid9IBX0FVX3lxTE5DNGFfU29FeGZ2cHRhcHB5T04wLXhsX293QV9rSkR2NUU4SzZKRzJlQ3VNdlJQMy1vckFNd3NlTFRfNDZnZ2dxR3I0MFlLYnFPdnh6UWh4OXFHTjg0djhj</guid></item><item><title>一种微小的肽可以在有毒之前冻结帕金森氏症的蛋白质- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/a-tiny-peptide-can-freeze-parkinsons-proteins-before-they-turn-toxic</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/parkinsons-disease"&gt;Parkinson's disease&lt;/a&gt; progresses, harmful protein clumps build up in the brain, blocking communications between neurons and killing them off – but what if we could prevent these clusters from forming?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers led by a team from the University of Bath in the UK have achieved just that in a &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Caenorhabditis_elegans"&gt;basic worm model&lt;/a&gt; of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IYl" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73029" data-postid="176557" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Parkinson's&lt;/a&gt;. They engineered a peptide, a small amino acid chain, to essentially keep a protein called alpha-synuclein locked in its healthy shape. This &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Protein_folding"&gt;prevented the misfolding&lt;/a&gt; that leads to clumps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/parkinsons-discovery-suggests-we-could-have-an-fda-approved-treatment-already"&gt;potential treatment&lt;/a&gt; checks several important boxes: it's durable, and it can survive inside cells without causing any toxic side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/parkinsons-disease-could-be-ignited-by-burned-out-brain-cells"&gt;Parkinson's Disease Could Be Ignited by Burned-Out Brain Cells&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This opens an exciting path towards new therapies for Parkinson's and related diseases, where treatment options remain extremely limited," &lt;a href="https://www.bath.ac.uk/announcements/bath-scientists-design-peptide-switch-that-keeps-parkinsons-protein-in-its-healthy-form/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; biochemist Jody Mason, from the University of Bath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study follows on from &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.xcrp.2023.101563"&gt;previous work&lt;/a&gt; by some of the same researchers, which identified part of the alpha-synuclein protein that may stop it building to dangerous levels. This key part or fragment acts like a guide for the protein to follow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176560" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176560" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/ProteinDiagram.jpg" alt="Peptide and protein diagram" class="wp-image-176560 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/ProteinDiagram.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/ProteinDiagram-560x415.jpg 560w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/ProteinDiagram-600x445.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-176560" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The team used a shortened peptide to make sure alpha-synuclein proteins behaved. (Meade et al., &lt;em&gt;JACS Au&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;That fragment was then cut down into the smallest possible size to form the new peptide tested here. The researchers also added extra stability to their peptide molecule, using chemical structures called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lactam"&gt;lactam bridges&lt;/a&gt; to stop it from breaking down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crucially, the peptide created by the researchers can patrol cells and prevent misfolding without interfering with the normal, healthy job that alpha-synuclein is there for: regulating neurotransmitter signaling chemicals &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/dopamine-doesnt-work-in-our-brains-quite-the-way-we-thought"&gt;such as dopamine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our work shows that it is possible to rationally design small peptides that not only prevent harmful protein aggregation but also function inside living systems," &lt;a href="https://www.bath.ac.uk/announcements/bath-scientists-design-peptide-switch-that-keeps-parkinsons-protein-in-its-healthy-form/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Mason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part of the challenge of finding effective &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/parkinsons-discovery-suggests-we-could-already-have-an-fda-approved-treatment"&gt;treatments for Parkinson's&lt;/a&gt;, and other diseases like it, is that it can be difficult to disentangle the causes of the condition from the consequences – are alpha-synuclein protein clumps appearing because of the effects of Parkinson's, for example, or helping to drive its progression?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With that in mind, the treatment outlined here seems preventative. It could eventually be used to stop proteins from building up in the brains of people &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/men-have-higher-risk-of-parkinsons-and-we-may-finally-know-why"&gt;at risk of developing Parkinson's&lt;/a&gt;, rather than breaking up existing protein clumps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_astro"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Astronaut in space, with text overlay" class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-177074" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;There's a lot of progress to be made – including figuring out the best way to deliver these peptides into the body (which will be significantly more difficult for humans than it is with worms) – but the early signs from this research are positive ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also want to explore using similar techniques for related conditions, including Lewy body dementia and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimer-s-disease"&gt;Alzheimer's disease&lt;/a&gt; – which are characterized by dangerous protein clumps of their own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"To make progress towards a cure for all forms of dementia, we need research focused on developing a broad range of treatments that can slow, stop and ultimately reverse these diseases," &lt;a href="https://www.bath.ac.uk/announcements/bath-scientists-design-peptide-switch-that-keeps-parkinsons-protein-in-its-healthy-form/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Julia Dudley, the head of research at  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="176557" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; Research UK, which helped fund this study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although this is early research in an animal model, it's exciting to see that this new molecule can prevent the build-up of misfolded alpha-synuclein."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1021/jacsau.5c00694"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Journal of the American Chemical Society&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:01:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQamlFVmduWjBjYllLbGc0ZGhMQ1laWElOYzJNcm9iZUI2WGZxR1BOWWp1NWYyZ3E0OGg5eUo5SWZBMlkxY3JNbHJIU1NRRXVqWHVXNnZIczlza190UXpiN2c4TDNBUXJ6MTZJQjlncktnOVhOdEMzZHY1amx1aVJja3RUNWtBWUxYMWdmcVlPbUgtRHpzZWdxTDkzeUFXdw</guid></item><item><title>加州mpox病例引发担忧。但卫生官员表示，风险仍然很低-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/mpox-california-cases-fef12a2ccb332967fd0a2068bf170049</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Two Californians diagnosed with mpox may be the first U.S. cases resulting from the local spread of a different version of the virus, health officials said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Long Beach Department of Health and Human Services this week confirmed the first case through testing at a state lab. Los Angeles County health officials on Thursday reported a second, similar case. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The risk to the public is low, officials say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are not the U.S. first cases of what is known as clade I mpox. But all six previous cases were among international travelers who were believed to have been infected abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both infected people in California were hospitalized, and they are now recovering at home. Officials declined to give other details. But “at this point in our investigations, we have not identified any association between the two cases,” Long Beach health department acting public affairs officer Jennifer Ann Gonzalez said.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Long Beach is located in Los Angeles County but has its own city health department. Investigators there say they have not found a close contact who traveled abroad, nor have they confirmed additional cases. A few of the person’s close contacts have been given a vaccine, said Nora Balanji, the Long Beach department’s communicable disease coordinator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We don’t have any proof that there has been ongoing community transmission,” she said. “It’s something we’re looking into. That’s something we’re concerned about.”&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/africa-mpox-outbreak-who-f1c5d501223ccf3b53c6d9a2727d5c8a"&gt;Mpox&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; — also known as monkeypox — is a rare disease caused by infection with a virus that is in the same family as the one that causes smallpox. It is endemic in parts of Africa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Milder symptoms can include fever, chills and body aches. In more serious cases, people can develop lesions on the face, hands, chest and genitals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One version of the virus — called clade II — was the source of an international health crisis in 2022, when infections escalated in dozens of countries, mostly among men who have sex with men. At one point, the U.S. &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/monkeypox-public-health-emergency-us-f336fc99abd57f0866a38b578d5bb44c"&gt;was averaging&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; close to 500 cases per day.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;The infections were rarely fatal, but many people suffered painful skin lesions for weeks. Those outbreaks waned &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/monkeypox-health-medication-public-313a2781a28f6b17230843432a609118"&gt;later that year&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, thanks in part to the Jynneos vaccine made by Bavarian Nordic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other version — known as clade I — likewise can spread through sex, but also through other forms of contact. In Africa it has infected a broader range of people, including children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A newer form of the clade I virus has been widely transmitted in eastern and central Africa. The World Health Organization declared the situation a public health emergency, but last month it said the problem &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/mpox-health-world-health-organization-c39dea7fa56622eaab680bcb2ad7eeec"&gt;had waned enough&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; that it was no longer an international emergency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, “it’s concerning if this virus has come here and now is starting to be transmitted from person to person,” said Dr. William Schaffner, an infectious diseases expert at Vanderbilt University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The case report comes amid a federal government shutdown and the layoffs of hundreds of employees at the Atlanta-based Centers for Disease Control and Prevention — the agency that usually would be involved in responding. &lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Balanji said a few CDC experts have been available to talk to her department about the situation. But Schaffner noted that “the longer the shutdown, the more impaired public health responses are to any outbreaks.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A U.S. Department of Health and Human Services spokesperson referred questions to local health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 23:08:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOdGd1cXdwNl9mR1FmTnVjalpXUUh6eXd1dHB2NGo2SnJNR3lIanRRTk5tbFB4Sk44SFlLZTh6TjFsXzFDTWRUbVNpOENWcEdEUmJ0am96MkxHWUxwaTNaTTJDWFFwd0Zqd0wzMGNHbmYtQk5oZWtCM2RCNVJCbHlfakQtdVYyaUhD</guid></item><item><title>当网红和其他人推出蛋白质粉末时，营养师是这么说的- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/influencers-protein-powders-supplements-dietitians/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The demand for protein has soared as 61% of consumers in the U.S. increased their protein intake last year, according to new research from Minnesota-based food corporation &lt;a href="https://www.cargill.com/doc/1432277049818/the-2025-protein-profile.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Cargill&lt;/a&gt;. And social media influencers and brands alike are taking note.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We're seeing that influencers, fitness professionals – they're all encouraging more protein after lifting," said Yasi Ansari, a clinical dietician at UCLA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The protein boom&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protein is now a $114 billion industry and growing, &lt;a href="https://store.mintel.com/report/us-proteins-and-protein-alternatives-market-report" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;according to Mintel&lt;/a&gt;, a global market intelligence company. The number of high protein shakes and drinks on the market rose by 122% from 2020 to 2024, Innova Market Insights &lt;a href="https://www.innovamarketinsights.com/trends/protein-beverages-trends-global-market-overview/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt;, noting that Gen Z is driving most of the online chatter around the beverages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chains like &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/starbucks-protein-lattes-cold-foam-menu-september-29/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Starbucks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, Dutch Bros, Smoothie King and others recently introduced protein-packed options and add-ons to their menus. PepsiCo CEO Ramon Laguarta also said protein would be a big focus for the company, telling investors in July that "consumers are adopting protein solutions in the diet at a pace that was not the case in a few months back, a few years back."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protein, an essential nutrient, certainly has health benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It's the building block of your bones, muscles and other organs, and getting enough is crucial for keeping your body working properly," Christine Byrne, a registered dietitian and owner of &lt;a href="https://rubyoaknutrition.com/about/christine/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Ruby Oak Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;, said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ansari noted it also helps to build enzymes, support hormone health and provide a structural component to hair, skin and nails.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But "today's wellness culture tends to overestimate the amount of protein most people actually need," Byrne said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ideally the source of your protein is whole foods, instead of powders and supplements, registered dietitian Helen Tieu said.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/protein-powders-shakes-lead-consumer-reports/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Consumer Reports&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; recently found some protein powders and shakes contain high levels of lead. A total of 23 protein powders and shakes were tested as part of their &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/lead/protein-powders-and-shakes-contain-high-levels-of-lead-a4206364640/?EXTKEY=M5ANXO" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;investigation&lt;/a&gt;, which determined that more than two-thirds of the products contained unsafe levels of lead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"For people who are able to reach their protein targets from whole foods, protein powders and supplements are not necessary," Tieu said. "Limit protein powder intake to an occasional use when necessary. Whole foods also provide more nutrients and keep us full for longer, compared to an isolated protein powder supplement."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For some people — including those with certain medical conditions or competitive athletes — protein supplements can be more crucial, Byrne said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although I'd caveat that this generally isn't the case for everyday exercisers, even those who hit the gym or the trail daily," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How much protein is really needed in a diet?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For growing children and adolescents, protein provides the building blocks for muscle, bones, skin and hormones. Getting enough protein is also essential for older adults. It can help preserve strength, maintain bone density and reduce the risk of age-related injury.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Government guidelines suggest most adults aim for about 0.8 grams per kilogram of body weight. For example, someone who weighs 150 lbs would need about 54 grams of protein — this is what's in about 6 ounces of cooked chicken breast, Byrne said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We want to look for high quality sources," Ansari said. "So those are generally speaking animal protein. Now another way to do this is by combining beans and grains and making it a full meal."&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Byrne said you can calculate your estimated protein needs by consuming 0.36 grams of protein per pound of bodyweight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That calculation is an oversimplification, and many people need more protein than this. But the idea that you need to slam a protein shake before and after every workout just to meet your needs and reach your goals is totally wrong," she said.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High-protein foods&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;"To boost protein intake from whole foods, make sure to include protein at every meal, and aim for a minimum of 20 grams per meal to boost muscle protein synthesis," Tieu suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some protein-rich foods include: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Meats, with options like chicken and turkey leaner than beef&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fish and seafood, like tuna, salmon, shrimp and scallops&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Greek yogurt and &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/social-media-health-trends-experts/" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;cottage cheese&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eggs, or egg whites for less cholesterol&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Milk or soy milk&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tofu and tempeh&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beans, lentils, chickpeas and edamame&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Whole grains&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Megan Meyer, a science communication consultant with a doctorate in nutritional immunology, said she aims to have both snacks and meals that include protein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Some of my favorite protein-rich snacks include Greek yogurt, cottage cheese, a handful of nuts, meat sticks and hard-boiled eggs," she said. "My go-to proteins for meals include lean meats like chicken breast, canned tuna, beans, lentils and tofu."&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/section&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQQVNSbGYwbXpQRC1yeTRJYzhDOWFOVDVvQkhMa2hkVzBQWE9JbkV0ZXJQTVFTUmpSMnNIb3RzNW9DWjhRc2t4VE56NFNPLVlKUlZJcmxaWHFxaVlLQWcwS1gyYktaa3pkM25VYWRkcGJ2MlhVcjBUdzNiR3dibG1mRmR1YjFFbE3SAYwBQVVfeXFMT0N0NXp2WWpOck5xTkdpUnp5R3U5NXZuQkZVWldFX2R3NU5td1JucGZYWU1zRU1xdWpwbkYyVFp3OWR4aFVWU09keXRuTHVqZ2JSWmp2YnVVS1E5bGFvZ1U1UkhYUXpSeXBYTjNtbTd2eG4tS0VhMmlLVjhweVp1QVIzLTh2MUNiNnpVWi0</guid></item><item><title>运动良好的小鼠将天然健康传递给雄性后代，但不是通过DNA -好消息网络</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/well-exercised-mice-passed-natural-fitness-to-their-male-offspring-but-not-through-dna/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Reprinted with Permission from &lt;a href="https://www.worldatlarge.news/2025/10/16/well-exercised-mice-passed-natural-fitness-to-their-male-offspring-but-not-through-dna/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;World at Large&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What if there were a way that didn’t involve CRISPR to give your offspring a natural talent for athletics?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well that’s totally possible as it turns out, because scientists just demonstrated it in mice, and it didn’t even involve so-called “good genes”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It involved a modern and exciting field of genetic biology called epigenetics: a term that refers to adaptations to genetic expression in response to life stressors. Here, the actual nature of the DNA doesn’t change, but adaptations packaged in the similarly important RNA made their way into sperm cells, the embryo, and the offspring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The story of this fascinating innovation begins in Nanjing University, where lead investigator on the study Xin Yin used to notice during his time as an undergraduate that the children of athletes seemed to possess a natural talent for sports. The reproductive biologist didn’t really see the sense in it; certainly, genes coding for larger lung volume would increase a child’s ability to run, but what could explain having a ‘knack’ for what takes months and years of training to master? There’s no gene that codes for having a knack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This curiosity led Yin to launch a research project with a fellow reproductive biologist at Nanjing to see whether a male mouse’s mastery of treadmill running could somehow imprint onto his offspring. Together with his co-authors, Yin subjected male mice to treadmill work everyday for 2 weeks before breeding them with female mice who did not exercise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1550413125003882?__cf_chl_tk=c9kzXKQan2ZWc25o1TcSWXzB3pZpaNuh5vWUUE9PO90-1760620819-1.0.1.1-AGlOF8TRukCrycqrwbGjDW3zJDLMWW0AOlYzUgfqVzE#sec3" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;they found&lt;/a&gt; was remarkable. The mice thusly born possessed more oxidative muscle fibers, could run for longer on treadmills, and were more resistant to weight gain from a high-fat diet, than the offspring of sedentary male and female mice. During the study period, Yin and his team sequenced the microRNA snippets in the sperm cells and the fertilized egg, and after observing the significant athletic adaptations, went back to see what might be causing it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exercise boosts the levels of a protein called PGC-1 alpha in muscle cells, where it activates genes that build more mitochondria, the organelles responsible for cellular energy and metabolism. PGC-1A is suppressed by another protein called NCoR1. In the exercised mice, sperm-bound microRNAs which proliferate under conditions of exercise target, once inside the mouse embryo, NCoR1. In effect, these RNAs released a natural, cellular brake on the development of metabolic power and muscle function.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;A true breakthrough&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To triple check whether or not classic genetic transfer was behind this adaptation for countering NCoR1, the researchers looked through 10 of the microRNAs that seemed most likely confer the exercise benefits, selected one in particular, and injected it into embryos fertilized by untrained fathers. Just that action alone, a single, non-DNA molecule, was enough to reproduce the endurance benefits seen in trained fathers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Biologists &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/well-exercised-male-mice-appear-pass-fitness-their-male-offspring?utm_source=sfmc&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_content=alert&amp;amp;utm_campaign=DailyLatestNews&amp;amp;et_rid=545277073&amp;amp;et_cid=5754571"&gt;commenting&lt;/a&gt; on the study to &lt;em&gt;Science Magazine &lt;/em&gt;said they were “surprised” that a single RNA could have such an impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that in mind, and to investigate whether similar effects were at work in humans, the team collected sperm from 8 men who trained regularly and 24 others who didn’t. An examination revealed that the equivalents of 7 of the 10 miRNAs seen in the mouse model were elevated in the sperm of trained men.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s the first study to show that RNA can pass down the benefits of exercise, commented Colin Conine, an epigeneticist at the University of Pennsylvania, who was not involved in the work but who called it “really a novel paradigm”. It probably suggests that the lifestyle choices of fathers need to be looked at with more scrutiny than in the past, he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Caveats included that the endurance/exercise benefit was only seen in male offspring, suggesting the sperm microRNAs only make it through the paternal germline. Grandchildren never received the benefit their parents did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yin’s study couldn’t go so far as to investigate the mechanism behind the transfer: why and how did exercise affect sperm? How did the microRNAs pass through the blood-testes barrier? How did they reach the epididymis, the tubes where sperm cells mature? They had time and data to present two hypotheses: that exercise codes for the creation of small-extracellular vesicles which themselves have the capacity to bring microRNA through the testes-blood barrier, or that within the blanket hormonal response of exercise, steroids and thyroid hormones may alter microRNA expression in sperm directly, without relying on the blood stream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The authors are now extremely curious to know what other effects microRNAs packaged in sperm cells are having on the father’s offspring. &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WaL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SHARE This Great Reason For The Fellas To Get Moving… &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:30:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxNNHR2TS1ibGM3dG5pWGJuY3dfeWF4X1ZiS1kxWmM0Qk4zaUJUb0IyNlNiWnhTY2pNMEhlY245cG42bDQyOUJLUXRUMHJLWEhfQW9uZ3dnS1BtNnZkWnRfcTBIbnplMFpaTXNnZm9lMk1qalFfWGZ6VWhXc2hJSnVTdU9YSmVzOGM5X1BOS0tJOHNtWTlhOFZsZUs3YmpHSEVZYXZNNjRuQkxFSzFxNFE4eVpjazk2NEtLcWdF</guid></item><item><title>加利福尼亚州官员确认美国首例没有旅行史的严重mpox病例- ABC新闻-突发新闻、最新新闻和视频</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/california-officials-confirm-1st-us-case-severe-mpox/story?id=126587395</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;The first U.S. case of a more severe strain of mpox without any recent travel history has been identified in California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Health officials said this week that the case was confirmed in a Long Beach resident. The patient required hospitalization and is now isolating and recovering at home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;No other identifying details were provided about the patient, including name, age or sex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;While this is the seventh case of the more severe strain confirmed in the U.S this year, it is the first without known travel, according to local officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Officials say the risk to the general public is low and the health department is conducting an investigation, including working to identify the patient's potential sources of exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Colorized transmission electron micrograph of mpox virus particles (blue) found within an infected cell (green), cultured in the laboratory.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;NIH-NIAID/Image Point FR/BSIP/Universal Images Group via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"We are taking this very seriously and ensuring our community and health care partners remain vigilant so we can prevent any more cases," Long Beach Mayor Rex Richardson said in a press release. "This underscores the importance of continued surveillance, early response and vaccination."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;There are two types of the virus that cause mpox: clade I and clade II, with clade roughly meaning they are descended from a common ancestor organism. Clade I has historically been associated with severe illness and death, and is endemic to parts of central and western Africa, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/monkeypox/situation-summary/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; (CDC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Clade II was responsible for a large outbreak that peaked in summer 2022, leading to more than 100,000 cases in 122 countries, including more than 30,000 cases in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The less severe strain in the U.S. has continued circulating at low levels and has remained relatively stable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Parts of Africa have been dealing with sustained person-to-person spread of the more severe strain of mpox. All six previously confirmed cases of the more severe strain in the U.S. have been among people who had recently traveled to areas associated with the outbreak in central and eastern Africa, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In November 2024, California reported the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/california-confirms-us-case-severe-mpox-strain-risk/story?id=115936257" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;first domestic case of the more severe strain&lt;/a&gt; in a traveler from Africa who experienced mild illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;People with mpox, which was formerly known as monkeypox, often get a rash that can be located on hands, feet, chest, face, mouth or near the genitals, the CDC said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Most people with mpox typically recover within two to four weeks without specific treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Currently, the JYNNEOS vaccine, a two-dose vaccine approved by the Food and Drug Administration to prevent smallpox and mpox, is the only vaccine being used in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The JYNNEOS vaccine is  recommended for adults at high risk for mpox, which includes people who are gay, bisexual or other men who have sex with men and have recent or upcoming risk factors like multiple sexual partners, intimate contact with someone who may have mpox, or sex at commercial venues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;ABC News' Mary Kekatos contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News - Breaking News, Latest News and Videos</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:23:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxNbzViSmNTcExkeVNtaEFsYTFzSkx1QzB1c0ZSZEtsTjk5TThZaFFVM0VGQnByT0lTbmpxQ2xUM0VvbGhwMmt0MlB2YURncDR3NEh2dWFLN0JCUjJsZWU1UVI4TzdvUXloUUc1S0pnVEE1YzJPMUZfbmRHLVBnczN0SGRmbEZ3cnNoUkVuTWVabkNCbjBxQnJkR2k1Qjg3SjNydDJN0gGoAUFVX3lxTE9PVWVYc3hZd0pqNmdCR01UNjZBNWs5Qm9pNTliUU1udUtRaUROX09lOF9DTmNvdmNfUjhPM05vZmthcEVzRGZTbThoYnk0TkFOT3hpNHl3NF9nMnZlNGYzdDU5NE9kTTAyaHVBNFFXeURUU09XU0dRZ0VzcF9CNFJkRTlreTBHc2NrQWNwR2dNQzhweXJuY0FpVW1fbXNIaEg4dzlHWjB2YQ</guid></item><item><title>《纽约时报》：匹克球运动员眼睛受伤人数上升</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/16/health/pickleball-eye-injuries.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:10:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE9IWml1dm1HRndkOEQ4alh1VXR2R2hlNWV3UWFyX2lWckFrTldUelhLbG1iU1JLc093VlY2X2xDUU0yb24wQVF1R1lHenhOT3V6UUwzMHg0VDV0a3RaNzdVLVhnYjlOV1F5WGh0WHU0QkpHUEFMNXNVSk5R</guid></item><item><title>根据新的定义，现在有数量惊人的美国人被认为是肥胖的- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/a-staggering-number-of-americans-are-now-considered-obese-under-new-definition-2000673086</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl "&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever wondered, even briefly, whether you have obesity, you might want to double-check right about now. New research suggests that over two-thirds of Americans are considered obese under criteria released this year—well above the obesity rate based on the older standard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Researchers at Mass General Brigham examined health records from a large, diverse sample of Americans. They found that nearly 70% of people met the new criteria for obesity, which takes into account other measurements besides body mass index. Those only classified as obese under this new definition still had a higher overall risk of health problems than nonobese people, suggesting the expanded criteria can help doctors better catch these issues before they worsen, the researchers say.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“Our findings suggest that the new obesity definition effectively stratified individuals at high-risk of organ dysfunction and long-term complications,” the authors wrote in their paper, &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2840138"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; Wednesday in JAMA Network Open.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Beyond BMI&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;In January 2025, a large group of obesity experts around the world backed by the Lancet &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/say-bye-to-just-bmi-experts-call-for-a-major-shift-in-how-we-measure-obesity-2000549992"&gt;pushed&lt;/a&gt; for a dramatic change in how doctors diagnose the condition. It was the culmination of a long-running movement by some doctors and patients to think beyond BMI. Their newly devised criteria, &lt;a href="http://linkinghub.elsevier.com/retrieve/pii/S2213858724003164"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in a report that same month, was endorsed by many health- and obesity-related organizations, including the American Heart Association in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;BMI is calculated using a person’s weight and height. And traditionally, obesity is defined as having a BMI of 30 and over. The updated definition doesn’t entirely abandon BMI but rather calls for doctors to use other bodily measurements, either alongside BMI or in place of it. These other measurements are waist circumference, waist-to-hip ratio, waist-to-height ratio, and the DEXA scan (a test that directly measures a person’s bone density and body fat).&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The criteria authors argued that their new definition makes it easier for doctors to determine when someone has excess body fat, one of the main reasons why obesity can negatively affect health. They also stated their criteria can better capture cases of clinical obesity—obesity especially likely to be harmful and raise the risk of other serious health problems—than the old BMI-only system. But the researchers say theirs is the first study to comprehensively examine the implications of applying this criteria in the real world.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;Hidden obesity&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The researchers examined data from the All of Us program, a long-running federal initiative to collect detailed health information from a diverse group of Americans. All told, they looked at the long-term health outcomes of over 300,000 American adults.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Under the old criteria, 42.9% of people in the sample were considered obese, a percentage in line with the national obesity rate &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/products/databriefs/db508.htm"&gt;tracked&lt;/a&gt; by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (a smidge over 40%). But under the new criteria, the percentage of obese people rose to 68.6%, including 36.1% who were considered clinically obese.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Nearly all the people who met the old standard of obesity continued to be included under the new framework of using BMI plus another measurement. And just about all the extra new cases of obesity involved people who appeared to have “normal” BMI but had elevated levels of the other measurements. Importantly, people with less stereotypical obesity were still more likely to have organ dysfunction and a later risk of diabetes than people not classified as obese under the new definition. That said, people with classic obesity still seemed to have a higher risk of these health problems than people with obesity who had a normal BMI.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The results indicate that this new criteria isn’t excluding people who would have been diagnosed obese in the past—a finding supported by other &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/bmi-is-actually-pretty-accurate-at-measuring-american-obesity-study-finds-2000594382"&gt;recent research&lt;/a&gt;. Moreover, it should help doctors identify people with hidden excess body fat and obesity, the researchers say. Ideally, this earlier detection can then help doctors prevent or better manage people’s obesity-related complications like diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“Identifying excess body fat is very important as we’re finding that even people with a normal BMI but with abdominal fat accumulation are at increased health risk,” said co-lead author Lindsay Fourman, an endocrinologist at MGB’s Department of Medicine, in a &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-adults-definition-obesity.html"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; from the hospital. “Body composition matters—it’s not just pounds on a scale.”&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If widely adopted, this new system could pose some unique wrinkles of its own, though. The authors note that about a quarter of people with clinical obesity in the study wouldn’t be eligible for newer obesity medications like GLP-1 therapy, for instance. And while clinical trials have found that these drugs are substantially effective for people with classical obesity, it’s an open question as to how beneficial they would be for people who don’t fit the traditional standard of obesity.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“Thus, implementation of the new framework may have significant ramifications for patients, including existing GLP1RA users, and creates a compelling need to evaluate use of antiobesity medications within this redefined target population,” the authors wrote.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:35:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxOQXVXc1BoSWJZcUVycXhld0V4WFFibzZtYmVpSlhLQWJ0dzVjdENEWlF1cVJ6Mml4azQzQXRBbjRSYTRjSDdxay1kUWgwZEY1VERzcmhZbWJxdG5HUGI2OEV4dXVNNEo2N2FIM3IyYzM1M1AtN09NZklJUUpWZEFYaTl3eW40MWxQMHZkdjBxMU9OMHRPWmtKUlVmdXV6bVhCZkk5NzZ3NWVJQnFBRlE</guid></item><item><title>为什么每天5克肌酸不能削减它以获得真正的效果–这是您的新最佳剂量-男性健康</title><link>https://www.menshealth.com/uk/nutrition/a69055830/creatine-dose-new-research/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-journey-body="standard-article" class="article-body-content article-body standard-body-content css-hh5w7d et2g3wt7"&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="1" class="css-m281hg emevuu60"&gt;&lt;br data-node-id="1.0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-node-id="2" class="body_content_break_0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="3" class="css-m281hg emevuu60"&gt;Popularity in &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/uk/nutrition/g64753267/best-creatine-supplements/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.menshealth.com/uk/nutrition/g64753267/best-creatine-supplements/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="creatine" data-node-id="3.1" class="body-link css-1d8p8n5 emevuu60"&gt;creatine&lt;/a&gt; is at an all-time high. But what if we told you &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/uk/building-muscle/a750240/what-is-creatine/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.menshealth.com/uk/building-muscle/a750240/what-is-creatine/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="you've been taking it wrong" data-node-id="3.3" class="body-link css-1d8p8n5 emevuu60"&gt;you've been taking it wrong&lt;/a&gt; all this time? Turns out, you'd see far greater improvements in various areas of your life by taking even more than the recommended 5g a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-node-id="4" class="piano-inline-newsletter"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-node-id="5" class="body_content_break_1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="6" class="css-m281hg emevuu60"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/uk/nutrition/a65157906/creatine-super-dose/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.menshealth.com/uk/nutrition/a65157906/creatine-super-dose/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="I personally took a 25g super dose of creatine for a month" data-node-id="6.0" class="body-link css-1d8p8n5 emevuu60"&gt;I personally took a 25g super dose of creatine for a month&lt;/a&gt; and felt some profound effects, and a narrative review published in &lt;em data-node-id="6.2"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2950273X24000249#ab0010" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2950273X24000249#ab0010" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Advanced Exercise and Health Science" data-node-id="6.2.0" class="body-link css-1d8p8n5 emevuu60"&gt;Advanced Exercise and Health Science&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; has indicated 5g of creatine a day isn't enough if you want real results. Despite making clear that creatine is conditionally essential, whereby it's not required for survival, the review highlights how you might need to start taking more of the supplement if you want to achieve the full benefits of increased longevity, &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/uk/nutrition/a68128816/creatine-brain-health-intelligence/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.menshealth.com/uk/nutrition/a68128816/creatine-brain-health-intelligence/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="improved brain function" data-node-id="6.4" class="body-link css-1d8p8n5 emevuu60"&gt;improved brain function&lt;/a&gt;, and stronger bone structure, alongside better muscular performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;section data-node-id="7" data-lazy-id="P0-8"&gt;&lt;h2 title="Where Did the 5g Recommendation Originate? " data-anchor-id="where-did-the-5g-recommendation-originate" class="body-h2 css-1gywm4a emt9r7s1"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="7.0"&gt;Where Did the 5g Recommendation Originate?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p data-node-id="8" class="body_content_break_2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="9" class="css-m281hg emevuu60"&gt;Creatine supplementation &lt;a href="https://portlandpress.com/clinsci/article-abstract/83/3/367/75945/Elevation-of-creatine-in-resting-and-exercised?redirectedFrom=fulltext" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://portlandpress.com/clinsci/article-abstract/83/3/367/75945/Elevation-of-creatine-in-resting-and-exercised?redirectedFrom=fulltext" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="research from 1992" data-node-id="9.1" class="body-link css-1d8p8n5 emevuu60"&gt;research from 1992&lt;/a&gt; focused solely on muscle saturation in young men who were well-versed with resistance training, with participants taking a maintenance dose of 5g per day. Since then, that number has stuck. But the study had limitations, with researchers only looking at the affect creatine had on muscular performance, while women, older adults or vegans – who don't get creatine from their regular diet – weren't accounted for either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="piano-paywall-container" data-node-id="11" class="piano-container"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-node-id="13" class="body_content_break_3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="14" class="css-m281hg emevuu60"&gt;'Five grams per day is a great start, but it’s optimised for skeletal muscle only,' Dr Darren Candow, who authored the aforementioned narrative review, said on a &lt;em data-node-id="14.1"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ICsO-EHI_vM&amp;amp;t=1s" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ICsO-EHI_vM&amp;amp;t=1s" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="FoundMyFitness" data-node-id="14.1.0" class="body-link css-1d8p8n5 emevuu60"&gt;FoundMyFitness&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;podcast.&lt;em data-node-id="14.3"&gt;&lt;/em&gt; 'If you want full-body benefits – bone, brain, immune, anti-inflammatory – you’ll need more.' He also highlighted how studies that highlight creatine's ability to improve brain function, reduce oxidative stress and even support neuroplasticity used more than 5g.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;section data-node-id="16" data-lazy-id="P0-12"&gt;&lt;h2 title="How Much Creatine Do We Need? " data-anchor-id="how-much-creatine-do-we-need" class="body-h2 css-1gywm4a emt9r7s1"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="16.0"&gt;How Much Creatine Do We Need? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p data-node-id="17" class="body_content_break_4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="18" class="css-m281hg emevuu60"&gt;Candow suggests that, for every kilogram you weigh, you should take at least 0.1g of creatine each day to achieve the best skeletal muscle benefits. So, if you weigh 70kg, a more optimal amount to take is 7g per day. The review suggests that could even rise to 0.14g per kilo of body weight when taking into account bone benefits in healthy older adults, while the minimum required for brain function is 4g per day – though that figure should be increased during acute stress, such as when sleep deprived, to as much as 20g. &lt;br data-node-id="18.1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-node-id="19" class="body_content_break_5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="20" class="css-m281hg emevuu60"&gt;'At 10 grams per day, you’re not just topping off &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/uk/nutrition/a61931768/how-much-muscle-can-i-gain-on-creatine/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.menshealth.com/uk/nutrition/a61931768/how-much-muscle-can-i-gain-on-creatine/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="muscle creatine" data-node-id="20.1" class="body-link css-1d8p8n5 emevuu60"&gt;muscle creatine&lt;/a&gt;: you’re potentially reaching the bone, brain, and other tissues that are often overlooked,' Dr Candow said. 'The lowest effective dose for bone strength was 8g daily; 5g didn’t move the needle. If you want to preserve skeletal strength, especially around the hips, higher daily doses are required – and always in combination with weight-bearing exercise.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-node-id="21" class="body_content_break_6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="22" class="css-m281hg emevuu60"&gt; It's important to note that the research doesn't prescribe an 'optimal' dose, rather offering guidelines on how much creatine helps in specific health markers, such as brain function and bone strength. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-node-id="23" class="body_content_break_7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="24" class="css-m281hg emevuu60"&gt;'Confounding variables such as baseline (pre-supplementation) tissue creatine levels, muscle fibre morphology, bone remodelling/repair processes, brain bioenergetics, habitual dietary intake of creatine, biological sex, age, and physical activity likely dictate the dose of creatine required to produce a meaningful tissue response,' the study concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr data-node-id="25" class="css-1xkwtv6 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;div data-journey-blur="partial" data-ad-exclude="true" class="css-19m4yzp e1jy25xv0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-sfzxfp ev8dhu59"&gt;&lt;span class="css-3mrz81 ev8dhu51"&gt;&lt;img src="https://hips.hearstapps.com/rover/profile_photos/9a3b97c1-b0c5-43e7-9528-f0e6add2a5e6_1747745685.file?fill=1:1&amp;amp;resize=120:*" alt="Headshot of Ryan Dabbs" title="Headshot of Ryan Dabbs" decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="css-o0wq4v ev8dhu53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="css-1dsojn8 ev8dhu55"&gt;&lt;div class="css-cmvt2k ev8dhu54"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ryan is a Senior Writer at &lt;em&gt;Men’s Health&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;UK&lt;/em&gt; with a passion for storytelling, health and fitness. Having graduated from Cardiff University in 2020, and later obtaining his NCTJ qualification, Ryan started his career as a Trainee News Writer for sports titles &lt;em&gt;Golf Monthly&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Cycling Weekly&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Rugby World&lt;/em&gt; before progressing to Staff Writer and subsequently Senior Writer with football magazine &lt;em&gt;FourFourTwo&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During his two-and-a-half years there he wrote news stories for the website and features for the magazine, while he also interviewed names such as Les Ferdinand, Ally McCoist, Jamie Redknapp and Antonio Rudiger, among many others. His standout memory, though, came when getting the opportunity to speak to then-Plymouth Argyle manager Steven Schumacher as the club won League One in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having grown up a keen footballer and playing for his boyhood side until the age of 16, Ryan got the opportunity to represent Northern Ireland national futsal team eight times, scoring three goals against England, Scotland and Gibraltar. Now past his peak, Ryan prefers to mix weightlifting with running – he achieved a marathon PB of 3:31:49 at Manchester in April 2025, but credits the heat for failing to get below the coveted 3:30 mark…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can follow Ryan on Instagram &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/ryan.dabbs/?hl=en" title="https://www.instagram.com/ryan.dabbs/?hl=en"&gt;&lt;ins&gt;@ryan.dabbs&lt;/ins&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or on X &lt;a href="https://x.com/ryandabbs_" title="https://x.com/ryandabbs_"&gt;&lt;ins&gt;@ryandabbs_&lt;/ins&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Men's Health</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:46:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQNEl5N3pVbkNINWtMcjJzVlNwNUNsMUlpTEhIZWhaV2ZjM3ktUUpxbThZcjBtRDFTYlBRUXNFMmpGMHhwZjZ3bFJpN09qMFVhenUtWGg1ZUtvdDV2QUd2N2h4VjFQMG9FbFJnX1F5SldCVUh4aU1UZC1NdE1TOEpnRmk2WQ</guid></item><item><title>当快乐感觉遥不可及时--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/16/well/mind/psych101-anhedonia.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:30:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTFA2WXdJTFlxY040UGlmY0hWLWJDTklvdGNDa2xwenctcG9sZmlxWWRpWFl2ZEtmUHp6NV9aci1uMHdjal9Ia2xScUtCb29WMUUyc29BUGdsb0c1ZmpXeU1oRUphdWt1WWpXLXVXQ25oNThzdHZhLXlN</guid></item><item><title>你的头发可以告诉你关于你的健康的什么-纽约时报</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/16/well/hair-health.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:14:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZ0FVX3lxTE1uc3ktd3ZTM2psWEFselJCenlFandyUWc1NmJBbTZZVndrU203TWJ2OEh0RDNITWZYdzZ3WVo0SXJZcndLb2lfWlBVQjlIXzcyV2ZrdWIwNWJieGYyS3MyZHkzb0w5NE0</guid></item><item><title>黑眼圈、眼眶骨折和视网膜脱离：与匹克球相关的眼损伤在美国呈上升趋势- Live Science</title><link>https://www.livescience.com/health/black-eyes-orbital-fractures-and-retinal-detachment-pickleball-related-eye-injuries-are-on-the-rise-in-the-us</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto paywall-locker"&gt;
&lt;p id="b0500eea-dfba-49eb-855b-73fd687f3a06"&gt;Eye injuries related to pickleball have increased at an "alarming rate" as the sport's popularity has exploded in the United States, a new study finds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More and more people in the U.S. are taking up pickleball as a leisure activity, with &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://sfia.org/resources/sfias-topline-participation-report-shows-247-1-million-americans-were-active-in-2024/#:~:text=For%20the%20fourth%20consecutive%20year,increase%20from%20three%20years%20ago." target="_blank" data-url="https://sfia.org/resources/sfias-topline-participation-report-shows-247-1-million-americans-were-active-in-2024/#:~:text=For%20the%20fourth%20consecutive%20year,increase%20from%20three%20years%20ago." referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;recent estimates suggesting&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that 19.8 million people participated in the sport in 2024, up about 45% from 2023 and 311% from 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="b0500eea-dfba-49eb-855b-73fd687f3a06-2" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true"&gt;Now, in a study published Thursday (Oct. 16) in the journal &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://media.jamanetwork.com/embargoed-articles/?_articles=1e0dd5c86e#" target="_blank" data-url="https://media.jamanetwork.com/embargoed-articles/?_articles=1e0dd5c86e#" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;JAMA Ophthalmology&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, three eye doctors found that this uptick in people playing the paddle sport has triggered a rise in related eye injuries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="45bce1f7-1510-4eba-9987-f7deb6790bfe"&gt;For this study, they turned to the National Electronic Injury Surveillance System (NEISS), a government-funded database that documents consumer product-related injuries. &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cpsc.gov/Research--Statistics/NEISS-Injury-Data/Neiss-Frequently-Asked-Questions" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cpsc.gov/Research--Statistics/NEISS-Injury-Data/Neiss-Frequently-Asked-Questions" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;NEISS primarily gathers its data&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; from samplings of about 100 hospitals with emergency departments (EDs), which are selected as a representative snapshot of the more than 5,000 U.S. hospitals with EDs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team focused on data gathered between the start of 2005 and the end of 2024. The search turned up a total of 2,472 pickleball-related injuries to any part of the body, including 73 eye injuries. Those numbers suggest that there were about 137,470 total injuries and 3,110 eye injuries nationwide across that timeframe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notably, no pickleball-related eye injuries were reported prior to 2014, and 88% of the eye injuries reported took place between 2022 and 2024. The results suggest the rate of eye injuries increased by about 405 cases per year from 2021 to 2024, the authors calculated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About 70% of all the eye injuries were reported in players ages 50 years or older, which may hint that older age groups are more vulnerable to these types of injuries due to changes in muscle mass, bone density or balance, the researchers speculated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-TJSvqkHRbs6WLusQuodPyV" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-TJSvqkHRbs6WLusQuodPyV slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get the world’s most fascinating discoveries delivered straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In cases where the cause of injury was known, the most common mechanism was getting hit with the ball, followed by falling or getting hit with a paddle. Periocular lacerations — cuts to the area immediately around the eyeball — made up the highest proportion of reported injuries. Other minor injuries included scratches to the cornea, the clear window at the front of the eye; inflammation to the iris, the colored part of the eye; and periocular contusions, better known as black eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More serious injuries that could threaten a person's eyesight included hyphema, where blood pools in front of the eye; orbital fracture; retinal detachment; and globe trauma, in which the wall of the eyeball is ruptured, typically by blunt force.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study authors noted that recent surveys suggest the uptick in pickleball participation is being driven by an "influx of casual players," as opposed to "core players" who play more than eight times a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although the increase in ocular injuries may simply reflect the increasing number of players, it is also possible that casual players are more susceptible to injury due to limited experience, unfamiliarity with the game, or lower level of physical fitness," the researchers suggested. But more data are needed to confirm that suspicion, they said in their report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="f8ab6b75-1609-47c2-808c-733c44dafb31"&gt;Notably, because the NEISS data are pulled from just a sample of EDs, they may not be completely representative of the nation as a whole, the authors added. The study also didn't capture patients who may have sought care at outpatient clinics, rather than the ED. But nonetheless, the data point to a potentially "alarming" trend, the researchers concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Currently, no official guidelines exist regarding eye protection in pickleball," they added. The American Academy of Ophthalmology recommends that pickleball players &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.aao.org/eye-health/glasses-contacts/pickleball-eye-protection-black-eye" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.aao.org/eye-health/glasses-contacts/pickleball-eye-protection-black-eye" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;wear protective eye gear&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; during games, but this precaution is not mandated or promoted by pickleball organizations, the study authors noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Increasing awareness for age-specific risk factors and establishing standardized recommendations for eye protection may help reduce injury rates and prevent vision loss," they wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mb-6" id="f17749c4-5893-47f6-9f9d-ea69e780883e"&gt;
&lt;div class="[&amp;amp;_a]:text-[#2f6e91] [&amp;amp;_a]:visited:text-[#09c] p-5 bg-[#F5F5F5] text-sm text-[#333]"&gt;

&lt;p class="infoDisclaimer tracking-[.02em] pt-2 font-normal"&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and is not meant to offer medical advice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:12:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3AFBVV95cUxNcHBiejdWZE9jczNfQ1dWUzdJTGNBeHRWWXZxQmNaMC1wb1NMZXV4bVhWdUlPcVpScmtPcXl6ZlhIbDI4VzlsX2kxdVU0dFVkXzlSY3pzNjhrVENoc2VUX1pKMmZHYlBqbDJQV2JLbktQMXZieEVmT1JIeWJCc3E5dkJHQlVqRGhNM3dvb3JUSjY1VzFoeWowRFVHLWVRODY3dlZNeTllTXhsS0hIQ0VGdmJrMUxaN2M5aWpBemx4S3N5VnNQaHRxODBlT0pqaVF5SDMyVVZMNFJZTzJ5</guid></item><item><title>她活了117年。她的秘密是什么？ -《华尔街日报》</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/science/biology/worlds-oldest-person-longevity-secret-1aae5f66</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Wall Street Journal</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQbWIydEJDa2ZCa2thcTFZejJqUmtjZXA0SlZKVkRvVGFUOG1wREpxS1FKc1VFbVFUdVVZa1VSUnBXNjlrOTk4MVZyNHVwXzNrZHJ0dHluTmJHVExpUlNHdVJpUkJ3aEt2WjM4VnFIQXRxY2xLRVE2ZXByZHEzOUtyLWpmYnBSTFVoV2c</guid></item><item><title>美国是如何迷上超加工食品的-黑客新闻</title><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45605921</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hacker News</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:52:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWEFVX3lxTE1OeGRlNHZ0S2VVVkNaYVlSX2Vrd2NFN3d2UDFMckdJYmJYdFVWV213eEsyUXFyMUFZaEpnbXEwLVlDTk01TVFqX1VfTnVDQ0lVdXBab211Mlo</guid></item><item><title>报告声称圣克莱尔Heritage Valley Sewickley医院进行不必要的背部手术- TribLIVE.com</title><link>https://triblive.com/local/sewickley/report-claims-heritage-valley-sewickley-st-clair-hospitals-perform-needless-back-surgeries/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="container"&gt;
	
		

				
		
		&lt;a class="logo triblive-logo-link" href="/"&gt;
    		&lt;img src="https://triblive.com/wp-content/themes/TribLIVE2/assets/visuals/images/icons/head/TribLIVElogo.png" alt="TribLive" class="triblive-logo"&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
	
		&lt;h1&gt;&lt;i class="fa-solid fa-shield-halved"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; NOTICE OF YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS  IN California &lt;/h1&gt;

		
	
		
	
	
		&lt;p&gt;Because you are coming from a location (California) covered by a Privacy Law, many of the features of TribLIVE.com, like videos and social media elements are disabled.  If you wish to proceed to the site under those conditions (doing so will effectively opt you out of the sale of your personal data) &lt;a href="#" id="setCookieLinkOut" class="setCookieLinkOut"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;. However you will not experience the full features of TribLIVE.com that rely upon third party networks that may require your personal data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="privacy-boxes"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#" id="setCookieLinkIn" class="setCookieLinkIn"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to agree to experience the full features of TribLIVE.com and to opt in to the use of your personal data to provide that experience and advertising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			
			
		&lt;p&gt;Bookmark this page to manage your preferences any time in the future. &lt;/p&gt;
	
	&lt;div class="privacy-boxes"&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;If YOU ARE NOT visiting us as a resident of California?  Please update your location to ensure you are presented with the best experience. &lt;/p&gt;
	


		
		
	&lt;/div&gt;
		
		
		
		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TribLIVE.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixwFBVV95cUxQX1ZtZXM2MDlQMmxfN29jYUg0TXpjS19TaU5SYVlvWE0xam9kcFk4LWM4UDl3Wld1Q1V0OXZXZkJWdzJ0Xy1GanZ3NGg0UFozRGJ5TGVYTDJTVDhyU3RPbUIwZnk4aHBtTHRYdndOSG55WnhTZEx0ei1OcWxpLXZCamZrVUNZZHZkeHlRY2VQNDdHTllqaUNIOFVldFlQUGRMVzFlaWVWR3lMQkljVGdwVEFmZHpWN0ozSTEzV2hlaDI0WGFRN2E4</guid></item><item><title>德国研究人员发现高效HIV抗体- DW</title><link>https://www.dw.com/en/germany-new-hiv-antibody-discovered-immunity-aids-map/a-74363818</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-tracking-name="rich-text" data-tracking-skip="true" class="c17j8gzx rc0m0op r1ebneao s198y7xq rich-text l1evdo4u blt0baw s16w0xvi rcjjkz7 w128axg5 b1fzgn0z"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Worldwide, 44 million deaths — that is the sad toll of &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/hiv-aids/t-18932088"&gt;HIV/AIDS&lt;/a&gt; since it was first detected in 1981; it was officially discovered in 1983. AIDS is considered one of the worst epidemics in human history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number of AIDS-related deaths has steadily decreased over the years, thanks to awareness campaigns, education and prevention, but people are still dying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2024, &lt;a rel="noopener follow" target="_blank" class="external-link" href="https://www.unaids.org/sites/default/files/media_asset/2024-unaids-global-aids-update_en.pdf" title="External link — UNAIDS reported the number of AIDS-related deaths"&gt;UNAIDS reported the number of AIDS-related deaths&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.5 3.5 11.5 4.233C14.342 4.233 15.167 4.245 15.167 4.258L8.984 10.467 10.033 11.516C14.826 6.725 16.228 5.333 16.242 5.333L16.267 9 17.733 9 17.733 2.767 11.5 2.767 11.5 3.5M2.267 11 2.267 17.233 16.733 17.233 16.733 12 15.267 12 15.25 15.75 9.5 15.75 3.75 15.75 3.75 6.25 9.5 6.233 9.5 4.767 2.267 4.767 2.267 11 "&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt; a year was about 630,000 people worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a rel="noopener follow" target="_blank" class="external-link" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41590-025-02286-5" title="External link — new discovery of an antibody against HIV"&gt;new discovery of an antibody against HIV&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.5 3.5 11.5 4.233C14.342 4.233 15.167 4.245 15.167 4.258L8.984 10.467 10.033 11.516C14.826 6.725 16.228 5.333 16.242 5.333L16.267 9 17.733 9 17.733 2.767 11.5 2.767 11.5 3.5M2.267 11 2.267 17.233 16.733 17.233 16.733 12 15.267 12 15.25 15.75 9.5 15.75 3.75 15.75 3.75 6.25 9.5 6.233 9.5 4.767 2.267 4.767 2.267 11 "&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt; by the University Hospital of Cologne, &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/germany/t-17871182"&gt;Germany&lt;/a&gt;, has raised hopes that another weapon in the fight against the virus may be on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p data-vendor-cmp-id="c43449" data-lang-code="en" data-id="74359583" class="embed dw-widget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;More than 800 antibodies tested against HIV&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The research team, led by Florian Klein, Director of the Institute of Virology in Cologne, examined blood samples from 32 people. They were all infected with HIV, but had developed a particularly strong and broadly effective antibody response against the virus, on their own — without any medical intervention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The researchers tested more than 800 different antibodies from these blood samples for their ability to neutralize HIV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of them, named 04_A06, stood out. The antibody blocks a site where the virus binds to cells when it infects a person. It therefore prevents HIV from entering the body's cells. When the virus enters a cell, it reprograms the cell to reproduce the virus, and that weakens the immune system in the long-term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Antibodies in &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/immune-system/t-66950642"&gt;the human immune system&lt;/a&gt; are produced by B lymphocytes, or B cells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When B cells detect pathogens, they become plasma cells that release antibodies, such as the 04_A06 antibody discovered by the Cologne researchers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The researchers decoded this process, or "blueprint," for the 04_A06 antibody in the hope that they could reproduced it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"You use the genetic blueprint of the antibody, transfer it to a cell line in the laboratory and use another cell and tell it: Please produce this antibody," Klein told DW.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="placeholder-image master_landscape big"&gt;&lt;img data-format="MASTER_LANDSCAPE" data-id="69157342" data-url="https://static.dw.com/image/69157342_${formatId}.jpg" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" alt="Person doing an HIV self-test at home; no face visible, just hands, arms, legs and a table with the self-test equipment on it"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="img-caption"&gt;Home testing kits: It's been possible for a while now to test your blood for HIV&lt;small class="copyright"&gt;Image: ALICE/BSIP/IMAGO&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Antibody 04_A06: HIV treatment and prevention&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In experiments with mice that had been infected with HIV, the 04_A06 antibody was seen to neutralize most HIV infections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In total, the researchers ran experiments with almost 340 variants of HIV, including those that were resistant to other antibodies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"HIV has a high genetic diversity, the viruses are all quite different," said Klein. "That's what makes HIV so difficult to treat."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the 04_A06 antibody neutralized 98% of the HIV variants they tested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The researchers said the 04_A06 antibody may be able to help people who are already infected with HIV — because it blocks the virus' access to cells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"It attaches itself to the envelope protein of the virus, so the virus can no longer infect the target cell," said Klein. In addition, viruses blocked by 04_A06 were better recognized and actively eliminated by the body's immune system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The researchers hope that 04_A06 could also prevent HIV infections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"The antibody intercepts viruses before they can infect cells and multiply in the body," said Klein.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, the newly discovered antibody could act as a passive immunization. An active immunization would be a vaccine that enables the body to produce antibodies itself. But there is no HIV vaccine as yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-vendor-cmp-id="c44391" data-lang-code="en" data-id="68339716" class="embed dw-widget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The state of HIV vaccine development and medication&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Studies into an HIV &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/vaccines-and-vaccination/t-73605776"&gt;vaccine&lt;/a&gt; based on mRNA technology are ongoing. Researchers aim to stimulate an immune response with a protein taken from the HIV envelope. That is the virus' outer coat, which, like the one of the virus that causes &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/covid-19/t-62123668"&gt;COVID-19&lt;/a&gt;, has protein spikes embedded in it that enable the virus to attach itself to cells and infect them. However, this method has so far only been tested for one HIV variant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Klein said it will be a challenge to induce the body's own production of potent and broadly neutralizing antibodies with an active vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="placeholder-image master_landscape big"&gt;&lt;img data-format="MASTER_LANDSCAPE" data-id="70324847" data-url="https://static.dw.com/image/70324847_${formatId}.jpg" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" alt="Hands holding a vial of lenacapavir "&gt;&lt;figcaption class="img-caption"&gt;HIV prevention with "depot" function: Lenacapavir is now also approved in the EU&lt;small class="copyright"&gt;Image: Nardus Engelbrecht/AP/picture alliance&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Various medicines are offered as pills or injections as a prophylactic measure against HIV infection. And they are very successful. However, the tablets usually have to be taken daily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are long-acting, injectable prophylaxis drugs, such as &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/miracle-hiv-drug-lenacapavir-approved-amid-drastic-us-health-budget-cuts/a-73023089"&gt;lenacapavir&lt;/a&gt; or cabotegravir, that create a "depot" function in the body. The depot allows the body to release the active ingredient slowly. And that means you only need two injections per year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Klein said the idea behind antibody prophylaxis with 04_A06 was, "that you [could] do without tablets, because you would have a more than 90% chance of preventing an infection." An antibody prophylaxis using 04_A06 would have to be taken approximately every six months, much like lenacapavir.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span data-slot-id="Article_InContent-1" class="rich-text-ad"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Alternatives to the 04_A06 antibody&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Researchers have found other broadly &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/hiv-cure-research-progress-2025/a-71445979"&gt;neutralizing antibodies against HIV&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Alexandra Trkola, Director of the Institute of Medical Virology at the University of Zurich said, "04_A06 is definitely an extraordinarily potent representative of this group."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The antibody's potency determines how many — or how few — of the antibodies are needed to create a strong effect. This is important if the Cologne discovery is to become a drug that is administered by injection, for example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Potency also determines how often you would need an injection. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"Theoretically, 04_A06 alone achieves an efficacy that is otherwise only achieved in antibody combinations," said Trkola, who was not part of the research in Cologne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it will probably be a while before 04_A06 becomes a drug, said Christoph Spinner, Head of Infectiology at the &lt;em&gt;Klinikum rechts der Isar&lt;/em&gt; at the Technical University of Munich (TUM).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Cologne study has so far only involved laboratory data, said Spinner, who was also not involved in the research. "So, the effectiveness cannot be directly transferred to real life."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further studies on the dosage, people's tolerance to it and its efficacy would need to follow, he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trkola agreed it was not yet possible to predict whether the antibody would prove its efficacy in clinical use but added that the signs were "definitely promising."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The article was originally published in German and translated into English.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>DW</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:12:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxPbS0tdlNXQldUNFI4TVVLSHZ4d0oxcngycng1Nzk0OHpsSHB4OXB6UUdwdXhXT2tMdTM3SVJ3REZXSlNUQWdtU3ZxTG1nQzlZNXdVbkdSQ1pIa2JyRVE0Y1pVWjJscGZhdVFqb1hPNzN5b20yWUdscVVLY0Qyc1RQRXhNSmxvc2dHOS1ZS0RxRdIBjwFBVV95cUxQazd1cnJFTWc0a3c0LUxjNzlWUlMtaUdyNktRaEVxSUh6LTVJY2tvT1pzMWVPMHpLQWxRYnBLMG8wRU41TGZoU2hhazR4azdMQlAzZ0hmMWJFQl9ZMnl6aVJfYUpEN2EzOW1TMnZ2WE9QMm8tYWxLeGh2Z2pPdURyYVJPc2FNT00xSDl5X1NXZw</guid></item><item><title>如果您已经超过70岁，但仍在不假思索的情况下做这8件事，那么您的头脑比大多数40岁的人更敏锐- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/s-if-youre-over-70-and-still-do-these-8-things-without-thinking-twice-your-mind-is-sharper-than-most-40-year-olds/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;div class="intro"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's something fascinating about watching someone in their seventies navigate a smartphone with more ease than their middle-aged children. Or the grandfather who picks up conversational Spanish just because.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These signs of something deeper—a kind of mental resilience that has less to do with luck and more to do with how you approach everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1. Learning new things for no practical reason&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My neighbor is 73 and just started learning to play piano. Not because she needs to, not because anyone's watching. She heard something that made her curious and went for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When older adults take on genuinely new skills—woodworking, astronomy, a language—their brains show increased activity in &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8151174/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;memory networks&lt;/a&gt; that usually quiet down with age. The trick is that it has to be *new*. Doing the same crossword format you've done for twenty years doesn't cut it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2. Actually wanting to hear what younger people think&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some septuagenarians talk to their kids and grandkids out of obligation. Others are genuinely curious what a 25-year-old thinks about dating apps or the housing market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That curiosity across generations keeps something important flexible in the brain. Research shows that older adults with &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/mind-and-mood/bonds-that-transcend-age" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;age-diverse friendships&lt;/a&gt; do better on tests of mental agility. You're literally exercising your ability to see from different angles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3. Figuring out tech without having a meltdown&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look, nobody loves it when their bank changes the app interface again. The difference is in how you respond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sharp 70-somethings treat confusing technology like a puzzle rather than a personal insult. They poke around, ask questions, maybe get frustrated but keep going. That willingness to experiment matters. &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S266703212300001X" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Technology use&lt;/a&gt; in older adults tracks with better executive function—your ability to plan, focus, and juggle tasks. The tech itself is less important than the mindset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4. Being willing to be wrong&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know someone who spent decades convinced butter was terrible for you, then read new research and just... changed her mind. No drama, no doubling down. Just "huh, I guess I was wrong about that."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most people get more rigid in their thinking as they age. But being able to update your beliefs when you learn something new? That's a sign your brain is still operating at a high level. The willingness to be wrong keeps your mind loose in ways that matter for everything else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5. Getting randomly curious about weird topics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You're at dinner and someone mentions how octopuses think, and instead of politely nodding you actually want to know more. Or you hear about some historical event and find yourself Googling it later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That instinct to follow curiosity—even when it's impractical—predicts how well your brain ages. The 70-year-olds who are still wondering "why" and "how" about random things are keeping neural pathways active. Curiosity isn't just nice to have; it's doing actual work in your brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6. Doing things that feel a little awkward&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most people's comfort zones shrink over time. Fewer new restaurants, fewer unfamiliar places, fewer situations where you might look foolish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cognitively sharp ones lean the other way. Travel somewhere you don't speak the language. Try a cuisine that seems bizarre. Go to a lecture on something you know nothing about. These novel experiences create what's called &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nrn.2017.45" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;neuroplasticity&lt;/a&gt;—your brain forming new connections. Mild discomfort is actually good for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7. Reading or watching things that make you think hard&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's entertainment that washes over you, and there's stuff that makes your brain work. Long articles about evolution or economics. Documentaries where you can't check your phone. Books that require real attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you regularly engage with complex ideas, you're building something called crystallized intelligence. Unlike other cognitive abilities that fade, this one can actually get stronger if you keep challenging it. The catch is you have to actually challenge it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;8. Still giving a damn about what happens next&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one's subtle. It's not about forced optimism. It's about maintaining real interest in the future—what your grandkids will do with their lives, how technology might change things, plans you want to make for next year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When older adults keep that forward-looking mindset, they perform better on cognitive tests. It's like your brain needs something to reach toward. The moment someone decides the interesting part is over, things start to slide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Final thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;None of this guarantees anything—genetics matter, and brains are complicated. But these habits definitely stack the deck in your favor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What strikes me most is how simple these things are. Not expensive supplements or complicated programs. Just staying curious, staying open, refusing to let your world get smaller.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 70-year-olds with unusually sharp minds aren't doing anything mysterious. They're just still interested. Still learning. Still reaching for what they don't understand yet. That reaching might be the whole game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-1991832237"&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What’s Your Plant-Powered Archetype?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever wonder what your everyday habits say about your deeper purpose—and how they ripple out to impact the planet?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This 90-second quiz reveals the plant-powered role you’re here to play, and the tiny shift that makes it even more powerful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12 fun questions. Instant results. Surprisingly accurate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:02:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3wFBVV95cUxORkpyMVR6WXhGaU10WHNFdG5QcG1MMXBXX1BtQ2ItdVRLeGJ5dTQwZkVwY1ZVc1g4QUFHU1ZYVjF3M1Q0Q2JxSEUzcGMxRkZaaVI4TFZ1d2p3R0RtS2VTN2Qtd1o4ZlZ3X01zRGF6czZwenRGVU9KeEh0WGg0cERpNHlsV3NDTk1RcjNpWjJVUzR3OEZkYi00bUx1cDVUaGJUcThEeUFseTEyM19sbmRKSFkwMEhxbUpaZ1V1ZWx3ODRuaXVaVDJtRkQ0cXE4U3czNVp0RmR2dmk0aE5oMFM4</guid></item><item><title>越来越多的年轻人患上早发性结直肠癌。5件须知事项- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/16/health/early-onset-colorectal-cancer-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmgslnuup00223b6npqq95t0t@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    &lt;span class="editor-note__prefix"&gt;EDITOR’S NOTE:&lt;/span&gt;  The podcast Chasing Life With Dr. Sanjay Gupta explores the medical science behind some of life’s mysteries big and small. You can listen to episodes &lt;a href="https://swap.fm/l/cldw101425" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgsjybhb001w27nn22wic507@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;(CNN) — &lt;/strong&gt;Nobody ever wants to hear they have cancer, but when it strikes a young person, the news is perhaps even more devastating because everything about the future they were imagining and working toward is thrown into question.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslcanv00023b6nzwrrpv0l@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Unfortunately, early-onset cancer —  disease   in people younger than 50 years old — is being &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/08/16/health/early-onset-cancer-increase"&gt;diagnosed more frequently&lt;/a&gt;, according to &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12082829/" target="_blank"&gt;various&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2808381" target="_blank"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt;. And among early-onset cancers, &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/03/01/health/colorectal-cancer-statistics-2023-report/index.html"&gt;colorectal cancer&lt;/a&gt; hovers near the &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9177054/" target="_blank"&gt;top of the list&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslcanv00033b6ngkk7j59e@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It was shocking to see that a young person — perfectly fit and healthy, no risk factors, no family history — could be diagnosed with Stage 4 disease. And then it just became more and more common, which is also distressing,” Dr. Kimmie Ng told CNN Chief Medical Correspondent Dr. Sanjay Gupta recently on his podcast, Chasing Life.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslcanv00043b6n5fd9epcq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Ng, a gastrointestinal oncologist and associate professor of medicine at Harvard Medical School, has been treating patients for two decades at Boston’s Dana-Farber Cancer Institute, where she is the founding director of the Young-Onset Colorectal Cancer Center, one of the nation’s first centers that treat younger adults with the disease.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslcanv00053b6n08193x21@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The incidence of both colon and rectal cancer has been increasing by about 2% per year in younger people since the mid-1990s, Ng said, noting that it’s happening to both men and women, not just across the United States but globally, too.&lt;s&gt;&lt;/s&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgskb62a000t3b6nje3v4pkn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It’s difficult to receive a cancer diagnosis no matter what age you are, but younger people face really different challenges,” Ng said. “Eighty percent have children under the age of 18. They’re also caring for elderly parents. They’re in the midst of their careers. Some people are still getting education. Some people are still planning to expand their families.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgsldczr00083b6n83to3p0s@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            You can listen to the full episode &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/why-are-so-many-young-people-getting-cancer/id1501029683?i=1000731143074" target="_blank"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/html-embed/instances/cmgsleds8000c3b6nyfqbzhlu@published" class="html-embed" data-editable="settings" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
     
&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgsl8im600003b6nijt494s8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Early-onset colorectal cancer is already the leading cause of cancer-related death in the US in men &lt;a href="https://acsjournals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.3322/caac.21820" target="_blank"&gt;younger than age 50&lt;/a&gt;, and if the trend continues, Ng said, it will become the leading cause of cancer death in women under 50 by 2030. (After breast cancer, colorectal cancer is the second leading cause in younger women now.)
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslfz5u000i3b6nmwz8l2f3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            She points out, however, that in absolute numbers, these cancer cases in younger people are “still quite small,” noting “it is still relatively rare to develop any of these cancers at a really young age.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslfz5u000j3b6nl4glc8b1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Across all ages, colorectal cancer cases and related deaths in the US have been declining for decades, Ng said, attributing that success to improvements in treatment and public health efforts to promote screening. “But that benefit has not been seen in people under the age of 50,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgskfvcs000w3b6nvhwrbjt3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In 2021, the &lt;a href="https://www.uspreventiveservicestaskforce.org/uspstf/recommendation/colorectal-cancer-screening" target="_blank"&gt;US Preventive Services Task Force&lt;/a&gt;, an independent board of medical experts, lowered the recommended age to start screening for colorectal cancer in asymptomatic people of average risk from 50 years old to 45.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslgr1j000m3b6n3rbftqrw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But Ng doubts the panel will lower the age again soon, noting not only the relatively small absolute numbers but also other factors that go into implementing a successful screening program, such as cost and the risks associated with screening, including bleeding, sedation complications and false positives.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslgr1j000n3b6n1ceizw7v@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Instead, Ng believes the focus should be on figuring out why this surge in early-onset colorectal cancer is happening. “What are the risk factors?” she said. “Who is at risk, and can we tailor that high-risk 30-year-old for earlier screening?”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslgr1j000o3b6njtzj3tsr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Also important: More people need to &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/04/health/colorectal-cancer-screening-trend"&gt;get screened. &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslgr1j000p3b6n10fitjoy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “There was this effort to get 80% of the population screened in the United States, but we haven’t yet reached that goal,” Ng said. “And so it is really important that we continue public health efforts to really advocate that screening can be lifesaving and it really needs to be done.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgsljzg600163b6nsiagyw7y@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            What do you need to know about early-onset colorectal cancer? Ng shares five things that matter.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslhgz0000s3b6nh47huqrw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Many types of cancer are rising among young people around the world, Ng told CNN via email, but cancers of the digestive system are rising most rapidly. That includes colorectal cancer, pancreatic cancer, gastric cancer and biliary tract cancer.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslhgz0000t3b6nvycd9rku@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Early detection is critical. And knowing the &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/latest-news/signs-and-symptoms-of-colon-cancer.html" target="_blank"&gt;red-flag symptoms&lt;/a&gt; associated with colorectal cancer is essential, Ng said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslv5yj00283b6nxjjgldfk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “For young people … the most predominant presenting symptom is seeing blood in the stool. For example, if you see blood that’s actually mixed into the stool rather than sitting on top of it or in the toilet bowl or just on the toilet paper. If it’s mixed in the stool, that’s perhaps a little bit more concerning and a little bit more characteristic of a malignant cause.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslhgz0000u3b6nq49ed9g4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Unintentional weight loss is another red-flag symptom, Ng added.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslhgz0000v3b6nha2rywh1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Other common symptoms include prolonged changes in bowel habits, such as new diarrhea or new constipation, thinner stools and abdominal pain. In addition, fatigue could indicate anemia or low red blood cell counts.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslhgz0000w3b6ni18asc8y@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            No matter how uncomfortable these conversations might be, Ng said it is crucial to discuss any changes in bowel habits with your doctor.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p00193b6n656r92az@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            With each generation, the risk has gone up, Ng observed.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001a3b6n5tdrfuio@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The increase in young-onset cancers is generational, with every generation after 1950 experiencing rising incidence,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001b3b6nruu4qs8y@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “For example, someone born in 1990 now has &amp;gt;4x (greater than four times) the risk of developing rectal cancer and &amp;gt;2x (greater than two times) the risk of developing colon cancer compared to a similarly-aged person who was born in 1950.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001c3b6nuw0f32nm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “When we see these … effects, what it usually suggests is that there’s some environmental exposure or exposures that have happened recently that are contributing to that rise,” Ng told Gupta on the podcast. “So, the big question now is what are these things that are actually leading to this increasing incidence in young people?”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001d3b6nfnity0i6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Researchers have been trying to pinpoint the drivers of   this unsettling trend.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001e3b6n1hqqeiza@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The cause of the rising rates of young-onset cancers is thought to be due to environmental factors,” Ng said, noting that our genes could not have changed so much in 30 years to be the culprit.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001f3b6np01m5oe4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Environmental factors might include obesity, sedentary behavior, and diets that are high in red meat, processed foods, added sugar and sugar-sweetened beverages.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001g3b6n3wd5wn8a@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The leading hypothesis has been obesity,” Ng told Gupta, adding that the obesity rates   in the US, which “have been skyrocketing in recent decades,” seem to parallel the rise in young-onset gastrointestinal    cancers, which include colorectal cancer. Obesity increases body-wide &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/12/11/health/colon-cancer-omega-6-ultraprocessed-food-wellness"&gt;inflammation, which can set the stage&lt;/a&gt; for precancerous changes.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001h3b6nakdsnuqt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Nevertheless, Ng said, most younger colorectal cancer patients she and her colleagues are seeing are not obese. “Many are marathon runners, they’re triathletes, they’re eating really healthy, they eat organic — and yet they’re still being diagnosed with young-onset   colorectal cancer.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001i3b6nau8ln0ni@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The influence of other environmental factors are still being studied, Ng said, citing &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/06/24/health/microplastics-food-packaging-study-wellness"&gt;microplastics&lt;/a&gt; as one example. Exposure to toxins and diet in the first decade of life can also &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40691977/" target="_blank"&gt;affect the microbiome&lt;/a&gt;, allowing certain cancer-promoting microbes to take hold.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001j3b6nm0lfi7py@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We are still in our infancy in understanding whether those are true risk factors, whether there is a link and actually how do they actually lead to cancer, in terms of these biological mechanisms.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001l3b6n613u45f7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Most cases of early-onset cancer are not explained by a heritable factor, but Ng said those diagnosed with any cancer at a young age have a higher chance of being diagnosed with a hereditary syndrome, such as &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/lynch-syndrome/symptoms-causes/syc-20374714" target="_blank"&gt;Lynch syndrome&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/familial-adenomatous-polyposis" target="_blank"&gt;familial adenomatous polyposis&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001m3b6n6aeyqr3r@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “All young patients diagnosed with cancer should undergo familial genetic testing,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001n3b6n4zsqbe94@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It is also important to know your family history of cancer, Ng said. “If there is a family history, then an individual may be eligible for cancer screening, or eligible to start cancer screening at a younger age, and this could be life-saving,” she noted.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001p3b6n56h02ekz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            If you have been diagnosed with any cancer, being young has its advantages, Ng said. Younger patients tend to be healthier, for one. They are more likely to withstand higher doses and more cycles of chemotherapy compared with older patients, and they can undergo surgery and radiation more often as well.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001q3b6nzp913lcl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Nevertheless, Ng, said, “their survival   is not necessarily better than that of an older patient with cancer.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001r3b6nad16lo7l@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            She noted that for colorectal cancer, “the very youngest patients” — those younger than age 35 — “seem to have shorter survival.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001t3b6n2huyrhl8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Ng  reiterated the importance of screening at the appropriate age for your level of risk: 45 if you are of average risk, and earlier if you have a family history.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001u3b6nyv3lag3e@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            She also stressed how crucial it is to put embarrassment and stigma aside and to reach out to your doctor, and even a family member, if you are having unusual symptoms, like those mentioned above.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001v3b6ngk18h03k@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It’s so important that we try to normalize these conversations,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgslkh1p001w3b6n33gdl0xz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            She added she also would like to see physicians routinely and systematically ask their patients two questions: “‘Are you having blood in the stool? Are you having a change in your bowel habits?’ so that these symptoms can come to light.” Especially because many people are reluctant to bring them up themselves.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmgslksim001y3b6n2k0jvldv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    &lt;span class="editor-note__prefix"&gt;EDITOR’S NOTE:&lt;/span&gt;  To learn more about early-onset colorectal cancer, listen to the full episode &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/why-are-so-many-young-people-getting-cancer/id1501029683?i=1000731143074" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. And join us next week for a new episode of the Chasing Life podcast.
&lt;/p&gt;

  

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:00:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxOZXpCbkx2NjdsdmxpbjN0ZTI0UWJJQmxqY1M5QWQ5ZlFBaFlaRFhWTkxmbHVpajNrZDFBd0YwYThuOWNwcktjcTJMVHkybXN5dHlnQlYxWjlOVFRPZVNmdjVRUVktdnI3eXVFdTAwYmRDWk1hMWxzRjY3Qkg0eUdjSExn</guid></item><item><title>保险公司正在向人们邮寄未经请求的Cologuard测试，这是一个糟糕的主意- The Hill</title><link>https://thehill.com/opinion/healthcare/5556547-colorectal-cancer-screening-kits/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>The Hill</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQdDFrTmtkSENyZmE3cW0yVHIzLVRRc0lfOEFMOGFxTkJXTFZNX1B0a0hiclkzZHdnTjR3THNOTkJtT0YzOG1PUUVLZFdnZDFSRVJyV0ZSZGdkMzdQR2l6MUNGdEl0OUZOZWpLYXFRb2hHWTRYUVAwZTRKc1l4X20xRUsxbDliUnfSAYwBQVVfeXFMT3NMYjhCSXF4T1kzQjF2ZjhUVktNc2N6TDVlS01wdEl2WEdXS3RXRXpEODRma1l0N2U5UkxKN3hWWWlscWgwQkNDd1JlUDl6bFZnd0JHWE5jbXp0LUFua0NwbWVFX2I5RnFpNUtmS29Bbm1wZ3VIOW5WZll2ZkJDaUZRTzFYQmVhLWJNZ2M</guid></item><item><title>科罗拉多州记录了美国最低的肥胖率- Axios</title><link>https://www.axios.com/local/denver/2025/10/16/colorado-obesity-rate</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:11:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE10bm83Vm9EM3FyNTBmbmRjQ3ZGdWNLOVYwYVdEWU9kRkV3bXlYM3FoMmZOWXJKMzdNQ3hyMEFJa3U3U1pPbWQzSnBhUVlCdEZodnp5YU0yUm9SbEh0WldlSHVackpCaHdtU0F2elR4S0l1N1hKYWc</guid></item><item><title>长期新冠疫情是真实的—它正在改变整整一代人-滚石</title><link>https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-features/long-covid-kids-school-absenteeism-1235447552/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="pmc-paywall"&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	&lt;span class="a-style-intro lrv-a-floated-left lrv-u-display-inline-block lrv-u-margin-r-050 u-margin-b-n025"&gt;
			&lt;span class="a-font-theme-primary lrv-u-align-items-center lrv-u-flex lrv-u-height-100p lrv-u-justify-content-center lrv-u-width-100p u-font-size-150 u-font-size-104@mobile-max u-line-height-124 u-line-height-94@mobile-max"&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;/span&gt;n January 2020, just weeks before the NBA shut down and Costco shelves emptied and Tom Hanks got sick, Joy Corbitt’s only brother died in his mid-forties with symptoms of &lt;a href="https://www.rollingstone.com/t/covid/" id="auto-tag_covid" data-tag="covid"&gt;Covid&lt;/a&gt;. Which meant, from the pandemic’s earliest days, Joy was taking no chances. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	She’d heard that Black and brown people like her seemed to be getting sick and dying at higher rates than other Americans. And that kids were either not getting sick, or getting less sick, or getting sick in ways we didn’t really understand. So, when it came to protecting her then-14-year-old daughter Lia, the North Carolina mother was vigilant.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“I was consumed with the news — consumed with the numbers,” Joy says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	As one week of lockdown slogged into the next, Lia, a straight-A student, struggled through that chaotic, ever unmuted, camera-off Zoom version of school. Which is to say, she didn’t learn much. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	With Joy’s husband James, a long-haul trucker, frequently on the road, the mother and daughter did their best to fill the time. They got a crazy Shih Tzu puppy named Zane. They spent long hours playing foosball and air hockey. They watched Netflix and cooking shows and &lt;em&gt;Bridgerton&lt;/em&gt; together (yes, even the sex scenes). 

	&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	By the time fall 2020 poked its head onto the horizon, Lia’s high school was set to resume in-person classes. Joy kept her daughter home. She was anxious; it was too soon for students to return. But Lia, a budding theater kid, was eager to get back to her friends, to her life, to try her luck onstage. 

	&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	A couple months into the school year, after Lia scored a role in a production of &lt;em&gt;The Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe&lt;/em&gt;, Joy relented. Lia “just lit up” about theater, her mom recalls. Joy figured, we had to let kids be kids. She took some consolation in the rules mandating universal masking.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	The masking, of course, didn’t last long. Kids.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	On an otherwise unremarkable day in January 2021, Lia came home with what she described as a “very minor sore throat.” She isolated, per school policy, counting down the 10 days until she could return. On Lia’s first day back, though, her throat was sore all morning. She threw up at lunch. Joy took her home early.



&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“I was very confused,” Lia says. “I thought, ‘Am I still sick?’”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“I thought it would go away,” she adds, “quickly.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	It didn’t. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Over the next three years, Lia would develop a perplexing, debilitating, and persistent set of symptoms. Extreme fatigue that turned mornings into catatonic nightmares. Brain fog that made memories slippery. Incessant vomiting. It all kept her out of class, stuck in the nurse’s office — or out of school entirely. The straight-A’s evaporated. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Lia’s story is one I’ve heard from dozens of families over two years investigating the impact of long Covid on kids. It’s a slow-moving spiral: first their health, then their grades, then their future. And as the country throttles past the pandemic’s fifth anniversary, those for whom Covid looms very present are feeling increasingly forgotten, subject to pervasive skepticism and a kind of cultural fatigue when it comes to their illness.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="post-content-image //  "&gt;
	

&lt;figure class="o-figure   size-large alignnone lrv-u-max-width-100p"&gt;

			

	
			
			
&lt;figcaption class="c-figcaption  lrv-u-flex lrv-u-flex-direction-column lrv-u-align-items-center"&gt;
	
					&lt;span class="u-border-color-black u-border-lr-2 lrv-u-padding-tb-025 lrv-u-padding-lr-075 lrv-u-border-b-2 lrv-u-width-100p lrv-u-text-align-center a-font-basic-secondary-s"&gt;Lia and Joy Corbitt at their dining room table in Davidson, North Carolina. “When you have a disability people can’t see,” Joy says, “you don’t get as much empathy.”&lt;/span&gt;
		
									&lt;cite class="lrv-u-text-transform-uppercase lrv-a-font-body-xs lrv-u-margin-t-050 lrv-u-text-align-center"&gt;Eli Cahan&lt;/cite&gt;
					
	&lt;/figcaption&gt;

			
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	The Make America Healthy Again movement has recently gestured at embracing the long Covid community. In September, the Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) convened two roundtables with the stated purpose of bringing long Covid “out of the shadows,” including by launching a “public awareness and &lt;a href="https://www.rollingstone.com/t/education/" id="auto-tag_education" data-tag="education"&gt;education&lt;/a&gt; campaign.” Kansas Sen. Roger Marshall — a physician with a loved one suffering from long Covid and who co-led the convenings — says those conversations were the first step to “take this invisible illness seriously.”



&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	But since the earliest days of the second Trump administration, the dollars that could help those suffering from the illness have quietly faded away. In March, cuts to the National Institutes of Health (NIH) disappeared the nearly $2 billion invested in the &lt;a href="https://recovercovid.org/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;RECOVER (Researching Covid to Enhance Recovery) initiative&lt;/a&gt;, hamstringing research that might have yielded diagnostic tests or better treatments. The same week, the administration shuttered the Department of Health and Human Services’ Office of Long Covid Research and Practice. 

	&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	In April, the Department of Government Efficiency (DOGE) gutted the NIH’s Vaccine Research Center — the entity whose work laid the foundation for the Moderna Covid shot. In May, health officials installed by Trump overrode career scientists at the Food and Drug Administration to limit approvals of new Covid vaccines. Around the same time, HHS Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. disavowed the vaccine for healthy kids and pregnant women. (“We’re now one step closer to realizing President Trump’s promise to make America healthy again,” Kennedy said in a video announcing the policy.) &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	In the weeks that followed, the secretary also removed every member of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) vaccine advisory committee, replacing them with a merry band of loyalists and skeptics. That committee has since walked back recommendations for the Covid shot. And since the committee’s suggestions only move forward with the approval of the CDC director, RFK Jr. fired Susan Monarez, whom he’d appointed to that role 29 days earlier, for her refusal to “commit in advance to approving every [committee] recommendation regardless of the scientific evidence,” as Monarez later testified at a Senate hearing.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Then there was Trump’s so-called Big Beautiful Bill, expected to boot tens of millions of Americans, including potentially one in five kids, off Medicaid. Where health insurance goes, vaccine access follows: Uninsured or partially insured children are less likely to get the shot, studies show. And unvaccinated children are up to 20 times more likely to develop long Covid.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	The Department of Health and Human Services did not respond to requests for comment on how the measures taken since March could impact young people with long Covid. But in the leadup to this school year, these developments led experts to warn that Covid cases may start ramping up again. That could have devastating effects in an education system beset by plummeting achievement levels and an epidemic of absenteeism (more than 10 million kids, or nearly one-third of all school-aged children, regularly missed school last year). And for families already affected by long Covid, absence after absence is prompting threats of investigations for truancy that have led to children being removed from school altogether, either by choice or upon the advice of the district. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“Millions of Americans are impacted by long Covid, and they deserve a federal government that will have their back,” Virginia Sen. Tim Kaine said in response to inquiries from &lt;em&gt;Rolling Stone&lt;/em&gt;. “The Trump administration is not only failing to achieve those goals, but actively taking us in the wrong direction.” 

	&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	It all suggests a brewing public health crisis for a generation of Americans — including people like Lia Corbitt, who, since 2022, has been largely in virtual education. That’s left doting parents like Joy disheartened. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="post-content-image //  "&gt;
	

&lt;figure class="o-figure   size-large alignnone lrv-u-max-width-100p"&gt;

			

	
			
			
&lt;figcaption class="c-figcaption  lrv-u-flex lrv-u-flex-direction-column lrv-u-align-items-center"&gt;
	
					&lt;span class="u-border-color-black u-border-lr-2 lrv-u-padding-tb-025 lrv-u-padding-lr-075 lrv-u-border-b-2 lrv-u-width-100p lrv-u-text-align-center a-font-basic-secondary-s"&gt;A decorative pep talk on the Corbitts’ bookshelf&lt;/span&gt;
		
									&lt;cite class="lrv-u-text-transform-uppercase lrv-a-font-body-xs lrv-u-margin-t-050 lrv-u-text-align-center"&gt;Eli Cahan&lt;/cite&gt;
					
	&lt;/figcaption&gt;

			
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“When you have a disability people can’t see, you don’t get the same level of empathy,” Joy says. “It feels like the world has moved on.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	THE CDC DEFINES LONG COVID as a wide array of chronic symptoms — including fatigue, difficulty concentrating, memory changes, and sleep disturbances — that began after an infection with the virus and last more than three months. The most recent data from HHS estimated that, as of December 2024, around 22 million American adults had the illness at some point. More than nine million were still sick with it by the end of 2023. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Data is harder to come by for children, who since the earliest days of the pandemic were noted to experience a wider-ranging and less predictable set of symptoms than adults. In February 2024, a paper published in the &lt;em&gt;Journal of the American Academy of Pediatrics&lt;/em&gt; (AAP) estimated that up to six million children in the United States had suffered from long Covid at some point. A year later, CDC researchers put the figure at closer to one million, with 300,000 actively suffering from the disease; it also noted the numbers, based on national survey data, may significantly undercount the illness’ true toll.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Whichever figure you use, the numbers are enormous, rivaling conditions like ADHD and autism as one of the most common chronic diseases in American youth today. And for the children and teens I’ve spoken with, long Covid has done serious physical and emotional damage. It’s also hindered their ability to participate in school — something that becomes an all-encompassing source of frustration for children and parents alike. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	All of the students interviewed for this story were diagnosed with long Covid. And they all met the &lt;a href="https://www.rollingstone.com/t/department-of-education/" id="auto-tag_department-of-education" data-tag="department-of-education"&gt;Department of Education&lt;/a&gt;’s (DOE) eligibility criteria for specialized school accommodations because of their illness. It’s a group that’s ballooned in size: The number of children receiving specialized accommodations increased by 500,000 after the pandemic relative to before. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	There’s Alexander, in eighth grade when the pandemic hit, the adventurer extraordinaire from Massachusetts whose Covid-related exhaustion meant tardy after tardy — but who was denied accommodations because his grades were too good. 

	&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	There’s Eliza, a kindergartner in Washington state whose severe stomach pain constantly kept her out of school, but who was denied accommodations because the principal said that “we have great teachers here.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	There’s ninth-grader William, a Mets fanatic from suburban New York, who was denied accommodations because school officials told him that “Covid is over.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Those struggles are despite a July 2021 joint statement from HHS and the Department of Justice clarifying that long Covid is a protected condition under the Americans with Disabilities Act. But early actions under the second Trump administration stand to further jeopardize their ability to access special education. An Inauguration Day executive order targeting DEI withdrew federal support through the DOE for learning loss caused by the pandemic, including from long Covid. (The rollbacks specifically targeted special education for Hispanic, Black, and Tribal communities, whose children who faced higher rates of severe illness due to Covid, and who use special education at higher rates.) The Big Beautiful Bill’s Medicaid cuts likewise stand to dry up billions more in special education dollars. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	And should the Trump White House fulfill its campaign promises to axe the DOE entirely, billions of federal dollars upon which schools rely to support millions of children who need special education may vanish overnight. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	WITHIN THE SCIENTIFIC COMMUNITY, the legitimacy of long Covid has been a wellspring of controversy. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	What the wide-ranging long Covid symptoms have in common is that they’re a challenging combination of persistent yet intermittent, incapacitating yet invisible. Too often, especially for young people, that means adults — even doctors — “don’t believe there’s anything wrong with the child,” says Alexandra Yonts, a pediatric infectious disease specialist who is also the director of the post-Covid program at Children’s National Hospital in Washington, D.C. “They think they’re being a teenager.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;blockquote class="pullquote larva // a-blockquote-type-pullquote lrv-u-color-black u-border-tb-2 lrv-u-margin-lr-00 lrv-u-text-align-center u-padding-lr-150@tablet lrv-u-padding-tb-150@mobile-max lrv-u-padding-tb-2 u-margin-tb-250@tablet lrv-u-margin-tb-2@mobile-max u-font-weight-900 u-font-family-theme-primary lrv-u-font-size-38@tablet lrv-u-font-size-32 u-line-height-30 u-line-height-36@tablet   "&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;“I’m battling with the school because they don’t believe anything is wrong with Dakota. They don’t believe he has long Covid. They don’t believe long Covid exists.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Michelle Hooker, Dakota Presnell’s mother&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	At various points, skeptical doctors have attributed the symptoms to a kind of neurosis: patient as hypochondriac, equipped with a fancy new diagnosis. “It is hard to know if this kind of long-tail phenomenon is more pronounced or more common [with Covid],” Adam Lauring, an infectious disease doctor at the University of Michigan, &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2020/06/11/coronavirus-chronic/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/em&gt; in June of 2020, “or we are just seeing things that come to our attention because there is a heightened awareness.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Other doctors have chalked up the symptoms to a kind of societal malaise: patient as emotional sponge in a chaotic world, sickness quite literally all in their heads. “Whether long Covid can be considered just a consequence of a viral infection or should be attributed to the implications of ‘the pandemic era’ we are now living in is still a matter of debate,” Achille Marino and Rolando Cimaz, pediatric rheumatologists at the University of Milan, &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/pidj/fulltext/2022/01000/long_coronavirus_disease_in_pediatric_rheumatology.30.aspx" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt; in 2022 in the journal of the European Society for Paediatric Infectious Diseases.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Some in the medical community have even called for dumping the diagnosis altogether. “It is time to stop using terms like ‘Long Covid,’” John Gerrard, former chief health officer of Queensland, Australia, &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1037611" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt; in a press release for a March 2024 study comparing symptoms of Covid patients to those with the flu. “This terminology can cause unnecessary fear, and in some cases, hypervigilance to longer symptoms that can impede recovery.”

	&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Another piece of the long Covid puzzle is a practical issue: getting diagnosed. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	According to Elizabeth Pray, former president of Washington state’s chapter of the National Association of School Nurses, who herself has cared for numerous kids with symptoms of long Covid, there are two major steps in the diagnostic odyssey. First, the child needs a documented Covid infection. Second, they need to find a doctor able — and willing — to make the diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	But many kids may not have tested at the time of their infection, Pray says. Months into the pandemic, the U.S. faced severe shortages in Covid tests for everyone. Well into the winter of 2022, major retailers like CVS and Walgreens were still rationing tests to favor adults, who were at greater risk of severe illness and death. At various points, tests were restricted for kids under 16 years of age, and then under 12. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Even in kids who did test, studies show that &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanepe/article/PIIS2666-7762(21)00115-0/fulltext" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;up to 90 percent of cases can go missed&lt;/a&gt; due to differences in how kids’ immune systems handle the virus. “If you have families that didn’t test,” Pray says, “how would you tie it back to know how big the problem is?” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	In the situation where a child does have a confirmed case, finding a doctor to ink the long Covid diagnosis can still be a challenge. According to the patient advocacy group Long Covid Alliance, there are fewer than a dozen long-Covid pediatric clinics across the country, compared with 400 adult clinics. That means many kids who live far from major medical centers — like Pray’s students in Moses Lake, a town of 25,000 that’s 200 miles from Seattle — won’t ever be seen at such a clinic. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Dakota Presnell was one of those kids. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Before the blackouts, the vertigo, the sniffle and the cough, Dakota’s childhood in the seaside North Carolina vacation town of Manteo was idyllic. 

	&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;div class="post-content-image //  "&gt;
	

&lt;figure class="o-figure   size-large alignnone lrv-u-max-width-100p"&gt;

			

	
			
			
&lt;figcaption class="c-figcaption  lrv-u-flex lrv-u-flex-direction-column lrv-u-align-items-center"&gt;
	
					&lt;span class="u-border-color-black u-border-lr-2 lrv-u-padding-tb-025 lrv-u-padding-lr-075 lrv-u-border-b-2 lrv-u-width-100p lrv-u-text-align-center a-font-basic-secondary-s"&gt;Dakota Presnell on a dock in Manteo, North Carolina. He used to spend the summers roller skating and playing in the ocean, his mom says, before his long-Covid symptoms hit.&lt;/span&gt;
		
									&lt;cite class="lrv-u-text-transform-uppercase lrv-a-font-body-xs lrv-u-margin-t-050 lrv-u-text-align-center"&gt;Eli Cahan&lt;/cite&gt;
					
	&lt;/figcaption&gt;

			
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	He’d spend summers leaping off story-high footbridges and docks and jetties, and slipping down slides into the rollicking Atlantic surrounding Roanoke Island. In the off-season, he’d roller skate down deserted streets and frequent the laser tag arena or the bowling alley, playing one or the other until they closed up shop.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Dakota was “a happy-go-lucky kid,” his mother, Michelle Hooker, says. “It was hard to keep him home… He was always on the go, always doing something.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Then, sixth grade. Winter, 2021. Omicron.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Dakota had gone back to school in-person and — like many who contracted Covid’s most infectious variant — he was quickly bedridden, Michelle says. Of all his symptoms, the dizziness and fatigue were the worst. At one point, a friend told Michelle that she should “look into” long Covid; she’d bring it up time and time again with Dakota’s pediatrician, to little avail.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	In the summer of 2022, the blackouts started. Out of nowhere, like a limp marionette, Dakota would drop to the ground. Michelle “became his legs,” she says, as she’d carry her son from room to room. By the fall his fatigue and fainting spells were a “complete and utter nightmare.” By January 2024, Dakota’s symptoms also included memory loss and severe pain in his arms and legs that he couldn’t shake. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Michelle says that, during this time, they went to loads of doctors — pediatricians, neurologists, the works — and racked up several hospitalizations where they were seen by still more clinical teams. They accrued loads of diagnoses: non-epileptic seizures, amplified musculoskeletal pain syndrome, functional neurologic disorder.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	That last diagnosis, in particular, irked Michelle. “That’s a fancy way of saying it’s all in your head,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Long Covid, she adds, never made the list.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	To Yonts, at Children’s National, experiences like Dakota’s are no longer surprising. She’s heard story after story of undiagnosed patients who, by the time they make it to her clinic, have been seen by doctors who “think there’s something else going on, [something] not physical.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	At the same time, Yonts knows specialized long Covid clinics, including hers, can’t see the vast majority of patients who request a visit: Their capacity is “woefully inadequate,” she says. “We’ve had really lengthy waitlists for most of our existence.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	FOR KIDS LIKE DAKOTA suffering from long Covid, navigating school is a mess, too. 

	&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Under &lt;a href="https://www2.ed.gov/about/offices/list/ocr/504faq.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;federal law&lt;/a&gt;, any student with a “physical or mental impairment” impacting their ability to participate in school is entitled to accommodations under a so-called 504 or an Individualized Education (IEP) plan. The DOE’s language is deliberately inclusive: Such entitlements stand whether students are diagnosed with — or are “regarded to have” — any such impairment, William Koski, director of the Youth and Education Law Project at Stanford University, says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="post-content-image //  "&gt;
	

&lt;figure class="o-figure   size-large alignnone lrv-u-max-width-100p"&gt;

			

	
			
			
&lt;figcaption class="c-figcaption  lrv-u-flex lrv-u-flex-direction-column lrv-u-align-items-center"&gt;
	
					&lt;span class="u-border-color-black u-border-lr-2 lrv-u-padding-tb-025 lrv-u-padding-lr-075 lrv-u-border-b-2 lrv-u-width-100p lrv-u-text-align-center a-font-basic-secondary-s"&gt;A table of contents for one of many notebooks maintained by Dakota’s mom, Michelle, charting his medical care and correspondence with the school district.&lt;/span&gt;
		
									&lt;cite class="lrv-u-text-transform-uppercase lrv-a-font-body-xs lrv-u-margin-t-050 lrv-u-text-align-center"&gt;Eli Cahan&lt;/cite&gt;
					
	&lt;/figcaption&gt;

			
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	The accommodations provided under the plans can run a broad spectrum. They include everything from rest breaks to extra time to provision of quiet spaces for testing. They can also be more tailored: For example, for children with conditions that put them at risk of passing out — in which staying hydrated is critical — accommodations can include things like keeping pretzels or a water bottle at their desk. More intensive plans can include tutors or &lt;a href="https://www.nea.org/professional-excellence/student-engagement/tools-tips/differences-between-504-plan-and-individualized-education-program-iep" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;“changes to the curricular expectations”&lt;/a&gt; altogether.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Since the onset of the pandemic, the number of school-aged students with IEPs has jumped. In the 2018-2019 school year, 6.3 million children received special education services. In 2022-2023, 6.8 million did. Still, some long-Covid families say they’ve been in the dark when it comes to accommodations. In some cases, they’ve faced pushback for seeking special education.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	That’s true for people like Lia, who had a pre-existing special education plan for ADHD, and who had, by then, a long Covid diagnosis. But Lia struggled to convince her school to provide additional accommodations for her fatigue, nausea, and frequent absences. After much back and forth, the school offered a compromise: She could have two extra days to hand in her homework. Oh, and she could go to the bathroom when she needed to. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“That was really the only change that they gave us,” Lia says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“If there had been other options,” Joy adds, “they weren’t discussed or offered.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	The obstacles to accommodations have been especially stark for people like Michelle and Dakota, who hadn’t previously navigated special education, and who lacked a formal diagnosis of long Covid. It took more than three years before Michelle realized they could even seek help. “[The school] didn’t give us any information,” Dakota says. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	When they finally did hear through Facebook about the possibility of a 504 — and started pinging the school to advocate — things quickly became contentious.

	&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“I’m battling the school,” Michelle says, “[because] they don’t believe anything is wrong with Dakota.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	(Dare County Schools, Dakota’s district, did not respond to requests for comment.)&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	To Laura Malone, pediatrician and director of the Post-Covid-19 Rehabilitation Clinic at Kennedy Krieger Institute in Baltimore, part of the trouble around accommodations traces back to lack of knowledge around the illness. “Long Covid is a newer diagnosis…[that] schools, education systems aren’t as aware of,” Malone says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Michelle puts it more bluntly. “They don’t believe he has long Covid,” she says of the school. “They don’t believe long Covid exists.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	AFTER MONTHS OF BATTLING, by the beginning of eighth grade in fall 2023, Dakota successfully got a 504 plan. Theoretically, that entitled him to extra time on tests and deadlines, as well as breaks throughout the school day. On paper, it was a version of school that retained a sense of normalcy while being feasible given his fatigue and brain fog. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Unfortunately, the text on paper didn’t translate to real life, Michelle says. The plan “didn’t do much — he was still expected to [take] all these classes, carry all of this homework, do the daily assignments,” she says. “It was kind of a B.S., fly-by-the-seat-of-your-pants type answer.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	In this way, Dakota and Michelle’s experience reflects a different issue with learning accommodations: the difficulty implementing and enforcing them.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	One of the biggest pieces of the implementation issue is that of dogma, Kathy Riley, nurse at the Plymouth school district in Massachusetts and co-lead for the National Association of School Nurses’ long Covid efforts, says. There are cases where teachers, much like some school officials, simply disagree with the notion that long Covid is real, or that kids with it need help. “The teachers have to buy into the accommodations…or it’s not going to work,” Riley says. “If a teacher doesn’t really agree with it, then the kid doesn’t get it.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	That gets into the problem of enforcement, which typically falls upon the districts themselves. The DOE’s Office of Civil Rights “generally will not evaluate the content” of 504s or IEPs, the agency &lt;a href="https://www.ed.gov/laws-and-policy/civil-rights-laws/disability-discrimination/frequently-asked-questions-section-504-fape" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;states&lt;/a&gt; on its website. Nor does it “review the result of individual placement or other educational decisions.” Instead, “any disagreement can be resolved through a due process hearing.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	But a &lt;a href="https://www.gao.gov/products/gao-20-22" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;2019 report&lt;/a&gt; from the Government Accountability Office found that the ability and willingness of families to pursue such hearings varies widely due to language barriers, ability to find an attorney, legal costs, and fears of retaliation, among other factors. Such barriers were particularly marked in low-income school districts, which on average have more children of color, and which tend to have higher numbers of children with disabilities. 

	&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;blockquote class="pullquote larva // a-blockquote-type-pullquote lrv-u-color-black u-border-tb-2 lrv-u-margin-lr-00 lrv-u-text-align-center u-padding-lr-150@tablet lrv-u-padding-tb-150@mobile-max lrv-u-padding-tb-2 u-margin-tb-250@tablet lrv-u-margin-tb-2@mobile-max u-font-weight-900 u-font-family-theme-primary lrv-u-font-size-38@tablet lrv-u-font-size-32 u-line-height-30 u-line-height-36@tablet   "&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;At various points, skeptical doctors have attributed the symptoms to a kind of neurosis: patient as hypochondriac, equipped with a fancy new diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“Many parents feel they are at a disadvantage in a conflict with the school district due to an imbalance of power and so may be reluctant to engage in dispute resolution,” the report concluded. (The DOE did not comment on inquiries from &lt;em&gt;Rolling Stone&lt;/em&gt; about the inability of students with long Covid to receive 504s or IEPs, or lack of enforcement of 504s or IEPs in cases where they are granted. )&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Recent reporting suggests that kids’ access to special education may worsen further following widespread cuts to the DOE. In March, the administration &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/13/us/politics/trump-education-department-civil-rights.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;hollowed out&lt;/a&gt; the department’s Office of Civil Rights — including entire investigative teams in the majority of regions — leaving thousands of pending cases in limbo, according to the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt;. And in May, &lt;em&gt;ProPu&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;blica&lt;/em&gt; found that, in the period following the cuts, hundreds fewer ongoing cases &lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/education-department-civil-rights-donald-trump-discrimination" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;were investigated&lt;/a&gt;, and new cases were dismissed outright at rates 30 percent higher than previously. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	In late September, Maryland Sen. Angela Alsobrooks introduced a bill to exempt funding for special education from any future DOE cuts. “Any attempt to slash programs and protections for our students with disabilities is beyond callous,” Alsobrooks said in a press release. Still, by October — amid the government shutdown — mass layoffs were &lt;a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/special-education-staff-decimated-after-trump-administration-shutdown/story?id=126432474" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;imperiling the DOE’s ability&lt;/a&gt; to administer special education, department sources told &lt;em&gt;ABC News&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	To Dakota, politics shouldn’t play a role in whether kids with long Covid get the support they need. That’s true for teachers not following certain special education plans rather than others. It’s also true for government-wide initiatives that pull out the rug from under children like him.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“People are inclined to their opinion,” Dakota says, “but at the same time, in some situations, like [with] long Covid…opinions get in the way.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	THE TUG-OF-WAR AROUND accommodations comes at a time when fewer American students are attending school than ever before.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	In January 2024, a study published in the &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences&lt;/em&gt; found that chronic absenteeism — defined as the number of students missing at least one out of every 10 school days — &lt;a href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.2312249121" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;nearly doubled&lt;/a&gt; following the Covid pandemic. Every state saw increases in chronic absenteeism, the study found: In total, nearly 30 percent — some 13 million children — regularly missed school.

	&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	The alarm bells around the absenteeism crisis partly relate to learning loss. In January 2025, an annual Congressional analysis known as the “nation’s report card” found that American students’ achievement levels were declining to some of the &lt;a href="https://www.nagb.gov/news-and-events/news-releases/2025/nations-report-card-decline-in-reading-progress-in-math.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;worst in recent history&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	The alarm is also related to money. Attendance is one of the key factors that determines school funding in most states. That incentivizes schools to do what they can to make sure students show up, since absences can only hurt their bottom line. As a result, some districts are taking a punitive approach to chronic absenteeism. On one extreme is Missouri, where, following an August 2023 decision from the state’s Supreme Court, parents of children with poor attendance records &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/missouri-school-absences-tardy-attendance-fa2372189ee7cb55e59aa35165d9691c" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;are now liable&lt;/a&gt; for jail time.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	A more common mechanism involves truancy. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	States like Indiana are &lt;a href="https://indianacapitalchronicle.com/2024/03/08/i-cant-teach-a-kid-thats-not-there-indiana-lawmakers-give-final-approval-to-absenteeism-bill/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;already moving to toughen truancy laws&lt;/a&gt; by introducing bills to tighten attendance requirements and immediately refer families for investigation in ways that can lead to prosecution of children, parents, or both. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Truancy hinges on defining an absence as unexcused. But that’s a definition “really dependent on the school itself,” Christy McGill, deputy superintendent for educator effectiveness and family engagement for the Nevada Department of Education, says. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	For example, some schools may require doctors’ notes for every missed day, McGill says, while others do not. Studies have found that children of color were &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/full/10.1177/23328584211003132" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;up to four times more likely&lt;/a&gt; to have their absences marked unexcused than those who were white.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	&lt;em&gt;Rolling Stone&lt;/em&gt; contacted every state’s education department for this article, the majority of which did not respond to requests for comment. Most of those that did — Colorado, Kentucky, Oregon, and Utah among them — lack visibility into the reasons for excused versus unexcused absences. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Such variability worries Hedy Chang, executive director of Attendance Works, a national nonprofit organization focused on chronic absenteeism. “Unfortunately, across the United States, absences are too often deemed ‘unexcused’ for arbitrary reasons,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	The lack of clarity around excused versus unexcused absences includes those potentially related to medical conditions such as long Covid. Even as large-scale reviews of children with long Covid find &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC9476461/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;absenteeism to be a consistent issue&lt;/a&gt;, schools have little insight into whether poor attendance in their district may derive, in part, from kids struggling with the condition. “There’s no question there could be long Covid symptoms out there we don’t know about,” Eric Mackey, Alabama’s state superintendent of education, says, “[but] I don’t have any information on that.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	(The DOE did not respond to inquiries from &lt;em&gt;Rolling Stone&lt;/em&gt; about policies for determining unexcused absences or the initiation of truancy investigations. The agency also did not respond to inquiries about how schools should incorporate protections under the Americans with Disabilities Act into their policies around absences or truancy.)

	&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;blockquote class="pullquote larva // a-blockquote-type-pullquote lrv-u-color-black u-border-tb-2 lrv-u-margin-lr-00 lrv-u-text-align-center u-padding-lr-150@tablet lrv-u-padding-tb-150@mobile-max lrv-u-padding-tb-2 u-margin-tb-250@tablet lrv-u-margin-tb-2@mobile-max u-font-weight-900 u-font-family-theme-primary lrv-u-font-size-38@tablet lrv-u-font-size-32 u-line-height-30 u-line-height-36@tablet   "&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;“We’ve been beat up and chewed up, and it’s not fair, because Dakota’s falling through the cracks. His light is getting dimmer and dimmer — because he’s losing hope.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Michelle Hooker&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Many of the families I spoke to, at one point or another, found themselves staring down threats of truancy. For some, those threats came via robocall after robocall. For Dakota and Michelle, they came in meetings with school officials. And for Lia and Joy, they came more insidiously. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“I always wondered what my teachers thought,” Lia says. “They knew I was sick — but did they believe me, [or] did they think I was making it up?”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	So, when Lia’s medical waiver fell off seemingly overnight in the fall of 2022, Joy was concerned. If Lia missed 10 days of a given course, she’d automatically fail — if not worse, when it came to the specter of truancy.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	(Charlotte-Mecklenburg Schools, Lia’s district, did not respond to requests for comment.)&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“I tried to communicate from the beginning that…there is no way, at this point, she is not going to miss more,” Joy says. “[But] it didn’t matter. It felt like she was being punished for being ill.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	AFTER MONTHS OF FRUITLESS morning wake-ups and early afternoon pickups, tardies and absences and missed assignments, months of blackouts and vomiting and forgetfulness and dozing off, Dakota and Lia were left with only one option: hybrid education. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Education outside the schoolyard has long been considered the option of last resort, Koski, at Stanford, says: Keeping kids with their peers “is one of the bedrock principles of …the disability rights movement.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Based on how their accommodations were implemented, though, the families I interviewed say they felt trapped. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	In Lia’s case, even as her 504 entitled her to two extra days to submit homework, she kept racking up absences for not bringing it to class on the original due date. And even as she and Joy heard through the grapevine that other students across the country struggling with long Covid were offered additional services, such IEPs that included hybrid school with teachers coming to their homes for in-person tutoring, she was never offered such a plan.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“Given how the school was handling [accommodations], and their procedures, and their rules, I really had no choice but to switch to virtual school,” Lia says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	That switch came with its own costs. She was always missing out: parties, prom, homecomings. She kept finding herself on the outside of inside jokes. She lost close friends, who accused her of being flaky, or avoiding them entirely. “It’s still affecting me to this day,” Lia says.

	&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Dakota found himself in a similar spot when, this past summer — after Michelle finally had an opportunity to advocate for his special education plan — officials rendered a decision: Dakota would be enrolled at Dare Learning Academy, the district’s “alternative” educational option. It was the worst of both worlds: simultaneously denying Dakota additional accommodations and punting him further to the margins. It also felt like confirmation of what his family had dreaded: that school officials saw him as undisciplined or unmotivated rather than sick. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	To Michelle and Dakota, the decision felt premeditated: People “sometimes have their minds made up before we even see them,” Dakota says. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	It’s hard to know whether the experiences of kids like Lia and Dakota are becoming more common. The most recent data available from the DOE shows that the number of students in homebound or hospital-bound, residential facility, or separate school-based programs has stayed roughly stable since the pandemic. But that data doesn’t account for the kind of hybrid education that became mainstream during the pandemic. (The DOE did not comment on inquiries from &lt;em&gt;Rolling Stone &lt;/em&gt;about how students in hybrid school settings are counted.)  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	The longer-term consequences on a generation of struggling children taught without adequate support — or via hybrid education — are also not yet clear, says Susan Kressly, president of the American Academy of Pediatrics. But, based on what she’s seen, she’s afraid that “every community is going to pay the price in the long run.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“We absolutely know the best place for a kid is in school,” Kressly says. In virtual education, she adds, “are we just putting them out of sight?” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Some parents — like Michelle — are already observing changes in their children.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	“We’ve been beat up and chewed up, no one’s taken account for what they’ve done, and it’s not fair, because he’s falling through the cracks,” she says of Dakota. “As long as this goes on,” she adds, “his light is getting dimmer and dimmer — because he’s losing hope.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Dakota, for his part, still has big dreams. He wants to live in a big city (Norfolk, Virginia), and work a demanding job (general surgeon). Dakota thinks he’ll be good, too: “I know how to listen and take other people’s opinions and worries into account,” he says.

	&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	But Dakota also knows he faces long odds. And he knows how much his illness plays a role in that. “Long Covid has taken my life and turned it around,” Dakota says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Lia is also trying to concentrate on the future. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	After she got into a pediatric long Covid clinic and began implementing a variety of different treatments — salt tabs day and night, electrolyte powder infused in every drink, this and that medication prescribed off-label — slowly but surely, she has been feeling better. So, she’s got her eyes on the prize. A high school diploma. A college welcome weekend. Most recently, a beauty pageant title. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	Even still, life looks different now. In particular, there’s a void where her friends and classmates used to be. “I’m back,” Lia says, “and at the same time, so much has changed, because I’ve missed out on so much.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	This fall, she was excited to make a fresh start at college. New place, new people, new her. A her that feels like the real her. Not the long Covid version. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	College “is a place where no one really knows me,” Lia says. “I can start over — and kind of, maybe, separate myself from the illness a little bit.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="paragraph larva // lrv-u-line-height-copy  lrv-a-font-body-l   "&gt;
	&lt;em&gt;This reporting was supported by the Fund for Investigative Journalism.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
















&lt;/div&gt;																	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Rolling Stone</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxNTk9LbkpXY3laQ25nZGFNSXVvNmM3V1NZdmt3OFJZZU5sZlpKV0RIZ3VBazZkUWlKakl4U29CMWVRdGdfRUVvOUtRN3VwZ3VOckhpelZuUV94dEdZR1JTOG8ybWpON1U4Y0RyY2xpS2o3OUlmcHhwVmNtc3dkYjdIbWpFMldJTTJTLWtMc0lXd2RxVWpmQi1HRnRzeHpaZk55TWc</guid></item><item><title>每个40岁以上的人都需要的五种血液检测-《每日电讯报》</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/conditions/ageing/essential-blood-tests-over-40/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;p&gt;Amongst all the newfangled tech now out there to track different health metrics, the humble blood test is still the mainstay of a good, proactive health regime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I advise everyone that I train in the gym to get these regular checks to ensure their health is on track, particularly those in their forties and onwards. We can expect to live well into our eighties these days, but around 40, our bodies do start to break down in a more significant way. &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/advice/blood-tests-before-and-after-holiday-results/"&gt;Blood tests&lt;/a&gt; are a great way to keep track of what is happening inside of your system as that happens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;The blood test to check your cholesterol&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of us know that there is “good” cholesterol (high-density lipoprotein, or HDL) and “bad” cholesterol (low-density lipoprotein, or LDL). Cholesterol gets a bad rap generally but it’s there for a reason, to repair the damage in your blood vessels. The truly important thing is the balance between your HDL, which is made by your liver and small intestine, and your LDL, which is also produced by your liver, but can enter your system through animal fats too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both HDL and LDL play a role in keeping you healthy and a fairly even split is what is best for most people – though your doctor might advise you on the levels that you, in particular, should aim for. The NHS recommends that you keep your HDL at 1/1.2 or above, and your LDL below 3. An imbalance indicates that there is a problem somewhere in your system: if you’re accumulating too much LDL, it might be that you have atherosclerosis, which causes heart blockages and plaque build-ups in your arteries.&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNLWJRYnFaVVdIdzIybUgzRmNOdUNJc0J0bTN2SW9OSHZDRW85cEFYMnpURVpZaTY5SEtDRXhCanJMRWZVV1V6OUl6SFB5VExISzMwUnpYVlhleFF0YzUxc2RRM3BHc2EzZ0p1UlVBZXp6TDlEaEE0NG82cVhWMU9tdEdtbXoyMUpHSy05aXltVVBnNGFwWEE</guid></item><item><title>您可能不知道的7种最佳蛋白质棒- GQ</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/the-7-best-protein-bars-you-probably-dont-know</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best for:&lt;/strong&gt; Nose-to-tail adherents with Purell nearby or a tolerance for fingerprints on phone screens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardBody-hIYvDT cYxZHF product-embed" data-item='{"ctaHref":"https://cna.st/p/bfsED2YUx11p2RJtJxa7RrCgnm97eB6qHU4u1kJsJuhbT3YjzBgCwC4BjkembrrENe54L97uacGrYkuRFV44UNAWRgejCxbWn3aAd2DZVfeS8hkUCXs5ciRPYF8HHsbCkFwiaqMccVckU5C6nqdfnqWn89PGufwjorCShdyri9hbLtrWrNifMzDq7CG1eCbuhF5u6kkqSwha9kWtQL9mweu3azhdXrhtU9aSqbKGdipxVJ36jCsiLgNyVvT5dyCr74BCKBir1p6Q32okX8zR94qdUGLptn16ThQSXj7Ewo8wRDAazdLgduLGfkcGZjNgSHvuuCuLLp3456NdE75Wt37NJPpJM6rfyh8QPh464WKxEcRCgi8AYXm9geARuseKmQSWDU7CA8k9x1YdugsPr2CdiNQ4UEsKjYtgbwGR3gpmGfa9Nj","dangerousDek":"","productBrand":"Prima","dangerousHed":"Ancestral Protein Bar - Cookie Dough","embedSize":null,"isFirstProduct":false,"image":{"altText":null,"credit":null,"sources":{"sm":{"aspectRatio":"3:4","width":320,"url":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_320,c_limit/bars5.jpg","srcset":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_120,c_limit/bars5.jpg 120w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_240,c_limit/bars5.jpg 240w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_320,c_limit/bars5.jpg 320w"},"md":{"aspectRatio":"3:4","width":720,"url":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_720,c_limit/bars5.jpg","srcset":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_120,c_limit/bars5.jpg 120w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_240,c_limit/bars5.jpg 240w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_320,c_limit/bars5.jpg 320w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_640,c_limit/bars5.jpg 640w"},"lg":{"aspectRatio":"3:4","width":748,"url":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_748,c_limit/bars5.jpg","srcset":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_120,c_limit/bars5.jpg 120w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_240,c_limit/bars5.jpg 240w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_320,c_limit/bars5.jpg 320w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_640,c_limit/bars5.jpg 640w"},"xl":{"aspectRatio":"3:4","width":748,"url":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_748,c_limit/bars5.jpg","srcset":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_120,c_limit/bars5.jpg 120w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_240,c_limit/bars5.jpg 240w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_320,c_limit/bars5.jpg 320w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326cbd9adf8925b5529/3:4/w_640,c_limit/bars5.jpg 640w"}}},"isSponsored":false,"offerRetailer":"Prima","offerUrl":"https://eatprima.com/pages/ancestral-protein-bar","contentType":"product","productId":"68ed54d8a9c348b100b223e2","productOfferVariation":"PriceOutsideCenter","showOfferUrl":false,"showPriceOnButton":true,"showAffiliateDisclaimerOnFirstProduct":false,"dangerousCredit":null,"showLocalisedOffers":true,"isUpcEnabled":true,"showClampedProductDescription":true,"productDescriptionLineLength":3,"hasReadMoreFeature":false,"index":7,"hasAffiliateLinkDisabled":false,"isMobileView":false,"hasMultipleImageSupport":true,"showImageCreditText":true,"showMultipleImageCount":4,"hasProsConsFeature":false,"hasRatingFeature":false,"pros":[],"cons":[],"rating":"","shouldUseAmazonPrimeDayLiveAPIData":true,"contentInfo":{"contentUrl":"https://www.gq.com/story/the-7-best-protein-bars-you-probably-dont-know","contentName":"The 7 Best Protein Bars You Probably Don’t Know About"},"enableGtmFixesIntersectionObserver":false,"enableGtmFixesUseRef":false,"textBadge":null,"seal":null,"id":"68ed54d8a9c348b100b223e2","brand":{"name":"Prima"},"offers":[{"offerUrl":"https://eatprima.com/pages/ancestral-protein-bar","price":"$24","currency":"USD","purchaseUri":"https://cna.st/p/bfsED2YUx11p2RJtJxa7RrCgnm97eB6qHU4u1kJsJuhbT3YjzBgCwC4BjkembrrENe54L97uacGrYkuRFV44UNAWRgejCxbWn3aAd2DZVfeS8hkUCXs5ciRPYF8HHsbCkFwiaqMccVckU5C6nqdfnqWn89PGufwjorCShdyri9hbLtrWrNifMzDq7CG1eCbuhF5u6kkqSwha9kWtQL9mweu3azhdXrhtU9aSqbKGdipxVJ36jCsiLgNyVvT5dyCr74BCKBir1p6Q32okX8zR94qdUGLptn16ThQSXj7Ewo8wRDAazdLgduLGfkcGZjNgSHvuuCuLLp3456NdE75Wt37NJPpJM6rfyh8QPh464WKxEcRCgi8AYXm9geARuseKmQSWDU7CA8k9x1YdugsPr2CdiNQ4UEsKjYtgbwGR3gpmGfa9Nj","sellerName":"Prima","countryCode":"US","offerId":"68ed54d8a9c348b100b223e1","reducedPrice":""}],"component":"unified_product_card","total_index":1,"hasMultipleImage":false,"componentType":true,"showProsConsData":false,"videoIds":[],"offersLength":1}'&gt;&lt;div id="68ed54d8a9c348b100b223e2" class="UnifiedLandscapeProductCardWrapper-lpCYz jIpDWx"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardContainer-jfmyrc hJJXyx"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetailsContainer-jzIVFy dEeeEw"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetailsWrapper-ieavYi hsDOut"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetails-dTZxUl hEAQFX"&gt;&lt;p class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardBrandName-kmvqXz deqABF AOBEo llymtF upc-brandName"&gt;Prima&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardNameWrapper-fsdgKv deqABF fUMMUG kngrYw"&gt;&lt;h3 id="upc_68ed54d8a9c348b100b223e2" type="embed" class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardName-jDmuEE deqABF gKpkyK goVFxQ"&gt;Ancestral Protein Bar - Cookie Dough&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Power Fit Foods Bare Bar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Macros:&lt;/strong&gt; 20g protein, 15g fat, 12g carbs (0g fiber, 12g sugar), 280 calories&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protein source:&lt;/strong&gt; grass-fed beef protein&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can tell this is an authentic family-run business because on the FAQ page on their website—under “What makes Power Fit Foods different from other protein snacks?”—they, endearingly, seem to have accidentally left an internal edit note: &lt;em&gt;This ingredient list mostly describes Bare Bars. Do we want this to be about Bare Bars or all the products?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is by far the thickest of the bars here but also the fluffiest. It has a whipped nougat mouth feel rather than the slow chew of a nut butter based bar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I particularly enjoy the Honey flavor (though the ingredient itself, honey, is present in all five flavors) which tastes like a brown butter meringue, maybe. The ingredients list is short: beef tallow, beef protein, raw honey, and salt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more protein (and 1,000 calories) Power Fit also makes an interesting circular snack called The PowerPuck, which has similar ingredients to the Bare Bar, plus pork rinds cooked in pork fat, and the slogan: “Pure. Satiating. Power.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best for:&lt;/strong&gt; Ingredient minimalists looking for an airy mouthfeel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardBody-hIYvDT cYxZHF product-embed" data-item='{"ctaHref":"https://cna.st/p/4jRkjnASZ8FuqsBD5ttqawrnShc6bavQXDEugKRa6TmS9BFsrCAFHcNokTJvYhkruSQhptFtZzNJa3Woob4n82C3eHrmG8Ne82L3dX9FbpfoCaTThYKXCzeK8Lo4Gg2smX8MHBhJFngnNb2846LGHv9nFhUj38bwnzjCDmCHcSYyW7sGmdK37gUoTqgvdnPWNgV3NrjAkR96qsrfEVzF5HbosZnubGpuPAGQe6h529LH5z4jkrUnY5JnbizX5PPPRRnFzNsRpDBmV67YFv7b99XppzFTX9KJq6ehK6t7aU3vnj6Am4587kvzxQhsEKKGPbJtmTEDA9y826mkScRkJsDrn1L4K8k1CoTDU65HP3KU3ukMXbTP84KLCDbzZq6ectDquzAAepxKvbqBPw1uoQ1szsfJSg4wQNhhGTvesr7dgb9J2baTY9oh1saiM7ERroLocZ3pQAyccWaArS1FCUeaCN9AC21qvGxGr1tWjysMWnRrTedNjXWWDBuAFgcyAHQnv51dWSrHxV3uENghFY7rtmqnePsJyVWfuwJwN3iWkSFX1JfkDU7jB9vt7yBQCyW9mBmuWGHNFDZofUAxfbk4Ai1YNfKUxvhyKXRpDWUqm8EU82NDWGHKc3hcYxxZFmKoHAvw9rvByPQaPYmrymLbV1sUekbe7CWJENKLKUCm5gms83dbp6czLq8ccTwCdiNJB86NUcHmZGh61TFsmYKpDNvCRyC3moNut3aqAJDjaNTxN2GoQb2spYBo5ArFavKiL7CEv9E7w7iQ7av3EE1KxsRHLmdC94PZvy7bSf1qLdaaNfM4zpDbf8Lk112QTuQ4WMH8odqw4LdaEbxxtbDsmGfW3D","dangerousDek":"","productBrand":"Bare Bar","dangerousHed":"Clean Grass-Fed Protein Bar","embedSize":null,"isFirstProduct":false,"image":{"altText":null,"credit":null,"sources":{"sm":{"aspectRatio":"3:4","width":320,"url":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_320,c_limit/bars6.jpg","srcset":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_120,c_limit/bars6.jpg 120w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_240,c_limit/bars6.jpg 240w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_320,c_limit/bars6.jpg 320w"},"md":{"aspectRatio":"3:4","width":720,"url":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_720,c_limit/bars6.jpg","srcset":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_120,c_limit/bars6.jpg 120w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_240,c_limit/bars6.jpg 240w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_320,c_limit/bars6.jpg 320w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_640,c_limit/bars6.jpg 640w"},"lg":{"aspectRatio":"3:4","width":748,"url":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_748,c_limit/bars6.jpg","srcset":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_120,c_limit/bars6.jpg 120w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_240,c_limit/bars6.jpg 240w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_320,c_limit/bars6.jpg 320w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_640,c_limit/bars6.jpg 640w"},"xl":{"aspectRatio":"3:4","width":748,"url":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_748,c_limit/bars6.jpg","srcset":"https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_120,c_limit/bars6.jpg 120w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_240,c_limit/bars6.jpg 240w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_320,c_limit/bars6.jpg 320w, https://media.gq.com/photos/68ed5326a9c348b100b223d8/3:4/w_640,c_limit/bars6.jpg 640w"}}},"isSponsored":false,"offerRetailer":"Power Fit Foods","offerUrl":"https://powerfitfoods.com/products/bare-bar?variant=49671112130864&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;currency=USD&amp;amp;utm_medium=product_sync&amp;amp;utm_source=google&amp;amp;utm_content=sag_organic&amp;amp;utm_campaign=sag_organic&amp;amp;gad_source=1&amp;amp;gad_campaignid=23086188433&amp;amp;gbraid=0AAAAApamwVFW2vKllw3jFK71KBD6Z-2gK&amp;amp;gclid=CjwKCAjwxrLHBhA2EiwAu9EdM7uG60ZbgjAjWrFa5Yn_8PI-C-acI-9yTdr5Tf8kpifYM6UkdmUulBoCYOoQAvD_BwE","contentType":"product","productId":"68ed54d8a9c348b100b223df","productOfferVariation":"PriceOutsideCenter","showOfferUrl":false,"showPriceOnButton":true,"showAffiliateDisclaimerOnFirstProduct":false,"dangerousCredit":null,"showLocalisedOffers":true,"isUpcEnabled":true,"showClampedProductDescription":true,"productDescriptionLineLength":3,"hasReadMoreFeature":false,"index":10,"hasAffiliateLinkDisabled":false,"isMobileView":false,"hasMultipleImageSupport":true,"showImageCreditText":true,"showMultipleImageCount":4,"hasProsConsFeature":false,"hasRatingFeature":false,"pros":[],"cons":[],"rating":"","shouldUseAmazonPrimeDayLiveAPIData":true,"contentInfo":{"contentUrl":"https://www.gq.com/story/the-7-best-protein-bars-you-probably-dont-know","contentName":"The 7 Best Protein Bars You Probably Don’t Know About"},"enableGtmFixesIntersectionObserver":false,"enableGtmFixesUseRef":false,"textBadge":null,"seal":null,"id":"68ed54d8a9c348b100b223df","brand":{"name":"Bare Bar"},"offers":[{"offerUrl":"https://powerfitfoods.com/products/bare-bar?variant=49671112130864&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;currency=USD&amp;amp;utm_medium=product_sync&amp;amp;utm_source=google&amp;amp;utm_content=sag_organic&amp;amp;utm_campaign=sag_organic&amp;amp;gad_source=1&amp;amp;gad_campaignid=23086188433&amp;amp;gbraid=0AAAAApamwVFW2vKllw3jFK71KBD6Z-2gK&amp;amp;gclid=CjwKCAjwxrLHBhA2EiwAu9EdM7uG60ZbgjAjWrFa5Yn_8PI-C-acI-9yTdr5Tf8kpifYM6UkdmUulBoCYOoQAvD_BwE","price":"$120","currency":"USD","purchaseUri":"https://cna.st/p/4jRkjnASZ8FuqsBD5ttqawrnShc6bavQXDEugKRa6TmS9BFsrCAFHcNokTJvYhkruSQhptFtZzNJa3Woob4n82C3eHrmG8Ne82L3dX9FbpfoCaTThYKXCzeK8Lo4Gg2smX8MHBhJFngnNb2846LGHv9nFhUj38bwnzjCDmCHcSYyW7sGmdK37gUoTqgvdnPWNgV3NrjAkR96qsrfEVzF5HbosZnubGpuPAGQe6h529LH5z4jkrUnY5JnbizX5PPPRRnFzNsRpDBmV67YFv7b99XppzFTX9KJq6ehK6t7aU3vnj6Am4587kvzxQhsEKKGPbJtmTEDA9y826mkScRkJsDrn1L4K8k1CoTDU65HP3KU3ukMXbTP84KLCDbzZq6ectDquzAAepxKvbqBPw1uoQ1szsfJSg4wQNhhGTvesr7dgb9J2baTY9oh1saiM7ERroLocZ3pQAyccWaArS1FCUeaCN9AC21qvGxGr1tWjysMWnRrTedNjXWWDBuAFgcyAHQnv51dWSrHxV3uENghFY7rtmqnePsJyVWfuwJwN3iWkSFX1JfkDU7jB9vt7yBQCyW9mBmuWGHNFDZofUAxfbk4Ai1YNfKUxvhyKXRpDWUqm8EU82NDWGHKc3hcYxxZFmKoHAvw9rvByPQaPYmrymLbV1sUekbe7CWJENKLKUCm5gms83dbp6czLq8ccTwCdiNJB86NUcHmZGh61TFsmYKpDNvCRyC3moNut3aqAJDjaNTxN2GoQb2spYBo5ArFavKiL7CEv9E7w7iQ7av3EE1KxsRHLmdC94PZvy7bSf1qLdaaNfM4zpDbf8Lk112QTuQ4WMH8odqw4LdaEbxxtbDsmGfW3D","reducedPrice":"$103","sellerName":"Power Fit Foods","countryCode":"US","offerId":"68ed54d8a9c348b100b223de"}],"component":"unified_product_card","total_index":1,"hasMultipleImage":false,"componentType":true,"showProsConsData":false,"videoIds":[],"offersLength":1}'&gt;&lt;div id="68ed54d8a9c348b100b223df" class="UnifiedLandscapeProductCardWrapper-lpCYz jIpDWx"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardContainer-jfmyrc hJJXyx"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetailsContainer-jzIVFy dEeeEw"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetailsWrapper-ieavYi hsDOut"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetails-dTZxUl hEAQFX"&gt;&lt;p class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardBrandName-kmvqXz deqABF AOBEo llymtF upc-brandName"&gt;Bare Bar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardNameWrapper-fsdgKv deqABF fUMMUG kngrYw"&gt;&lt;h3 id="upc_68ed54d8a9c348b100b223df" type="embed" class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardName-jDmuEE deqABF gKpkyK goVFxQ"&gt;Clean Grass-Fed Protein Bar&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Timbar Protein Bar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Macros:&lt;/strong&gt; 12g protein, 14g fat, 22g carbs (9g fiber, 4g sugar alcohol, 8g sugar), 220 calories&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protein source:&lt;/strong&gt; almond protein powder&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another nice dense chew to report. This one is made by a physician assistant with Celiac disease so it is certified gluten-free—which is key for anyone actually diagnosed with an intolerance because even bars without glutenous ingredients often contain trace contaminants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s a granular texture that I enjoy, sort of sandy but in a good way, like brown sugar (though sweetened with honey and erythritol). Two co-workers referred to a “crystal” aspect; others said it was “like Parmesan,” “halva,” and “a cinnamon sugar Pop-Tart and clay.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>GQ</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE5rNHZwc2NzRktjeWxCci1ycUxZaXhSODNndmtkWlRFbVp4UDJUU1FiWWVvU0h1M0pzUk9JajRER0hpQ01tdWtwelRlNGYxTzZiTDB0U1lKSjlkdTVYeGFCR2I2bWJXMXRoS21GczRFbnBRRjI2WjVQVmhQNA</guid></item><item><title>癌症疫苗在250天内阻断小鼠的多种肿瘤- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer-vaccine-blocks-multiple-tumors-in-mice-for-250-days</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A new vaccine can effectively prevent multiple types of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="177506" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;, with up to 88 percent efficacy for some forms of tumor in mouse tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like a vaccine designed to prevent or reduce illness from &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-flu-is-different-this-year-and-cases-are-surging-an-expert-explains-why"&gt;viral infections&lt;/a&gt;, this cancer vaccine works by training the immune system to attack tumors when they next appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Nanoparticles in the vaccine present a recognizable component of cancer cells as an antigen – a label that alerts our immune cells to a threat. A second material, described as a 'super' &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccine-safety/about/adjuvants.html"&gt;adjuvant&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;span&gt; further stimulates the immune system to go on the offensive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/universal-cancer-vaccine-destroys-resistant-tumors-in-mice"&gt;'Universal' Cancer Vaccine Destroys Resistant Tumors in Mice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the first tests, scientists at the University of Massachusetts Amherst vaccinated a group of mice with nanoparticles containing melanoma peptides, before exposing the test animals to melanoma cells a few weeks later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of the mice that received the nanoparticle vaccine, 80 percent survived and stayed tumor-free for the 250-day duration of the study. By contrast, all of the mice that weren't vaccinated or were given different formulations succumbed within seven weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the second test, the team used a more general antigen – a substance called tumor lysate, made of broken-up cancer cells. It was hypothesized that the lysate may alert the immune system to a range of cancer types, which would be helpful in preventative cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mice were given this version of the vaccine before being exposed to either melanoma, pancreatic, or triple-negative breast cancer. And again, the majority remained tumor-free: 88 percent of those exposed to pancreatic cancer, 75 percent for breast cancer, and 69 percent for melanoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177508" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177508" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fx1_lrg-642x486.jpg" alt="Cancer Vaccine Could Prevent The Disease in High-Risk Patients" class="wp-image-177508 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fx1_lrg-642x486.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fx1_lrg-891x675.jpg 891w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fx1_lrg-768x582.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fx1_lrg-600x454.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fx1_lrg.jpg 915w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177508" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;A graphical abstract of how the cancer vaccine works. (Kane et al., &lt;em&gt; Cell Rep. Med.&lt;/em&gt; 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers unsuccessfully attempted to simulate the spread of cancer in the surviving mice, finding 100 percent of them remained tumor-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"By engineering these nanoparticles to activate the immune system via multi-pathway activation that combines with cancer-specific antigens, we can prevent tumor growth with remarkable survival rates," &lt;a href="https://www.umass.edu/news/article/umass-amherst-researchers-create-nanoparticle-vaccine-prevents-cancer-mice"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Prabhani Atukorale, biomedical engineer at UMass Amherst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team says the key is the so-called super adjuvant, which consists of lipid nanoparticles that encapsulate two immune adjuvants and deliver them together to boost the immune response.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_launch"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Launch" class="alignnone wp-image-177073 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Of course, at this stage, the work has only been conducted in mice, so there's no guarantee that results will translate to humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this technique could potentially be adaptable to a range of different cancer types, helping to both &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-vaccine-for-two-deadly-cancers-shows-promise-in-clinical-trial"&gt;treat patients after diagnosis&lt;/a&gt; and prevent cancer from taking hold in high-risk patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in the journal &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.xcrm.2025.102415"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cell Reports Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 11:58:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxONWN1TThOeFJMUzVrUmx5RzJfN1ZHdHp2aXNTbFpJUDVYeTVZaGUwWkhqb0YxenBJRUs3b0xlejgyMk4wTWdyYjhnNDlRaHNIOXpWZzVSWExJSFpraUc0WlR5Yk9sMGdYN3lHMmF0bW85QldWakhjU1psOEtyYWM5X1dMMUxxSm16RWdEY0FXRXo</guid></item><item><title>医生分享了痴呆症的“最早”迹象-并说这是“清晰而有说服力的” - The Mirror</title><link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/health/doctor-shares-earliest-sign-dementia-36078697</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="article-body" class="ArticleBody_article__AwrJE" data-testid="body"&gt;&lt;h1 class="HeadingOne_heading-one__mmNWJ  __className_88f20d" publication="mirror"&gt;Doctor shares 'earliest' sign of dementia - and says it's 'clear and telling'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 class="LeadText_lead-text__wd_PA __className_274238" data-testid="leadtext" publication="mirror"&gt;The doctor said the symptom is "clear and telling" of someone developing one of the cognitive diseases&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="Byline_byline-container__K_Owl" data-testid="byline"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-content" class="Byline_byline-content-wrapper__Imque"&gt;&lt;div class="Byline_author-badge-date-wrapper__Q7jj1"&gt;&lt;p class="Byline_dates-container__Rqzf2"&gt;&lt;span class="" data-testid="byline-publishedDate"&gt;11:42, 16 Oct 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="Byline_updated-date__8vEV8 Byline_updated-date-with-published__ApG_G" data-testid="byline-updatedDate"&gt;Updated 12:55, 16 Oct 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="LightboxBtn_lightbox-btn__eoxYS" aria-label="Open image viewer" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-controls="image-lightbox"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX ImageEmbed_image-lead__Ti3qQ" data-testid="leadimage" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="36078696"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Doctor says 'earliest' sign of dementia is 'clear and telling'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: LordHenriVoton via Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;A doctor has revealed the "earliest" sign of dementia and &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/alzheimers-disease" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;Alzheimer's &lt;/a&gt;disease. He describes it as a "clear and telling" symptom of the &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/mental-health" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;cognitive&lt;/a&gt; conditions. &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/dementia" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;Dementia &lt;/a&gt;is a syndrome (a group of related symptoms) characterised by an ongoing decline in brain function, with numerous causes and types.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;According to the &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/nhs" target="" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt;, people often get confused about the difference between Alzheimer's disease and dementia. Alzheimer's disease is a type of dementia. Dr Stephen Cabral, a Neuropathy expert and host of The Cabral Concept podcast, shared one particular sign that could suggest dementia. He also highlighted another symptom to be aware of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;The video was titled: "The earliest sign of Alzheimer's and Dementia is getting lost more easily... This is the most clear and telling sign that somebody later in life is developing one of these cognitive diseases."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;In the brief video, Dr Cabral explained: "The earliest sign of dementia and Alzheimer's that truly is an indicator, not the mis-recalling of memories or words or names, but it's actually the number one is getting lost more easily. If you're younger and stressed, you forget where you put your keys, you forget someone's name, you forget the next thing that you were supposed to do? Not uncommon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BoxStyles_box-container__Qk3WH BoxStyles_non-commercial__aiWwo undefined" data-testid="recommended-1" publication="mirror"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;"What would be uncommon even when you're younger is to say, 'I don't know where I am right now. I'm lost.' That's a different story than not being able to recall something."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="HtmlEmbed_container__x6svQ"&gt;&lt;figure data-testid="embed-placeholder" class="EmbedPlaceholder_figure__NLMFl undefined false"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 90 90" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" data-testid="consent-placeholder-icon"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_10846_5865)"&gt;&lt;circle opacity="0.16" cx="45" cy="45" r="33.75" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-neutral-default)"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M21.1351 21.1351C15.0276 27.2427 11.25 35.6802 11.25 45C11.25 63.6396 26.3604 78.75 45 78.75C54.3198 78.75 62.7573 74.9724 68.8649 68.8649M21.1351 21.1351C27.2427 15.0276 35.6802 11.25 45 11.25C63.6396 11.25 78.75 26.3604 78.75 45C78.75 54.3198 74.9724 62.7573 68.8649 68.8649M21.1351 21.1351L68.8649 68.8649" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-neutral-default)" stroke-width="7.5" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_10846_5865"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Content cannot be displayed without consent&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="BoxStyles_box-container__Qk3WH BoxStyles_non-commercial__aiWwo undefined" data-testid="non-commercial-1" publication="mirror"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;The doctor also revealed a secondary warning sign that could point to dementia. He described it as '1B', meaning it is just secondary to the first symptom. He added: "And a 1B that they gave, let's say that's the 1A, a 1B would say that they're no longer able to park straight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;"So if you're with a parent or grandparent, with a loved one, and they're not able to. Maybe they couldn't parallel park before, but they're not able to pull into a spot and straight, that can be an early sign of dementia and Alzheimer's."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image-group"&gt;&lt;button class="LightboxBtn_lightbox-btn__eoxYS" aria-label="Open image viewer" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-controls="image-lightbox"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX false" data-testid="imageembed-36078695" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="36078695" data-tmdatatrack-type="image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Dementia and Alzheimer's are both cognitive diseases&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: Westend61/Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3 class="HeadingThree_heading-three__PBHLs  __className_88f20d" publication="mirror"&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;Signs of dementia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;The &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/dementia/about-dementia/what-is-dementia/" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;NHS states that dementia symptoms&lt;/a&gt; may include difficulties with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="UnorderedList_unordered-list__gzblI" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="unordered-list" publication="mirror"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;memory loss&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;thinking speed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;mental sharpness and quickness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;language, such as using words incorrectly, or trouble speaking&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;understanding&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;judgement&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;mood&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;movement&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;difficulties doing daily activities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;Those living with dementia can show less interest in their regular activities, and might struggle to control their behaviour or emotions. They may also find social interactions challenging and show reduced interest in maintaining relationships and socialising. Their personality might shift, and they may demonstrate less empathy (understanding and compassion).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="HeadingThree_heading-three__PBHLs  __className_88f20d" publication="mirror"&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;Early signs of Alzheimer's&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;During the initial stages, the primary symptom of Alzheimer's disease is lapses in memory. The &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/alzheimers-disease/symptoms/" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;NHS notes that &lt;/a&gt;someone in the early stages of Alzheimer's disease may:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="UnorderedList_unordered-list__gzblI" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="unordered-list" publication="mirror"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;forget about recent conversations or events&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;misplace items&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;forget the names of places and objects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;have trouble thinking of the right word&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;ask questions repetitively&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;show poor judgement or find it harder to make decisions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;become less flexible and more hesitant to try new things&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;There are often signs of mood changes, such as increasing anxiety or agitation, or periods of confusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Mirror</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 11:55:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQUm5PdWF4RTg0ekhxMVQzTUNzTS1LOFFRSV9vTk5YLXN2VXVaN01uanU5WTNMeUtQb2JzRTFlMTJOeW1PMWxIOVZqRlZ5Z21XVTNzYUUwUkY5Z1NoSHlWUS14TTMzcU9xR0Q4bUFlUG1IeVg0ZThRYzEwSjhjOHhQb25BVXBPSlBCTkHSAY8BQVVfeXFMTTFzMC1PQWI2WF91UVJmTXhyWXl0WU1GYmJNX19mV2JucGJpT1VOWTRSOVFWOGxUcXEtMWZMSWhFQnNGdi1UeUpwUmd3YzRIWFpQd0EzZzF1QzdEWl9ZZTNJem1RdmFLRzlyUFRObnA1TGRwTU96b2d3NVZ3TnBSblhPNG91VVJhTnhhUHdhMHM</guid></item><item><title>增强记忆力和注意力的10大大脑食物-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/top-10-brain-foods-to-sharpen-memory-and-focus/photostory/124604619.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fatty fish are rich in omega-3 fatty acids, especially DHA and EPA, which are important structural components of brain cells. These fats support neuronal communication, help reduce inflammation, and also promote blood flow in the brain-- and thus, regularly eating fatty fish can help improve one's brain function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;A &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0002916523463204#sec3"&gt;study titled 'The Relationship of Omega-3 Fatty Acids with Dementia and Cognitive Decline&lt;/a&gt;' published in The American Journal of Clinical Nutrition reads, "Our findings suggest that 1) long-term omega-3 fatty acid supplementation may reduce risk of Alzhimer's Disease; 2) dietary omega-3 fatty acid intake, especially DHA, may lower risk of dementia or cognitive decline; and 3) peripheral biomarkers of omega-3 fatty acids may serve as predictors of cognitive decline."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 11:50:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3gFBVV95cUxOcFpNN25wQ2N4RW82VVNIZERfX3BUWWNXVkItWWlNRkZYUTB4dGtjcDRvMGZLelFyYzdJZFZoMTA2TUNBcm53YjdzSGthZkdWQ0hQTUJnUEgyRlBSLXhJSW5JeWFaLUk5SkpEUzBqNXlnTE5BRl9UaVFTZFBRd2F2MTZMczRiSW9UTEphTEt5ektVXzQ4TlZ1S2xBcFYxLVcxZVZkMWpsYzlMZC1hb0RlYXZsTUtEbzRPVWluY3g4M2FEdlRsRzR6aDlkdTZpeV9ja3FibVFFSXFxd25EUHfSAeYBQVVfeXFMT21SZkM1dWlCckN2WjQ0T0trZXc4MjdEeUsySTZaSVp1Tm5NU0dXbHR0aGhOVDRpMXB3Q0ctWDJENTdPTHlUNzFvZms1b0RvQWRxM21lOGp6b2NzWXE0MkYzMU8zWUVBeElCUjJteldnMW1jVWM2UFBPeWt2dS05bzZBX1FYckNXZjFEaS1oaVhXLWdxTE1saFY3M2R0MTNuZUpHRnZEZkNMTGRIRmVaUlBla3hWRHJUbGU1d19wOXVFc19adTRlUXpJaXBfZTB2RG9YRG9SWENtZWxhTmo5Y3p3Vndxc2c</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现大脑中可能预示痴呆症的隐藏脉搏- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-discover-hidden-pulse-in-the-brain-that-may-warn-of-dementia</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The subtle pulses of tiny blood vessels in the brain can now be mapped in greater detail than ever before using a new imaging method.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's the first noninvasive tool to measure the expansion and contraction of microscopic arteries and capillaries in the living human brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3233/JAD-170349"&gt;Previous studies &lt;/a&gt;suggest that arterial pulses in the cerebrovascular system are predictive of dementia or cognitive decline. This technique could reveal whether that's true or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists can now identify dynamic changes across the entire cerebrovascular tree, from the largest branches to the tiniest twigs and offshoots at their ends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/just-one-high-fat-meal-can-disrupt-blood-flow-to-your-brain-study-finds"&gt;Just One High-Fat Meal Can Disrupt Blood Flow to Your Brain, Study Finds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Arterial pulsation is like the brain's natural pump, helping to move fluids and clear waste," &lt;a href="https://keck.usc.edu/news/usc-researchers-develop-new-brain-imaging-method-to-reveal-hidden-vascular-changes-with-aging/"&gt;explains&lt;/a&gt; neurologist and senior author Danny Wang from USC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our new method allows us to see, for the first time in people, how the volumes of those tiny blood vessels change with aging and vascular risk factors. This opens new avenues for studying brain health, dementia, and small vessel disease."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177829" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177829" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/GettyImages-2188820639-642x428.jpg" alt="Brain Vasculature" class="size-medium wp-image-177829" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/GettyImages-2188820639-642x428.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/GettyImages-2188820639-1013x675.jpg 1013w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/GettyImages-2188820639-768x512.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/GettyImages-2188820639-1536x1024.jpg 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/GettyImages-2188820639-2048x1365.jpg 2048w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/GettyImages-2188820639-600x400.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177829" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Cerebral arteries. (Rujirat Boonyong/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The method was developed at the University of Southern California in collaboration with the medical technology company &lt;a href="https://www.siemens-healthineers.com/en-us/about"&gt;Siemens Healthcare US&lt;/a&gt;. It combines two  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/magnetic-resonance-imaging" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73063" data-postid="177813" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;MRI&lt;/a&gt; techniques – &lt;a href="https://radiologykey.com/vascular-space-occupancy-magnetic-resonance-imaging/"&gt;vascular space occupancy&lt;/a&gt; (VASO) and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arterial_spin_labelling"&gt;arterial spin labeling&lt;/a&gt; (ASL) – to measure subtle changes in the volume of the brain's vasculature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The increased pulsation of arteries in the brain is &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3233/JAD-170349"&gt;closely linked&lt;/a&gt; to cognitive impairment, and some scientists think it might contribute to certain forms of dementia, like  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="177813" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease. But studies so far have been limited in what they can glean from living human brains, meaning that much research is based on animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wang, lead author and neuroscientist Fanhua Guo, and their team at USC hope their new technique will help fill that gap. They analyzed microvascular pulses in the brains of 11 young participants, in their 20s and early 30s, and 12 older participants in their mid-50s and early 60s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, researchers found pulses of blood in deep white matter sped up with age, and those older individuals with hypertension showed more changes than most.&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_launch"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Launch" class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-177073" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings align with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41467-018-07318-3"&gt;recent animal studies&lt;/a&gt;, which suggest that the vasculature of white matter in the brain (composed of nerve fibers) pulses more with age or disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our method shows strong potential for both research and clinical use, enabling accurate imaging of the cerebral microvascular system and capturing volumetric pulsatility in gray matter and white matter," the authors &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s44161-025-00722-1"&gt;conclude&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers are not yet sure why this is happening, but they have some hypotheses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The density of the brain's microvascular system is thought to naturally decline with age, and this reduction in volume and branching may mean that the arteries cannot dissipate the pressures of each pulse as well as they used to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If that's true, then to release the residual pressure, outer arteries in the brain's white matter may increase the volume of their pulsations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That in turn could slow the flow of cerebrospinal fluid, which bathes the brain, and which is closely linked to aging and disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These findings provide a missing link between what we see in large vessel imaging and the microvascular damage we observe in aging and Alzheimer's disease," &lt;a href="https://keck.usc.edu/news/usc-researchers-develop-new-brain-imaging-method-to-reveal-hidden-vascular-changes-with-aging/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Guo, who is a postdoctoral researcher in Wang's lab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s44161-025-00722-1"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Nature Cardiovascular Research&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 11:04:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOVXBiTHJUTDgzWVdkcmtMcnpxZ3F1WE9XVlc4aEI5NDJlbTcxaGVYZEhpZXI5Z1ZrU1VhOEIxdVFQV0ZNNi1kSFlJRm9UaVY0bkdKMWlZbkxzSmdPTXplMDRHRG5rUDB3MlNHcVY1ZUM0SjFyMkp0ZVViYXc2MGN0eHVpdEdzdGNQUzJtYWE3UUlNYTF1QnAwb0FHajNVazd3NVE</guid></item><item><title>您的大脑不仅会随着年龄的增长而萎缩，还会做一些更奇怪的事情- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/your-brain-isnt-just-shrinking-with-age-its-doing-something-much-stranger/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41467-025-63628-3" target="_blank"&gt;Nature Communications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; provides evidence that the human brain does not simply shrink with age but changes shape in consistent and measurable ways. The research suggests that these shape changes are closely tied to age-related cognitive decline and may offer a new way to detect dementia risk before symptoms appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most research on brain aging has emphasized the loss of volume in specific regions, like the hippocampus, which plays a key role in memory. These studies have revealed that certain brain areas are more vulnerable to aging than others, showing pronounced shrinkage as people get older. However, the brain is not made up of isolated parts. Its regions are connected and interact in complex ways. The new study focused on these broader patterns, aiming to understand how aging affects the geometry of the entire brain rather than just the size of individual pieces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was motivated by growing evidence that the brain’s shape affects how it functions. Studies have shown that the brain’s physical structure can place constraints on how different regions communicate. Subtle shifts in position, shape, or spacing between regions might disrupt the brain’s internal coordination. Despite this possibility, previous methods typically did not examine the geometry of the brain’s spatial layout. This study set out to fill that gap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s well known that the brain changes as we age, but most research has focused on individual regions, like the hippocampus, that are known to shrink over time,” said study author &lt;a href="https://sites.google.com/view/nielsjanssen/" target="_blank"&gt;Niels Janssen&lt;/a&gt;, an assistant professor of psychology at Universidad de La Laguna in Spain. “In our study, we looked instead at how aging affects the shape of the whole brain. We found that the brain doesn’t just get smaller—it sags, almost as if it’s slowly settling under its own weight. The lower parts of the hemispheres spread outward, while the upper parts draw together, producing a gentle downward slouch in the brain’s overall shape.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team analyzed more than 2,600 brain scans from adults between the ages of 30 and 97. The research team analyzed 2,603 brain scans from adults between the ages of 30 and 97. These scans came from two large and independent datasets: the primary analysis used 2,039 scans from the Open Access Series of Imaging Studies, and the findings were then confirmed in a separate set of 564 scans from the Cambridge Centre for Ageing and Neuroscience. All participants had undergone high-resolution magnetic resonance imaging, allowing the researchers to observe fine-grained structural features.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To measure changes in the brain’s shape, the team used a method that calculates the distance between points on the brain’s surface and across matching regions in the left and right hemispheres. For example, they assessed how far apart the left and right hippocampus were, and whether that distance changed with age. This approach allowed the researchers to identify patterns of “expansion,” where regions appeared to move farther apart, and “compression,” where they shifted closer together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They found a consistent pattern across the samples. As people aged, the lower front parts of the brain tended to move outward, creating a subtle bulging effect. At the same time, the upper back parts of the brain drew inward. This produced a sloping or sagging effect, almost like the brain was slowly settling downward. These patterns became more pronounced with increasing age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to looking at overall shape, the study examined how the distances between paired brain regions across hemispheres changed over time. Many of these distances, especially between temporal and subcortical areas, increased with age. These shifts were not merely byproducts of brain shrinkage. Even after accounting for changes in volume, the spatial shifts remained significant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also linked these shape changes to cognitive performance. Participants who performed worse on memory and executive function tests tended to show more extreme patterns of expansion and compression. For example, individuals with poorer memory showed greater separation between parts of the temporal lobe and more compression in parietal regions. These associations were found even after accounting for age, suggesting that shape changes might track with cognitive function more closely than age alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Understanding how the brain ages is a complex challenge that requires looking at it from many angles,” Janssen told PsyPost. “Most studies focus on the microscopic level—on molecules and cells—but our findings show that the shape of the brain itself also changes in meaningful ways. Viewing the brain at this larger scale may provide new insights into the mechanisms of healthy aging and the changes that occur in neurodegenerative diseases such as Alzheimer’s.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the findings are consistent and supported by two independent datasets, there are several limitations. One is that most of the data came from cross-sectional samples, meaning different people were compared at different ages. This makes it difficult to track how an individual’s brain changes over time. The study did include a smaller group of participants scanned more than once, and their results supported the larger trends. Still, more long-term studies are needed to confirm these patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another limitation is that the method used in the study measures distances between points in space, but not the biological mechanisms driving these changes. For example, it remains unclear whether the observed expansion and compression are due to changes in tissue composition, fluid balance, or other factors such as gravity and head positioning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research may investigate whether mechanical stress, such as gradual downward shifting of the brain, contributes to age-related damage. This could open new pathways for understanding how structural changes lead to functional decline. It may also be possible to develop early warning systems based on the shape of the brain, identifying those most at risk for cognitive impairment before symptoms appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these limitations, the study presents a new way of thinking about brain aging. It suggests that how the brain is shaped may matter just as much as how much brain tissue is lost. Subtle shifts in geometry may affect how different parts of the brain communicate and how efficiently they work together. Some regions, like the entorhinal cortex, sit close to hard structures like the base of the skull and might be particularly vulnerable to pressure from surrounding tissue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This could help explain why the entorhinal cortex is ground zero of Alzheimer’s pathology,” said study co-author Michael Yassa, the director of the University of California, Irvine’s Center for the Neurobiology of Learning and Memory and James L. McGaugh Endowed Chair. “If the aging brain is gradually shifting in a way that squeezes this fragile region against a rigid boundary, it may create the perfect storm for damage to take root. Understanding that process gives us a whole new way to think about the mechanisms of Alzheimer’s disease and the possibility of early detection.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We’re just beginning to unlock how brain geometry shapes disease. But this research shows that the answers may be hiding in plain sight – in the shape of the brain itself.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41467-025-63628-3" target="_blank"&gt;Age-related constraints on the spatial geometry of the brain&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Yuritza Y. Escalante, Jenna N. Adams, Michael A. Yassa, and Niels Janssen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:07:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxOZVBrd1lVXzFjckdRUk5Xa2UtRHJpZEVNV0cwYjZVTzdyak83a0xIY216R3Z1V3daYktOQlA3TWJlTVNJQkg0VnRpcXFHdWpoN24yaXNwcXdUR2Z6OTF2Y0t3YTRRNzFJREZSQ3hEXzFvSEJWdk5nVFFjRjkwWlFIWHJiQzBrZnQtYjYxWkNJdTBadjR2bVhBSTI1YnVsREU</guid></item><item><title>阿波罗医生警告：影响体内维生素B12吸收的两种常见药物-经济时报</title><link>https://m.economictimes.com/magazines/panache/apollo-doctor-warns-two-common-medicines-that-affect-vitamin-b12-absorption-in-the-body/articleshow/124531947.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-brcount="14" class="artText"&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/vitamin-b12-deficiency" target="_blank"&gt;Vitamin B12 deficiency&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; is often associated with poor diet or absorption issues, but according to a recent video shared by Dr. Sudhir Kumar, MD, a senior neurologist at &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a rel="dofollow" href="/apollo-hospitals-enterprise-ltd/stocks/companyid-62.cms" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" target="_blank"&gt;Apollo Hospitals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; in Hyderabad, certain commonly prescribed medications can also play a significant role. Speaking through his YouTube channel, Dr. Kumar explained that two types of medicines — metformin and proton pump inhibitors (PPIs) — can interfere with the body’s ability to absorb vitamin B12, potentially leading to deficiency over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Metformin and Its Impact on B12 Absorption&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Kumar highlighted that metformin, a widely used drug for managing diabetes and also prescribed in cases of polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS) and metabolic disorders, is one of the key culprits. He explained that metformin can reduce vitamin B12 absorption in the small intestine. This interference, if prolonged, can result in a gradual decrease in B12 levels in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-newpos-mgid="mgid_124531947" id="div-mgid-mid-newpos-124531947"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He advised that individuals who are on long-term metformin therapy should remain aware of possible signs of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/vitamin-deficiency" target="_blank"&gt;vitamin deficiency&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. These may include fatigue, numbness, tingling sensations, or even cognitive changes such as forgetfulness and mood disturbances. Regular testing of B12 levels is recommended at least once every one to two years, especially for those taking the drug for extended periods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="E_3" class="etoro"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;PPIs and the Role of Stomach Acid&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second class of drugs Dr. Kumar referred to are proton pump inhibitors (PPIs), commonly prescribed for acidity and peptic ulcers. Medications such as omeprazole, pantoprazole, rabeprazole, and esomeprazole are widely used for gastric conditions. Dr. Kumar explained that while PPIs are effective in reducing stomach acid, this decrease in gastric acid secretion affects how vitamin B12 is released from food, resulting in lower absorption levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He noted that individuals who depend on these medications for chronic acidity or digestive issues could unknowingly become deficient in B12. This is because the stomach acid required to extract B12 from dietary sources becomes significantly reduced during long-term use of PPIs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-grx-impression="Article Recommendations - Edit#articleshow_inline_impression#magazines/panache/apollo-doctor-warns-two-common-medicines-that-affect-vitamin-b12-absorption-in-the-body | " class="ar_wrp arwd_ld_chk font_mon clr hide custom_ad"&gt;&lt;div class="ar_survey hide"&gt;&lt;p class="ar_back_btn"&gt;&lt;span class="arb_btn"&gt;&lt;span class="ar_lt_arr"&gt;«&lt;/span&gt; Back to recommendation stories&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-mid-vdoai="vdoai_124531947" id="div-vdoai-mid-124531947"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div data-ga-action="Preference Banner InArticle Widget" data-ga-impression="Preference Banner InArticle Widget#Impressions | Preference Banner | Articleshow#url" class="Pbanner"&gt;&lt;div class="Pbannertext"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img alt="ET Logo" src="https://img.etimg.com/photo/123467569.cms"&gt;&lt;p&gt; as a Reliable and Trusted News Source&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Kumar emphasised that those taking metformin or PPIs should not stop their medication without consulting a doctor. Instead, he recommended regular monitoring of B12 levels and prompt testing if symptoms of deficiency appear. Early detection, he added, allows for easy correction through supplementation or dietary adjustments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;meta content="cms.article3" name="cmsei-article3"&gt;&lt;p class="inSideInd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Economic Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 09:30:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi8AFBVV95cUxNczFuaFpielBSWWxJWmtuMURYRnB3cmhVbDMxTy1vZ2hNRUljZjFkYUI1bWo4bzJLaW12ZnhFSEk0UERhUmZNMTB0Zzk0TGdhS3hFa3RVU1JoS09fSzR0TVlIcUVzTW92dFMybkwtTGlfVENoM1ItaWwxeWF2cVB3eVVEeEg2ZzFOVkk2cXM1Rm1OZUJiNUxnaWJNaEFnTHZjVjNzUk1oeDJuUlB3MzVvM05pZHZidjUtcE9peXRUU3hudTNYNDV2eVNqZjVPTlRjLWhQVERqLTNMazN5R01jY1UzWVdwNnJZZ0pyb0FKRUfSAfYBQVVfeXFMTnI4cnd6TDFVZUx0VThUelV0UXY3SlB6a1pzaTktMUN5Q1FKUHcwZVIwWDJhUF9SMUREeU9CQW05NlR3bndTQXp4V1d4V1U2aTljWnZ2T0VHV1BzR3J2aGIxUDY3ZWJoWkF1MlM5SktKSWFvbms1eUFGaElqdjBmaUd5UEhwdmctNV9BUDlsZW53ZzBpbnA3b0lKSWNIOEFCc0lobWRVUzJTbkR0T3pROFhMRGwzX09rUVJmeGRUWUhxU1VybnhkWGNRZ0hLMGpsaFVjU3lRSjZOUUdlLUJxWE02SV81YjZkS3lXWmVod2lnS0pHcU53</guid></item><item><title>“死亡折叠”蛋白质可以使细胞自我毁灭。科学家想要控制它们：疫苗-健康新闻- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/10/16/nx-s1-5575582/death-fold-proteins-apoptosis-alzheimers-cancer</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-93592" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Researchers are exploring the behavior of "death fold" proteins in the hopes of understanding why some cells die too soon and why others don't die soon enough.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    faithiecannoise/iStockphoto/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        faithiecannoise/iStockphoto/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;In Alzheimer's, brain cells die too soon. In cancer, dangerous cells don't die soon enough.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That's because both diseases alter the way cells decide when to end their lives, a process called programmed cell death.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;"Cell death sounds morbid, but it's essential for our health," says &lt;a href="https://www.stjude.org/people/g/douglas-green.html" target="_blank"&gt;Douglas Green&lt;/a&gt;, who has spent decades studying the process at St. Jude Children's Research Hospital in Memphis, Tennessee.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;For example, coaxing nerve cells to live longer could help people with Alzheimer's disease, Parkinson's disease or ALS (Lou Gehrig's disease), he says, while getting tumor cells to die sooner could help people with cancer.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So researchers have been searching for disease treatments that "modify or modulate the tendency of a cell to die," Green says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;One of these researchers is &lt;a href="https://www.stowers.org/people/randal-halfmann" target="_blank"&gt;Randal Halfmann&lt;/a&gt; at the Stowers Institute for Medical Research in Kansas City, Missouri.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;He has been studying immune cells that self-destruct when they come into contact with molecules that present a threat to the body.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"They have to somehow recognize that [threat] in this vast array of other complex molecules," he says, "and then within minutes, kill themselves."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;They do this much the way a soldier might dive on a grenade to save others' lives.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;Halfmann's team has been focusing on special proteins inside cells that can trigger this process.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;When these proteins recognize molecules associated with a virus or some other pathogen, he says, "they implode."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The proteins crumple and begin linking up with other crumpled proteins to form a structure called a "&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kPiuq7zqCyI" target="_blank"&gt;death fold&lt;/a&gt;" polymer. That starts a chain reaction of polymerization that ultimately kills the cell.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Halfmann's team knew this process takes a burst of energy. But they couldn't locate the source.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;Then they thought about a &lt;a href="https://home.howstuffworks.com/question290.htm" target="_blank"&gt;process found in reusable hand warmers&lt;/a&gt; — which produce heat by changing from a liquid to a crystallized solid.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Users start the chain reaction by flexing a metal disk inside the warmer. The mechanical disturbance causes the formation of a few tiny crystals, which quickly grow into much larger crystals.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"That releases all this energy," Halfmann says. "That's exactly what we envisioned was happening for these proteins."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;His team provides &lt;a href="https://elifesciences.org/reviewed-preprints/107962" target="_blank"&gt;evidence&lt;/a&gt; supporting this explanation in the journal &lt;em&gt;eLife&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Halfmann found it a bit unsettling to think that so many cells carry these self-destruct buttons just waiting to be pushed.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It just seemed like a really terrible way to live," he says, "every moment of a cell's life, to be at risk of spontaneously dying."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Of course, death is what you want for a cancerous cell or one that's infected with a virus. But Halfmann suspects this hair-trigger system is needlessly killing brain cells in diseases like Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;He notes that one hallmark of Alzheimer's is a misfolded protein called amyloid.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"That amyloid, for reasons we don't really understand, ends up killing the neurons," he says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That could be because misfolded amyloid proteins, much like death fold proteins, seem to replicate and form crystal-like structures.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So Halfmann has begun looking for ways to keep brain cells alive by making it harder for those crystals to form. He's hoping to use an approach that's a bit like adding antifreeze to water to keep it from freezing.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Biotech firms are also trying to halt the process, but at a different point — by interrupting various communication pathways involved in cell death.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Several companies are "working furiously" to block one pathway in particular, Green says. It's a pathway that involves some of the same death fold proteins Halfmann's lab has been studying.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The pathway leads to inflammation as well as the death of neurons in Alzheimer's and other neurodegenerative diseases.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The biotech companies are betting on products known as antisense drugs, which can prevent a cell from making specific proteins, including death fold proteins, Green says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;If they're right, he says, these efforts are "going to cure a lot of diseases that we associate with aging and inflammation."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;They'll do this, in part, by changing how cells make life-or-death decisions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxQVjctZzIxMlBWeWdCUWljNDMweFBmSHdveXFxRElBVlBQY3kzT25OYzRqalJ1NVhXeDJ6SF9hX0FyTi1rTW1rWm9uZTZPN2JCeWt1bjRUai1pTnRFaFNjdEUzdzNiOXRwR3NvTU1kcDB2eEx4OExZSUZCcTE0cmtpUkt6bGkyYkxTX2prUl94S2pycHJocmlWZEY0NXc1WlI1aGQwckFwVlFpeW9QVmFkaFItZ2R4NnRaenk4</guid></item><item><title>“坚果后现象”影响了40 ％的男性，专家解释说，这种现象揭示了何时寻求帮助- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/post-nut-phenomenon-bedroom-weird-science-health-785680-20251016</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Sex can be a wonderful experience at times and it can prompt some huge emotions when it's over but millions of people are having the same reaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Whether you're connecting deeply and emotionally with a long-time partner, or you and your spouse have just welcomed a new couple into your bed on a &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/entertainment/tv/open-house-channel-4-great-experiment-sharmayne-jamie-638554-20250626"&gt;swinging show&lt;/a&gt; live on &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/tv"&gt;television&lt;/a&gt;, sex can make you feel a lot of different things.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;If you're not able to keep up with &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/science/how-long-average-man-lasts-bed-love-study-health-384484-20251005"&gt;the averages&lt;/a&gt; in the bedroom, it might leave a partner disappointed, but it turns out that them crying might not be as worrying as it sounds as it's actually a &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/health"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; condition that millions of people deal with on a regular basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is the post-nut phenomenon?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;You've probably heard of post-nut clarity, which is the clearness you might feel in your brain after an orgasm, but as many as 40 percent of men are actually facing something very different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The health condition, known as post-coital dysphoria (PCD), triggers an emotional response moments after climaxing, and there are several different explanations for it, ranging from hormones to psychological distress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;PCD can prompt tears after sex even if it was the best you've ever had, with &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/community/adult-star-angela-white-three-things-never-do-822449-20250604"&gt;famous adult star Angela White&lt;/a&gt; opening up about the time she went &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/viral"&gt;viral&lt;/a&gt; for crying after a particularly pleasurable porn shoot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;It isn't anything to be embarrassed about (Getty Stock)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;She said: "One of my most viral scenes is a scene where I cried for 20 minutes afterwards in my partner's arms," she said, "and it was just such an incredible, beautiful moment that I had with Manuel [Ferrara]. I just had this full body release."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What did researchers find about PCD?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Although PCD has more commonly been associated with women, a study from researchers Robert D Schweitzer and Joel Maczkowiack found that 41 percent of men have experienced PCD at some point or another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The descriptions of how PCD feels included: 'I don't want to be touched and I want to be left alone'; 'I feel unsatisfied, annoyed and very fidgety'; and being 'emotionless and empty'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;PCD can also lead to feelings of sadness, anxiety, or irritability, and there are a number of potential causes, with one of the most likely a hormonal shift after finishing sex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;It's something that regularly affects both men and women (Getty Stock)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why does PCD happen and what can be done to help it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The rapid drop in hormones like oxytocin and dopamine after an orgasm can cause a temporary mood change, while there is also sometimes a rapid change from intimacy to detachment, which can lead to moments of vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Sex and relationships psychotherapist Gigi Engle &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://metro.co.uk/2025/10/15/confusing-post-nut-phenomenon-common-think-24424263/"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;: "PCD – often referred to as the ‘post-sex blues’ – is when someone experiences feelings of sadness or agitation after consensual sex, even if the sexual encounter was loving and pleasurable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;‘This can happen whether orgasm was experienced or not, but often is a comorbidity with orgasm.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Neuro Wellness Brand suggest that if the feelings continue to happen regularly or are troubling you, then therapy sessions with a clinical psychologist or psychiatrist, group counselling sessions led by a trained mental health professional, or online resources such as self-help groups or chat rooms, are a great way to find help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 07:35:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQT0lBZWViRTBIOEZPNk5NRXgxZ1pTcmhNYU9tUzhQeXNnR01QNmhCUkRFOUY2Z0duRlYybGpxVGJBaHNMRnNQbkNQUVgtRWlUT2RuWUNvbmRpWG9WTmZPVmJRcW9uVXN2ZnA2RlhKTDdYNktVUHFTNFJrLUtyYVZEVjhLVm4zd1ZiakViWElYVHZmTUpRZ2xQX0ltWjBzTHhOS3Zn</guid></item><item><title>美国的肥胖率仍然很高。但一份新的报告发现，更多的州正在取得进展- ABC新闻-突发新闻、最新新闻和视频</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/wireStory/obesity-remains-high-us-states-showing-progress-new-126569472</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;For the first time in more than a decade, the number of states with &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/article/children-health-maha-rfk-jr-jama-d920bb5421bfdc2c83d4356986e9ade7"&gt;rates of obesity&lt;/a&gt; of 35% or more dropped, an encouraging sign that America's epidemic of excess weight might be improving. But cuts to &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/article/trump-hhs-cdc-fda-nih-cms-layoffs-5aba829b829d9e1a0167c4a0d968aadb"&gt;federal staff and programs&lt;/a&gt; that address chronic disease could endanger that progress, according to a new report released Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Nineteen states had obesity rates of 35% or higher in 2024, down from 23 states the year before, according to an analysis of the latest data collected by the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. The CDC data was analyzed by the nonprofit group Trust for America's Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The group’s analysis follows a &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/article/how-common-is-obesity-us-5663c0388b19009eae3834d695710bc4"&gt;CDC report last year&lt;/a&gt; that found that the overall rate of obesity in the U.S. is high but holding steady, affecting about 40% of the population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;While the decline is positive, “it's too soon to call it a trend,” said Dr. J. Nadine Gracia, president and chief executive for TFAH. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;And with recent federal funding cuts, staff layoffs and eliminated programs, “this potential progress is also at risk,” Gracia said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;A U.S. Health and Human Services Department spokesman said in an email that the administration is “encouraged by the new data showing progress in the fight against obesity." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“We are restructuring public health programs to eliminate waste, reduce bureaucracy, and redirect resources toward real prevention,” said spokesman Andrew Nixon. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The latest report analyzed data from the CDC's 2024 Behavioral Risk Factor Surveillance System, which uses annual telephone surveys to collect data on health behaviors and chronic conditions in U.S. states and territories. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;It showed that 19 states had obesity rates among adults of 35% or higher, 22 states had rates between 30% and 35% and nine states had obesity rates of below 30%. The rates varied from a low of 25% in Colorado to a high of more than 40% in West Virginia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Between 2023 and 2024, no state had statistically significant increases or decreases in their obesity rates, after 18 states saw significant increases in the previous five years, the report found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Before 2013, no state had an adult obesity prevalence at or above 35%, By 2019, a dozen states had rates that high — and the number continued to climb. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In adults, obesity is defined as having a body mass index of 30 or higher. Body mass index is a calculation based on height and weight. Obesity is a chronic disease linked to a host of serious health problems including diabetes, stroke, cancer and heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;It's not clear exactly what may be driving the apparent improvements in obesity. Wider use of drugs such as Wegovy and Zepbound — which target appetite and slow digestion — could be starting to show up in reported data, said Aviva Musicus, a science director for the Center for Science in the Public Interest, an advocacy group. Increased support for nutrition assistance programs during the COVID-19 pandemic might also be a factor, she suggested. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The report also details a broad range of federal, state and local efforts that focus on improving nutrition and boosting physical activity, said Solveig Cunningham, an Emory University global health expert who specializes in obesity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“I think the report would argue that some of these interventions may actually be successful,” said Cunningham, who was not involved with the research. “That would suggest that there are possibly ways in which we could prevent obesity at the population level, which would be a really, really big deal.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News - Breaking News, Latest News and Videos</author><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:05:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQanllWWRRaVNzUVdxSEhpcm04d2hLb1Nka3V1enY4a0hQSklyNVRrYXZBdGgwYWhfcDJpWW5jZUJIV0Q1Q1FNaENBWHQ0X3QxaUZ4ckNGYlVOZTFEeHpqbjZNT1ZsNVhNQTZmclJGb2tBWGxsSnVSRUhxVnFiS3hqR0ZsSmZocmgyTDBQaGtZRmRrbFhIYUxBS3VkdHA1bDVSbXhR0gGoAUFVX3lxTE92ZGl4UXFnN2dMN3daOHlFTFFrQ2d1SnpqNXFFTk5Yb2htQmIwdEhkTjc1RmwtdHQyUDNlSVZ0SDRveHh0NjlFMTMxVFlZNUVHbkpoakdtVzFqWXBZdFdJOVJKNUNxREtIb1VsSVRObzd5djhHZW9PYkRPOUFBLThRVHF1TVB2cWc1dkpTclFwVzd0VE1LOGoyUzU3R211ZEhHbE5ZTUxZNQ</guid></item></channel></rss>