<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>你真的可以通过“一个奇怪的把戏”来获得更健康的面包消费吗？ - Boing Boing</title><link>https://boingboing.net/2025/12/07/can-you-really-one-weird-trick-your-way-to-healthier-bread-consumption.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Boing Boing</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 19:31:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxOY1EtNVpsOXVzaHlyS3JST2JUTDJjdHhZWnNSZzFxb01YWDBzS2oyM2tBMFpITGJieXV6cld0Zjd6SDM1WGF2Qm1QaUJWM1I2RUk3a1RwVnNLZjJXcEVMVzJLRHRaNWtQRjJheHY1Ym9PZFVxUTRlcWpQZ2hUSEdQRHQyN2xDSlA5cDlXUzZoWXJ2ZEpzVlpQaGNiXzNBQjNibzJrNGI2bS03SDMxd2fSAbMBQVVfeXFMTnY1MFJDdWI2dHFJcW5NUHA3YW1GNE1yRVlNY2ZUVFR2c2F2aE9ja3dqUFVSalJxS1o4Z195bkwxY1J5LTY2eFlCRFBLRjl5dG1rVkk3U2ZYU0RHNlliTk0zdHB4LWVZQlpjcDE1QWlhcFZfVFJCQVBUejVuLUowbGhNRU44d1ZRbDlmS0tfV2FWSFB2YURxdHU0dzI2TEZNTFJTMnJmT2tIVnR0SmQzWm1qMjA</guid></item><item><title>“Scromiting”是一种与慢性大麻使用有关的奇怪疾病，正在上升- East Idaho News</title><link>https://www.eastidahonews.com/2025/12/scromiting-a-bizarre-condition-linked-to-chronic-marijuana-use-is-on-the-rise/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleText"&gt; &lt;p&gt;(CNN) — It was a pain worse than childbirth, said a TikTok mom as she described bouts of uncontrollable vomiting after marijuana use.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“I was crying and screaming and I was like ‘I can’t take this anymore!’ I hate my life,” she said. “I’m just begging God, like please make it stop!”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dubbed “scromiting” by social media due to the combination of screaming and loud vomiting, the medical name for the condition is cannabis hyperemesis syndrome, or CHS, which is on the rise in the United States. Habitual users of cannabis, including teenagers, are showing up in emergency rooms complaining of severe intestinal distress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mediumRec1Mobile" class="mobile-ad medium-rectangle centered"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“They are writhing, holding their stomach, complaining of really bad abdominal pain and nausea,” said Dr. Sam Wang, a pediatric emergency medicine specialist and toxicologist at Children’s Hospital Colorado, who treats adolescents with the condition.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“They vomit and then just continue to vomit whatever they have in their stomach, which can go on for hours,” Wang told CNN in a prior interview. “They often say they took a scalding hot shower before they came to the ER but it didn’t help.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="smallTile1Mobile" class="mobile-ad small-tile centered"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Immediate treatment consists of anti-nausea medications and IV fluids to combat dehydration from the vomiting. But patients also undergo a battery of tests to rule out other causes: blood and urine tests, expensive CT scans, unpleasant upper GI endoscopy and gastric emptying tests, to name a few.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For some adolescents, those tests could be repeated again and again.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“For some of our kids, this is their fifth ER visit in the past two months, with symptoms that they can’t control,” Wang said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mediumRec2Mobile" class="mobile-ad medium-rectangle centered"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And if they wait too long to come in, the condition can be life-threatening.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Regardless of whether it’s cannabis hyperemesis syndrome or another virus that makes you vomit a lot,” Wang said, “if you let it go too long, you can have electrolyte disturbances, go into shock and have organ failure. CHS is no different.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A bizarre condition&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Cannabis hyperemesis syndrome burst upon the medical scene in 2004, when a group of Australian researchers wrote about 19 chronic marijuana users who had repeated episodes of abdominal pain and retching. The researchers followed nine of the patients over time and found symptoms went away when cannabis use was stopped but returned when it was restarted.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Oddly, over half of the 19 reported using extremely hot baths or showers to self-treat their symptoms. As more and more cases of CHS began to appear, hot bathing as a home treatment became a recurring theme.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“It’s pretty universal for these patients to say they need a really, really hot shower, or a really hot bath, to improve their symptoms,” he said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Why hot? “That’s not entirely clear,” said Wang, who is also an associate professor of pediatrics at the University of Colorado Anschutz Medical Campus in Aurora, Colorado.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tetrahydrocannabinol, or THC, the main psychoactive compound in weed, has access to the body’s pain receptors, so one theory is that the distracting sensation of the extreme heat interrupts the pain cycle, thus easing symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mediumRec4Mobile" class="mobile-ad centered"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To compound the strangeness of the disorder, THC and other cannabinoids in the marijuana plant have been used for pain relief — paradoxically relieving nausea and vomiting in cancer patients undergoing chemotherapy. However, despite the popularity of marijuana as a painkiller, study results on its effectiveness have been mixed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Still, why would the same compound relieve and also cause pain? Among a myriad of possibilities: dosage levels. Wang points to the ever increasing potency of THC in today’s marijuana products.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“It’s been well documented that the amount of THC that now comes in cannabis is increasing substantially,” Wang said. “In the ’90s the average was like 4% or 5%. Now in Colorado, it’s anywhere from 15% to 20%.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Another mystery: Not all heavy users of weed are affected by CHS.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“It’s not entirely clear who is predisposed to getting it,” Wang said. “Is it a certain frequency or duration of use? Is it a specific potency? Or is it a specific type of product? We don’t have that data.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CHS is on the rise&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Data show CHS is a national problem. Between 2005 and 2014 when only medical marijuana was legal in most states, a 2020 study found nearly 1 in 5 people hospitalized for cyclical vomiting in the United States reported concurrent cannabis use.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;After Colorado legalized recreational marijuana in 2012, Wang and his colleagues found over 800,000 cases of reported vomiting due to cannabis in Colorado between 2013 and 2018. That’s about a 29% increase since legalization, Wang said. The study, published in September 2021, found the rate was highest in counties with no prior marijuana dispensaries.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A newer study, published in July 2025, found emergency room visits for adolescents aged 13 to 21 years across the nation increased more than 10-fold between 2016 and 2023. Yet another November 2025 study found the rate of CHS among adults 18 to 35 rose sharply during the pandemic years of 2020 and 2021 and remained high.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;However, all of these studies have been limited by the lack of a medical diagnosis or insurance billing code to enable objective tracking of CHS. To do the studies, researchers had to compare medical records of vomiting with documented or self-reported cases of marijuana use — data that many people decline to provide.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;That’s changed. On October 1, 2025, a US federal committee created R11.16, an official medical diagnosis code for cannabis hyperemesis syndrome. The World Health Organization did the same, allowing researchers worldwide to better track the condition. Experts say future studies will be more accurate, allowing researchers to shed more light onto this unusual condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>East Idaho News</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxNbzI4d2c2YUpQQnNtMzBGVUpfWlNVb0JHYXhYY2RTRXloM1FQcFBHMTBibTNuMFE0NE0zVU9PWVhHT1hPaDhKeGtKSFF2MWQ4VzRaa1p5aHNZTy1xWEZzTFJBTlBObFRUTDBDZlc4dUxQU2FwRmw0SHhjQy13djFCQXh4amR2TDBRMV9oSHBWenhiMEVjVGowSG43UHZrNkpHR0hPY3pVSndKTEhfQVFrMmRCZHVEc1E</guid></item><item><title>犹他大学健康研究经费在2025年达到创纪录的5.31亿美元- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51414035/university-of-utah-health-research-funding-reaches-record-531m-in-2025</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;SALT LAKE CITY — University of Utah Health has amassed record research funding totals, surpassing the half-billion mark for 2025, reaching $531 million.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Securing competitive funding is essential to the University of Utah's mission of delivering exceptional societal impact. These investments fuel research, advance knowledge, improve health in Utah and worldwide and support the training of future scientific leaders," the U. said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The National Institutes of Health was once again the largest source of funding support, providing $264.1 million.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That chunk comes despite the NIH &lt;a href="https://www.ksl.com/article/51250766" rel="follow" target="_blank"&gt;cutting billions of dollars&lt;/a&gt; in research projects under the Trump administration, a move U. President Taylor Randall described in February as an "imminent threat" to the university's mission as a research institution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bob Carter, senior vice president for health sciences and CEO of University of Utah Health, said, "Research, innovation and advancing knowledge is an uncompromising part of who we are as an institution, a culture and a nation," when the cuts were announced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Challenges to NIH's attempted cuts to funds known as "indirect costs" of medical research are currently making their way through the courts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carter added that in Utah, National Institutes of Health funding supports over 45,000 jobs and nearly $785 million in economic activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, the U. secured the bulk of its funding from the NIH, with industry partnerships making up the second-largest funding category at $99 million.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other federal agencies like the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Environmental Protection Agency, and Department of Defense contributed $57.4 million, and additional contributions from the state, other universities and various foundations totaled $110.7 million.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Rachel Hess, system chief research officer for University of Utah Health, said faculty submitted $2.3 billion in research proposals in 2025 — a $500 million increase compared to the previous year and a testament to the perseverance of the research community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notably, research in the health sciences sector continued its rise, growing 24% over the past five years and more than doubling since 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year, health sciences funding accounted for 68% of the university's &lt;a href="https://www.research.utah.edu/facts-and-figures/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;total research portfolio&lt;/a&gt; that totaled $782 million, the university said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:03:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxPT25BMkt5YUp1M2JZU3YzLUVaYmRZcXV6d0g5N2NzUnpIelFCSVVyYUppS3NvWDF1T1BxTFpRNllsNVA5N0lfUUtGSWFwVHBOXzdNenNaekY1LU9fWTVrQ0x1cEd3NnVDcU9uQmg1bE1xM3BiMlFYaF84YjRZSjNKY08zRHlvbHhCdm1WX1JSNFQ2ZnFRNVhpbTA5WWZOdzZzUmE4QmZCM1NJVDQ</guid></item><item><title>成绩单：斯科特·戈特利布在“与玛格丽特·布伦南面对国家” ， 2025年12月7日-哥伦比亚广播公司新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/scott-gottlieb-face-the-nation-transcript-12-07-2025/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The following is the transcript of the interview with former FDA commissioner Scott Gottlieb, who now serves on the boards of Pfizer and United Healthcare, that aired on "Face the Nation with Margaret Brennan" on Dec. 7, 2025.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: For a look at some recent changes to U.S. public health policy. We're joined now by former FDA commissioner Dr Scott Gottlieb. He also serves on the boards of Pfizer and United Healthcare. Welcome back. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: Thank you. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: You know there was some pretty big news on Friday, and the American Academy of Pediatrics said they are deeply alarmed that the CDC vaccine advisory panel, ACIP voted in this 8-3 decision to change this 30 year long policy regarding Hepatitis B and newborns. They are now recommending delaying the dose until a child is two months old, instead of within 24 hours of birth. What does this decision mean for families of newborns?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: Yeah. Well, look, I think we first need to understand why we give that birth dose of the vaccine, because the idea of giving a vaccine to a newborn, to a lot of parents, sounds discomforting, that the first thing a child is going to face when they're born is going to be a vaccine within the first 24 hours. For a child over the age of five, if they develop Hepatitis B infection, if they're exposed to it, they're going to have a 95% chance of clearing that infection, and they'll go on to develop lifelong immunity. For children between the ages of one and five, they only have about a 25 to 50% chance of clearing the infection, so about 25 to 50% of kids will develop chronic infection, and about a quarter of them will go on to die from hepatitis B if they're between the ages of one and five. So children are more vulnerable to this virus and can't clear the infection. But when you're talking about a newborn, an infant, 90% of newborns who become infected, and they'll become infected during delivery, will go on to develop chronic infection, they won't be able to clear the hepatitis B, and about 25% of them will die from sequelae of that infection, either from liver disease, cirrhosis or from liver cancer. So we have this unique opportunity by giving this birth dose and the subsequent inoculations to virtually eliminate the chance that a newborn can contract Hepatitis B and go on to develop chronic infection, it's almost 99% effective at preventing that chronic infection. And the refrain is.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    &lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: And– &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: And one final point, the refrain is, oh, sorry, please.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: No, no. And this decision now is to wait two months before giving that dose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: Right.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: The President of the United States came out and said, this was very good, because Hep B is only transmitted sexually or through dirty needles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: Yeah, look, that's the problem. That's simply not true. The fact is, there's a refrain that if you just test the moms during, while they're pregnant, you can detect whether they have hepatitis B, and if they have hepatitis B, you continue to give that birth dose. But the reality is, many moms don't get tested, even though they intend to, many times, those test results aren't checked, and the tests themselves have a false negative rate, meaning they're going to say you don't have hepatitis B, when in fact, you do, of about 2 percent. That may not sound like a lot, but that 2% is going to translate into at least 1000 babies being born and getting infected with hepatitis B. There was one modeling estimate that estimated in the first year of this new guidance, there's going to be 1,400 children, infants contracting hepatitis B, and again, 25% of them will die from that infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: Well, we look at this because there is this broader scrutiny of vaccines right now by the Trump administration and in this board decision, which the public could listen into. It was publicly broadcast. The board was hand picked by RFK Jr, who is a skeptic here of vaccines, from those who voted against the decision to delay. One of them who you heard at the top of the show said the CDC is doing harm. Another said, "No rational science has been presented, and the committee must accept responsibility when harm is caused." Those are pretty extraordinary statements. If the group making a decision that has such high consequences for the most vulnerable Americans isn't basing it on science, no rational science, what does that indicate about what comes next?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: Well, look, this is the ACIP by and large, except for a handful of members, are anti-vax activists who were put there to carry out a specific agenda. And look, the Secretary, to his credit, has been very honest about what his intentions are here. He's the most prominent anti-vaxer in the country prior to coming into this position, and he stated that his goal is to eliminate childhood immunization, or many of these childhood immunizations, and I think they're going to take a methodical approach and slowly chip away at this. This is a big unforced error insofar as ACIP was a esteemed body that a lot of states tie their own decision making to, and what we're seeing right now is as a group, it's being degraded, and I don't think it will ever be restored. I don't think you can just flip the switch and restore this where people are going to suddenly respect its decisions again. There's about 600 state laws that were tied to decisions ACIP made. About 17 states have already passed new legislation saying they will no longer respect the decisions of ACIP. The insurers came out and said they're going to tie their own coverage decisions to the professional bodies like the American Academy of Pediatrics and not ACIP. So I think in time, ACIP is going to be fully degraded as a decision making body, and it's going to be more symbolic. There will be certain states that- that adhere to it, but will be more symbolic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: So you this week, we saw a big sell off in biotech stocks following these reports that the FDA, which you used to run the first part of the Trump administration, is now going to require one study to clinch approval of vaccines. You were one of the former commissioners who put out this really extraordinary editorial in the New England Journal of Medicine, arguing that the FDA and top vaccine regulator, Dr. Vinay Prasad, are changing policies in a way that's going to slow down new and better vaccines. What specifically is the problem you see? Because this isn't just hep B, this is the vaccines of the future. You're saying just won't be created?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: Right. So Vinay Prasad, who is the head of the biologic center. Also oversees the vaccine Division. He also has been appointed the head of biostatistics, the Chief Medical Officer of the agency, and chief scientific officer. So he occupies a lot of positions. Put out a memo saying that they're going to do away with, or move away from, what they call immuno bridging studies. These are studies that allow you for well validated vaccines, like the flu vaccine, to be able to demonstrate each year that the vaccine, the new vaccine, that's formulated against the circulating strain, can elicit antibodies that are effective against that particular strain, and that could be the basis of approval, rather than requiring new outcome studies every year to prove that the vaccine actually reduces the incidence of influenza. For established vaccines, where we know that antibody production is a good correlate for immunity, this has been a long standing practice. It's, we do it for flu vaccine, we do it in covid Certainly, we do it for things like pneumococcal vaccine, the vaccine for pneumococcal disease, where we look at serotypes circulating bacterial serotypes. This allows us to update vaccines as these viral and bacterial strains change, and as the composition of the strains change in time to provide protection for the Fall respiratory season. If they move away from this, which is what he said, they plan to do, we're just not going to be able to update vaccines each season, as we've done historically, to accommodate whatever the circulating strain is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: And 12 former FDA commissioners came out saying they're deeply concerned about what is happening. That memo that made clear the changes that are happening within the FDA from Dr. Prasad was obtained by CBS, and it claimed that career FDA staff are making changes in part because they found at least 10 children have died after and because of receiving the Covid vaccine, referred to it as a profound revelation, and said and asked, Did it kill more healthy kids than it saved? The administration, to date, has not backed up information to back up these claims, but, but, what questions do you have for the FDA commissioner, because they're arguing they're doing this to help people?&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: Yeah, look, well, first of all, one thing doesn't flow from the next. So the idea if, in fact, they found cases where the covid vaccine was linked to tragic deaths, it doesn't then follow that you make these policy changes. In fact, the policy changes wouldn't address what the concerns are related to the covid vaccine itself. These are- every case needs to be carefully adjudicated. It's tragic to see any suspected case that could be linked to a vaccine. And these were looked at previously by the FDA, and I don't believe that the new FDA had access to the case level data analysis of cases, individual cases that get filed with the agency where there is a death in proximity to vaccination, and some of these are filed by the manufacturers themselves are very subjective and require the goodwill the people involved in that. And so I think that they should make that analysis public so it could be scrutinized and people can get comfort in that they've already backed away from the 10 is reporting from endpoints that now they're saying it's eight or nine, so they're already backing away from it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: Okay. And HHS said they will eventually make that data public. We'll look for it when it comes out. Dr Gottlieb, thank you for your analysis today. We'll be back in a moment.&lt;/p&gt;

    

                    
        
  
    
  
  &lt;aside class="component list recirculation component--type-recirculation component--type-recirculation-collection"&gt;
                    
                                            
        &lt;div class="component__heading-wrapper recirc"&gt;
          &lt;h3 class="component__title"&gt;Face The Nation Transcripts
                          &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/feature/face-the-nation-transcripts/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="component__view-more component__view-more--lg" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                More
                &lt;svg viewbox="0 0 32 32" class="icon__caret-right" aria-hidden="true"&gt;
                  &lt;use xlink:href="#icon-caret-down"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                &lt;/svg&gt;
              &lt;/a&gt;
                      &lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;div class="component__item-recirc-block"&gt;
            
    &lt;ul&gt;
                                                                                
            &lt;li id="inline-recirc-item--id-b53438d6-6dba-43ca-816e-02c4ad629fc3" class="card-recirc item"&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/face-the-nation-full-transcript-12-07-2025/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="item__anchor" draggable="false" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                    &lt;article&gt;
                        &lt;svg&gt;
                            &lt;use xlink:href="#recirc-cbs-news"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                        &lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;h2&gt;Full transcript of "Face the Nation with Margaret Brennan," Dec. 7, 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;/article&gt;
                    
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/li&gt;
                                                                            
            &lt;li id="inline-recirc-item--id-efc3e268-2996-4179-84b6-bee9c59e4e9e" class="card-recirc item"&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/scott-bessent-treasury-secretary-face-the-nation-transcript-12-07-2025/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="item__anchor" draggable="false" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                    &lt;article&gt;
                        &lt;svg&gt;
                            &lt;use xlink:href="#recirc-cbs-news"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                        &lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;h2&gt;Transcript: Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on "Face the Nation with Margaret Brennan," Dec. 7, 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;/article&gt;
                    
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/li&gt;
                                                                            
            &lt;li id="inline-recirc-item--id-753905f8-8fe7-43b6-85d2-999edb6eb94c" class="card-recirc item"&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/ilhan-omar-minnesota-democrat-face-the-nation-transcript-12-07-2025/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="item__anchor" draggable="false" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                    &lt;article&gt;
                        &lt;svg&gt;
                            &lt;use xlink:href="#recirc-cbs-news"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                        &lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;h2&gt;Transcript: Rep. Ilhan Omar on "Face the Nation with Margaret Brennan," Dec. 7, 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;/article&gt;
                    
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/li&gt;
                                                                            
            &lt;li id="inline-recirc-item--id-70be51bd-e072-4ec1-97e0-22704cc3ab4f" class="card-recirc item"&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/scott-gottlieb-face-the-nation-transcript-12-07-2025/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="item__anchor" draggable="false" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                    &lt;article&gt;
                        &lt;svg&gt;
                            &lt;use xlink:href="#recirc-cbs-news"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                        &lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;h2&gt;Transcript: Scott Gottlieb on "Face the Nation with Margaret Brennan," Dec. 7, 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;/article&gt;
                    
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/li&gt;
                                                                            
            &lt;li id="inline-recirc-item--id-1b74ae6c-9388-4317-88c5-4d2f0d866fe0" class="card-recirc item"&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/jim-himes-connecticut-democrat-face-the-nation-transcript-12-07-2025/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="item__anchor" draggable="false" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                    &lt;article&gt;
                        &lt;svg&gt;
                            &lt;use xlink:href="#recirc-cbs-news"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                        &lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;h2&gt;Transcript: Rep. Jim Himes on "Face the Nation with Margaret Brennan," Dec. 7, 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;/article&gt;
                    
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;/ul&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
                            &lt;/aside&gt;



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

  
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:49:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxPMkZuRWw3ZDNfMkZWQVBOTmtnLXU4aGFwT1FRc3JoLVBQbVdabzBUaHVyS2Y0ZnByd1RTd1lLbURqZVQwQVdnd1BiSzBiNUxMdEpucjNQMklwZDUwNGRsbVdSaTJiWHZyWFNQd0xScGhJOGxvRU5GcC11Qk1vTUtYamhETElnVTJlcGfSAY8BQVVfeXFMT2I1alRlZmN4YmI1c2x0V1MxajNmY1JTZGx4VDQwd1U2QklTdVFIMEVvMFNHNmVpNzZXd3NOYmloaHJfc3pUYnp1VF9mQ3hFaWdtRHU0UXdMdzVrc0FldWRXYU41ZVplamFXWEZDYzgzQUdIYm9xNDZCbkZneXJ4TDlrcG12ZUlTYmI1WGRiaXM</guid></item><item><title>​结直肠外科医生分享了她避免降低结肠癌风险的5件事-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/colorectal-surgeon-shares-5-things-she-avoids-to-lower-colon-cancer-risk/photostory/125817504.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Ultra processed foods” refers to industrially manufactured foods that go far beyond traditional cooking. These typically contain many ingredients,  preservatives, emulsifiers, flavorings, artificial additives etc. They are often ready-to-eat or ready-to-heat, highly processed, and low in dietary fiber. As per Dr. Karen, even baked goods and snacks are dangerous. &lt;br&gt;A 2025 &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/about/newsroom/press-releases/ultra-processed-foods-early-onset-colorectal-cancer-study"&gt;study &lt;/a&gt;of nearly 30,000 women under age 50  found that participants with the highest intake of Ultraprocessed foods had around  45% higher risk of developing adenomas, compared with those with the lowest intake. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 13:57:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAJBVV95cUxPZ281eV9WX21IWlUyOURIb2JBXzJKTXhIMFN3bEpqSzNGVHNQaWNrR3dsN2NMdmhXcy1YbTNVZ1hZSmJKZUpSWUFrOXJzREF5NjNlTlZJZ3dOay05bmRES3RYMy1jMlcyX3pJb0UwZ3pZMGFCX2JURHRHZVl0Z3E0YWptcUZPaHpBdWh3RDNPUjBiYTlJVHVoQ1ZpaFl6bXdPOTg0SFdFRjVBRi1zWVJkY1hlSHAzLWFpRXFUcFNLQk5DdEhxZ3VrX3o3UkhTNWtFUlc5MENiV09IQ1QtUG5mR3FDOTJnZ0hoOW9pajV1SUdsWXN2clYyc082WWhSTkQx0gGIAkFVX3lxTE5WdG45UzhWVlBQTjk4cXVvSzRBcXNUS2FIemFqelItTVVlT0s0ZjhNZXhIOE5OallIMndQakFKWDBDMVAweVRpRmtSbFl4ai1rRGpvOW9ISGtCVjBWbGdwdTdtWUJnVmJTTUZlOGRLMEJRSUFIT2ZGanZlZVhncWRwbHhnY3R5SU90Y1BSM3JOZnJlLURKeGh3ZzhNOEpLRFhBeHIyTU44bU0zTVBrV2x4cHQ5a0paczFkOHJDMS1RM1Z2aWlfcGtSUklqMk44OXlsd0w2MS1INDJHdVkwUE9ScFlvb3h5cjU1dkxodUJwT1pQc0NfaEdJWEt1MXhFZVlBc1E3akpTSA</guid></item><item><title>减肥刺拳可能会使身体老化十年，并增加虚弱和跌倒的风险-每日邮报在线</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-15361247/Weight-loss-jabs-age-body-decade-increase-risk-frailty-falls.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    &lt;div class="message-box"&gt;
        &lt;h2&gt;Associated Newspapers Ltd&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;Access Restricted&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
Thank you for your interest. Unauthorised access is prohibited. 
To access this content, you must have prior permission and a valid contract. 
Please contact our team at 
&lt;a href="mailto:partnerships@dmgmedia.co.uk"&gt;partnerships@dmgmedia.co.uk&lt;/a&gt; 
 to discuss licensing options.
 &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; If you are a registered user, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:websupport@dmgmedia.co.uk"&gt;websupport@dmgmedia.co.uk&lt;/a&gt; , quoting the reference code on this page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference ID: 0.ad423917.1765117855.676996d4&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail Online</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 13:28:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxNNWVmZDlVWXEycVMyaG1EXzFQSUtOdEx6bHVmTGoxTjhZT19Nb0otZFBLZkUzSDhaSllVSlFadTQ5c0VodHAzZ0tPS2IwRERZVmV3bDN4REhMTXJsYm13bXBLMVg0VDd3WFlWU2VkdkQyallqbUdzelYtWk9iWFdXUW5EWkgycWgtRzJRUkRMbXAxcUhGc0FhVW9KNkg1YTdHXzZLMHZhbWZJODV6WmtPQW5jTUpEQdIBuwFBVV95cUxObDdrWHd4VEVHTmNXQ2lfZjMwR2xpVlc5U29kcm5fbjZPX1VqSE9xTmVDYS1PcUFKX05BNFoyODJOUEVQcW1EN2l0dlNkNGdtc24xZno0bEpKREZYMmp0NUFVM3RfVExYNnROeEsxT1NYVk5NdGZZa195Vy00dmluX1dvNFBmVDhtVkJTRG5rSTZoTFJlbWdiNDZWUGFOcjBLdDU4TUdnYVY4dEluX0o0UVozam5OU1JJWFpz</guid></item><item><title>美味食物如何降低血压-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/hypertension-foods-can-lower-high-blood-pressure/articleshow/125816095.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly half of Americans have hypertension, according to the US FDA’s data from 2024. This means more than &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/drugs/special-features/high-blood-pressure-understanding-silent-killer" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;119 million US adults&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; are struggling with high blood pressure, according to the US Food &amp;amp; Drug Administration. What’s more shocking is that only one in four of them has this condition under control. Far worse, many are even unaware that they have hypertension, which is exactly why it is called a silent killer. Hypertension can &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.who.int/health-topics/hypertension#tab=tab_1" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;increase the risk of heart,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; brain, kidney, and other chronic diseases, according to the WHO. This is why keeping blood pressure in check is crucial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; What if you could lower blood pressure naturally? How? By eating the right foods. A recent study from the University of Surrey, published in the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;European Journal of Preventive Cardiology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, found that &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/eurjpc/article-abstract/32/14/1322/8092214?redirectedFrom=fulltext" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;foods rich in flavan-3-ols&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; can significantly lower blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;5 Basic yoga poses that bring down BP naturally&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How flavan-3-ols help to lower blood pressure&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; You may have a new reason to enjoy your daily cup of tea or a small piece of dark chocolate. A new study found that naturally occurring compounds called flavan-3-ols, found in cocoa, tea, apples, and grapes, may improve blood pressure and the health of your blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The researchers analysed data from 145 randomised controlled studies to understand the impact of flavan-3-ols on blood pressure. They found that consumption of foods rich in these specific flavanols can lead to a reduction in blood pressure readings, especially in people with elevated or high blood pressure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, in some cases, the researchers even observed that the average blood pressure-lowering effects were comparable to those seen with some medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; These flavan-3-ols improved the function of the endothelium, the inner lining of blood vessels, which is crucial for overall cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to eat your way to normal blood pressure&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; For people who are struggling with high blood pressure, incorporating flavanol-rich foods into the diet, along with medications, can significantly improve the condition. “The findings are encouraging for those looking for accessible ways to manage their blood pressure and support their heart health through enjoyable dietary changes. Incorporating small amounts of commonly consumed foods like tea, apples, dark chocolate, or cocoa powder into a daily balanced diet could provide beneficial amounts of flavan-3-ols,” Professor Christian Heiss, lead author of the study and Professor of Cardiovascular Medicine at the University of Surrey, said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; “While not a replacement for prescribed medications or medical advice, including more flavan-3-ol-rich foods in a daily routine could be a valuable addition to a healthy lifestyle, especially for those with higher blood pressure. These are findings that, although promising, require ongoing investigation,” Heiss added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt; The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment, or before changing your diet or supplement regimen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4gFBVV95cUxOSllFMjhoclp4Y2Y3OEQ4V0NaZXVoLUF0RVZBNDB0UGZRYjg2Z3VTS0tHUHhHN0dLZzAzQTZ0b0RReFlxVGFsMm0yRG91aE5zSkFCWUl0cHNwV2FHZDVZYjJBRzh6b2VCTHc5QnFZXzdEQlpmVDVOeUU1R3cxSDZsTDBUaExGY1NlRmNGekxIWTBoU0RiOXNoQ200SmZLeEdua1pNd0xINzVOeHB2eWhOdVd5Ty1NaXFlaVRtcEM0dWdpa2FYaUZ5NVNXeFVuWnJwQ3UyaFNwWnNVRHJhd3JUQVl3</guid></item><item><title>原料amla vs amla果汁：哪种更健康-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/diet/raw-amla-vs-amla-juice-which-is-healthier/photostory/125816694.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both raw amla and amla juice deliver valuable health benefits, but raw amla emerges as the healthier choice for regular, long-term consumption. Eating amla in its whole form preserves its full nutrient profile, including dietary fibre, which supports digestion, gut health, and better metabolic control. The fibre-rich structure of raw amla allows for the gradual release of vitamin C and antioxidants, potentially offering more sustained protection against oxidative stress and metabolic disturbances.&lt;br&gt;So, from an evidence-based nutrition perspective, raw amla offers greater nutrient stability and long-term advantages, while amla juice works best as an occasional or supplementary option. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizgFBVV95cUxQS2pLaGNpemQ5UU5WWVZCMFpZY1gzeURVNWkwek5aVlZYR25oTlhJRk5qQUFsOXdIbTBjYk53V0NZa2FzbUY1eXNCYnpmWm8tZFY5RElDaGhTRE1RdENtMjBmbTF3OFhPTlZ6dHhuQXNIOHYzb1FWZWpQV3pfYm9GdlEwRVUwaG5jcndhdTJjZ1BHUXJUeDZkSzBMeml2SjdzeWhyMW5FVHpnemJtU2xWWE53MjZyZlUzQ2tJY2ZtbWVFNG9VQWo4bmFSMUN5Z9IB1gFBVV95cUxNTXM3d3ltS0ZOYmF4dmFOTm1MNERvSWQtTGRVOUppTHRtd0R0RFgxTjk5Ym1hRWZnTU9Xejh2ejlwLXdaZTdtVjBSN2dqYUJhdDFqU2RuUU8zNEN0djJ2Q1dLc0p3OFFlbDdWTWlvSWF4d09aZ1hlOUlDNDBGLTE1R3RjMnk1ODRLc2NTclVUbU9BTWNUZkdOaGtqbVQ5Rm1PX2RLcld4ZDhHTlFkVG5NTEttaVpLSTl5YzhRMWJzbF9iS0owVjVybEMzZ0pSM051LWNCWlBn</guid></item><item><title>还在每天早上整理床铺吗？你可能应该停止……这是一个可能会适得其反的习惯--《银河日报》</title><link>https://dailygalaxy.com/2025/12/daily-bed-making-habit-linked-to-allergies-and-asthma/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content dynamic-entry-content" itemprop="text"&gt;
			
&lt;p&gt;Every morning, it happens without question. Duvets are pulled tight. Pillows are fluffed. &lt;strong&gt;The bed&lt;/strong&gt;, now perfect, marks the transition from rest to productivity. For generations, this ritual has been seen as a cornerstone of discipline—an act of daily order in an otherwise unpredictable world.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Across cultures, “&lt;strong&gt;making the bed&lt;/strong&gt;” is promoted not just as a chore, but as a small win, a psychological anchor. Military routines, parenting blogs, and productivity books all hail it as a symbol of self-control and success. But what if this common act is masking an overlooked problem—one that’s quietly affecting millions?&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Unmade-bed-in-morning-light-with-rumpled-sheets-and-open-window-in-a-sunlit-bedroom.jpg.webp" alt="Unmade bed in morning light with rumpled sheets and open window in a sunlit bedroom" class="wp-image-112241" srcset="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Unmade-bed-in-morning-light-with-rumpled-sheets-and-open-window-in-a-sunlit-bedroom.jpg.webp 1000w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Unmade-bed-in-morning-light-with-rumpled-sheets-and-open-window-in-a-sunlit-bedroom-420x280.jpg.webp 420w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Unmade-bed-in-morning-light-with-rumpled-sheets-and-open-window-in-a-sunlit-bedroom-520x347.jpg.webp 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leaving your bed unmade for a few hours allows moisture to evaporate, disrupting the dust mites’ ideal environment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Credit: Shutterstock&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;In recent years, indoor air quality and respiratory health have become urgent public concerns. Conditions like &lt;strong&gt;asthma&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;allergic rhinitis&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;chronic sinusitis&lt;/strong&gt; are now closely linked to the quality of the air inside homes—especially bedrooms. And that’s where the story of the made bed takes a surprising turn.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Unseen Consequences of a Tidy Bed&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In a landmark study from &lt;em&gt;Kingston University&lt;/em&gt; in the UK, researchers found that &lt;strong&gt;leaving your bed unmade during the day could reduce the population of dust mites living in your bedding&lt;/strong&gt;. Led by environmental building scientist &lt;strong&gt;Dr. Stephen Pretlove&lt;/strong&gt;, the team investigated how these microscopic organisms respond to changes in heat and humidity trapped inside the bed.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The conclusion was striking. A made bed traps &lt;strong&gt;moisture and warmth&lt;/strong&gt; from the night’s sleep—conditions that &lt;strong&gt;dust mites&lt;/strong&gt;, which feed on dead skin cells, need to thrive. When the bed is left open and exposed to circulating air, those conditions evaporate. This &lt;strong&gt;disrupts the mites’ habitat&lt;/strong&gt;, making it harder for them to survive.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Magnified-microscopic-view-of-dust-mites-on-fabric-fibers.jpg.webp" alt="Dust,mite,under,the,light,microscope,view." class="wp-image-112243" srcset="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Magnified-microscopic-view-of-dust-mites-on-fabric-fibers.jpg.webp 1000w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Magnified-microscopic-view-of-dust-mites-on-fabric-fibers-420x280.jpg.webp 420w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Magnified-microscopic-view-of-dust-mites-on-fabric-fibers-520x347.jpg.webp 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Up to 1.5 million dust mites can live in a single bed, feeding on dead skin and thriving in warm, humid conditions. Credit: Shutterstock&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;“Something as simple as leaving a bed unmade during the day can remove moisture from the sheets and mattress,” Dr. Pretlove explained in &lt;a href="https://www.kingston.ac.uk/about/news/messy-bedroom-could-spell-end-for-creepy-crawlies" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Kingston University’s release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Why does this matter? Dust mites are one of the most common sources of &lt;strong&gt;indoor allergens&lt;/strong&gt; worldwide. Their waste particles can trigger a range of reactions, from mild sneezing and nasal irritation to more serious respiratory problems like &lt;strong&gt;asthma&lt;/strong&gt;. The &lt;em&gt;American Lung Association&lt;/em&gt; highlights &lt;strong&gt;bedding and pillows&lt;/strong&gt; as the most concentrated reservoirs of dust mite allergens in the home.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;An estimated &lt;strong&gt;1.5 million mites&lt;/strong&gt; can live in the average bed. Their presence is invisible—but the effects often aren’t. By simply giving your bed time to dry out naturally, you may be taking a meaningful step toward &lt;strong&gt;reducing allergy triggers&lt;/strong&gt; in your home.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A Warmer Bed, a Bigger Problem&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Most people associate a tidy bed with cleanliness, but in reality, &lt;strong&gt;a freshly made bed may seal in moisture&lt;/strong&gt; from overnight perspiration. The typical adult loses about a liter of fluid each night through sweat and respiration. Combine that with thick comforters, insulated bedrooms, and limited morning ventilation, and the bed becomes a microclimate tailor-made for mite colonies.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Colder months make things worse. Heating systems dry out the ambient air while homeowners keep windows closed, limiting natural airflow. In this environment, &lt;strong&gt;moisture trapped in bedding has nowhere to escape&lt;/strong&gt;, allowing mites to feed, reproduce, and expand their reach.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Health agencies including the &lt;em&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC)&lt;/em&gt; recommend reducing indoor humidity and increasing airflow to help control allergen levels. Yet few guidelines consider how something as basic as bed-making affects these dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For households with children, seniors, or anyone with &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2024/11/yellow-stains-pillows-alarming-signs-their-hidden-meanings-bed/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="72006" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;allergic asthma&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, reconsidering how—and when—you make the bed could be a low-cost way to improve &lt;strong&gt;bedroom air quality&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Airing It Out&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Rather than abandoning the idea of a &lt;strong&gt;clean bed&lt;/strong&gt;, researchers suggest a &lt;strong&gt;strategic delay&lt;/strong&gt;. Instead of making the bed right after waking up, allow the bedding to remain open for several hours to promote &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2025/11/an-event-so-extreme-it-erased-a-sea-new-evidence-reveals-what-happened-6-2-million-years-ago/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="109281" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;evaporation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Pull back the duvet. Crack a window. Let the mattress and sheets breathe.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t replace good hygiene. Washing bedding every one to two weeks in hot water, vacuuming the mattress, and using &lt;strong&gt;dust-mite-proof pillow covers&lt;/strong&gt; are still essential. But making the bed later in the day—or even just airing it out first—can tip the balance against an invisible indoor threat.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Well-ventilated-bedroom-with-open-windows-and-sunlight-over-loosely-arranged-bedding.jpg.webp" alt="Breeze,blowing,through,open,window,in,cozy,bedroom" class="wp-image-112244" srcset="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Well-ventilated-bedroom-with-open-windows-and-sunlight-over-loosely-arranged-bedding.jpg.webp 1000w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Well-ventilated-bedroom-with-open-windows-and-sunlight-over-loosely-arranged-bedding-420x280.jpg.webp 420w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Well-ventilated-bedroom-with-open-windows-and-sunlight-over-loosely-arranged-bedding-520x347.jpg.webp 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Simple ventilation—like pulling back the covers and opening a window—can significantly reduce indoor allergens. Credit: Shutterstock&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;These changes are especially relevant for allergy sufferers. Data from the &lt;em&gt;National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases&lt;/em&gt; indicates that &lt;strong&gt;10–20% of the population&lt;/strong&gt; is sensitive to dust mite allergens, and symptoms often peak after prolonged exposure in poorly ventilated bedrooms.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In homes where people now work, rest, and sleep in the same room more than ever before, these small shifts matter. They’re not about rejecting routine—but about adapting it to reflect what we now know about the spaces we inhabit.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Daily Galaxy</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxQaGlqRmF6LS1LRTNfaWFpel9CLUpUeE5XSXJzN3FqaTl5Ym45Y3NDWjFGcjc1NFdEbmZOTTdBOEMzWFpobjg3YVJmaGxCM2s2V0ZKaXQ3RHliQUtpelNCYlZXRWpTVW5sOHJRN1M2NXNLT0haSFFNSGVxZl9sR3pGTGxwNlF1MFIwSnR2cDhTTQ</guid></item><item><title>潜伏在污水中的未来抗菌素耐药性的严峻信号- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/grim-signals-of-future-antimicrobial-resistance-found-lurking-in-sewage</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Dangerous bacteria and other disease-causing microbes are rapidly evolving ways to defy our best antibiotic medications, a phenomenon known as antimicrobial resistance. Humans are inadvertently contributing by overexposing pathogens to our limited defenses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With drug-resistant bacteria already killing &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(24)01867-1/fulltext"&gt;more than 1 million people a year&lt;/a&gt;, researchers are seeking clues about the future of these superbugs by examining the world's wastewater.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study by an international team of researchers has found that latent antimicrobial resistance is more common than we realised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-reveals-alarming-rise-of-superbugs-in-newborn-babies"&gt;Study Reveals 'Alarming' Rise of Superbugs in Newborn Babies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists hunted for clues in wastewater from around the world, sifting through 1,240 sewage samples from 351 cities across 111 countries in search of the &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/jobm.202100201"&gt;antimicrobial resistance genes&lt;/a&gt; (ARGs) that grant microbes protection against our life-saving medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aside from known ARGs, the researchers used a process known as functional metagenomics to scour their samples for latent genes, or genetic variations that exist within an organism's DNA but are not actively expressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Latent genes can become active under certain circumstances, which means latent ARGs might play important roles in the poorly understood evolution of drug-resistant 'superbugs.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_184430" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-184430" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/redpills_antibiotics_superbugs_642.jpg" alt="antibiotics" class="wp-image-184430 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/redpills_antibiotics_superbugs_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/redpills_antibiotics_superbugs_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-184430" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Latent genes in the environment may give infecting bacteria a way to resist antibiotic treatment. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAD0CUkOF5I/"&gt;Olesya22/Getty Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study suggests latent ARGs are &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/antibiotic-resistance-can-emerge-in-your-gut-even-without-antibiotics-use"&gt;abundant nearly everywhere&lt;/a&gt;, forming a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/antibiotic-resistance-genes-can-travel-through-the-air-and-we-re-slightly-terrified"&gt;hidden global library&lt;/a&gt; of latent antimicrobial resistance. This latent resistance is apparently even more prevalent than the known resistance conferred by already active, or acquired, genes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The research shows that we have a latent reservoir of antimicrobial resistance that is far more widespread around the world than we had expected," &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107666"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; first author Hannah-Marie Martiny, a bioinformatician at the Technical University of Denmark (DTU). &lt;span&gt;This may be because selection and competition seem to play a larger role in the development of these resistance genes than dispersal, the researchers found.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One noteworthy takeaway from this discovery is the need for more proactive wastewater surveillance, says co-first author Patrick Munk, an associate professor with the DTU National Food Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"To curb future antimicrobial resistance, we believe that routine surveillance of antimicrobial resistance in wastewater, in addition to including already acquired resistance genes, should also encompass latent resistance genes, in order to account for tomorrow's problems as well," Munk &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107666"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers often focus on ARGs that can be transferred among species of microbes, since these acquired ARGs already pose a threat to public health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If we broaden our surveillance of sewage, however, we might learn valuable secrets from latent ARGs, possibly helping researchers demystify the origins of antimicrobial resistance (AMR) or &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/researchers-trace-the-genes-for-antibiotic-resistance-back-to-their-source"&gt;map the ecology of the genes&lt;/a&gt; involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"By tracking both acquired and latent antimicrobial resistance genes, we can gain a broad overview of how they develop, change hosts, and spread in our environment, and thereby better target efforts against antimicrobial resistance," Martiny &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107666"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wastewater is a practical and ethical way to monitor AMR," she &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107666"&gt;adds&lt;/a&gt;, "because it aggregates waste from humans, animals, and the immediate surroundings."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of these genes may not endanger public health right now, the researchers note, but some of them probably will in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In general, I don't think we need to be too worried about most latent antimicrobial resistance genes, but I do believe that some of them will eventually cause problems, and we would like to know which ones," Martiny &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107666"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That kind of knowledge could help us predict which microbes in the future might be vulnerable to which antimicrobial treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When new antibiotics are developed – a process that takes many years – bacteria may already have invented new 'scissors' capable of destroying them," Munk &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107666"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If we can study both types of genes over time," he &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107666"&gt;adds&lt;/a&gt;, "we may be able to find out which of the latent genes become problematic resistance genes, how they arise, and how they spread across geography and bacteria, and in that way lessen the burden of antimicrobial resistance."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-025-66070-7"&gt;Nature Communications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:02:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOMGh6alYwRF9QSzdHR3kwaXlUTVFEcGZpUGhkQmthMFg3Nm1jOGt3Zk54WUNQT0wyeTNnVjJOZno4dlhKRGNIdlM3MV81bzFiZEhmR09VMzVKUXNIV2pYZXdCTHdrSWNVT2F5ZVVqMVNtenViMkhKM1F4eUxMUDdWNm1yV3l4akhKWDBkTG10U1VmV210TllQN21GQS1Jc0hzeEE</guid></item><item><title>行业和官员表示，乙型肝炎疫苗的保险范围不会改变- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/07/health/hepatitis-b-vaccine-insurance-coverage</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit92yov0002356nzsrwf9e8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Parents will still be able to get the &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/health/live-news/cdc-vaccine-meeting-hepatitis-b-12-05-25"&gt;hepatitis B vaccine&lt;/a&gt; for their children at no cost even though the US Centers for Disease and Control Prevention’s vaccine advisers recommended a major change to the immunization practice.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit91wid0000356nplwgs1i8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The CDC’s Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices, whose members were chosen by US Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., voted Friday to end universal hepatitis B vaccination recommendations for newborns.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit9a4l8000f356nv7rcbzrv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The revised recommendation calls for mothers who test negative for the virus to consult with a doctor or other health care provider before having their babies vaccinated. This could create confusion and place additional hurdles in front of parents and result in fewer children being immunized.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit9ctxj000l356nh6f67o8v@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The advisers also voted in favor of recommending that babies who don’t receive a dose at birth should wait at least two months before being immunized.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit92yov0003356nqh0tg1ue@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Two major health insurance industry groups, the Blue Cross Blue Shield Association and AHIP, reiterated Thursday that they will continue to cover all vaccines recommended by the committee as of earlier this year, with no cost-sharing, through 2026.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit92yov0004356n84bc98b3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            BCBS companies will cover all immunizations recommended by ACIP as of January 1, 2025, while operating within federal and state laws and meeting program and customer requirements, a spokesperson told CNN. AHIP members will do so for all vaccines recommended by ACIP as of September 1, 2025, a spokesperson said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit92yov0005356nc3b10dfl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Both groups released these &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F10%2F07%2Fhealth%2Fcovid-19-vaccine-free-health-insurance&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CTami.Luhby%40cnn.com%7C1d2d2b3566ab4484afce08de336a415f%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C639004728613843954%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=21uN25sTPL2BFJ%2FiUDoZJgkPO3Z8CcjCIWpoL7E8Kag%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;statements&lt;/a&gt; earlier in the fall, before ACIP announced changes to recommendations for the &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F19%2Fhealth%2Fcdc-acip-hepatitis-mmrv-covid-vaccine&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CTami.Luhby%40cnn.com%7C1d2d2b3566ab4484afce08de336a415f%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C639004728613861325%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=%2FxcYYsHhqNUbtxFMI0O%2B7ESjWOEIFdVhJweXv%2BLf%2BCM%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;Covid-19 vaccine&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F18%2Fhealth%2Fcdc-vaccine-panel-acip-mmrv-hepatitis&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CTami.Luhby%40cnn.com%7C1d2d2b3566ab4484afce08de336a415f%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C639004728613877970%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=rrk2E7p3mms5A6xC%2FYIxUVhRPHlUyGMnLvaLHPz%2BQ6k%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;combined measles, mumps, rubella and varicella (MMRV) vaccine&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit9ct09000i356n0zwbq2so@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The CDC committee members recommended in September that patients consult with a health care provider for a Covid-19 vaccine, a process known as shared clinical decision-making, but do not need to have a prescription. And the members voted to recommend against using the combined MMRV vaccine for young children.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmita5j5w0015356nt0nt35dg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The change to requiring a consultation with a doctor has raised concerns that insurers would no longer be required to cover the full cost of the immunization. The Affordable Care Act mandates that most private insurers cover vaccines recommended by ACIP at no cost, and Medicaid’s no-cost coverage of vaccines is tied to the committee’s recommendations.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmita8jnm001c356ng05pizbz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The shift to shared clinical decision-making will not affect the ACA’s mandate for insurers, said Jen Kates, senior vice president of global and public health policy for KFF, an independent health policy research organization.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitbsj2y001p356naml2bowi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The change today will have an impact, but not on insurance coverage,” Kates said Friday.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Rather, she said&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; the effect will be that fewer newborns will receive the vaccine.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit92yov0006356n6c84vpuc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            ACIP also voted to &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/health/live-news/cdc-vaccine-meeting-hepatitis-b-12-05-25?post-id=cmit1w40t000u2e6fwghwjhf7"&gt;recommend&lt;/a&gt; shared clinical decision-making on the hepatitis B shot for parents who get free vaccines through the federal Vaccines for Children program. The program provides a variety of immunizations at no cost to children who are eligible for Medicaid, are uninsured or are underinsured.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitd3at600043b6qv8xrr0op@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Georgina Peacock, director of the CDC’s Immunization Services Division, said Thursday that if that recommendation was approved, those immunizations would be covered by Vaccines for Children.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit92yov0007356nqc8r0nsl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Also Thursday, a Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services official said the inclusion of individual-based decision-making language would not affect coverage of the vaccine without any cost-sharing.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit9ctxj000m356nrloe2tg8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The CDC makes the final decision on vaccine recommendations&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;but typically aligns with the advisory panel’s vote.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:00:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxQMkdKaWNQVFQ5alhnTnV2ZUNpZjVEVlN0NFFhclR6S3NjYUVISXVJRlJtbUdaUDhwOTg3em1yQjNHM3Rud3ZweHI3WkZwUjFEeTZ6c0JMRldxSVRjSXVKYWtWdlNpNmNYUUNvVnRZZXhTdzhPdmRBdFpMbDZ1RHY3TVRn</guid></item><item><title>香蕉的成熟度实际上对您的健康很重要—方法如下- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/banana-ripeness-and-health-g_l_6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here’s something you may not have thought about: For some foods (in this case we’re talking about bananas), the nutritional effects on your health can vary depending on the ripeness level when you eat it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a banana ripens, its nutritional content — the amount of sugar, starch and vitamins — changes. Meaning, if you &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/are-carbs-and-sugar-bad_l_670fcbbce4b072cc9eb529a1" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="need more sugar before a workout" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="670fcbbce4b072cc9eb529a1" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;need more sugar before a workout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, or less sugar because of diabetes, you may want to eat your banana at a certain ripeness level.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ahead, registered dietitians share the various ripeness levels, what a banana looks like at each stage, and the health conditions or goals that are best addressed at each level of ripeness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Underripe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Dorin Musat / 500px via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Dorin Musat / 500px via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;An underripe banana can help you feel full longer.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bananas at this stage look green; they’re firm and difficult to peel. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“This stage has the highest resistant starch and low sugar content,” said &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mycrohnsandcolitisteam.com/writers/683f0deb46c7aa1e0f3349e2" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Avery Zenker" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.mycrohnsandcolitisteam.com/writers/683f0deb46c7aa1e0f3349e2" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Avery Zenker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;span&gt;a registered dietitian at MyCrohnsAndColitisTeam.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The benefits of resistant starch are many, including helping to feed healthy gut bacteria that &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/im-a-nutritionist-follow-these-steps-to-reduce-chronic-inflammation_uk_65b24b41e4b074981636f0e7" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="reduce inflammation" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="65b24b41e4b074981636f0e7" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;reduce inflammation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and keeping blood sugar levels stable, according to Zenker. It’s also digested more slowly, which can keep you full for longer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Resistant starch acts very similarly to fiber, which means it’s fermented in the gut (so it fuels your good gut bacteria) and it can be helpful for blood sugar control,” added registered dietitian &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.csulb.edu/media/page/amanda-sauceda" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Amanda Sauceda" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.csulb.edu/media/page/amanda-sauceda" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amanda Sauceda&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;span&gt;a nutrition lecturer at California State University, Long Beach.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While good gut bacteria and blood sugar management are generally important for your health, they may apply to some individuals more than others. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“This level of ripeness is ideal for people who are trying to control blood glucose levels, such as those with insulin resistance as seen with prediabetes, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/meal-times-type-2-diabetes-prevention_l_64c1269ce4b053a700938ca7" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="Type 2 diabetes" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="64c1269ce4b053a700938ca7" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Type 2 diabetes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and other metabolic conditions,” Zenker said. “Unripe bananas can also be beneficial for anyone looking to improve &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/gut-health-experts_l_61c0b9eae4b0bb04a627fe69" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="gut health" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="61c0b9eae4b0bb04a627fe69" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;gut health&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; by improving microbiome balance.” The latter may be especially important for people who are trying to manage digestive issues like &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/issues-irritable-bowl-syndrome_l_62587134e4b0be72bff476af" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="irritable bowel syndrome" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="62587134e4b0be72bff476af" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;&lt;span&gt;irritable bowel syndrome&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“If you want to up the health benefits of your green banana, consider pairing it with some peanut butter,” Sauceda added. “You get a little protein and healthy fats, which help for a better blood sugar response and are good for the gut.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Some people may want to avoid an underripe banana, however. Zenker said athletes may fall into that category since slow digestion can cause stomach heaviness. People who are sensitive to resistant starch and experience gastrointestinal discomfort after may want a different ripeness level, too.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Barely Ripe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Barely ripe bananas still have a little green near the ends.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bananas at this stage are mostly yellow with some green at the ends. While slightly softer, they’re still firm. This ripeness level suggests the banana is still high in fiber and low in sugar, but not to the same extent as underripe bananas. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“The resistant starches have started converting into simple sugars,” Zenker said. “Their mineral levels remain stable, particularly potassium and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/magnesium-has-definite-uses-but-isnt-the-cure-all-social-media-says-goog_l_685d64f9e4b0dc2d3f533c53" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="magnesium" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="685d64f9e4b0dc2d3f533c53" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;magnesium&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;She recommended a barely ripe banana to people who want the digestive benefits of an underripe banana without that chalky taste, as well as those who need steady energy throughout the day without major effects on their blood sugar. That means, similar to underripe bananas, barely ripe ones are great for people with insulin resistance, prediabetes, diabetes, metabolic syndrome or digestive conditions. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“They can also be ideal for peri- or post-menopausal women due to the resistant starch content that helps combat the effects of insulin resistance and supports gut health as hormonal changes occur,” Zenker added.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ripe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Yaorusheng via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Yaorusheng via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;A fully ripe banana has no green showing on the ends.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bananas at this stage are fully yellow and soft, but not mushy. They’re easy to peel and have a sweet smell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;While ripe bananas are listed separately from barely ripe ones here, it’s important to note that not all experts find the differences noteworthy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Nutrition-wise, these types of bananas are pretty much the same,” Sauceda said. “In fact, the &lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/1105314/nutrients" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="USDA nutrient database categorizes these two types of bananas together" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/1105314/nutrients" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;USDA nutrient database categorizes these two types of bananas together&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;With that said, if we’re going to make distinctions, Zenker shared what they are: In ripe bananas, starches have mostly converted into natural sugars, &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/signs-not-enough-fiber-digestions_l_66ba37afe4b0eabd2393b96d" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="fiber" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="66ba37afe4b0eabd2393b96d" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;fiber&lt;/a&gt; decreases, and sugar and antioxidant content increase. Vitamins and minerals hit their peak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sauceda added more noteworthy benefits. “One banana has 8% of your daily value for potassium, which is a mineral many people don’t get enough of,” she said. “This mineral is important for blood pressure and muscle contraction. It also meets 8% of your daily value for magnesium, which is important for &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/the-best-types-of-milk-to-drink-for-bone-health-including-non-dairy-options_l_6564b70be4b05f498ba14f45" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="bone health" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="6564b70be4b05f498ba14f45" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;bone health&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zenker encouraged a ripe banana for people who are about to work out, want quick and convenient whole-food energy, or are looking to increase potassium intake (perhaps to manage high blood pressure or other cardiovascular issues), as well as for kids who want an easy-to-eat, sugary food. Ripe bananas are also a good in-between for people who want fiber without the digestion-related concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Very Ripe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Stefania Pelfini la Waziya via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Stefania Pelfini la Waziya via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Two very ripe bananas, indicated by brown spots on the peel.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bananas at this stage are soft, have brown spots and emit a strong aroma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Sugar content is near its peak, and fiber continues to decrease,” Zenker said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;That’s great for people who need quick energy, have sensitive digestive symptoms, have low appetite or want a sweet treat, Zenker said. Individuals who are trying to manage their blood sugar may want to avoid very ripe bananas, however, since they’re higher in sugar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overripe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Karl Tapales via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Karl Tapales via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;An overripe banana looks brown or black and is usually mushy.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bananas at this stage look brown or black and are soft, even mushy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;They’re highest in sugar and antioxidants, lowest in fiber, losing their vitamin C content and maintaining their potassium content, according to Zenker. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As far as other vitamins go, some are increasing while others are decreasing. “For example, a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/1105314/nutrients" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="ripe banana has 14 milligrams of vitamin C" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/1105314/nutrients" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ripe banana has 14 milligrams of vitamin C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; but an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/1105073/nutrients" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="overripe one has 10 milligrams" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/1105073/nutrients" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="12"&gt;&lt;span&gt;overripe one has 10 milligrams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;,” Sauceda said. “Interestingly, overripe bananas have a bit more folate than ripe bananas.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;So again, there are pros and cons, and certain populations and situations for which it’s best suited. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“This stage is best for baking and freezing (banana bread, cookies, smoothies) rather than as a raw snack,” Zenker said. “It’s gentle on digestion and good for anyone needing fast calories, such as athletes, [but] not as ideal for people with diabetes or those seeking fiber or nutrient density.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sauceda is a fan of the smoothie option. “You don’t need to add as much banana when you use an overripe one for your smoothie, which can mean less added sugars,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As evidenced here, the banana to pick at the grocery store isn’t necessarily &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;just&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt; the one you like the taste or color of. Yes, we know this concept is a bit bananas, literally — &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt; it’s true.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;At the same time, we can’t blame you for going by the taste metric. Plus, bananas are nutritious whenever you eat them. “Overall, bananas are a great fruit whether you eat them green or ripe,” Sauceda said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxNenBwbHI2dGl2RVJxYXRsZ0xMV25WVlNmYWJVeVhOYS1DQ09UTk8yMFFPU0NXc2t1M3cyejVhVmN2aHdBbS1IX2hGSlNVR0RaQ0xDd1RlbHlTdUZiamxkcDFZSGJXX1dFcUc1LUtjdGxZWGwxNm10WDN6dzZUQkZmUUpQSlZ1ck1jZkJLQzBzc9IBlAFBVV95cUxPaVFfTGs1RGRRNzBfNDJ3NWNWRVN6YU1mMVFZLXdtYmdJYUNtc25yaV9EVkxmUlpqV1pxaDJUUDZTUHIwT2pJVFB0M0ZReDVkX043RW9XQUZuSndaSE5vTndHc3pMeGJFOFpyUHAybmFsSzBtcFRMbGlPSG1HRjZyVUVBTXRFUFZSVkxydW1ydm05dEI0</guid></item><item><title>带状疱疹疫苗可能会减缓，防止痴呆进展，研究发现-今日美国</title><link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/graphics/2025/12/07/shingles-vaccine-slow-prevent-dementia-study/87606825007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_dt"&gt;Updated Dec. 7, 2025, 11:10 a.m. ET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;A new &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-025-08800-x" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; suggests the &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2025/03/24/how-long-does-shingles-last/82634260007" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;shingles&lt;/a&gt; vaccine may lower the likelihood of developing dementia as well as slow its progression in people who have already been diagnosed with the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Researchers are finding more evidence that certain herpes viruses, such as shingles, which can infect the nervous system, might play a role in causing dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;An initial study published in &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41380-021-01138-6" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Nature&lt;/a&gt; and a follow-up study conducted by &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Stanford Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, published in the journal &lt;a href="http://linkinghub.elsevier.com/retrieve/pii/S0092867425012565" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Cell&lt;/a&gt; on Dec. 2, show the shingles vaccination may also have therapeutic benefits against dementia by reducing the disease's progression and lowering the chance of dying from it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;For those battling dementia, these findings are promising. Dementia cases have been predicted to increase in the coming years, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-024-03340-9.epdf?sharing_token=rnJZ3-p0kX4lowC-Bt-PZ9RgN0jAjWel9jnR3ZoTv0MVutFf8dmYDbw6diQeD5ESeQi4_Zi5WoMqvnLv8j67SeaLJo1TjACSb9yKKx4AwC_iAdWBIDfJ40ornjGdxmiLTnVLuT6dUNYY2YtjrXKeceIH6e5jENTgtkHdPsSYgI6GHyMXllcVUIxrhsnLYz5FGk4ZEeVfqe5qNp-7Zak-6IJOS7XZGEGWiDZlU7o4OYo%3D&amp;amp;tracking_referrer=www.scientificamerican.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; released in 2024, which states the lifetime risk of dementia could rise to 42% after age 55 − a much faster rate than anticipated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Unable to view our graphics? &lt;a href="/story/graphics/2025/12/07/shingles-vaccine-slow-prevent-dementia-study/87606825007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Click here to see them.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“We see an effect on your probability of dying from dementia among those who already have dementia,” Dr. Pascal Geldsetzer, assistant professor of medicine at &lt;a href="https://profiles.stanford.edu/pascal-geldsetzer" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Stanford University&lt;/a&gt; and senior author of the most recent study, said of the potential effects of the shingles vaccine in a recent interview with &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/02/health/shingles-vaccine-dementia-progression-study-wellness" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;CNN&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“That means that the vaccine doesn’t just have a preventive potential, but actually a therapeutic potential as a treatment, because we see some benefits already among those who have dementia,” he said. “To me, this was really exciting to see and unexpected.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;The link: Shingles and dementia&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The varicella-zoster virus is a type of herpes virus that causes both chickenpox and shingles. The virus stays dormant in the body after a person has fully recovered from chickenpox. The &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2025/03/24/elizabeth-banks-shingles-vaccines-aging-parenting/82633098007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;shingles virus&lt;/a&gt; often doesn't cause any more issues, but it can reappear years later and cause shingles, a painful rash, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/shingles/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The CDC estimates that about 1 in every 3 people in the United States will develop shingles in their lifetime. Shingles can be prevented by getting the two-dose vaccine, which is about &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/shingles/vaccines/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;90% effective&lt;/a&gt; in preventing shingles in the elderly. The CDC recommends getting the vaccine when you turn 50.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The study results support the growing theory that viruses affecting the brain's function may raise the risk of dementia. Dementia affects over 55 million people worldwide, according to &lt;a href="https://www.alzint.org/about/dementia-facts-figures/dementia-statistics/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Alzheimer's Disease International&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Scientists suspect that the shingles vaccination may help by preventing the reactivation of dormant viruses like varicella zoster and herpes simplex, which are thought to contribute to brain inflammation and the accumulation of dangerous proteins linked to dementia. How that works is still unknown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Another theory is that the vaccine may strengthen the immune system more broadly, preventing immunological deterioration as people age, according to &lt;a href="https://www.cardiff.ac.uk/news/view/2985389-shingles-vaccine-may-help-prevent-and-slow-dementia,-study-finds" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Cardiff University&lt;/a&gt; in Wales.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The scientists note that more research is necessary to confirm the results and gain a deeper understanding of how the vaccine affects brain health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>USA Today</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:26:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxOZDhVYjg1bUhuWW5fczQ2ZHQ2em9yTFp2QV9oLVM2RFhkZEVhMVUxdFJpYUVCc0s5d0RhRjFzNkZ6T1Fycy1ad1RSYmIxb2ltTUJrc29rb1VoWFFPWE5iR0VobGdNQ01KaExqSHRwRk9DMlRfRUNxRmlPMzRvVS1BcWpHNWJwZy1LemtmRkt1SV84Sk1oMlU3NUltSzAyeEhPcGFJREMtcmtUNUlo</guid></item><item><title>您是不是睡得太多了？新的研究揭示了成年人真正需要多少小时来维持大脑健康-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/are-you-sleeping-too-much-new-research-reveals-how-many-hours-adults-really-need-for-brain-health/articleshow/125814858.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of us worry about not sleeping enough, the bleary mornings, the heavy eyelids, the sense of running on fumes. What almost no one considers is the opposite problem: the idea that getting too much sleep might quietly work against your brain. It sounds counterintuitive. It even borders on unfair. But researchers in Washington, US, found that the range of sleep linked to better brain health may be smaller than expected, with both short and long nights tied to decline, a finding that contradicts years of official guidance and could make even good sleepers pause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;And yes, it’s unsettling. Most of us have had nights where eight or nine hours felt like a luxury; few imagine it could put them in the same risk bracket as someone sleeping far too little. But that’s exactly what one new study suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Fix Your Sleep Naturally! Sadhguru’s 5-Step Routine for Deep Rest&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What the Washington researchers found&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Their &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/brain/article/144/9/2852/6401973" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;looked at a group of older adults whose sleep varied widely but whose sleep quality was consistently poor. The striking finding was that people sleeping less than 4.5 hours a night, and those sleeping more than 6.5 hours, showed greater risk of cognitive decline over time. The pattern, they noted, resembled the kind of deterioration associated with ageing ,one of the strongest predictors for conditions such as Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; They even suggested an ideal zone: between 4.5 and 6.5 hours of sleep, at least for the specific population they studied. It’s a narrow band, and the conclusion is the kind that makes both the public and the sleep-science community sit up a little straighter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why this challenges what health bodies say&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Writing in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/sleeping-longer-than-6-5-hours-a-night-associated-with-cognitive-decline-according-to-research-whats-really-going-on-here-170989" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, senior psychology lecturer Greg Elder acknowledged that the results run counter to what major health bodies teach. He explained that, “The study showed that sleeping longer than 6.5 hours was associated with cognitive decline over time, this is low when we consider that older adults are recommended to get between seven and eight hours of sleep every night.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elder notes that neither the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/every-mind-matters/mental-health-issues/sleep/#:~:text=a%20great%20night.-,How%20many%20hours%20of%20sleep%20do%20I%20need?,between%208%20to%2016%20hours." rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;NHS &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;nor the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/sleep/about/index.html" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt; US Centres for Disease Control (CDC)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; currently suggest that sleeping more than 6.5 hours is harmful. But he emphasises that the Washington study measured sleep quality as well, and that all participants who slept very little or a lot were also sleeping badly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why might sleep duration affect the brain?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; He also notes that researchers still don’t fully understand why lack of sleep is linked to cognitive decline. “One theory is that sleep helps our brain flush out harmful proteins that build up during the day,” he writes. “So interfering with sleep might interfere with our brain’s ability to get rid of these. Experimental evidence even supports this, showing that even just one night of sleep deprivation temporarily increases beta-amyloid levels in the brain of healthy people.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Beta-amyloid is one of the proteins associated with Alzheimer's disease. The theory is not a certainty, but Elder points to it because it illustrates how sensitive the brain may be to disrupted sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;So is it too much sleep, or something else entirely?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, he is careful about what the study cannot claim. All participants, regardless of how long they slept, struggled with poor sleep quality. That detail matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elder suggests that the real story may be less about the clock and more about what happens while you’re asleep. “It could be the case that it isn’t necessarily the length of the sleep that matters, but the quality of that sleep when it comes to risk of developing dementia,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the study found a correlation between sleeping more than 6.5 hours and cognitive decline, Elder stresses an important point: the people sleeping the most may have had underlying issues that weren’t detected in the tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For example, this could include poor health, socioeconomic status or physical activity levels. All of these factors together may explain why longer sleep was linked to cognitive decline.” In other words, long sleep may be a marker of something else, not a cause in itself. It’s a reminder that correlation and causation rarely hold hands as neatly as we’d like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Another study says sleep duration may be genetic &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the Washington findings challenge conventional assumptions, another group of researchers on the opposite side of the US is offering an even more complicated picture. A separate &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ucsf.edu/news/2022/03/422416/when-it-comes-sleep-its-quality-over-quantity" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study from San Francisco&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; centred on Familial Natural Short Sleep (FNSS), a genetic trait in which people naturally function fully on four to six hours of sleep. These individuals aren’t sleep-deprived; they simply don’t need the traditional eight-hour benchmark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neurologist Louis Ptacek, lead author of the study, said: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;“There’s a dogma in the field that everyone needs eight hours of sleep, but our work to date confirms that the amount of sleep people need differs based on genetics. Think of it as analogous to height; there’s no perfect amount of height, each person is different. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;We’ve shown that the case is similar for sleep.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Ptacek and his team have spent over a decade studying these short sleepers, though he warns that understanding the genetics will take time. Mapping the sleep genes, he says, is like solving&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt; “a thousand piece jigsaw puzzle.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; What they can say for certain is that some people are built for shorter nights, and that treating them as chronically underslept would be a mistake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The San Francisco researchers also point out how often sleep patterns intersect with neurological disease&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;. “Sleep problems are common in all diseases of the brain,”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; they write, explaining that sleep relies on many parts of the brain functioning together. When any of these areas are damaged, disrupted or degenerating, sleep disturbances often follow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="80"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="81"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What all of this actually means for sleepers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="83"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Taken together, the two studies paint a picture that is more nuanced than any single recommendation can capture. On one hand, sleeping significantly less than 4.5 hours or more than 6.5 hours &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;in a population already experiencing poor sleep quality&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; was associated with cognitive decline. On the other, the San Francisco team reminds us that some people are genetically wired to do perfectly well on short nights, and that sleep quantity is far from the whole story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="88"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; For readers, it’s tempting to interpret the Washington findings as a directive, a new rule to replace the old one. But neither Elder nor the researchers themselves suggest rewriting national guidelines based on a study of 100 people. Instead, Elder leans toward a simpler, more intuitive takeaway: focus less on the number of hours you’re asleep, and more on &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;how well&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; your sleep restores you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="92"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; If anything, the emerging research nudges us toward a more personalised understanding of sleep. The idea that everyone needs eight hours may have been a convenient shorthand, but the science, and the people studying it, are telling a more complex story. Sleep is individual. Sleep is layered. And sometimes, sleep is too much of a good thing, not because of the number on the clock, but because of what the brain is struggling with while you’re in it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="94"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:25:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowJBVV95cUxPczhVbHZfY05SQlEzWEhrSmh5czNyRVZBOVdmcnNfOWpWRjNPckFNUFVid2FPbm0wc050MUJnekVINmUxZnpxam5za2ZrbDNMRGlqTXRscEFKZDdpT09GMENRQkMxM1pobXpPOEtzOHpFU3Jib1NZTEJSbUdwaFdOOFh5YXQ4eGJHbjNxSzh4Ny1EWnI0bGxfYmY3NVZiQTZRWHVmcW1ScTV5TTFjZHRKYW5STkw3dlROb0pzT3BHbkwwa3hkdTV2WWVkaWNsOHRyTVcxUFFPekZEU1AzeFNzQk5CX1AzeEo1U2JQRnREYTE0bThVUWxod1djaE82SXFFZVpQZjJaTHpWSFdVN0VqV3pfcDZHYUNvWVI5aUhlbnJGQUk</guid></item><item><title>专家表示，肯尼迪疫苗顾问“扭转了局面” -路透社</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/kennedy-vaccine-advisers-turned-back-clock-disease-prevention-experts-say-2025-12-07/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Reuters</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:08:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3gFBVV95cUxPQ0tleU1rU2xSdTl1SG1jNXkzeWZNNTNyU1hVZXRpeEZuaXhVaWo0dmRrR0RvNmtyckNxUzB2NVY1MkdvdmJ3U2ZvTjhBeFRxODRHbndxS2ZjSlBFZ0Q3TDU4MW9hR1o2ZmFfNDVIaHJPOVR3cXpWbmhZa08yVHd1OHdFSzkxRERLX1RXcUdBbVBMNmxFNnM4LVJUcHE2WVppY2ZwcWprT0VrN2JaY2U0Q1BTTkxRRXFuX0ZHY2dDU2pYQ01wbTU1QlhCN2tkNnM4c3czQXdydzVoY0hWaXc</guid></item><item><title>女性在亲戚几乎不知道被要求借钱后处于尴尬的境地，发短信“连续多次” - Yahoo Life UK</title><link>https://uk.style.yahoo.com/woman-awkward-position-relative-she-110000702.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A woman said that a relative recently texted and requested to “borrow” money for an “urgent” reason&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She said she has only met the relative twice in her life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The woman shared her story on a community forum and asked others what they thought she should do&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A woman says that a relative who she barely knows recently asked to &lt;a href="https://people.com/husband-refuses-to-lend-sister-in-law-money-after-borrowing-8k-now-hes-being-called-controlling-11858009" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:borrow money,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;borrow money,&lt;/a&gt; and she’s not sure what to do about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The woman shared her story on the &lt;a href="https://www.mumsnet.com/talk/am_i_being_unreasonable/5452330-relative-asking-for-money" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:“Am I Being Unreasonable?”;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;“Am I Being Unreasonable?”&lt;/a&gt; forum on the U.K-based community site Mumsnet.com, a place where people can go to seek input on a variety of interpersonal topics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In her post, the original poster (OP) shared that she and her parents recently came back from visiting family abroad. She said that shortly after returning home, one of her relatives texted and asked to “borrow money.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Bear in mind, I've met her twice — the last time being 12 days ago and before that about 10 years ago when she was a child,” the OP explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty Stock Images&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Woman worriedly checking her phone (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“She said she would pay it back in a few months and that it was 'urgent' — to the point where she was texting multiple times in a row,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The woman said that she is not only shocked by the unexpected request, but she &lt;a href="https://people.com/woman-annoyed-after-her-neighbor-lets-their-kids-run-amok-on-her-property-11852667" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:is also “annoyed”;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;is also “annoyed” &lt;/a&gt;due to the fact that the relative didn’t ask for a specific amount, but rather “asked me 'how much I'd be willing to give.’ ”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The OP said that she has since told her parents about the request and they are “also baffled.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty Stock Images&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Hand holding cash (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“AIBU [am I being unreasonable] to say 'no' outright, despite [the relative] knowing we obviously have some money to travel (having just seen them all)?” she asked at the end of her post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In a follow-up comment, the OP clarified that the relative in question lives in a &lt;a href="https://people.com/health/ranchers-struggle-with-access-to-mental-health-services-as-covid-puts-stress-on-rural-communities/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:small rural area;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;small rural area&lt;/a&gt;, and that her family gave their family cash on their recent visit as is the “custom” in that area of the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Commenters unanimously agreed that the OP should not lend her relative the money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Sounds like there may be a family or &lt;a href="https://people.com/woman-wants-to-buck-tradition-and-not-name-firstborn-son-after-father-in-law-11682823" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:cultural tradition;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;cultural tradition&lt;/a&gt; where your parents have sent money to relatives back home? And now the younger generation have been brought up with this and are expecting money from you,” one person said, before adding, “Families are complicated and if you don’t want to do this then don’t. You might need to block the relative though as it doesn’t sound like they’ll stop asking.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-puzzler-8620185" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now!;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“They are being very cheeky. I would respond sorry I’m broke not sure how I’ll make it to payday myself,” said some else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Someone else suggested a simpler route and advised the OP to “say no and stick to it,” then &lt;a href="https://people.com/woman-finds-out-friends-girlfriend-blocked-her-reddit-11827020" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:“block and ignore”;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;“block and ignore”&lt;/a&gt; if needed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/woman-in-awkward-position-after-relative-she-barely-knows-asked-to-borrow-money-11860028" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Life UK</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNVnZFcTRNUWlmX20takxKZ1N2ekpsWHNabUxGZ2NyVllPRW5mRkpDUUh6bU5oeW1WR1pUdTlfSWFtdklxbjR2WkR2amx1aDd5WEs5NWQ0VTg4a0dJRU1GM0llemR3YldSTVlBenVRbFZ6QVpxcXVvd1VMcFNBYjQ4R0lhTQ</guid></item><item><title>泰勒·斯威夫特（ Taylor Swift ）确保永远不会做这1件事。Neuroscience Says She's Right - Inc.com</title><link>https://www.inc.com/minda-zetlin/taylor-swift-makes-sure-never-to-do-this-1-thing-neuroscience-says-shes-right/91274508</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Inc.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 10:37:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxOWHFGazlKcDVwWVQ1NmlRVjNQMFlmRXB3QkFDN0pyWTB0VDRvdnlGRWg2QWYxYy01TEVXaXI0SkpTbW5tb1N6eW9jcmdSbXFOVXlEU2tJY1U5WEtabFZUWXhpNWcxT3A5bHRUTG9vbkdZOEd5d2M0MUdrbzZLaXBnendpYXBiZDVXMXlHSTByTmJOVzkwOExORTRSeEF0dWoyMFdCNVg1NmtJcHgtM1d1ZkxmRHdZUU9GTWlv</guid></item><item><title>随着疫苗指南被颠覆，父母的困惑和焦虑-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/07/us/vaccines-chlldren-hepatitis-guidelines.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 10:02:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNSGZ2Sy1aVXgzb3hWZjdkMENJYVNSWHl2QkJpLWI2TzZPZ3FDYk1HX0xrZ3NtRTlzZUhBQ3JqMXk5aTdzcnZuYWc5dnM5aDBFUktVSWxqY0VkaVBMYmJDd1VSWWpVenJEY2YtZ0FObXFQbWlEdFhVRW5WbEZqeFE1amlxYUZhRWxX</guid></item><item><title>德里肿瘤学家诺伊达警告“持续咳嗽不正常” ；分享您不应忽视的肺癌早期迹象|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/noida-delhi-oncologist-warns-persistent-cough-is-not-normal-shares-early-signs-of-lung-cancer-you-should-not-ignore-101765098880586.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/noida-delhi-oncologist-warns-persistent-cough-is-not-normal-shares-early-signs-of-lung-cancer-you-should-not-ignore-101765098880586.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;A cough that continues for weeks despite rest, routine medication, and familiar home remedies is often the body’s way of indicating that something deeper may be happening inside the lungs.&lt;/span&gt; A persistent cough is rarely just a leftover &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/infection" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="infection"&gt;infection&lt;/a&gt; or a seasonal reaction, and when it lingers without a clear reason, it becomes a clinical sign that deserves attention.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/07/550x309/105361_1763808507134_1765099562312.jpg" alt="Lung cancer symptoms often overlap with common ailments, leading to delays in diagnosis.(Freepik)" title="Lung cancer symptoms often overlap with common ailments, leading to delays in diagnosis.(Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/07/550x309/105361_1763808507134_1765099562312.jpg" alt="Lung cancer symptoms often overlap with common ailments, leading to delays in diagnosis.(Freepik)" title="Lung cancer symptoms often overlap with common ailments, leading to delays in diagnosis.(Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Lung cancer symptoms often overlap with common ailments, leading to delays in diagnosis.(Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In many early-stage &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/lung-cancer" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="lung cancer"&gt;lung cancer&lt;/a&gt; cases, this cough appears long before any noticeable pain or breathlessness, which is why people tend to brush it aside. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;In an interview with HT Lifestyle, Dr Manish Sahni, surgical oncologist and robotic surgeon, Kailash Hospital, Noida and Delhi, shares why a persistent cough is never “normal” and lists the early signs of lung cancer to watch for.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; (Also read: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fitness-coach-shares-3-simple-tips-to-lose-1-kg-per-week-before-new-year-2026-exact-plan-for-quick-results-weight-loss-101765083736736.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Fitness coach shares 3 simple tips to lose 1 kg per week before New Year 2026: 'Exact mini-cut I use for quick results'"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fitness coach shares 3 simple tips to lose 1 kg per week before New Year 2026: 'Exact mini-cut I use for quick results' &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;What lung-cancer coughs look like&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sharing key symptoms, Dr Sahni says, “A cough linked to lung cancer behaves differently from one that follows a cold or a &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cities/mumbai-news/hosps-see-sharp-spike-in-heat-exhaustion-viral-illness-cases-amid-soaring-temperatures-101744140408533.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="viral illness"&gt;viral illness&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;It often carries on for more than three weeks, does not respond to usual symptomatic treatment, and may slowly become deeper or more forceful as the tumour irritates the airway lining.&lt;/span&gt; Some individuals notice blood tinges in the mucus or a change in their voice. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;These shifts occur because an early tumour can alter the airflow pathways or create subtle pressure inside the lungs, triggering irritation that results in a steady cough.&lt;/span&gt;”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Pollution is changing who gets diagnosed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Sahni, smoking still remains a major contributor, but it’s no longer the only one. “There is also a visible change in the profile of patients being diagnosed today. &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/smoking" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Smoking"&gt;Smoking&lt;/a&gt; remains a major risk factor, yet a growing number of cases are now being detected in individuals with no history of tobacco use. Long-term exposure to polluted air is emerging as an important contributor.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/img/2024/08/09/550x309/shutterstock2401940947_1723203498457_1723203516451.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Many significant factors contribute to lung cancer risks that are frequently overlooked((Shutterstock))" title="Many significant factors contribute to lung cancer risks that are frequently overlooked((Shutterstock))"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Many significant factors contribute to lung cancer risks that are frequently overlooked((Shutterstock))&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;He adds, “Fine particulate matter and toxic gases can travel deep into the lung tissue, causing persistent inflammation that, over time, may alter the genetic behaviour of lung cells.&lt;/span&gt; This helps explain why people living in severely polluted cities are reporting symptoms earlier, even without traditional risk factors.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;The subtle signals most people overlook&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;He also highlights that lung cancer symptoms are often mistaken for everyday fatigue or minor infections: “The early phase of lung cancer often blends into everyday life.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Unexplained tiredness, a sense of heaviness in the chest, mild breathlessness during routine tasks, frequent throat irritation or a sudden drop in appetite are frequently mistaken for minor health fluctuations.&lt;/span&gt;”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Tuberculosis is a major public health challenge in India, and its symptoms mimic early signs of lung cancer, making it one of the important factors for delayed &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/diagnosis" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="diagnosis"&gt;diagnosis&lt;/a&gt;. Some individuals also experience recurrent chest infections because tumour-related obstruction can prevent air from moving freely in the affected area,” says Sahni.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Ending with a reminder, Dr Sahni emphasises, “Lung cancer tends to progress quietly, which is why delays in seeking care remain common. Any cough that persists beyond a few weeks, particularly in high-pollution environments or in people with a family predisposition, should be evaluated. With timely diagnosis supported by advanced imaging and precise treatment options, outcomes can improve considerably. Recognising the earliest signs and responding without delay can make a meaningful difference.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 09:41:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgJBVV95cUxOYnhGM1hQY05INnI5TXBYM3dhSF9DejFiLWMySlFSRU9GUG1XTWo2TndkQjJLc0FFSDg1MnZlamRqSTBpclQzaDFrVFNtNGp1ZWdSSU5qRUd2c0RILXZYN1piQXk5OGZUTTlqRWcwZ1o5QlZ2bjBxN2ZnM0FMbU5ZbU83QVJOR2RlTzZZeC04bEVfUURMaENUNFh6MWZRWmQtbHJEb05wdGxrLWJhVEFBYk5XbVNaT21XUURuU29hOV9xUUNOdE9NVkszOVRSdDFHUHE5bWYyZ1BlQlJpUmZoalJjdnpuRGRhNG95ZklEb28ycGRUbC1zLU9xM0l6dnlqazdVQ3FxWTl5TURTMkc4VEtR0gGXAkFVX3lxTE1HTjkwQ0I4NHp4NkNJM1VEQl9ScHBVbjlpR0NORUVSd3A4Z1pzeUpXVm1VTFdlVnA2NjFuTEJPWUVqaWVaVVlsNGNNX1NScGxwblM5RGpZR3RsYldxbzRablFzbl9WemlMdXplNUhnVHp3WmJLMVB6RUpkZ215YjNaOU9IRXFISjY2clFGaEJ5UUowVVRPbm5DSUlCMmE4b2Z4V2NZUmJVN2U1WW5nMkpKMmxyNWRFa1FIWlZPdjJGYnFEMmhUa2w3MWtaUS1VQzJiQzkwSURmM3IyRnRIVG40M0JyXzlNdDR4dDJNRll2YlJ3ZFJPY1g4ZlZuakpfR3lobWY5al81LUxBeEZ2NUtGVkZsUnU0TQ</guid></item><item><title>声称导致黑死病的未知火山爆发- DW</title><link>https://www.dw.com/en/unknown-volcano-eruption-claimed-as-cause-of-black-death/a-75021225</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-tracking-name="rich-text" data-tracking-skip="true" class="c17j8gzx rc0m0op r1ebneao s198y7xq rich-text l1evdo4u blt0baw s16w0xvi rcjjkz7 w128axg5 b1fzgn0z"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A climate catastrophe that forced a rethink in trade routes was probably responsible for introducing the plague to Europe and causing the Black Death in the 14th century, researchers suggest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Published in the journal &lt;a rel="noopener follow" target="_blank" class="external-link" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s43247-025-02964-0" title="External link — Communications Earth &amp;amp; Environment,"&gt;Communications Earth &amp;amp; Environment,&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.5 3.5 11.5 4.233C14.342 4.233 15.167 4.245 15.167 4.258L8.984 10.467 10.033 11.516C14.826 6.725 16.228 5.333 16.242 5.333L16.267 9 17.733 9 17.733 2.767 11.5 2.767 11.5 3.5M2.267 11 2.267 17.233 16.733 17.233 16.733 12 15.267 12 15.25 15.75 9.5 15.75 3.75 15.75 3.75 6.25 9.5 6.233 9.5 4.767 2.267 4.767 2.267 11 "&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the new study combined historical records with studies of polar ice cores and European tree rings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Researchers Martin Bauch at the Leibniz Institute in Germany, and Ulf Büntgen at Cambridge University, UK, conclude that an unidentified volcanic eruption around the year 1345 pumped climate-cooling ash and sulfur into Earth's atmosphere and caused crop failures across the Mediterranean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This forced powerful port cities to open trade with the Golden Horde, which dominated Central Asia at the time. In doing so, it provided safe passage for &lt;em&gt;Yersinia pestis&lt;/em&gt;, the bacterium that caused the Black Death, into Europe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Italian city-states had developed successful food security strategies. But they were no match for the plague.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"By a combination of several coincidences at a time, you get a side effect that you were not expecting. You couldn’t — from a 14th century perspective — calculate and expect this to happen — the same system which successfully saves you from starvation, will lead to their mass death if the Black Death reaches your city," said Bauch, who is an environmental historian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span data-slot-id="Article_InContent-1" class="rich-text-ad"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Origins of the Black Death&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plague is caused by &lt;em&gt;Yersinia pestis &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/black-death-causing-bacteriums-dna-sequenced/a-15457747"&gt;bacteria&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;The Black Death is the name given to a major plague wave across Europe from 1347 to 1351.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If bitten by an animal, such as a flea or a rodent, that is infected with the bacteria, a person would develop symptoms of swollen lymph nodes — called "buboes" — and potentially a mix of fever, fatigue, vomiting, nausea, and aches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the lungs were infected, the bubonic plague became pneumonic plague — a type that spread faster and was always fatal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, the development of bacteria-killing &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/antibiotics/t-64386318"&gt;antibiotics&lt;/a&gt; has largely consigned plague to the past. But it still exists as a problem in some parts of the world, especially &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/bubonic-plague-festers-in-madagascars-slums/a-18085422"&gt;Madagascar&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/democratic-republic-of-congo-drc/t-38232616"&gt;DR Congo&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/peru/t-38335614"&gt;Peru&lt;/a&gt;. Cases continue to occur in the western United States, parts of Brazil and Bolivia, South and Central Asia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p data-vendor-cmp-id="c43449" data-lang-code="en" data-id="75023046" class="embed dw-widget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it's in Central Asia where the Black Death likely originated. In 2022, another group of researchers from Germany and the UK were able to &lt;a rel="noopener follow" target="_blank" class="external-link" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-022-04800-3" title="External link — pinpoint"&gt;pinpoint&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.5 3.5 11.5 4.233C14.342 4.233 15.167 4.245 15.167 4.258L8.984 10.467 10.033 11.516C14.826 6.725 16.228 5.333 16.242 5.333L16.267 9 17.733 9 17.733 2.767 11.5 2.767 11.5 3.5M2.267 11 2.267 17.233 16.733 17.233 16.733 12 15.267 12 15.25 15.75 9.5 15.75 3.75 15.75 3.75 6.25 9.5 6.233 9.5 4.767 2.267 4.767 2.267 11 "&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the origin of the so-called "source strain" of &lt;em&gt;Yersinia pestis.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They connected evidence of the disease that tore through Europe to outbreaks in the Tian Shan mountains, which border modern day &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/kyrgyzstan/t-38960474"&gt;Kyrgyzstan&lt;/a&gt;, in 1338.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It's likely that through trade and human movement, disease-carrying rodents and insects were transported the long distances into western Eurasia and Europe — bringing the plague with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="placeholder-image master_landscape big"&gt;&lt;img data-format="MASTER_LANDSCAPE" data-id="62145416" data-url="https://static.dw.com/image/62145416_${formatId}.jpg" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" alt="A mountain range"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="img-caption"&gt;The Tian Shan mountain region of Central Asia is considered the cradle of plague bacteria that spread across Medieval Europe&lt;small class="copyright"&gt;Image: Lyazzat Musralina/REUTERS&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Environmental markers, historical implications, plague trade&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How plague arrived to Europe has been widely debated by researchers. In this latest study, Bauch and Büntgen used a mix of scientific data and historical records to detail at least one, potential pathway for the disease to enter the continent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They argue in their paper that tree rings from eight regions across Europe, and volcanic sulfur in polar ice cores, show a major tropical volcanic eruption in 1345 could have caused a climate cooling effect that impacted the Mediterranean crops, and drove famine in southern Europe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Records show that major Italian port cities, such as Venice and Genoa, engaged with the Mongol Golden Horde near the end of this famine, to import grain via Black Sea trade routes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supplying the region with grain helped prevent starvation for locals but likely introduced plague that continued to move throughout Italian states when other cities acquired grain supplies the same way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-vendor-cmp-id="c43449" data-lang-code="en" data-id="75022605" class="embed dw-widget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using environmental references like tree rings and ice cores allows scientists and historians to work together to understand how environmental changes may have influenced social and public health events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Studies of subtle changes to tree rings and other "natural proxies" help what is known as paleoclimatic reconstruction — the understanding of ancient climates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"Only tree rings have the quality that really enables us to bring things together," Bauch said.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the scientific data is combined with historical records, researchers like Bauch and Büntgen, can begin to explain the factors that may have driven major events, including the Black Death.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maria Spyrou, a paleopathologist at the University of Tübingen, who led the group that identified the plague’s origin in 2022, said the new Bauch-Büntgen study added another piece to the puzzle of how plague had infiltrated and infected medieval Europe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"The [Bauch-Büntgen] study provides further support for a mid-fourteenth century emergence of the pandemic, and is in line with genetic data showing that the ancestors of Black Death strains in Europe existed in the Volga region as well as in the Tian Shan region," Spyrou told DW in an email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Spyrou also notes that while the journey of plague from the Black Sea to Europe now seems to taken had another potential route, it's still unclear how it moved throughout Central Asia itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bauch agrees with that assessment. He said their study provided only one of several potential explanations for how plague entered and spread across 14th century Europe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Edited by: Zulfikar Abbany&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-vendor-cmp-id="c44391" data-lang-code="en" data-id="68339716" class="embed dw-widget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>DW</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 08:04:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxNencwTFV2Sk53WHVfb09LU3dXLWxSRVJibmVpOGlvQmVyMWNQQjBnemZ0UTI1TzF5RFJ2TlpPZFhKMjhMT1RQa2NZMVdhN2FBdkVKWTVqWXY5X3ZFeUdNaVVYaTRXX2tFVmo2R0ZWTjdYNzhVR3IyZGo1RTc0RHZuZEpRZDhzUWVEYkdoczFZS0FibUnSAZMBQVVfeXFMTkpqblZyRGJqcEVoZ3NtekpIMlBLUGRQNUEydHpiX0dOMFA2TVNZSXhOVV9NUER3NHVmOGNOTTlOVndWS1MwcVF2bGV1M0h2S2pVYmc5TkpaOG5TaGlZdXVTOV9SUW45anRnc0lPQV9GcDhySUdSSHJtbmdicFhYU1BqVUtLaWtoVlNBdWQtN1IxV1FV</guid></item><item><title>癌症外科医生说肠癌的关系是真实的；解释为什么管理血糖对长寿很重要|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cancer-surgeon-says-the-gut-cancer-connection-is-real-explains-why-managing-your-blood-sugar-matters-for-longevity-101764937575165.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/cancer-surgeon-says-the-gut-cancer-connection-is-real-explains-why-managing-your-blood-sugar-matters-for-longevity-101764937575165.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;People trying to eat healthier struggle with sugar cravings and often think it's due to a lack of willpower. However, an oncologist, who often talks about longevity and lifestyle diseases, suggests that the real issue may be nutritional gaps in the body. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Some foods can help reduce sugar cravings by balancing hormones, stabilising insulin levels, and improving gut health, all of which are important for long-term control of cravings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/05/550x309/blood_sugar_1764939249173_1764939249388.jpg" alt="How do you flush sugar out of your gut?(Unsplash)" title="How do you flush sugar out of your gut?(Unsplash)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/05/550x309/blood_sugar_1764939249173_1764939249388.jpg" alt="How do you flush sugar out of your gut?(Unsplash)" title="How do you flush sugar out of your gut?(Unsplash)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;How do you flush sugar out of your gut?(Unsplash)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“As a laparoscopic cancer surgeon, I know how closely blood sugar levels connect to health. People see diabetes as just high blood sugar, but it affects much more than that. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Managing blood sugar can help prevent not just diabetes but also various types of cancer, and it's a critical link between gut health and cancer risk.&lt;/span&gt; Small changes can lead to a longer, healthier life,” Dr Arpit Bansal tells &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.healthshots.com/health-news/making-small-changes-to-your-diet-can-help-you-build-a-healthier-life-finds-study/" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Health Shots"&gt;Health Shots&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;What is the link between inflammation and blood sugar?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/diabetologist-explains-how-a-simple-15-minute-walk-after-meals-can-drop-your-blood-sugar-levels-instantly-101764660299365.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="blood sugar levels"&gt;blood sugar levels&lt;/a&gt; rise sharply, the body reacts with inflammation. Inflammation is like the body's alarm system, meant to protect us from harm. However, if high blood sugar happens often, this inflammation can become constant. "Chronic inflammation can harm sensitive systems in our body, especially our gut health", shares the doctor. Sudden spikes and drops in blood sugar can create small waves of inflammation. These may not be noticeable at first, but they can cause long-lasting damage.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/gi-cancer-surgeon-reveals-4-habits-to-avoid-and-suggests-3-dietary-choices-to-balance-your-gut-microbiome-101755786900528.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="gut microbiome"&gt;gut microbiome&lt;/a&gt; plays an important role in our health. Our intestines have trillions of bacteria, both good and bad. These bacteria are crucial for digestion, immune response, and overall wellness. "When we don’t manage blood sugar well, harmful bacteria can proliferate, leading to a condition known as leaky gut", says the expert. This happens when the gut's protective barrier is damaged, allowing toxins to enter the bloodstream and further inflaming the body.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Research in PubMed Central shows that inflammation in the body can lead to cancer, even before we notice any symptoms. "This connection is particularly strong for &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/gastroenterologist-says-unexplained-diarrhoea-and-constipation-are-red-flags-of-colon-cancer-shares-4-symptoms-101764746059335.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="colon cancer"&gt;colon cancer&lt;/a&gt; and other cancers of the digestive system", says Dr Bansal. Still, it may also affect different types of cancer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Is there a link between gut health and cancer?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gut health plays a key role in cancer risk. Our immune system depends on a healthy gut microbiome to work well. If the gut is not healthy, the immune response can weaken. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;A recent study by the American Diabetes Association shows that people with high inflammation from poor blood sugar control have a higher risk of developing certain cancers.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;For example, a study in the Journal of Clinical Oncology found that people with high blood sugar levels are more likely to get colorectal cancer, among other types.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;When the gut is healthy, it helps protect us from harmful substances and maintains a balanced internal environment. "To strengthen this natural protection, we should focus on food choices that support both blood sugar control and gut health", says the surgeon.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Why is it important to have a balanced meal?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Managing blood sugar is more than just avoiding sweets. It’s important to create balanced meals that keep you feeling full. "Include foods high in fiber, such as whole grains, fruits, vegetables, and legumes", adds Dr Bansal. These foods help keep blood sugar levels steady. In contrast, processed foods can cause quick spikes and drops in blood sugar, leading to inflammation.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Watch your portions and snack mindfully. Swapping a bag of chips for an apple is a simple choice that can make a big difference. "Eating a range of nutrient-rich foods helps control blood sugar levels", shares the gut expert. It supports healthy gut bacteria, which is important for a strong microbiome.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Is walking or cycling better for diabetes?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start small. Daily activities like walking or cycling can improve your metabolism and blood sugar levels. "Choose the stairs instead of the elevator, or take short breaks to move during the day", says the gut doctor. Adding brief exercise sessions can boost your metabolism and help control blood sugar, leading to better health over time.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Managing stress is very important. Practices like yoga, meditation, or deep breathing can help lower stress and stabilise blood sugar levels. When stress hormones rise, they can cause blood sugar spikes and negatively impact gut health.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;How often should you have your blood sugar checked?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the easiest ways to stay healthy for a long time is to have regular check-ups. "I recommend that my patients have their blood sugar levels checked annually. Catching problems early is critical," shares the doctor. If you notice any sudden changes in your digestion or strange symptoms, don't ignore them. These signs could mean something is wrong with how your body manages blood sugar.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Taking charge of your health means being proactive. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;“You can improve your health and live longer by changing your diet, being more active, and paying attention to your body's signals,” says the doctor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Diabetes beyond sugar intake&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diabetes is often linked to sugar intake, but it involves much more. It reminds us that our daily choices about food, exercise, and stress management are crucial to our long-term health. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;“The connection between gut health and cancer underscores the importance of taking a comprehensive approach to health, focusing on factors beyond one's control,” says the laparoscopic surgeon.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;(&lt;strong&gt;Note to readers:&lt;/strong&gt; This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 06:30:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAJBVV95cUxOOXRKWWVyczZNMGRHQlZDbC1ldFpXeGstaDF3QndCbnpqYXRfUHdPZk1Bd0g0XzktaTdSUEl6YjZzWWVlWndpQUY1aXZQRTVKMk04YldweF9kMWVpMTNyQUxtYlluaVRjNi1aLVBWajFTZXJ6VVgzMnAwMjZZVm1WYmVDbkZwY1EzODZ5UEZfT0ZYckU1amNoOS0tN1VOTUJFYUJnXzRydEtrN1FnOEliM2FKS1pyM19CcDFlWms0Q0dCOVItQU54N3hidE5ldGI0cDNkX01DcXVFMGI0VEFaakRPaGRJX3BBM0o3NUxySjQ3aWctblRwQ19iTnlsUUU0ck5FSTJwX0ZfcEV5WDgtZdIBlgJBVV95cUxQUlBJY2RVRmdCdzZpUzFzak1LNjVoZFRnaGY0VjlWYnhtdnF4ek9SaGlFWlpfZW1CeEdpeWRjd25zY0l4LUMtMTRUNjB5ZWVUMW5yMVVZeEdPLV9zWXM3eGxnU2FqNnNhYzhQSjI1TUszQ19fcFp1bFczd2o3OUxscWxzNTNGS2l2NTFFMzlKTUZWU3MwMHBfOUtZSDVYUHh2LVhpUzllUXNuMElWS1hiNGFZRDJVelJwR0R2QjluN1RkZmRBTDJ2SVJGWHNIMnFiN3N4MTlsOVRENXdzVGhmMU9HS0R1OXJONFl3X3psbEhmazhRY0NHcUFLemtpdlotczU3cTN5UlM4bV9oaXBPMEtJQl8xZw</guid></item><item><title>臀部肌肉的形状对您未来的健康可能意味着什么–以及如何改变它-独立报</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/health-and-fitness/how-to-reduce-diabetes-risk-b2878819.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 dCkqTN sc-jbiisr-1 sc-1wfc891-0 fooWDH" id="main"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="big-letter"&gt;R&lt;/span&gt;ecent research made associations between the shape and composition of the main muscles in the buttocks to the development of &lt;a href="/topic/type-2-diabetes"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Men who experienced shrinkage in certain areas of the gluteus maximus muscles as they aged, and women whose muscles increased in size with age due to a growing fat content, had a higher chance of developing type 2 diabetes. This sparked headlines that had everyone twisting to check their bum in the mirror. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But can a cursory check really provide an accurate prediction? In short, no, the study’s senior author Professor Louise Thompson tells me. Her team looked at the composition of the muscles themselves, which are buried under skin, subcutaneous fat and other bodily tissues. Yet the results of their research can have significant implications for your health, both now and in the future. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This research is part of a much bigger programme of work we’re doing – we are not just gluteus maximus people,” Professor Thompson jokes. Her team analysed MRI scans from tens of thousands of people to identify relationships between their organs and a wide variety of health conditions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We started looking at the gluteus maximus because that’s our biggest muscle, and as well as looking at its volume we look at its quality – that is, how much fat you store in it,” she explains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Higher levels of fitness were associated with healthier gluteus maximus muscles, while frailty and sedentary lifestyles were linked to muscle thinning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To find out how to look after your behind, and your whole body for that matter, read on – Professor Thompson and her colleague, exercise physiologist Paul Hough, explain all below. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The dangers of having high fat content within your muscles&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When most people think of body fat, it is subcutaneous fat they picture – the visible fat stored just beneath the skin. The focus of this research is intramuscular fat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Think about when you got to the butchers to buy a steak,” Professor Thompson explains. “You get marbling in steak, and that is happening to us as we get older.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This process, she says, has several negative health implications. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s linked with metabolic diseases in general, not just type 2 diabetes,” says Professor Thompson. “This includes things like cardiovascular disease, and it’s even really important for liver disease. There have been studies looking at mortality, and when they compare all the different parameters, muscle quality comes out as one of the biggest predictors of mortality.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another key predictor of mortality is frailty. One of the factors with the greatest association with frailty is having more fat in the muscle, Professor Thompson says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you’re frail, you're much more likely to have falls and lose your independence,” she explains. “Muscle quality is something nobody really thinks about, but you can see it’s actually really important.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The University of Westminster study used data from the UK Biobank – a detailed dataset of more than 100,000 people, including everything from neck-to-knee MRI scans to physical measurements such as blood pressure to activity levels. It honed in on those in their 40s, 50s and 60s. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The UK Biobank, as part of their study, measured everything before and after two years without any intervention,” says Professor Thompson. “We assumed, because it's such a short period of time, we wouldn't see anything, but pretty much everybody lost a significant amount of muscle mass, and there was a reduction in grip strength too, which is extraordinary. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Two years of just living your life is causing this decline in middle age. It makes me wonder what's going to happen over 10 or 20 years? And there’s evidence that you start losing muscle from your 30s.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/how-to-fix-tight-hips-b2847195.html"&gt;Mobility expert says you should swap stretching for this exercise to ease tight hips&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="5" class="sc-awdjp1-0 cDKnxE"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/05/13/54/Gluteus-maximus-shape-analysis-in-men-(above)-and-women-(below)--Blue-represents-inward-deformation.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/05/13/54/Gluteus-maximus-shape-analysis-in-men-(above)-and-women-(below)--Blue-represents-inward-deformation.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/05/13/54/Gluteus-maximus-shape-analysis-in-men-(above)-and-women-(below)--Blue-represents-inward-deformation.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Gluteus maximus shape analysis in men (above) and women (below). Blue represents inward deformation or atrophy, while red represents outward deformation or fatty hypertrophy." class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-105777"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Gluteus maximus shape analysis in men (above) and women (below). Blue represents inward deformation or atrophy, while red represents outward deformation or fatty hypertrophy.&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (University of Westminster/UK Biobank)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to fight against intramuscular fat &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those with higher fitness levels are most likely to swerve the deteriorating muscle quality linked to a higher risk of type 2 diabetes. The greatest intervention to achieve this is adding more movement and exercise into each week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Move more&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have a generally sedentary lifestyle, the first thing you can do to combat intramuscular fat is to move more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s about being active and using all of your muscles,” Professor Thompson says. “We’ve used lots of lifestyle interventions, and if you try to get anybody to do something too much, they don't stick to it. People don't like changing their diet and they don't like changing their exercise habits, so that's why simple things like &lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/exercise-more-effective-walking-heart-health-b2878666.html"&gt;walking&lt;/a&gt; and steps are quite easy for people to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But people are working and might have caring responsibilities, so even fitting in 10,000 steps a day is quite a long-term commitment.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key is finding ways to squeeze more movement into your day, which allows you to do so on a consistent basis. This could mean taking a work call while going for a walk, stepping off public transport one stop early when heading to the office or using &lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/exercise-snacking-workouts-heart-health-b2859776.html"&gt;exercise snacking&lt;/a&gt; techniques. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Strength Training &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1wypyku-0 sc-wn0aau-0 lnUWhb kfwxdp"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The University of Westminster’s research highlights the importance of building and maintaining healthy muscle mass. The gluteus maximus, as the body’s biggest muscle, is an excellent signifier of this. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best way to increase muscle strength and size is &lt;a href="/topic/strength-training"&gt;strength training&lt;/a&gt; – any activity that involves overcoming an external force by contracting your muscles. This could mean lifting weights or simply overcoming gravity using bodyweight exercises like squats and press-ups. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Regular strength training is best known for its effects on increasing strength and muscle size,” says University of Westminster sport and exercise scientist Paul Hough. “However, regular resistance training can also cause favourable metabolic changes within skeletal muscle, which improve glucose metabolism. Performing two to three resistance training sessions per week has been shown to reduce the risk of diabetes by approximately 17 to 30 per cent.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He prescribes compound exercises, or those that recruit multiple muscles at once, for those looking for the greatest impact on total-body strength and glucose metabolism. These include movements like the &lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/how-to-squat-correctly-b2606171.html"&gt;squat&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/how-to-deadlift-correctly-b2603126.html"&gt;deadlift&lt;/a&gt;, glute bridge, hip thrust, &lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/how-to-bench-press-properly-b2605570.html"&gt;bench press&lt;/a&gt;, overhead press, pull-up and bent-over row. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Choose a weight or resistance level that allows you to complete five to 10 repetitions with proper technique,” suggests Hough. “The final few repetitions should feel challenging, but there is &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29577974/"&gt;no need&lt;/a&gt; to reach complete exhaustion. A practical guideline is to end the set when you feel you can only complete one or two more repetitions with good form.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you want to target the gluteal muscles specifically, it is best to choose exercises that load your hip joint through a full range of motion, Hough adds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Three effective exercises are back squats, barbell hip thrusts and glute bridges. Another good option is the rear-foot elevated split squat or Bulgarian split squat [demonstrated in the video below]. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Additionally, overall glute development requires training all the gluteal muscles, not just the gluteus maximus. Including exercises that bias the gluteus medius and minimus muscles is necessary for overall glute development. Examples include hip abduction exercises, such as cable abductions or banded side steps.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1wypyku-0 sc-wn0aau-0 lnUWhb kfwxdp"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Moderate - and vigorous - intensity activity &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Higher-intensity activities have been linked to greater positive health impacts. This informs the World Health Organisation’s &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/live-well/exercise/physical-activity-guidelines-for-adults-aged-19-to-64/"&gt;weekly physical activity guidelines&lt;/a&gt; for adults aged 19-64, which prescribe at least 150 minutes of moderate-intensity exercise, 75 minutes of &lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/exercise-more-effective-walking-heart-health-b2878666.html"&gt;vigorous-intensity activity&lt;/a&gt; per week or a combination of both. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These minutes should be spread across the week, with no more than two consecutive days without activity,” says Hough. “Moderate-intensity activities increase your breathing rate but still allow you to maintain a conversation. For example, walking at a &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://bjsm.bmj.com/content/58/6/334"&gt;brisk pace&lt;/a&gt; [4-6kph] or cycling on level ground. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“During vigorous-intensity activities, your breathing rate increases further and speaking in full sentences becomes difficult. Examples include running or walking up a steep hill.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/negative-health-effects-of-sitting-down-b2842653.html"&gt;From back pain to heart health – Experts reveal how to counter the negative effects of too much sitting down&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="5" class="sc-awdjp1-0 dfOhoE"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/04/24/13/30/iStock-1295061941.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/04/24/13/30/iStock-1295061941.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/04/24/13/30/iStock-1295061941.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Walking up a steep hill will, for many people, represent a vigorous-intensity activity" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-105778"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Walking up a steep hill will, for many people, represent a vigorous-intensity activity&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;High-intensity exercise&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those who are able, including some form of high-intensity interval training (HIIT) in your week can offer attractive health perks, Hough says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“HIIT involves brief (anything from five seconds to four minutes), intermittent bouts of high-intensity exercise separated by periods of rest or low-intensity exercise,” he explains. “It differs from vigorous intensity activities because the intensity cannot be sustained. HIIT has been consistently demonstrated to improve &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26243014/"&gt;cardiovascular fitness&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/36740492/"&gt;glucose metabolism&lt;/a&gt; among healthy adults and &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4334091/"&gt;type 2 diabetic patients&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Although many studies have shown that HIIT can improve health outcomes with less total exercise time than moderate-intensity activity, it was not included in previous physical activity guidelines (Department of Health, 2011). More recent evidence has confirmed that HIIT can be just as effective as, or even more effective than, moderate-intensity activity for improving key health measures. As a result, the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/physical-activity-guidelines-uk-chief-medical-officers-report"&gt;UK physical activity guidelines&lt;/a&gt; now recognise HIIT as a suitable exercise option for the general population.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One well-studied and popular protocol Hough recommends is performing one minute of hard work followed by a one-minute recovery period for 10 total rounds. This can be done with walking, running, swimming, cycling or using exercise machines such as exercise bikes and rowing machines. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the hard work, assume a pace that corresponds to approximately 90 per cent of your maximal heart rate, or an eight out of 10 effort, Hough says. The light work could be walking or cycling at an easy pace, or complete rest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Including a warm-up and cool-down, this protocol takes approximately 25 to 30 minutes and is typically performed on three non-consecutive days per week,” he says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/best-healthy-habits-every-day-b2837119.html"&gt;Do these five things daily for 90 days to see a ‘profound difference’ in your health, fitness and energy levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="5" class="sc-awdjp1-0 dfOhoE"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/02/28/11/11/iStock-1015246866.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/02/28/11/11/iStock-1015246866.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/02/28/11/11/iStock-1015246866.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Consistently high activity levels of exercise that recruit all of your body’s muscles and regular strengthening activities are the common denominators to an effective exercise plan." class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-105779"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Consistently high activity levels of exercise that recruit all of your body’s muscles and regular strengthening activities are the common denominators to an effective exercise plan.&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to find out how much fat you have in your muscles&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you want to find out about your intramuscular fat levels, Professor Thompson says an MRI is necessary. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can’t tell the quality of the gluteus maximus muscles just by looking because of the subcutaneous fat over it, she says. “What you’re seeing is a mix of muscle and fat. You have to use an MRI to measure it, so it’s never going to be a population screening tool because it’s too expensive.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A private MRI scan can cost anywhere from £200 to £1,500, with a hospital near me listing one for £525 on the Nuffield Health website. For this reason, it is not an option – or, at least, an attractive one – for most people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But, if you are scanning somebody for one thing, it’s no extra effort to get a measurement in their muscle quality, size and shape,” Professor Thompson suggests. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/diet-and-exercise-advice-for-longevity-b2833750.html"&gt;Scientists reveal the small lifestyle changes that can reduce your risk of heart disease and add 10 years to your life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="5" class="sc-awdjp1-0 bHmhpR"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/10/20/14/20/Most-resistance-training-exercises-can-be-effective-for-improving-strength-mobility-and-flexibility.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/10/20/14/20/Most-resistance-training-exercises-can-be-effective-for-improving-strength-mobility-and-flexibility.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/10/20/14/20/Most-resistance-training-exercises-can-be-effective-for-improving-strength-mobility-and-flexibility.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Exercises like the squat, which require you to change the angle of your hip, will recruit the gluteus maximus muscles" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-105780"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Exercises like the squat, which require you to change the angle of your hip, will recruit the gluteus maximus muscles&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Implications of the research&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The body is often viewed as a collection of independent parts. If you have a kidney problem, you go to a kidney clinic; if you have a liver problem, you go to a liver clinic, Professor Thompson says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But most people have multi-organ diseases,” she continues. “If you have a problem with one organ, such as having too much fat in your muscles, you’re also likely to have problems with others, like fat in the liver. You might also have a bit of kidney dysfunction and dysfunction with your heart. The reality of our bodies is that we have this multi-organ involvement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We measure everything [in our research] because it gives you a much better picture of health – understanding how your fat is affecting everything in your body.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Professor Thompson uses type 2 diabetes as a case study to demonstrate the interconnected nature of the human body, and how it is impacted by disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you look at someone with type 2 diabetes, you know their pancreas is affected in some way because they'll have an issue with insulin production,” she explains. “But then you also know their muscles aren’t healthy because the muscles are insulin resistant and they’re not taking up glucose, then they store too much fat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We also know their kidneys aren’t functioning properly and their liver is affected, and then they have problems with their heart. Yet when you talk about disease, you don’t really think about all of these things that are going on. That’s why I think you get a really holistic picture of health through scanning.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UK Biobank scans people from their necks to their knees in roughly nine minutes, using automated scripts to analyse the results. Most of these scripts are freely available. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s quite remarkable what you could do if you could roll this out in the NHS,” says Professor Thompson. “Say you go for a gall bladder scan – in the same image, you could get lots of information about your body composition.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Through this, people could gain early warning signs for certain chronic diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Liver disease is one of the conditions that is rapidly growing in the UK,” Professor Thompson says. “One of the reasons is it is often picked up late because you don’t get symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If it’s picked up early, you can actually reverse a lot of the effects through lifestyle changes. If everybody who happened to be scanning for one thing also had their liver measured, it might really save the NHS money, because you could pick things up while you are still able to intervene with just lifestyle changes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UK Biobank plans to revisit participants in future years, helping researchers map patterns in the readings. It is hoped this will give them the ability to predict which people will develop which diseases based on a multitude of measurable factors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Then what you can look at is, ‘Are there simple biomarkers we can apply to the whole population so that you wouldn’t need to scan people?’,” Professor Thompson says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-us-premium-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“...I think until we start looking at the person rather than just the disease in one organ, we’re not going to understand how people are affected by these conditions. To understand health, you look at fat and muscle and all of the organs that get affected by them." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/strength-training-for-longevity-b2826608.html"&gt;The science-backed exercise method that can help fight the effects of ageing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQbTBrNnNfbjBUaVZpVnIxc3lPUnZILTBjS2g4cm5MallfQm5zT3lUUVBVb0k2b21xaUlObEFBa2RXMWFPendHSXFRQ0xGQU1GSGFYWmJIU1pJNTNSajBzRzNGMEU2UXdzTm5hb1d0NUttMk5Ha3RaclVuR3NkbmROdkIyZlYzTkdSZVFDQktzQ0JRLUMz</guid></item><item><title>血管外科医生揭示了为什么健康的动脉会被阻塞，并警告人们不要出现通常被忽视的5种症状-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/vascular-surgeon-reveals-why-healthy-arteries-get-blocked-warns-against-5-symptoms-that-are-commonly-ignored/photostory/125813495.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sumit Kapadia, Vascular Surgeon and Varicose Vein Specialist, recently on his IG handle, spoke about artery blockages, and why even healthy arteries get blocked. Dr Kapadia mentioned that arteries (even 'healthy' ones) don't get blocked all of a sudden, though gradual narrowing can occur without any warning, or mild signs only. This process, known as 'Atherosclerosis' literally means the presence of fat into the blood vessels. This fat, or cholesterol, Dr Kapadia says, when combined with calcium, and inflammatory cells, leads to plaque. When these narrowed arteries suddenly have a blockage, that can cause a blood clot, leading to a heart attack, brain stroke, or Peripheral Artery Disease (PAD) in the legs. Hence, people who think they are healthy, might be carrying an underlying condition that they are not even aware of, says Dr Kapadia. For this, it is important to get regularly tested, and to watch out for these 5 signs that are common indicators of artery blockage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 05:15:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAJBVV95cUxNZm85aEs0ekFaeXlFcG5DZ2czQkpmaW9uZ3h2bW8ySzNLZzhPSnBPYlA5NUFKYU92RHdQc0dkTnVZZzQ2Q3JMckF4NjQtdnZUNjYzRDJUeERoZGRUUmRMLW0taUFySGtDZlZaQVhUVkFnaGh4RmxJZG0tSGVLM0hieVBfNzdZMFEzcnJtdmFGbjRtS1dWS3Q4S0Jidkp2c2lwZ2xOOTMxQlhlLU5MaUVNSzV1SFIzaWNyS0NscDAxbDU4QUhNczVFc0R1dHVRcHdwcnJ6X29ra2pKWlFJbnptNkE5c0dmNmszY1V5U1BjekZLU3dCV2dvTkFsTUxuSWFDVlh2aUh0Y2F5bmYyN0xMUnB4TTZQQjFGcW1VbGtLaVjSAagCQVVfeXFMTUR1M1ZxcEJJakY0cmptUjhsdDFIVHhKUVBjUEFzMUJpVU5TV0pPaU5RbnpwRzY3ZkNhODhkeHJxVEZ3RF80SU5ScG85V3dyVXZDeU1uTmtXNlJvWWdidXJGNGI1Yjh6TVhMTlpaanlRSmgyc2dOWmNKLUVxaXJ1bndkZS10c3oybEhITUsxRXc4T3hoXy1ocEtjbWstX09BTlF6LXZ6OW9peVN2QjhzeWcxSmNvR24zUTNzUGh0aWdlcFp1WmxjRjRhU3BERXRWTDdFRVhLUzJRLU9vZEV0NDQwT1NjS2oxTWFHend6ZnFWcHM5MF9wbzhBMDhoVFpvOUdMNW5lSDZ5OGF2UU1sTkpjbTc4TEJnV0dSMVMzLVU4ZE5Id0QtWW8</guid></item><item><title>心理学家解释了被忽视的痴呆症状，这些症状在下午变得更糟- The Mirror</title><link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/psychologist-explains-overlooked-dementia-symptom-36345657</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="article-body" class="ArticleBody_article__AwrJE" data-testid="body"&gt;&lt;h1 class="HeadingOne_heading-one__mmNWJ  __className_b5b325" publication="mirror"&gt;Psychologist explains overlooked dementia symptom that gets worse in the afternoon&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 class="LeadText_lead-text__wd_PA __className_8efb9b" data-testid="leadtext" publication="mirror"&gt;Dr Kellyn Lee has highlighted sundowning, a lesser-known sign of dementia that often becomes more noticeable in the afternoon and evening&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="Byline_byline-container__K_Owl" data-testid="byline"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-content" class="Byline_byline-content-wrapper__Imque"&gt;&lt;div class="Byline_author-badge-date-wrapper__Q7jj1"&gt;&lt;p class="Byline_dates-container__Rqzf2"&gt;&lt;span class="" data-testid="byline-publishedDate"&gt;04:59, 07 Dec 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="Byline_updated-date__8vEV8 Byline_updated-date-with-published__ApG_G" data-testid="byline-updatedDate"&gt;Updated 09:20, 07 Dec 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="LightboxBtn_lightbox-btn__eoxYS" aria-label="Open image viewer" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-controls="image-lightbox"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX ImageEmbed_image-lead__Ti3qQ" data-testid="leadimage" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="36345655"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Dementia symptoms can differ depending on the type experienced&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: DBenitostock via Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;A psychologist has delved into a little-known &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/dementia" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;sign of dementia&lt;/a&gt; and ways for patients to help manage it. Dr Kellyn Lee, who heads up The Dementia Care Hub, highlighted that this particular &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/health/" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;symptom &lt;/a&gt;tends to intensify during afternoon hours, often leaving loved ones baffled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;"This can happen at any time of day, but what we see a lot with people living with &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/dementia" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;dementia &lt;/a&gt;is that it can happen in the afternoon," she said in a &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/tiktok" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;TikTok earlier this year&lt;/a&gt;. "So, what I would be looking at is this would be, again, a&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/health/" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt; symptom of anxiety&lt;/a&gt; and agitation and maybe increased confusion."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;Dr Lee is describing a phenomenon known as 'sundowning', where dementia patients display increasingly erratic behaviour during late afternoon and early evening periods. Throughout these episodes, people may become exceptionally distressed and could also suffer from hallucinations and delusions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="HtmlEmbed_container__x6svQ"&gt;&lt;figure data-testid="embed-placeholder" class="EmbedPlaceholder_figure__NLMFl undefined false"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 90 90" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" data-testid="consent-placeholder-icon"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_10846_5865)"&gt;&lt;circle opacity="0.16" cx="45" cy="45" r="33.75" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-neutral-default)"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M21.1351 21.1351C15.0276 27.2427 11.25 35.6802 11.25 45C11.25 63.6396 26.3604 78.75 45 78.75C54.3198 78.75 62.7573 74.9724 68.8649 68.8649M21.1351 21.1351C27.2427 15.0276 35.6802 11.25 45 11.25C63.6396 11.25 78.75 26.3604 78.75 45C78.75 54.3198 74.9724 62.7573 68.8649 68.8649M21.1351 21.1351L68.8649 68.8649" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-neutral-default)" stroke-width="7.5" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_10846_5865"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Content cannot be displayed without consent&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;Although the precise triggers behind sundowning are not fully understood, the &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.alzheimers.org.uk/about-dementia/symptoms-and-diagnosis/symptoms/sundowning" target="_blank" aria-label="Alzheimer's SocietyLink opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt;Alzheimer's Society&lt;/a&gt; suggests it is not necessarily connected to dusk. Instead, it is more likely driven by immediate unaddressed requirements, which could encompass:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="UnorderedList_unordered-list__gzblI" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="unordered-list" publication="mirror"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Disturbed hormone levels&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Side effects of prescribed drugs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Sensory impairment, including sight loss&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Hunger, pain or other unmet physical needs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Disturbance to the person's 'body clock' caused by damage to the brain&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Overstimulation during the daytime&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Overtiredness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Lack of exposure to sunlight&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Lack of interaction with other people or carers (if relevant)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Mood disorders, including anxiety and depression&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="BoxStyles_box-container__Qk3WH BoxStyles_non-commercial__aiWwo undefined" data-testid="non-commercial-1" data-position="6" publication="mirror"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span data-testid="readmore" class="ReadMore_readmore-prefix__xS44r __className_7c5650"&gt;READ MORE: &lt;span class="ReadMore_readmore-link__eF9pN"&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/lifestyle/world-top-doctors-explain-how-36338213" data-tmdatatrack="read-more" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="36338213" data-tmdatatrack-source="editorial" tabindex="0"&gt;'World' top doctors' explain how they avoid getting sick&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="readmore" class="ReadMore_readmore-prefix__xS44r __className_7c5650"&gt;READ MORE: &lt;span class="ReadMore_readmore-link__eF9pN"&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/health/gran-dies-months-after-dizziness-36337241" data-tmdatatrack="read-more" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="36337241" data-tmdatatrack-source="editorial" tabindex="0"&gt;Gran dies months after dizziness misdiagnosed as depression&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;"Sundowning can happen at any stage of dementia but is more common during the middle stage and later stages," guidance from Alzheimer's Society adds. "Some of these are related to the time of day, and others may happen at any time. Try to identify which of these problems might be affecting the person, as each problem may need a different treatment."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;If you suspect your loved one could be experiencing sundowning, Dr Lee recommends keeping a log of the symptoms you notice at different points during the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;According to &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.getsurrey.co.uk/news/health/psychologist-explains-lesser-known-dementia-31892441" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;Surrey Live&lt;/a&gt;, in the video, she continued: "So, what I would be looking at doing is noting down when this is happening and what's happening. There are tablets that can be used, such as lorazepam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;"Absolutely these drugs are drugs that need to be taken with caution because they are highly addictive. So, some GPs may not want to prescribe them. However, I think we really need to balance the risk of addiction compared to the fact the person has dementia."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image-group"&gt;&lt;button class="LightboxBtn_lightbox-btn__eoxYS" aria-label="Open image viewer" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-controls="image-lightbox"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX false" data-testid="imageembed-36345656" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="36345656" data-tmdatatrack-type="image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Sundowning describes a phenomenon in which people with dementia exhibit more unpredictable behaviour in the afternoons and evenings&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: Dobrila Vignjevic via Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="HeadingTwo_heading-two__4TTeG  __className_b5b325" publication="mirror"&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;Other potential symptoms of dementia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;Whilst dementia symptoms can vary depending on the specific form, common early indicators may include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="UnorderedList_unordered-list__gzblI" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="unordered-list" publication="mirror"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Mood changes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Difficulty concentrating&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Finding it hard to carry out familiar daily tasks, such as getting confused over the correct change when shopping&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Memory loss&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Struggling to follow a conversation or find the right word&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Being confused about time and place&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;The &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/nhs" target="" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt; encourages anyone experiencing these warning signs to seek medical advice. Its advice adds: "There is currently no cure for dementia. But there are medicines and other treatments that can help with dementia symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;"Most of the medicines available are used to treat Alzheimer's disease as this is the most common form of dementia. They can help to temporarily reduce symptoms."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;&lt;em&gt;For more information, head to the &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/dementia/about-dementia/what-is-dementia/" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;NHS website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Mirror</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 05:05:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxOSU1qNThYcWpXVkFZdTFBTkxzbmVzRFNjdU9POXVmN090ZjQxY2Q1dUtWZkwyWk0wbHFXR2xwSlRHSUhQcmFyVjNnNVhSYjBCRzhlRTlhLUJzajdlX1JWTnJ5dF84VXpMYmh2d0psSmFLR2lxbkVHc0RjYUw1VkNkdWJ1Vk1XT3JNcFpDMUdOQVpHQkVzaDlEby12TVnSAaIBQVVfeXFMT3VZVjR6UWtLMnZ6QTJwMUE5Y25zbGstQW11bW81dDZZLVMwQlBPQ3BYT1pNbFJqd0R5cm5OZHI5a1VONC1MZjFFb1BiQk1kSXQyQkdFcDBoS0MxX1A4OUpadUMzRDJ3dkdHNkktRzV4Ti1rYktQRFpHMnBfcjEyUkRBaXprQ2ljdG1FcWhvREF2NVpkbG1FUDhNcGZiQlFST3R3</guid></item><item><title>为什么这么多人认为他们今天患有多动症，以及激增背后的真正原因-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/why-so-many-people-think-they-have-adhd-today-and-the-real-reasons-behind-the-surge/articleshow/125807424.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It feels like everywhere you turn, someone is talking about ADHD. Whether on social media, in workplaces, or among friends, sudden awareness around attention and focus struggles has become impossible to ignore. Many people now wonder whether difficulty concentrating, forgetfulness, procrastination or mental restlessness could mean they have ADHD. For some, this new awareness brings relief and answers. For others, it creates confusion and uncertainty. Has ADHD really become more common, or are more people simply recognising symptoms that have always been there? Understanding why so many believe they have ADHD today involves looking at rising diagnoses, cultural changes, shifting expectations and the role of online information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A peer-reviewed meta-analysis published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37495084/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;PubMed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; in 2023 estimated that the global prevalence of ADHD in children and adolescents is around 8 per cent, with confidence intervals ranging from 6 to 10 per cent. The researchers concluded that ADHD has existed at significant levels for decades, and the apparent surge may reflect better recognition rather than an actual rise in the number of cases. The data suggest that rates have not exploded, but awareness has increased dramatically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Can adults have ADHD without knowing? 5 revealing signs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding &lt;keyword id="28613768" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="ADHD-awareness" source="keywords"&gt;ADHD awareness&lt;/keyword&gt; and rising diagnosis rates&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of ADHD diagnoses has increased substantially in many countries over the past two decades. Large studies from the United Kingdom and the United States show a marked rise in both assessments and prescriptions for ADHD, especially among teenagers and adults. Improved education for clinicians, expanded diagnostic criteria, and recognition of inattentive symptoms that were previously overlooked have contributed to this shift. Many adults are receiving a diagnosis for the first time after realising their childhood struggles fit the pattern only in hindsight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Modern lifestyle pressures are intensifying ADHD-like symptoms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our environment today places extraordinary demands on attention. Constant notifications, rapid task switching, long working hours and heavy screen use make it harder for anyone to focus. When daily life becomes overwhelming, ordinary distraction can resemble ADHD. People experiencing digital overload or burnout may misinterpret temporary cognitive stress as a chronic disorder. The blurring of boundaries between ADHD and environmental distraction fuels confusion and encourages more self-diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why does ADHD feel more visible and common than before&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;One major reason is the power of social media. Platforms like Instagram, TikTok and YouTube are filled with relatable content describing ADHD traits in simple language. Many individuals recognise themselves in short lists of symptoms and begin questioning whether they have been living with undiagnosed ADHD. Increased visibility also reduces stigma and encourages people to seek help. More open conversations create the impression of an epidemic, when in reality, more people are simply identifying long-standing struggles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another influence is that ADHD is now widely recognised in groups historically underdiagnosed, including girls, women and quiet or high-achieving students. These individuals were often missed because they did not show obvious hyperactivity. As awareness grows, many cases once overlooked are finally being identified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Medical evaluation matters more than online checklists&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Self-awareness is useful, but clinical diagnosis is essential. ADHD can only be confirmed through a structured assessment that rules out conditions with similar symptoms, such as anxiety, depression, trauma, sleep disorders or thyroid issues. Many people may believe they have ADHD based on relatable descriptions online, but not all attention difficulties originate from the same cause. Without proper evaluation, overdiagnosis and unnecessary medication become real risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Real reasons behind the surge in perceived ADHD cases&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Better understanding of inattentive and &lt;keyword id="23722902" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="adult-ADHD" source="keywords"&gt;adult ADHD&lt;/keyword&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wider access to &lt;keyword id="19956983" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="mental-health" source="keywords"&gt;mental health&lt;/keyword&gt; information&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cultural shift that values emotional openness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Academic and workplace pressure are exposing underlying symptoms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Online communities offering validation and visibility&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pandemic effects reveal long-ignored attention difficulties&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Broader definitions used in contemporary diagnostic practice&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why so many people think they have ADHD today, and the real reasons behind the surge, is a story of awareness rather than an epidemic. ADHD has always existed at meaningful levels. What has changed is that more people now understand it, recognise symptoms earlier and feel comfortable seeking help. Increased visibility is not a reason for panic but an opportunity for clarity and support. If attention difficulties affect everyday life, professional assessment is the most helpful next step. Knowledge and proper evaluation allow real needs to be met while preventing confusion and unnecessary labels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This content is intended purely for informational use and is not a substitute for professional medical, nutritional or scientific advice. Always seek support from certified professionals for personalised recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also read| &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/how-to-keep-your-feet-warm-during-winter-and-stop-cold-toes-from-ruining-your-day/articleshow/125807300.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;How to keep your feet warm during winter and stop cold toes from ruining your day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 04:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAJBVV95cUxOZnp6V0k0Q3NYdE9LWUNDWWw5QjR2dlNib2o3TVlYOEJmYVN3ellrelc4X2FxUnNJM2RUa1o0TTVKY2QwR2loRWxBcVFzeG9JeWNkWFhHSlN6VURfUmpPcnl4WWtUdGZtYWVJajNFeXlMTTJuTnRIckdoNk1QVEFUMnVBMDhMak1SRXdIaS0xZXFwYnBHaVdaWWRHVXF6Y2t3SDh2dmRSejJRemFZNjdPNGh4ZWRCU2ZPNXdaTDRvcjRnd21VTTF3M1czSHY3MzNLeTdxMXQxVUZKc1UzVUJTeV9WRjhoaGVpYmlJSFIwRjJDTlNial9sZ1MwN2FYeFBTOHpua3BKZlJPR01sSmNWRtIBlgJBVV95cUxOVzZBSUloSEVidGxhc3JFLU52MDV4Sksxb1c5V3Yxcl9hNXRxSjVsUkR1a0VzNW15eWVjaXE0UHE5Ujc4OEE2dU94a3FMMi14aWZtd0xwT1lidWQ1bWk2cVlrM25PbUVyMDU1U1FLdG5Ga1NHWXpPbXRsTXhWN3ZKWE5NcXZwWjFVYUE0Smh6WmVFTXVmUFFlVzJZYXFWSXVkTjk1SEkwZ1pTd0R3U2c3a2dPYTNRVzlVVzJ0OWgwc094QktTbFgwTURENHBJWW1FNFJQOWVqX1JGNmFyTEg5cVRLWVhHeHlQMjR3Y082YWtNOTl4MTdnRWhneVVOdVgyNXl1aEM2eks4ZjNIbFgyRkIyd0ZSQQ</guid></item><item><title>在如何看待自己与世界如何看待自己方面存在最大差异的工作- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/kellymartinez/people-are-sharing-the-jobs-with-the-biggest-discrepancies</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-25
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139808518" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title  "&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;Do you have a job that's actually totally different from the way society perceives it? Share your thoughts and experiences in the comments (or the anonymous form) below.&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note: Responses have been edited for length/clarity.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 04:31:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQczh4OVpwMG1aWXdTdDBvYThRM18zSmFGSFZuWUxQY2lVRmpXNEFZSmQzdVZJZlNCQ3haSnBUYWJHVjlUODVKckxtWUV3N3JKT3FZS1dRVWdYLWRKSm1QTEUzWnM5cDZTMm1JeDFIV0FvX3lHUTMtMG9qeWtXdXZYenZPMGFmbjN5NWNLOTB5SDVKQm03aHh5MjBWOFFsZw</guid></item><item><title>Fortis胃肠病学家揭露“营养学家最大的骗局” ；说这种食物不会增加心脏病发作的风险|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fortis-gastroenterologist-reveals-biggest-scam-by-nutritionists-says-this-food-doesnt-increase-heart-attack-risk-stroke-101765079037807.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/fortis-gastroenterologist-reveals-biggest-scam-by-nutritionists-says-this-food-doesnt-increase-heart-attack-risk-stroke-101765079037807.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Are egg yolks harmful to you? In a December 6 Instagram video, Dr Shubham Vatsya, a senior gastroenterologist and hepatologist at Fortis Vasant Kunj, challenged the long-held belief that&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/eating-eggs-weekly-lowers-risk-of-heart-disease-and-premature-death-study-101738926541794.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="egg yolks"&gt; egg yolks&lt;/a&gt; are detrimental to heart health, labelling this idea as a major nutritional misconception. He asserted that this common food does not cause heart attacks or strokes. &lt;strong&gt;Also read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fortis-gastroenterologist-shares-he-lost-38-kg-in-3-years-by-eating-eggs-daily-18-grams-of-high-quality-protein-101763532831135.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Fortis gastroenterologist shares he lost 38 kg in 3 years by eating eggs daily: ‘3 eggs is 18 gram high quality protein’"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fortis gastroenterologist shares he lost 38 kg in 3 years by eating eggs daily: ‘3 eggs is 18 gram high quality protein’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/07/550x309/431_1757647187977_1757647195958_1765079419390.jpg" alt="According to the doctor, healthy adults can likely enjoy up to 3 whole eggs daily, and no it will not increase heart attack risk. (Representative picture)" title="According to the doctor, healthy adults can likely enjoy up to 3 whole eggs daily, and no it will not increase heart attack risk. (Representative picture)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/07/550x309/431_1757647187977_1757647195958_1765079419390.jpg" alt="According to the doctor, healthy adults can likely enjoy up to 3 whole eggs daily, and no it will not increase heart attack risk. (Representative picture)" title="According to the doctor, healthy adults can likely enjoy up to 3 whole eggs daily, and no it will not increase heart attack risk. (Representative picture)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;According to the doctor, healthy adults can likely enjoy up to 3 whole eggs daily, and no it will not increase heart attack risk. (Representative picture)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;The cholesterol misconception&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;He explained that the human liver naturally produces most of the body's cholesterol, making the cholesterol consumed through egg yolks largely insignificant in terms of its effect on blood cholesterol levels.&lt;/span&gt; Dr Vatsya highlighted a large-scale study that found no increased risk of heart attack or stroke from consuming one egg daily.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In the video he posted, Dr Vatsya said in Hindi, “Making egg yolks the villain is the biggest scam run by nutritionists. Your liver produces 80 percent of your body's &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/high-cholesterol-cardiac-surgeon-reveals-10-foods-that-help-unclog-arteries-naturally-and-reduce-risk-of-heart-disease-101764580188816.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="cholesterol"&gt;cholesterol &lt;/a&gt;itself. The dietary cholesterol you take from egg yolks hardly affects blood cholesterol. A large study of 150,000 people has clearly shown that eating one egg daily does not pose a risk of heart attack or stroke.”&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Yolk’s benefits and the real culprit&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Furthermore, Dr Vatsya argued that egg yolks actually improve 'good' HDL cholesterol and contain beneficial components, such as lutein, choline, and essential vitamins, that support the heart, liver, and brain.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;The real issue is often the unhealthy way eggs are prepared, such as adding excessive butter, cream, or oil, rather than the yolk itself, he shared.&lt;/span&gt; Therefore, he stated, healthy, non-diabetic adults can safely consume up to three whole eggs per day.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Vatsya said: “In fact, the yolk improves HDL, or good cholesterol, and contains lutein, choline, and essential vitamins that support heart, liver, and brain health.&lt;/span&gt; So the real problem is not the yolk; it is in the cooking style. People cook the egg with butter, cream, and extra oil, and then say they face problems. If you are a healthy, non-diabetic, non-hypertensive adult, you can comfortably eat three whole eggs every day.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He wrote in his caption, “Egg yolk ≠ heart attack. For years, egg yolks were labelled “bad for your heart,” but modern science has completely overturned that myth. Your liver makes most of your cholesterol, which means dietary cholesterol from yolks barely affects your levels. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;One to two eggs a day doesn’t increase heart disease risk, in fact, yolks improve HDL and provide nutrients your brain, liver, and heart need.&lt;/span&gt; So, tell me… are you team 'eat the yolk' or 'throw it away'?”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 03:53:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwJBVV95cUxOaEt0bXRCZUxjMG1SdG5IazNIT2NGMENLM3gtZnlKbTJidGh3MVFQZmFyc2FxcFA5M2l0Y3dxVFhKbEc4cVhBM0IzaVpScDlrT2p3T0lfcVZuYmg3WXJ0MUF5QUpWQkFSV19Ed1BsaVlBeFdtdmpiR1d4V1JzdHlTbUNfU3RBVEVkSk51WDhBUk5xNFZjejg2WVVCcGRnY1gwNnlZVlI0NTVpWFJaQXZ0ZEhCMkVJUmpuMTFUXy1QNUNRWmpTUktJc0VHQWRrRzVvSjJpMmY2bE9IeXNsQ3NDTkZUX19nMFpzUS05WVpKMWtnOTFnY0JVRFowZFNFVGVnRW0yT0NMU1JUYXFrbHhidG5xLUZwRWPSAZwCQVVfeXFMTUdENF9Ya3RxYy1WVlNTcXdnSlRUM0hIQUV6NVQ0RGowTURvaTJlQWxkVXJEY2dCc0RYallfQ05qSWlfc3VORlZZa0o5QjRyaHJBVTlrM25qMmpCckZXM1hKdHV4SzdMM3lTTWVwU1JVSVNqZVdkdWdITExYbzdmcF9jQmxpSUN5c19GZm9OR2NaTXpDVHhsWE5ORnBvTG1mcVdFNWhOWkhVNm85Sm92Nm0zSUc0dzBOZE41NkhXbHEwdThqM2YzMGRKZmtEdVhtS0NGd21pWUVVcTlVOE5tS3JLQnFiVFV3azdIVWVEazZpR3dpNzZscW1kLW9lOGp4X2xxRWc5XzJxX1pOQnh5MjMtWGFCUkFFOENzeks</guid></item><item><title>超过35岁的NHS DOC揭示了保持年轻的5个简单习惯-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/over-35-nhs-doc-reveals-5-simple-habits-to-stay-youthful/articleshow/125812843.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;35 is more than a milestone birthday. It is when your body starts to shift. While your retinol and other carefully curated skincare might be protecting you from fine lines and wrinkles, true youthfulness runs far deeper than what any serum can reach. Starting from cardiovascular health to cognitive reserve, everything begins to change in ways that are not immediately visible. Before you start to panic, here’s the good news. According to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://medical.hee.nhs.uk/medical-training-recruitment/medical-specialty-training/general-practice-gp/choose-gp/choose-gp-career-stories/dr-amir-khan" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Dr Amir Khan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, ITV's resident doctor and an NHS GP, this decade is your golden window of opportunity. In a video shared on Instagram, Dr Khan explained five simple habits everyone over 35 must follow to stay healthy as they age. “If you're over 35 years old, these five science-backed habits genuinely can change how you age,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Get the morning light&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The morning light is nature’s anti-ageing ingredient. “After 35, your circadian rhythm becomes a little less responsive. So five minutes of outdoor morning light hits receptors in the back of your eyes, and it sends signals to your brain's master clock. That resets cortisol timing, boosts energy, improves sleep pressure at night, and even stabilises appetite hormones. It's the most powerful free tool we have,” the doctor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; A 2024 study by University of Washington School of Medicine/UW Medicine researchers found that the mesmerising blue and orange hues in the sky at the start and end of a sunny day have an essential role in setting &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/07487304241262918" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;humans’ internal clocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Keep your heart young post-30s with these 4 simple ways&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Boost your VO2 max every day&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, that’s right. You should make intentional steps to boost your VO2 max every single day. “VO2 max is essentially how well your body can deliver and use oxygen. And it's one of the strongest predictors of our health. As we age, our heart becomes slightly less efficient at pumping blood, and our mitochondria become less efficient at using oxygen,” Dr Khan said. How to increase VO2 max? You don’t really have to do intense exercise. “Short bursts of intensity, such as 20 to 40 seconds of fast stairs, a brisk uphill walk, or a quick cycle sprint, force your muscles to demand more oxygen than usual. And that stimulates new mitochondria and improves oxygen extraction,” the doctor explained. That’s right. You don’t have to do HIIT sessions; just short bursts of workout can help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Know your &lt;keyword id="22982" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="blood-pressure" source="Orion"&gt;blood pressure&lt;/keyword&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;High blood pressure is a silent killer. According to the WHO, 1.4 billion adults had hypertension in 2024, and about &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/hypertension" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;600 million are unaware&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; that they have the condition. So, checking your blood pressure is crucial. “Check your blood pressure at home, people. Blood pressure creeps up quietly as your arteries stiffen with age. Checking it, say once a month at rest, gives you a baseline,” the doctor said. If the readings are about 135/85, he suggests getting daily readings for a week and working out the average. “If that's high, speak to your doctor. That average is what predicts your stroke and heart attack risk, not one random reading, and catching it early can make all the difference,” Dr Khan said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Train your balance&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may sound simple, but your balance says a lot about your health. “Balance relies on your cerebellum, inner ear, and tiny sensors in your muscles called proprioceptors. These systems decline after 35 unless you challenge them,” the doctor said. How to train your balance? “Thirty seconds standing on one leg whilst brushing your teeth is a really good way to train it and train your core coordination and brain–body signalling. It dramatically reduces future fall and injury risk. So tonight, when you're brushing your teeth, do it on one leg,” he suggested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Build muscles and bone&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;After 30, most people experience muscle loss, a natural process called sarcopenia. Studies show &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2804956/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;a decrease of 3% to 8% in muscle mass&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; per decade after 30. Building muscle and bone is crucial for healthy ageing. “From your mid-30s onwards, you slowly lose muscle fibres and bone density. Strength and impact exercises send mechanical signals through your muscles and bones, which we call mechanotransduction. Your body responds by building them back stronger. This protects metabolism, joint stability, glucose control, and long-term fracture risk. So get them in twice a week,” the doctor suggested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Healthy ageing is all about giving your body what it needs to thrive. These simple habits recommended by Dr Khan require minimal time and zero expensive equipment, yet they help you age like fine wine. These small daily choices compound into dramatic differences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment, or before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 03:18:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7AFBVV95cUxQcDMxWC0tX2Qwd05udlFmZmdfYmtlT0N2cjVaOEMyUG9YMVpoWTFoZWFITm1fM1hMM19xQnViNm9qRnRJeXJKMF85UFVDYVNWbnhSS0ZRd1ViZm14UGZMMTNmb0hNNHVLTEkzQ1pjOUdpODBETUhWNFRXX0pHLVBTYnVFLWdYTER3Q0M2bHlKd3dvczI2RkVyMU5DaDlYRXBWUW1lRFA5ZXFDVGN0ajY5UjBUZXhuVll0WjBSZG5Zcmh5WkFhT3ZuTVVGTmh3UE5wV3FJUW5RXzRfWmxjeHVOZEI3MWYxVkxCYnhpQQ</guid></item><item><title>多吃维生素C ，直接促进胶原蛋白和皮肤更新- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/eating-more-vitamin-c-found-to-directly-boost-collagen-and-skin-renewal/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 03:03:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxOZVNCamZoLUJZNXRLTHNFTHNuSHpnel9pdjI1OTNtQnlNX3U2ak9tY2tlTDVQYURVNnU0UUhIVTRiQ29fSDJmSFByZXZYM2tsY2xOSHZxdnp3bE5uX01YVlQ0V1NLX2hNMWEtSXFCbklaRU42Q0ZxbG1SSkxOZ3RMRER1a1Bob2J5aTdhb0I3ZmEzb29QaFVTNmp4T041Zw</guid></item><item><title>哈佛研究为糖尿病和肥胖症开启新的潜在治疗方法- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/harvard-study-unlocks-new-potential-treatments-for-diabetes-and-obesity/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 02:28:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxOS2NiaWl0STJ5bHBHSldRckIzOUZBR2JtaTFaM2NvM0FMWE1mTDhySkE4U2N1ZFNCT1FqaVhpRmpwSHREMWwtT016bWhna0Y4akV5VlotVTFSUXFyRXhVYkJYeDRaSkZucE96ZTJrVXZhNExQMENfalk3X015WWpTMzBjdDR3NXF5TkZDbEZwQ2xkZlNMal8wWWRqbjVRQQ</guid></item><item><title>肾脏健康警告：低水摄入量并不是肾结石背后的唯一原因，肾脏学家警告说，再-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/low-water-intake-not-the-only-reason-behind-kidney-stones-warns-nephrologist-reveals-hidden-causes/articleshow/125803539.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to kidney stones, the most common perception is that they are caused by insufficient water consumption, however, that is not always the case. Dr Arjun Sabharwal, MBBS and nephrologist, recently posted an IG video in which he highlighted that kidney stones are not just caused by low water intake, but a host of other reasons. He said,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Kidney &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8208620/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;stones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; are not caused by low water intake alone. They form due to a combination of metabolic, dietary, genetic, and medical factors-this has been clearly shown in multiple large studies published in The New England Journal of Medicine (NEJM), American Journal of Kidney Diseases (AJKD), and Nature Reviews Nephrology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Don’t Ignore Silent Kidney Damage: How to Detect Issues Before It’s Too Late | Dr Sanjeev Bagai&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common causes include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;• High urine calcium (hypercalciuria)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;• High oxalate (from diet or gut absorption)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Low urine citrate (a natural stone protector)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;• High uric acid (often linked to red meat &amp;amp; gout)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;• High salt and animal protein intake&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Low dietary calcium&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Oxalate-rich foods (spinach, nuts, chocolate)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Excess vitamin C supplements&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Obesity, diabetes, gout, thyroid and bowel disorders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Recurrent urine infections&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Family history &amp;amp; genetic risk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;• And even some long-term medicines (diuretics, migraine drugs, calcium antacids)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Low water intake does increase stone risk by concentrating urine-but studies clearly confirm that recurrent stones always need full metabolic evaluation, including a 24-hour urine test to identify the true cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If stones keep coming back, don’t just increase water-find your stone type and treat the root cause."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Let us now examine that in closer detail...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Problems that arise because of kidney stones&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kidney stones cause sharp pain in the back or side, blood in urine, and nausea when they block urine flow. Many people blame low water intake, but stones form from a mix of metabolic, dietary, genetic, and medical factors. Low water does concentrate urine and raise risk, but recurrent stones need a full check with 24-hour urine tests to find the real causes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treating the root fixes the problem better than water alone. Let's examine reasons highlighted by Dr Sabharwal...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;High urine calcium&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;High urine calcium, or hypercalciuria, affects 30-60% of stone formers. It happens when kidneys leak calcium, or the body absorbs too much from food. This leads to calcium oxalate or phosphate crystals, that grow into stones. Studies show these imbalances cause supersaturation in urine, even with good hydration. A 24-hour urine test spots it, and drugs like thiazides lower calcium output. Managing diet, staying well-hydrated, and following medical guidance can significantly reduce the risk of stone recurrence and protect kidney health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Oxalate overload from diet and gut&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;High oxalate in urine comes from foods like spinach, nuts, chocolate, or excess vitamin C supplements. It binds calcium to form sharp oxalate stones, the most common type. Gut issues like low Oxalobacter formigenes bacteria, and boost absorption by 10-50%. Even though primary hyperoxaluria is genetic and rare, but severe. Even normal eaters get hit if urine volume drops, or calcium is low. To tackle this, limit high-oxalate foods, and pair with calcium-rich meals to bind it in the gut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="72"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Low citrate lets stones form easily&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="77"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Citrate acts as a natural blocker, by binding calcium and raising urine pH to dissolve crystals. Low urine citrate, or hypocitraturia, hits 20-60% of patients. Causes include chronic diarrhea, high animal protein, potassium lack, or infections. Without it, calcium stones grow fast. Acidic urine from exercise or drugs worsens this. Large studies link low citrate to recurrence even in hydrated people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="81"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Uric acid and excess protein&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="83"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;High uric acid forms acidic stones in 5-10% of cases, often from red meat, seafood, or gout. It lowers urine pH and seeds calcium oxalate stones too. Metabolic syndrome boosts this, via insulin resistance. High animal protein adds acid load, dropping citrate. Obesity and diabetes double odds. NEJM &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2839518/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;reviews&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; show purine-rich diets raise risk 2-3 times. To counter this, reduce meat consumption, and add veggies for balance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="88"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Salt, low calcium, and hidden diet traps&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="90"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;High salt intake pulls calcium into urine; over 6g daily doubles stone risk. Low dietary calcium fails to bind oxalate in the gut, raising absorption. To prevent this, get 1,000-1,200mg from dairy or greens, and not supplements, since excess vitamin C turns to oxalate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kidney.org/kidney-topics/kidney-stones" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Studies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; confirm these dietary shifts cause stones beyond dehydration. Track sodium under 2,300mg, and eat calcium with meals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="95"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Medical conditions and genetics play big roles&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="97"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obesity, diabetes, gout, thyroid issues, IBD, and UTIs change urine chemistry, while family history raises odds 2.5 times, via genes like those for hypercalciuria. Drugs like diuretics, topiramate, or calcium antacids too, can lead to kidney stones. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="99"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is informational only and not a substitute for medical advice&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="101"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="102"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="103"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="106"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="109"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 02:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAJBVV95cUxNUG9MX2lTeHJMM1Z2STgyR2hkWVJsb3NtNnlNVmk5X0xlR1hLS09lbHJ6NkFaYmZjUm1pTV9hVk9HZlZmX1NXYm1ibjNLbnZ6NnVOUElCU1ZSeHRIRlhEcGR4WGFjUUxLckI1WV96RW43d0ttWVBjMW5VX1VGQjhMRm9oc2syaW52ei1oREcyeDhIWjV6MkJkMFRfWC1ZSVBpcld2RFFhWU1ySUlpNWVfZDBFWm5tLXRYdVdXenBXYklJV21vcW5WcVRSSkg5b2dZM0tXdmt1VmV1N25BZWVIRUlLTDIwV0wtb3NoOXhWS19ySG5sT2xaOUJKX0xWSlNiRGU2QkNad294SW5UYjZlMWc4U0Y</guid></item><item><title>日本正面临痴呆症危机–技术可以提供帮助吗？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c4g9e34yzvgo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Japan is facing a dementia crisis – can technology help?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 gXJgDY"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 gqeTMs"&gt;Suranjana Tewari&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 bIfajQ"&gt;Asia Business Correspondent, Tokyo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251203-121739-f954f14c69-web-2.35.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images An elderly woman crossing a dimly-lit street, pushing a stroller and a white plastic bag" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Around seven million people suffer from dementia in Japan&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Last year, more than 18,000 older people living with dementia left their homes and wandered off in Japan. Almost 500 were later found dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Police say such cases have doubled since 2012, underscoring a growing strain on the world's oldest society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The crisis is further compounded by a shrinking workforce and tight limits on foreign workers coming in to provide care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Japan's government has identified dementia as one of its most urgent policy challenges, with the Health Ministry estimating that dementia-related health and social care costs will reach 14 trillion yen ($90bn; £67bn) by 2030 - up from nine trillion yen in 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In its most recent strategy, the government has signalled a stronger pivot toward technology to ease the pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Across the country, people are adopting GPS-based systems to keep track of those who wander.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Some regions offer wearable GPS tags that can alert authorities the moment a person leaves a designated area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In some towns, convenience-store workers receive real-time notifications – a kind of community safety net that can locate a missing person within hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Robot caregivers and AI&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Other technologies aim to detect dementia earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Fujitsu's aiGait uses AI to analyse posture and walking patterns, picking up early signs of dementia – shuffling while walking, slower turns or difficulty standing – generating skeletal outlines clinicians can review during routine check-ups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Early detection of age-related diseases is key," says Hidenori Fujiwara, a Fujitsu spokesperson. "If doctors can use motion-capture data, they can intervene earlier and help people remain active for longer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Meanwhile, researchers at Waseda University are developing AIREC, a 150kg humanoid robot designed to be a "future" caregiver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It can help a person put on socks, scramble eggs and fold laundry. The scientists at Waseda University hope that in the future, AIREC will be able to change diapers and prevent bedsores in patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Scientists at Waseda University in Tokyo are developing caregiving robots&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Similar robots are already being used in care homes to play music to residents or guide them in simple stretching exercises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;They are also monitoring patients at night - placed under mattresses to track sleep and conditions - and cutting back on the need for humans doing the rounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Although humanoid robots are being developed for the near future, Assistant Professor Tamon Miyake says the level of precision and intelligence required will take at last five years before they are safely able to interact with humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It requires full-body sensing and adaptive understanding - how to adjust for each person and situation," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Emotional support is also part of the innovation drive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Poketomo, a 12cm tall robot, can be carried around in a bag or can fit into a pocket. It reminds users to take medication, tells you how to prepare in real time for the weather outside and offers conversation for those living alone, which its creators say helps to ease social isolation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We're focusing on social issues... and to use new technology to help solve those problems," Miho Kagei, development manager from Sharp told the BBC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Toshio Morita (R) works at the Restaurant of Mistaken Orders&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;While devices and robots offer new ways to assist, though, human connection remains irreplaceable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Robots should supplement, not substitute, human caregivers," Mr Miyake, the Waseda University scientist said. "While they may take over some tasks, their main role is to assist both caregivers and patients."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;At the Restaurant of Mistaken Orders in Sengawa, Tokyo, founded by Akiko Kanna, people stream in to be served by patients suffering from dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Inspired by her father's experience with the condition, Ms Kanna wanted a place where people could remain engaged and feel purposeful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Toshio Morita, one of the café's servers, uses flowers to remember which table ordered what.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Despite his cognitive decline, Mr Morita enjoys the interaction. For his wife, the café provides respite and helps keep him engaged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Kanna's café illustrates why social interventions and community support remain essential. Technology can provide tools and relief, but meaningful engagement and human connection are what truly sustain people living with dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Honestly? I wanted a little pocket money. I like meeting all sorts of people," Mr Morita says. "Everyone's different - that's what makes it fun."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251203-121739-f954f14c69-web-2.35.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Lineup of Sharp Poketomo robots at Ceatec in Chiba, Japan" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Sharp's Poketomo robot has been designed to give companionship to patients&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 01:04:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1SLUtScW1DSExRZTZrU0pXblZMeFFFTTh3NFBnU1R2bXRqNUphOTM0Qk41X2NOUHZScDZUSmRNQW04RlRyU3Y4WlM5SENUbWJ5NFo1QWtha1p4UdIBX0FVX3lxTFBvNkQ2SS1NRVdVVXZfMTZhdEdtTHVhekdWQ3hyVUktb3l4ZXpkb21JSFltMnI0QU5wWGtrOVMwR2ttZXJqMXZncFZOVVNnVTZvZjZRQ1FTcTZiakdYTzVV</guid></item><item><title>每天坐8个小时？即使是锻炼也无法消除伤害；这些习惯可能会-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/sitting-8-hours-a-day-even-exercise-cant-undo-the-damage-these-habits-might/articleshow/125812278.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sitting at your desk for eight hours (or more) a day and heading to the gym in the evening to balance it out? You are not alone. But here’s the shocking truth: that daily gym session may not be enough to counteract the damage to your body caused by prolonged sitting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What happens when you sit for prolonged periods?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;All those long commutes, Zoom-packed workdays, and other tasks that require you to stay seated for several hours a day are causing you more harm than you assume. For instance, metabolic disruptions can begin in just 30 minutes of uninterrupted sitting. In just half an hour, your blood flow slows, muscles become less responsive to insulin, and glucose uptake drops. All this sets the stage for long-term health issues, even in people who exercise regularly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Unexpected dangers of sitting for long hours for young people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Mark Hyman, a physician and functional medicine expert who founded the Cleveland Clinic Center, prolonged sitting over time can contribute to chronic illness. In an Instagram post, he explained that prolonged sitting can lead to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Higher blood sugar and insulin resistance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Increased risk of type 2 diabetes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Poor circulation and endothelial dysfunction&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Higher triglycerides and metabolic syndrome&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When you sit for prolonged periods, it leads to the following changes in your body,” Dr Hyman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skeletal muscle activity drops, reducing glucose uptake from the blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Insulin signalling declines, making cells more resistant to insulin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood flow stagnates, impairing circulation and endothelial function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lipase activity (which breaks down fat) decreases, leading to higher triglycerides and slower metabolism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;All this can increase cardiometabolic risk factors over time and raise the likelihood of diabetes, heart disease, and obesity. “Even daily exercise doesn’t fully counteract these effects. You need to break up your sitting time,” the doctor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How to break out of prolonged sitting?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 2024 meta-analysis of 13 randomised crossover trials showed that how often you interrupt the sedentary habit can directly &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/sms.14769" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;affect your blood glucose levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. The study showed that interrupting sitting every 15–16 minutes can significantly reduce post-meal blood sugar levels. On the other hand, if you stay seated for 45–120 minutes at a time, there is little to no benefit. The takeaway? Break from the seated position every 15 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another 2024 study from the University of Colorado at Boulder found that &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0308660" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;millennials spend more than 60 hours per week sitting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. This prolonged sitting is potentially boosting their heart disease risk and accelerating other signs of ageing, the researchers said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Young adults tend to think they are impervious to the impacts of ageing. They figure, ‘My metabolism is great, I don’t have to worry until I’m in my 50s or 60s.’ But what you do during this critical time of life matters,” first author Ryan Bruellman, a doctoral candidate in the Department of Genetics, Genomics and Bioinformatics at UC Riverside, said. The researchers noted that even vigorous activity could not fully buffer the negative impacts of prolonged sitting. Their suggestion?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use a standing desk&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Take breaks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Organise walking meetings to reduce sitting time at work&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; If possible, do something that gets you out of breath for at least 30 minutes per day&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Be a “weekend warrior”, getting in longer, vigorous workouts when you can&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A third study by the American College of Cardiology found that &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="http://linkinghub.elsevier.com/retrieve/pii/S0735109724099200" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;sitting too long can harm heart health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, even for active people. The researchers found that more time spent sitting, reclining or lying down during the day may increase the risk of cardiovascular disease (CVD) and death. “Our findings support cutting back on sedentary time to reduce cardiovascular risk, with 10.6 hours a day marking a potentially key threshold tied to higher heart failure and cardiovascular mortality. Too much sitting or lying down can be harmful for heart health, even for those who are active,” said Shaan Khurshid, MD, MPH, a cardiologist at Massachusetts General Hospital and co-senior author of the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Practical tips to break from prolonged sitting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While certain jobs may demand being glued to a desk, it is important to break that sedentary habit for better health. Here are some practical tips that can help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Move every 30 minutes for 1–5 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; If possible, get up every 15 minutes for a short burst of activity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Walking is the most effective, but resistance exercises also help.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How to incorporate movement into your daily routine&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Set a reminder to stand or move every 30 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Take a 1–5 minute walk after meals to improve glucose metabolism.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Do bodyweight exercises (squats, calf raises, lunges) during breaks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Use a standing or treadmill desk for work.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Opt for ‘walk and talk’; get up when you attend phone calls.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Pace while reading or watching TV instead of sitting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember, even small movements matter, especially when you spend hours sitting. These small moves can decrease your current risk of heart disease, metabolic issues, and other chronic illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="72"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment, or before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:33:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgJBVV95cUxOYkRFc0FId0FROUFmUnhTWU4zN1RXdXptbFRVdFZTRlJJQ1BlNzVnWU9PR2luaDJheXl2STVjak5pWjljc0M3Yy1TYnZTUlpJSmRNU0l0bHNHaWI5Q2lPWlB6QTlhYkhQRjRoRExsYWVEV2RocUtPcTlFb3FPMXZhLWp6NVdScFkyNE1udi1TOEZ5OG5tN1pfaEN1c2h4SWxYQUh6Y2drUVlWSHB5cE94eFY3NnZVcXY2bU0wcUlGcjU3bGdGcFd1eFprV01KdXJpNktEbXRTZXEzRTBPZnJ5aE5nQnVEdnlGa19vMEV2ZkdKdENnZWV4Q1Y3eFY5d1hfVVVJNnN3</guid></item><item><title>根据胃肠病学家的说法， 10种最适合肠道健康的天然饮料-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/10-best-natural-drinks-for-gut-health-as-per-a-gastroenterologist/articleshow/125808928.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gut is one of the most sensitive parts of the body. Any harmful substance that you consume can send it into an overdrive of reactions and you into a whole lot of digestive trouble. Gut health is vital for digestion, nutrient absorption and immune function and it is linked to mental and physical wellness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thus, consuming the right kind of foods and drinks can help maintain gut health and even improve it. Dr Saurabh Sethi, MD, MPH, from Harvard, Stanford and AIIMS, is a gastroenterologist with a following of 1.4M on Instagram. In a recent video, he shared ten drinks that are the best for gut health, with all of them being natural and easy to make. Here are the drinks that are great for your gut health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Five Effective Ways to Detoxify Your Gut Health&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Water&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might raise an eyebrow over water being one of the best drinks for gut health, but it's the most natural drink in the universe and thus has a multitude of benefits. According to a 2024 study published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11126815/#sec3" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;iScience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, adequate water intake is vital for maintaining the bacterial and immunological balance in the gut. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Ginger tea&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ginger tea may not sound like the most delicious drink out there, but its health benefits are worth every nose-wrinkling sip. Ginger supplementation has been associated with significantly reducing functional dyspepsia symptoms such as stomach pain and bloating, as per a 2023 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10525921/#:~:text=A%20meta%2Danalysis%20of%20five,symptoms%20in%20patients%20with%20FD." rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Cureus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; study. It also improves digestion by helping the stomach empty faster. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thus, sipping on some ginger tea every day can be good for gut health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Green tea&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Green tea has phenolic compounds, protein, amino acids and more. The catechins in it favour the growth of beneficial bacteria and prevent the growth of harmful ones. Additionally, it can increase the production of beneficial metabolites such as short-chain fatty acids, as per a 2021 study published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8271705/#sec4-molecules-26-03907" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Molecules&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;keyword id="31358752" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="fennel-seed-water" source="keywords"&gt;Fennel seed water&lt;/keyword&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While its health magic might not be talked much about, fennel seeds are those hidden magicians. The active ingredients in these seeds have anti-inflammatory and protective effects on the gut and also improve symptoms of irritable bowel disease, as per a 2022 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9269469/#sec025" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;PLOS One&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Kefir&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the huge amount of reels on the internet was not able to convince you that drinking kefir is good for your gut, then it's time you trust the doc. It is a fermented drink made by adding kefir grains to milk. According to a 2019 study published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6769690/#abstract1" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Nutrients&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, kefir consumption for 12 weeks increased the volume of Lactobacillus and Bifidobacterium which are both required for good gut health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Buttermilk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Indian drink, buttermilk is made by diluting yogurt with water and spices like cumin and ginger. It has a high amount of probiotics that improve chronic low-grade inflammation and protect the integrity of the intestinal barrier. It is also known to improve IBS symptoms such as abdominal pain, bloating, anxiety and tension, as per a 2024 study published in the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ijrap.net/admin/php/uploads/3064_pdf.pdf" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;International Journal of Research in Ayurveda and Pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Coconut water&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While a glass of coconut water is as refreshing as a cup of joe, it also has positive impacts on the gut. According to a 2024 study published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38278200/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Clinical Gastroenterology and Hepatology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, coconut water is anti-inflammatory, positively manipulates the gut microbiome and is a rich source of potassium. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Unsweetened kombucha&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kombucha is a fermented drink made with tea, sugar, bacteria and yeast. According to the doctor, its unsweetened version is great for gut health. A 2023 study published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/34698580/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Critical Reviews in Food Science and Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; found that kombucha consumption improves oxidative stress, inflammation, liver detoxification, and reduces intestinal dysbiosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Bone broth&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bone broth is rich in amino acids and minerals that support the improvement of gut health, improve inflammation in the intestinal barrier, and enhance nutrient absorption, as per a 2025 study in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40180691/#:~:text=Through%20comprehensive%20reviews%20of%20animal,Review" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Digestive Diseases and Sciences&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Psyllium husk in warm water&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Psyllium husk water was at the top of the doctor's list of drinks for gut health. As per a 2024 study published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.gastrojournal.org/article/S0016-5085(23)05241-1/fulltext#:~:text=Psyllium%20husk%20supplementation%20can%20be,relief%20in%20IBS%20(constipation)." rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Gastroenterology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, psyllium husk supplementation positively altered the gut microbiota, regulated bowel movement and had anti-inflammatory effects on the gut. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="73"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are all natural drinks, quick fixes that have long-term impacts on gut health. Try including them in your dietary routine and see the gut magic happen. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult with a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment and before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-AFBVV95cUxPOFBYZGVlamVCY3A3MV9xQTN1RXNwbEhTcUtfd18wcTBGRGZmb0J6OFhUaWFUZE1iUHVTU1BKbWs2RERCclQtcDZRbHF0V29nS3lMZUVMbTh1Y3ItcGExY0ZYWnhxbWRDR2xVUmF1cklwbHFOeEpxWThKMktHVl9sWnpZSHllUDU2WXh5SFZ4R0ZUM2N1aWRVa0UtenR4UGhJZ0MwNnNmclZON09vaE9iSW9BV09MekNjS3hFdU5nNXhsa3RnQVQzVk9TaUdWcmRuYjFNYlk0NFVnb0NGWllIdlFoeUpMRU5jMkhDNC1VaS1Sd2drYkVGU9IB_gFBVV95cUxPVzg0Y1E4ODFzZk8xQm05S1hzRG01bnB1QUNBTE5UMldZZDQzMURVQzRIN2MwR0hWWi0zZUtkd2lyTkNqWkdVNUR0b2wyMW9jMU55a1RxWXhydlJxTlRjcHZYR1hVTEhKOThrNkRhX1VRSHpmVGdqN3ctcERTRnJyZ0o5cHZXb1dsOVlvVTJlZnA3TlJjUFUzZnFObzN6SnBPOG02NXBrOHIwZjJCYmFNVk1sSmtrUTFEaDFOWGd1a0k2aWtmWjk0U3Q0VXUyTWdPYmhicXRwcS1Lc2NhNTlSRFhQUmtpME1TZjBaSDNHMWFQZ0JfUG9MRC02a3VfQQ</guid></item><item><title>事实核查疾病预防控制中心专家组放弃普遍新生儿乙型肝炎疫苗推荐的原因- PBS</title><link>https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/fact-checking-the-cdc-panels-reasons-for-dropping-universal-newborn-hepatitis-b-vaccine-recommendation</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-text"&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.politifact.com/article/2025/dec/05/hepatitis-b-vaccine-acip-cdc-hep-b-baby/"&gt;PolitiFact&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since roughly 1991, the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has recommended all babies get a dose of the hepatitis B vaccine at birth. The CDC committee that helps set vaccine policy voted Dec. 5 to overturn that decadeslong policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices’ new recommendations say mothers who tested negative for hepatitis B should discuss the need for the vaccine with their doctors. For babies who do not receive a birth dose, the committee suggested the initial vaccine dose be given “no earlier than 2 months of age.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/show/rfk-appointed-cdc-panel-drops-hepatitis-b-vaccine-at-birth-recommendation"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WATCH:&lt;/strong&gt; RFK-appointed CDC panel drops hepatitis B vaccine at birth recommendation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The committee is composed of members hand-picked by Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy, Jr., an anti-vaccine advocate who in June fired all 17 of the prior panel’s members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are four fact-checkable moments that stood out from ACIP’s Dec. 4 and 5 discussion leading up to the vote:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Many people are unaware they have hepatitis B&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Several ACIP committee members and health administrators questioned the need for vaccination among certain children who they described as “low-risk” for hepatitis B exposure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it can be hard to know a child’s exposure risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hepatitis B is &lt;a href="https://www.hepb.org/prevention-and-diagnosis/transmission/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;transmitted&lt;/a&gt; through &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis-b/about/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;bodily fluids&lt;/a&gt; like blood, semen and vaginal fluids. But it is a highly infectious and &lt;a href="https://www.healthline.com/health/hiv/is-hep-b-more-contagious-than-hiv#risk-comparison" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;tough virus&lt;/a&gt; that can live &lt;a href="https://www.chop.edu/vaccine-education-center/vaccine-details/hepatitis-b-vaccine" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;on surfaces&lt;/a&gt; for up to a week. &lt;a href="https://www.chop.edu/vaccine-education-center/vaccine-details/hepatitis-b-vaccine" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Small amounts&lt;/a&gt; of dried blood on innocuous &lt;a href="https://www.pennmedicine.org/conditions/hepatitis-b" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;household items&lt;/a&gt; like &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29395503/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;nail clippers&lt;/a&gt;, razors or toothbrushes could be enough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hepatitis B infection is stealthy. It can be asymptomatic, sometimes for years. The &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis-b/about/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt; estimates about 640,000 adults have a chronic infection, but about half of them do not know they are infected and contagious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even if a pregnant mother tests negative for the hepatitis B virus, her newborn can come in contact with it in other ways and through other people. Before the vaccine became recommended universally at birth, only &lt;a href="https://publications.aap.org/pediatrics/article/108/5/1123/63723/Childhood-Hepatitis-B-Virus-Infections-in-the" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;around half&lt;/a&gt; of children under 10 who were infected with hepatitis B contracted it from their mothers during birth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since many people are entirely unaware of their infections, it can be hard to know if a person is at elevated risk or resides in a community with infected individuals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Vaccinations are to protect babies, who are most vulnerable to hepatitis B&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some ACIP members said that vaccinating all babies against hepatitis B at birth mainly protected other, higher risk people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s misleading. Vaccination at birth aims primarily to protect newborns, who are &lt;a href="https://www.politifact.com/article/2025/sep/17/hepatitis-b-vaccine-babies-risk/"&gt;particularly vulnerable&lt;/a&gt; to hepatitis B.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hepatitis B virus attacks the liver. Infected infants have a &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/hepatitis/learn-about-viral-hepatitis/hepatitis-b-basics/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;90% chance&lt;/a&gt; of developing the disease’s more dangerous chronic form. A &lt;a href="https://www.aap.org/en/news-room/fact-checked/fact-checked-hepatitis-b-vaccine-given-to-newborns-reduces-risk-of-chronic-infection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;quarter&lt;/a&gt; of those babies will go on to die prematurely from the disease when they become adults.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Untreated, chronic hepatitis B&lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/hepatitis/learn-about-viral-hepatitis/hepatitis-b-basics/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; infections&lt;/a&gt; can cause cirrhosis and death. It is also one of the&lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/liver-cancer/causes-risks-prevention/risk-factors.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; leading causes&lt;/a&gt; of liver cancer. Patients can seek treatments to reduce the virus’ worst effects. But there is no cure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We used to have 18,000 or 20,000 kids a year being born with this, a quarter of them going on to have liver cancer,” &lt;a href="https://www.politifact.com/article/2025/sep/17/hepatitis-b-vaccine-babies-risk/"&gt;said Dr. James Campbell&lt;/a&gt;, pediatric infectious disease doctor at the University of Maryland. “We now have almost none.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Infection rates are low because the decades-old hep B vaccination strategy was working&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This disease has become a victim of the vaccine,” said Dr. H. Cody Meissner, a committee member who voted against changing the recommendations. “We’re seeing disease rates go down because of the effectiveness of the vaccine.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meissner is right that hepatitis B cases dropped dramatically following the introduction of birth-dose vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hepatitis B vaccine uses&lt;a href="https://www.chop.edu/vaccine-education-center/vaccine-details/hepatitis-b-vaccine" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; proteins&lt;/a&gt; from the surface of the hepatitis B virus to provoke an&lt;a href="https://vaccineknowledge.ox.ac.uk/hepatitis-b-vaccine#Ingredients" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; immune response&lt;/a&gt; that gives the body a defense against future infection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before the vaccine, around 200,000 to 300,000 people were infected with hepatitis B&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/preview/mmwrhtml/mm5125a3.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; each year&lt;/a&gt;, including about 20,000 children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since hepatitis B vaccines began being universally administered to babies, overall cases are down to around&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis/php/npr-2025/hep-b-reduce-infections.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; 14,000 annually.&lt;/a&gt; The change is&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis/statistics/2020surveillance/hepatitis-b/figure-2.4.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; especially dramatic&lt;/a&gt; among young people. In 2022, the CDC reported&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis-surveillance-2022/hepatitis-b/table-2-6.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; 252 new chronic hepatitis B&lt;/a&gt; infections among people up to age 19, or 0.4 out of every 100,000 kids.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s a mistake to say that because we’re not seeing much disease, we can alter the roots or the frequency or the schedule for administration,” Meissner said. “Because we will see hepatitis B infections come back.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Many countries vaccinate for hepatitis B at birth; the U.S. is not an outlier&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Committee members repeatedly compared the United States’ guidance with other countries, including Denmark, as part of the rationale for walking back the universal recommendation to provide a hepatitis B vaccine dose at birth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The U.S. is not a global outlier in recommending hepatitis B vaccines for newborns. In &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/downloads/slides-2025-09-18-19/hep-b-birth-dose-briefing-508.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;September 2025, the CDC&lt;/a&gt; reported that “of the 194 WHO member states, 116 countries recommend universal hepatitis B birth dose vaccination to all newborns.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="attachment_541045" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-541045" class="size-large wp-image-541045" src="https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/12/Screenshot_2025-12-05_at_3.24.50PM-1024x544.png" alt="Screenshot_2025-12-05_at_3.24.50PM" srcset="https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/12/Screenshot_2025-12-05_at_3.24.50PM-1024x544.png 1024w, https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/12/Screenshot_2025-12-05_at_3.24.50PM-300x159.png 300w, https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/12/Screenshot_2025-12-05_at_3.24.50PM-768x408.png 768w, https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/12/Screenshot_2025-12-05_at_3.24.50PM-425x226.png 425w, https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/12/Screenshot_2025-12-05_at_3.24.50PM-1200x637.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px"&gt;&lt;p id="caption-attachment-541045" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Hepatitis B vaccine birth dose vaccination policy by county as of September 2025. Graphic by Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Denmark’s &lt;a href="https://www.sst.dk/en/english/General-public/Children#:~:text=this%20page)-,Vaccinations,-The%20Danish%20Childhood" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;standard vaccination schedule&lt;/a&gt; includes vaccines protecting against 10 diseases, but hepatitis B is not one of them. Denmark recommends hepatitis B vaccines only for babies whose mothers are infected with the virus, &lt;a href="https://vaccine-schedule.ecdc.europa.eu/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; the European Centre for Disease Prevention and Control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike Denmark, the U.S. does not have a national health care system, making it harder for Americans to access regular prenatal care and track patient records across doctors. The U.S. also has lower rates of prenatal screening for hepatitis B.&lt;/p&gt;

                                            &lt;div class="inline-invite inline-invite-type__funding inline-invite-style__default"&gt;
        
                    &lt;div class="inline-invite-funding__box"&gt;
                &lt;figure class="invite__logo default "&gt;
                    &lt;svg class="svg"&gt;&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#pbs-newshour-horiz-refresh"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
                &lt;/figure&gt;
                &lt;p class="invite_heading"&gt;
                    A free press is a cornerstone of a healthy democracy. 
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p class="invite_body"&gt;
                    Support trusted journalism and civil dialogue. 
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://give.newshour.org/page/88646/donate/1?ea.tracking.id=pbs_news_sept_2025_article&amp;amp;supporter.appealCode=N2509AW1000100" class="donation-link ga-click-funding ga-click-ender-funding"&gt;
                    &lt;button class="donate-button"&gt;Donate now&lt;/button&gt;
                    &lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="#000000" class="bi bi-arrow-right-short" version="1.1" id="svg1" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:svg="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;
                    &lt;defs id="defs1"&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;
                    &lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" d="M4 8a.5.5 0 0 1 .5-.5h5.793L8.146 5.354a.5.5 0 1 1 .708-.708l3 3a.5.5 0 0 1 0 .708l-3 3a.5.5 0 0 1-.708-.708L10.293 8.5H4.5A.5.5 0 0 1 4 8z" id="path1"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
                    &lt;/svg&gt;
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;


                                    &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PBS</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 23:53:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1AFBVV95cUxPUXpCanEtMDdHa1VJc1BkelZodGZQY0tlbC1VZGlVbmhneDIyU2daekZfX0J1QVIwZ0I1WEJWZ0xBaEtKOVUxVkFzYnZWbGtyWXR5OEQ0Z2dpR0o4cXAteVZURGFWOXE4dmV2WkYyaVJybWFqX3ZnM1lMZFBSRXZ5d3lpNWtuNllKZ1JkR3Bob284eGxhYU1qNVZEcDVfcG1UYWNSaFFqY0xwSlRnR3JHRHZXUDhjMFBFQi1BcTd1eHhrNXVWOHo1V1h3T2dFU2JFRjNDYQ</guid></item><item><title>新研究揭示纹身背后的潜在健康风险- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/study-reveals-potential-health-risk-232803322.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/topic/tattoos" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Tattoos;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Tattoos&lt;/a&gt; can cause lifelong changes to &lt;a href="https://www.aol.com/news/tattoos-may-increase-cancer-risk-114311927.html" data-ylk="slk:the body’s immunity;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;the body’s immunity &lt;/a&gt;as well as affect vaccine responses, according to a new study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An international team of researchers has found that tattoo &lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/topic/ink" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:ink;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;ink&lt;/a&gt; collects in the lymph nodes, affecting &lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/tattoo-melanoma-skin-cancer-symptoms-risk-b2873657.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:the body’s resistance to disease;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;the body’s resistance to disease&lt;/a&gt;, in findings published in the &lt;a href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.2510392122" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While studies have previously investigated the toxicity of tattoo ink, &lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/topic/scientists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:scientists;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;scientists&lt;/a&gt; say this is the first time their effect on immune responses has been explored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using tattoos on mice, researchers found that the animals demonstrated chronic &lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/topic/inflammation" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:inflammation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;inflammation&lt;/a&gt; in their lymph nodes that was “acute and long-lasting”, the death of macrophages (a type of white blood cell), and altered immune response to vaccinations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Tattoos could affect immune response and vaccine response (Getty/iStock)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This work represents the most extensive study to date regarding the effect of tattoo ink on the immune response and raises serious health concerns associated with the tattooing practice,” the team said, noting that at least one in five people have a tattoo globally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our work underscores the need for further research to inform public health policies and regulatory frameworks regarding the safety of tattoo inks.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists were first intrigued when they noticed that mice which had been tattooed for other experiments exhibited inflammation and decided to investigate further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They used standard commercial inks in black, red and green to tattoo the skin on the hind feet of mice. Using specialised imaging equipment, scientists noticed the ink travelled along the lymphatic vessels to nearby lymph nodes, often within minutes, where it accumulated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers also noted that the ink appeared to affect vaccination response with a reduced response to the Covid-19 vaccine and an enhanced response to the UV-inactivated influenza vaccine, “reflecting differences in the mechanisms of action between these vaccine classes”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One of the urgent concerns associated with the safety of tattoos regards the potential redistribution of the unretained ink from the tattoo site to organs other than the skin and the toxic effect that the accumulation of these insoluble pigments might have at systemic levels,” the researchers concluded in their report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, the ink is reported to stay in the lymph nodes for a lifetime, even if the tattoo is removed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Considering the unstoppable trend of tattooing in the population, our results are crucial in informing the toxicology programs, policymakers, and the general public regarding the potential risk of the tattooing practice associated with an altered immune response,” the authors of the study wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Extensive recent research has linked tattoos &lt;a href="https://www.aol.com/news/tattoos-may-increase-cancer-risk-114311927.html" data-ylk="slk:to a type of cancer called lymphoma;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;to a type of cancer called lymphoma&lt;/a&gt;. A study published in &lt;em&gt;BMC Public Health &lt;/em&gt;found that the risk of lymphomas could be three times higher for people with large tattoos compared to those without.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 23:40:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxPWUlpaHVhTTVkZld0b29URVR0Wk9hdFlVbXg1RDJJYnJDNkpFSVlEWEVTNnZGNVVhT1JnZ2xjT2dVSHhYekZQVktGWXluOWlmX1RpT0pUYXYySTJNQm9fd1k4cjhhZG9ja3FBVlNWY1E3ek5ZazNwbFMzOGVqN0M3VjdjNGZmUQ</guid></item></channel></rss>