<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>根据营养师的说法，如果您正在尝试减肥，您不应该服用的4种补充剂- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/supplements-to-avoid-for-weight-loss-11875734</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some supplements for weight loss are unregulated, may be harmful and are not recommended.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do not take green coffee bean extract, Garcinia cambogia, raspberry ketone or caffeine.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work toward an energy deficit for weight loss with a healthy diet and daily exercise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Losing weight is challenging, and many people turn to weight-loss supplements to help achieve their goals. Unfortunately, many supplements marketed for weight loss don’t do what they promise—and may even work against your goals. Not only are supplements expensive, but they are also unregulated, so you don’t always know what you’re getting. The best way to lose weight is to focus on a food-first approach, which means eating plenty of nutrient-dense foods and maintaining a slight &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7922773/best-way-to-lose-weight-and-keep-it-off-according-to-experts/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;calorie deficit&lt;/a&gt; over time. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In this article, we get into some popular weight-loss supplements and why nutrition professionals don't recommend them, plus helpful tips for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7893676/how-to-lose-weight-when-you-dont-know-where-to-start-according-to-a-dietitian/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;healthy, sustainable weight loss&lt;/a&gt;. Knowing what to watch out for can help you make informed choices and prioritize strategies that actually support your health and weight-loss journey.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-green-coffee-bean-extract"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Green Coffee Bean Extract &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’ve searched for supplements aiding weight loss, you’ve likely come across green coffee bean extract. Quite simply, this supplement is derived from the coffee plant’s seeds, which are green before roasting. “[Green coffee bean extract] has chlorogenic acid, a coffee compound that can supposedly decrease fat absorption and speed up metabolism,” says &lt;a href="https://foodsense.net/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Danielle VenHuizen, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;. She adds that these claims are mostly unwarranted. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Only a few human trials have examined the effectiveness of green coffee bean extract on weight loss. These trials had poor study design and showed mixed results.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; While one study found that green coffee extract may help reduce weight and body mass index, there wasn’t a significant effect on body fat percentage, meaning that the mass lost could come from water or muscle.&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Body mass index (BMI) is a flawed measure that’s often used in healthcare to determine a person’s body weight category, and therefore, chronic disease risk. However, it has limitations and does not account for individual factors that influence one’s health status, such as body composition, ethnicity, race, sex and age. This is why it shouldn’t be used as a comprehensive measure of someone’s health and can be a source of body size stigma and bias.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Additionally, in my clinical experience, I have yet to meet a client who has lost weight by using green coffee bean extract,” says VenHuizen. Lastly, there isn’t much information on the safety of green coffee bean extract, so buyers beware. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-garcinia-cambogia"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Garcinia Cambogia &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Garcinia cambogia is a fruit with ​​hydroxycitric acid (HCA), a compound thought to reduce fat production in the body and suppress appetite. “Studies seem to indicate that some of these claims might be true, but unfortunately, the benefits are modest, and the research is conflicting,” says VenHuizen. One study&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;states that there are only a small number of studies on Garcinia cambogia, and the methodology is poor, meaning that these results shouldn’t be trusted.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Even more alarming, “several studies have reported liver issues with long-term use of this supplement,” says VenHuizen.&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This is another pretty convincing reason to avoid adding this supplement to your weight-loss regimen. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-raspberry-ketone"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Raspberry Ketone &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Raspberry ketone is a compound found in the raspberry fruit. Small test-tube and animal studies suggest it may suppress the buildup of fat in the body, but the results are extremely limited. There has only been one human study on the effects of raspberry ketone on weight loss.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The participants took the supplement for eight weeks while also following a calorie-restricted diet. The raspberry ketone supplement was combined with caffeine, bitter orange, ginger, garlic, cayenne, L-theanine, pepper extract, B vitamins and chromium. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The 45 participants who finished the study lost weight, but it’s impossible to know if it was due to the raspberry ketone blend or the calorie deficit. In short, there isn’t enough evidence to support raspberry ketone for weight loss, so save your money. Instead, we recommend snacking on some raspberries, which have &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7835832/health-benefits-of-raspberries/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;several health benefits&lt;/a&gt;, including filling fiber and inflammation-fighting anthocyanins.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-caffeine"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Caffeine &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The most recognizable supplement on this list, caffeine is a compound that stimulates the nervous system. It’s naturally present in tea, coffee and chocolate, as well as in herbal supplements like guarana. Caffeine increases thermogenesis, the body’s natural production of heat. During this process, the body burns extra calories. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Research suggests caffeine can help with weight loss, but a large dose is necessary to create a response. One study concluded that more than 3 milligrams of caffeine per kilogram of body weight is necessary to stimulate the breakdown of fat.&lt;span data-cite="5" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; For a 150-pound person, that’s 200 mg of caffeine, or two cups of coffee. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It is recommended to cap caffeine consumption 400 mg daily for safety, but everyone has a different tolerance level.&lt;span data-cite="6" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8009784/how-much-caffeine-is-too-much/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;People sensitive to caffeine may experience symptoms&lt;/a&gt; like nervousness, jitters, heart racing and headaches, among others. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Although caffeine may increase fat loss, it’s not the best way to lose weight, especially because supplements with caffeine may contain more than that, plus other stimulants. That said, caffeine from natural sources like coffee is the safest way to consume caffeine. So, feel free to include a cup of coffee or tea in your day for an energy boost, but don’t expect it to affect your weight too much. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-tips-for-healthy-weight-loss"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Tips for Healthy Weight Loss  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Although they may not be quick or flashy, the most effective tools for losing weight are good old-fashioned healthy eating and exercise. VenHuizen recommends increasing &lt;a class="pseudoStyle" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8068570/best-high-fiber-fruits-for-weight-loss-according-to-gastroenterologist/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;fiber-rich fruits&lt;/a&gt; and vegetables and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/the-best-healthy-fats-for-weight-loss-8417296" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;healthy fats&lt;/a&gt; in the diet. “These foods naturally increase satiety and provide anti-inflammatory benefits that may aid in weight loss,” says VenHuizen. “And unlike supplements, studies on fruit and vegetable intake show that these foods improve weight-loss efforts,” she adds. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In addition, “Trying to stay moderately active throughout the day, especially for people who work sedentary desk jobs, can help with weight loss,” says &lt;a href="https://dietitianmadeleine.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Madeleine Putzi, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;. She recommends getting up and walking around once per hour to increase your total amount of steps for the day, which is an easy and non-taxing way to increase your daily calorie burn. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Putzi also suggests investing in a standing desk and/or a walking pad if possible. “If you walk for 10 minutes at 3 miles per hour, you will hit around 1,000 steps. Do that every hour, and that's an easy 8,000 steps by the end of your workday,” says Putzi.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Weight-loss supplements are usually not worth the expensive price tag. If a supplement promises to “magically burn fat or flatten your belly,” chances are it’s not the miracle that’s promised on the bottle. A food and exercise approach to weight loss is the most effective way to reach your weight-loss goals in a sustainable way.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE5UYUFDSkt3TURINDE5TUJxQUVfa004TEx1d096RDJBQ044amNvZXF0Ymk4d0hlazlicXk4aE5YYkdZbTdSU2FKQ0JEUEtUVjk5VDVsbnVkd0cxc1FrU0tYNnBkcnBISVYyd2FPZG93WHZkcjlHWWVTN2hpTzk</guid></item><item><title>黑金：调节血糖和血压的富含维生素的水果- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/black-gold-vitamin-packed-fruit-aronia-regulates-blood-sugar-pressure/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Berries from the genus &lt;em&gt;Aronia&lt;/em&gt;, often called black chokeberry, are native to North America and have gained attention for their high content of polyphenolic compounds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These natural chemicals have been associated with benefits that go beyond ordinary nutrition, such as antioxidant effects that may help calm the body’s inflammatory processes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People have started asking about aronia’s place in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/meal-timing-has-a-major-influence-on-our-health/"&gt;everyday meals&lt;/a&gt;, hoping to see if a simple fruit could support healthy lifestyles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists recently examined whether aronia juice might protect against diet-induced challenges linked to the gut microbiome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This project was led by &lt;a href="https://www.montana.edu/news/22109/stephanie-wilson-one-of-first-three-students-to-complete-montana-state-s-individual-interdisciplinary-ph-d-program"&gt;Dr. Stephanie M. G. Wilson&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href="https://www.montana.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Montana State University&lt;/a&gt;. Research in this area has looked at how bacteria in the digestive system respond when aronia berries are introduced, particularly in situations where unhealthy eating patterns could raise inflammation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early investigations point to intriguing changes in microbes, and hinting that this berry might shift certain bacterial communities and reduce the strain triggered by high-fat diets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-science-behind-aronia-berries"&gt;Science behind aronia berries&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team used a mouse model with transplanted human gut microbiomes that came from donors with different inflammation levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Aronia supplementation provided robust protection,” noted Dr. Wilson when reviewing the results at the end of the study. Scientists saw increases in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/gut-bacteria-have-very-clever-ways-of-supporting-human-health/"&gt;Eggerthellaceae&lt;/a&gt;, a family of bacteria that can process polyphenols. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some data also linked &lt;a href="https://extension.umn.edu/trees-and-shrubs/black-chokeberry" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;black chokeberry&lt;/a&gt; intake with changes in metabolites related to improved gut barriers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These shifts suggest that eating or drinking aronia-based products might assist in keeping the digestive system more balanced during periods of dietary stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-personalizing-nutrition"&gt;Personalizing nutrition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inflammation can arise when people eat high-fat or sugary foods for long stretches. Researchers point out that a person’s unique microbiome might determine how well they adapt to certain dietary habits. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aronia’s &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/1420-3049/27/22/7823"&gt;benefits&lt;/a&gt; may vary from one person to another, depending on individual gut ecology and background health status. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those who carry a set of gut bacteria already geared toward lower inflammation, the advantages from adding aronia might be more visible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This concept underscores how science is moving toward personalized nutrition, where different bodies respond to the same foods in slightly different ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-aronia-berries-help"&gt;How aronia berries help&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other published works indicate that aronia is not just a source of antioxidants; it may also be linked with healthier glucose levels and heart function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The presence of anthocyanins and other phenolic substances could explain how this fruit influences complex pathways connected to metabolism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Traditional uses of aronia include juices, jams, and powders, but emerging science is urging a closer look at its larger dietary potential. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While some folks already consume aronia to freshen up their breakfast or snack routines, others remain unaware of its possible contributions to gut stability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-unraveling-unexpected-twists"&gt;Unraveling unexpected twists&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some findings highlight the importance of gut diversity when it comes to inflammation. Researchers observed that mice with microbiomes from donors who had lower inflammation were more resilient during the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/high-fat-diets-cause-high-anxiety-through-changes-in-gut-bacteria/"&gt;high-fat diet&lt;/a&gt; challenge. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aronia seemed to shield this group even further. This suggests that, while aronia might help most individuals, those who have specific microbial imbalances might notice the biggest improvements. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On a broader level, it points to how small dietary changes, like adding a berry drink, can create ripple effects that protect overall wellness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-applications-on-the-horizon"&gt;Applications on the horizon&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aronia’s tart flavor might not suit everyone right away. In grocery stores, it often appears in juice blends, concentrates, or dried forms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because it’s easy to mix with other fruits, people can add it to smoothies or desserts without changing their routines too drastically. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research continues to evaluate how much aronia consumption is ideal for humans, since the dose can vary widely. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some clinical trials, individuals experienced potential &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/tackling-fat-with-food-tropical-plant-in-china-has-anti-obesity-properties/"&gt;anti-obesity benefits&lt;/a&gt;, in addition to improvements in the body’s natural defenses. These early observations pave the way for deeper investigations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aronia may carry special ingredients that bolster the gut’s ability to cope with stress, especially during nutritional challenges. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investigators are looking to see if these insights might lead to new strategies for lowering inflammation in the long term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This berry isn’t a magic bullet, and results will differ from person to person. Its potential, though, goes beyond just delivering antioxidants: it may connect with gut microbes in ways that support healthy balance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fresh interest in aronia keeps growing, and the findings so far hint at a fruitful path for future study.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/nutrition/articles/10.3389/fnut.2023.1244692" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Frontiers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 21:36:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxPclV4SkduQ0N6X0hYRXlOaHJ2VHRVMnFEYlBMbDFtRDJWaU9uY0wzeTFPZ1doWURndVlXTVJ2YXZtc09yVDJlWjhGVHJiTndlVkpnWWdya0RUdGtpbVZlZDcyTlhJbnZfeERXUEdOOW5RZElTREFuTkRpZHFCTkdvbGJFZWVPMjdmRTdjdzBsQXFjeXZPVFhPYWxmQURodw</guid></item><item><title>这种季节性35卡路里水果可以提高你的免疫力，改善你的皮肤—并帮助你的大脑健康-纽约邮报</title><link>https://nypost.com/2026/01/03/health/this-35-calorie-fruit-can-boost-your-immunity-skin-and-brain-health/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom"&gt;
							


&lt;p&gt;Want to stay healthy this cold and flu season — and look good doing it?&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There’s a budget-friendly fruit in season right now that’s bursting with nutrients, low in calories and might just be the secret weapon your immune system and skin need this winter.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;An added bonus: Your brain will also get a boost. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;By providing antioxidants and vitamin C, these fruits can brighten skin tone, improve texture and reduce wrinkles.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Rido – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Clementines, better known by their brand names Cuties or Halos, are like the smaller, sweeter cousins of the orange. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="connatix-outstream-video"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These tiny citrus fruits are easy to peel, usually seedless and hit peak season from October through January.  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But don’t let their small size fool you: &lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/168195/nutrients" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;One clementine&lt;/a&gt; clocks in at just 35 calories but delivers 36.1 mg of vitamin C — nearly 40% of what you need daily for optimal health. &lt;/p&gt;


	



&lt;p&gt;Vitamin C is essential nutrient, meaning your body can’t make it on its own so you need to get it from your diet. It’s a powerhouse for your immune system, helping to destroy infectious microbes while keeping your tissues safe from damage. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/23440782/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Research shows&lt;/a&gt; that getting enough vitamin C on a regular basis can help reduce the severity and duration of cold and flu symptoms. However, there is little evidence that popping vitamin C once you are already sick will speed recovery, so consistency matters when it comes to eating clementines.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;In the US, most clementines are grown in California and Florida.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Markus Mainka – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The perks don’t stop at immunity. Vitamin C is also crucial for &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/12/05/health/boost-collagen-in-your-skin-with-this-small-fruit-twice-a-day/"&gt;collagen&lt;/a&gt;, the protein that keeps your skin firm, plump and smooth. &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Maintaining adequate collagen levels can reduce fine lines, prevent sagging and even speed up wound healing. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Clementines are also packed with other antioxidants, like flavonoids, which can fight inflammation, calm redness and soothe skin conditions like acne or rosacea.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And with their high water content, these juicy snacks can help the skin stay hydrated, preventing dryness and flakiness.   &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But the goodness doesn’t end there. Clementines contain folate and thiamine, two B vitamins that are crucial for your body, supporting everything from cell development to a healthy metabolism.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And while a single clementine only has about 1 gram of fiber, snacking on a few throughout the day is an easy way to &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/05/30/health/what-is-fibermaxxing-dietitian-warns-about-viral-trend/"&gt;boost your intake&lt;/a&gt;, supporting digestion, gut health and weight management. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Like other citrus fruits, clementines are brain-friendly, too.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Clementines are nutrient-dense, helping promote brain function and healthy aging.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;WavebreakMediaMicro – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;They contain bioactive compounds such as polyphenols, which have anti-inflammatory and antioxidative properties that help protect the brain from damage.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Studies on animals have shown that supplementing the diet with citruis fruits improves deficits in learning and memory, particularly spacial memory, which helps us remember where we’ve put things and recognition memory, which is vital for facial and name recall,” Dr. David Vauzour, a senior research fellow at Norwich Medical School, &lt;a href="https://www.foodnavigator.com/Article/2021/03/03/The-role-of-citrus-in-brain-health-Citrus-bioactive-compounds-improve-general-cognition/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;told FoodNavigator&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Clementines are also a rich source of hesperidin, a bioflavonoid with antioxidant properties that may help reduce inflammation, improve blood flow in the brain and support overall brain cell health. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40694049/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Research suggests&lt;/a&gt; that getting hesperidin in your diet can help improve cognitive functions such as attention, learning and memory, as well as psychomotor skills like movement and coordination. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In fact, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40694049/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;studies show&lt;/a&gt; that eating citrus fruits like clementines daily could cut the risk of developing dementia in older adults by nearly 15%.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;They might even help your mood. Last year, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/03/09/health/eating-this-fruit-daily-can-lower-depression-risk-by-20-study/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;scientists found&lt;/a&gt; that people who ate a daily serving of citrus had about a 20% lower risk of being diagnosed with depression. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The effect seems to be specific to citrus,” Raaj Mehta, the lead study author, told &lt;a href="https://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2025/02/eating-citrus-may-lower-depression-risk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;The Harvard Gazette&lt;/a&gt;. “When we look at people’s total fruit or vegetable consumption, or at other individual fruits such as apples or bananas, we don’t see any relationship between intake and risk of depression.”&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;But before you grab a bag and start peeling, there’s something to keep in mind about clementines. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Some research has shown that clementines contain furanocoumarins, a compound also &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3589309/"&gt;found in grapefruit&lt;/a&gt; that can interfere with certain medications, including &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/27890698/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;cholesterol-lowering statins&lt;/a&gt;, and potentially cause complications.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To be safe, experts recommend checking with your doctor or pharmacist about possible drug interactions before adding large amounts of citrus fruit to your daily diet.&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;

												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOMzA3Z1pZYThFM1pPYUdhZjJQVEQ3dnRScHdHVENQRmZqZWtXR0pOeUxHaVRfYndUMUhydTdlZmc1OFBnbW8yQjVQUDJkVzRQSkFBZmlZVklpUjRNMFQtT0Vud2lGMVZ1WDJSTGhzZl9uNTdTYnlYUi1wZXVtODhiMnpEN3ZVZkF6TmhtbTV5d2paMjB0Z0ltdnFMM3lITkFVTmY5dEVnMEk</guid></item><item><title>我无法停止的高纤维、高蛋白晚餐- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/my-favorite-high-fiber-dinner-11875632</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Roasted Potato Tzatziki Bowls deliver comfort and flavor while packing 10g of fiber per serving.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Plant-based yet protein-rich, each bowl offers 17g of protein thanks to chickpeas and Greek-style yogurt.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Easy and satisfying, this 45-minute meal proves high-fiber dinners can be cozy and delicious.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When you hear “high-fiber meal,” chances are you’re thinking about salads, hearty soups or even bean skillets. These are great and all, but what if I told you that my favorite high-fiber diner is none of these things, and it doesn’t skimp on comfort?
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Meet the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/roasted-potato-tzatziki-bowls-11686979" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Roasted Potato Tzatziki Bowls&lt;/a&gt; that I swear by. Although they star roasted potatoes, the fresh and vibrant in this dish really shine any time of year. Besides the delicious mix of tangy and herby flavors, there’s so many things that I love about this dinner. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It’s hard to pick a place to start, but let’s talk about its surprising nutrition content. Thanks to the chickpeas, cucumbers, tomatoes and onions, these bowls are loaded with fiber, packing 10 grams per serving, which is 40% of the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-it-looks-like-to-eat-enough-fiber-11798470" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;recommended daily value for women&lt;/a&gt;. I’m acutely aware that most Americans &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/small-changes-that-helped-me-eat-more-fiber-11775341" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;do not get enough fiber&lt;/a&gt; in their eating pattern, so I’m always looking for ways to include the satisfying essential nutrient in my meal, as consuming more fiber can help reduce &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/287742/10-amazing-health-benefits-of-eating-more-fiber/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;the risk of type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; (which runs in my family).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Not only are they fibrous, but these bowls are also protein-rich, even while being a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/plant-based-protein-benefits-11712145" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;plant-based&lt;/a&gt; meal. Combining chickpeas and homemade tzatziki made with strained (Greek-style) yogurt, each bowl serves 17 grams of protein per serving. I love incorporating more plant-based proteins into my meals, and I usually always have a can of chickpeas in my pantry or a tub of yogurt in my refrigerator, making shopping for this dinner that much easier.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;
Speaking of easy, this recipe notes that it takes a total of 45 minutes to make, but the busy work is mostly just chopping veggies and mixing up the tzatziki. Once you have everything prepared, it’s easy: the base of the bowl is the tzatziki, then top with your chickpeas and veggies, add your roasted potatoes and drizzle the whole thing with some really good olive oil. Personally, I’ve been loving &lt;a href="https://canaanpalestine.com/products/rumi-olive-oil" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Canaan Palestine’s Rumi Olive Oil&lt;/a&gt; lately for its bold flavor, and it’s amazingly all-purpose, so I can use it for the potatoes as well as for the finish.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If I haven’t convinced you yet to make these tzatziki bowls, I don’t know what will. In fact, I just convinced myself to make them for dinner tonight. And I may even pair it with leftover Christmas cookies and New Year’s wine… it’s called balance!&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE81SVRFaDFQWWxrZDJMRkMxMjFzWTdTckF5QW0wZ3NQUzRhdXNrSFA2Y1BTZFVNZldnOWNad3haV0s5UExRVmltb2F6YnNnVkNNX2Vab1Foa3Zkb2tsclpWSzRRVURMaFpzYVVFUDhZTnBqVkE</guid></item><item><title>在NC中发现的麻疹暴露- WRAL</title><link>https://www.wral.com/news/state/gaston-county-measles-north-carolina-january-2026/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;
					&lt;p id="font-resize" class="font-resize-container"&gt;
						&lt;button id="small-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa small-buttom-font-svg" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;button id="medium-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;button id="large-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;

					
						&lt;p&gt;A person carrying measles traveled through Gaston County while infectious, according to the North Carolina Department of Health and Human Services. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Health officials ask anyone who was at Constantine’s Restaurant in Gastonia after 8:30 p.m. on Dec. 26, 2025, to monitor for measles symptoms until Jan. 16.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
								
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;The individual also attended Christmas Town USA in McAdenville from 5:30 to 8 p.m. on Dec. 26, 2025. The individual did not visit any indoor locations, so the risk of transmission of measles to others who were attending at the same time is low.  &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Measles is a respiratory disease that can be spread by coughing and sneezing.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;As of Dec. 30, 2025, the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has reported 2,065 people from 44 states as confirmed measles cases this year.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Symptoms of measles include:&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;High fever (may spike to more than 104 degrees)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cough&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Runny nose&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Red, watery eyes (conjunctivitis)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiny white spots on the inner cheeks, gums and roof of the mouth (Koplik Spots) two to three days after symptoms begin&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A rash that is red, raised, blotchy; usually starts on face, spreads to trunk, arms and legs three to five days after symptoms begin&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
						
							
							
								&lt;p class="opscoad-Mobile_In_Content" data-unit="wral-v4/news/state/gaston-county-measles-north-carolina-january-2026"&gt;
								&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;p class="opscoad-article_in_read" data-unit="wral-v4/news/state/gaston-county-measles-north-carolina-january-2026/"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;In December, &lt;a href="https://www.wral.com/news/local/rdu-measles-exposure-dec-10-2025/"&gt;a traveler infected with measles came through Terminal 2&lt;/a&gt; of Raleigh-Durham International Airport.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
					
				&lt;/div&gt;


				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WRAL</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 19:01:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNRXRVNWJvbXBQUnRCM1FfNjJfOGpOWENlRVZPUDlHelNpbnVJRnZqa1EwaE1nTDRWNE5EWUwzeFIxcnZjVnJ1Z09yQmhtT25Ub1M2cDB5MUFvMlJfZ2NRV2phSm5JaV9tREN3ZmtRUmgxYUZWRklwZk1wVlp3R1hhdXprdzJSZzBjMUE</guid></item><item><title>继2018年以来最严重的季节之后，美国12月流感病例激增--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2026/jan/03/us-spike-influenza-december</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The United States has seen the number of influenza cases climb significantly in December, coming after the most severe flu season since 2018, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It’s not yet clear whether there will be an increase in the total number of people who get the flu this season – or whether more people just got it at once in December – but more than 3,100 people died from the virus in the US in the year ending August 2025, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-51.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;latest data&lt;/a&gt; from the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;As such, people who have not yet gotten a flu vaccine should still get one, according to &lt;a href="https://vivo.brown.edu/display/jnuzzo" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Jennifer Nuzzo&lt;/a&gt;, an epidemiologist at Brown University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Bottom line for people, if they haven’t gotten vaccinated against the flu, they should get vaccinated, particularly young kids and older adults,” Nuzzo said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The spike in cases comes after a 2024-2025 flu season that was the most severe since 2018, according to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/whats-new/2025-2026-influenza-activity.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the CDC&lt;/a&gt;. It also included 279 influenza-associated pediatric deaths, the highest reported to the agency during a seasonal influenza epidemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;This year, a new variant, subclade K, has emerged and the flu season started earlier than usual in Europe, with “&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/dec/17/new-flu-strain-sweeping-across-europe-is-putting-pressure-on-healthcare-says-who" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;high or very high influenza activity&lt;/a&gt;”, in December in the region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the United States, there had been an estimated 7.5m influenza cases and 81,000 hospitalizations by 20 December. That marked a 25% increase in cases over the previous week, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;a href="https://gis.cdc.gov/grasp/fluview/main.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Thirty-two states&lt;/a&gt; have seen a “high or very high” number of flu illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“A lot of people are getting the flu at the same time, which is always tough. That is actually tougher than a situation in which people get it and it’s spread out over a longer period,” Nuzzo said. “It could be a worse season, in part because more people are going to need care than hospitals can easily deliver.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Epidemiologists are also concerned that fewer people could opt to get the flu vaccine because the CDC, led by the health secretary, Robert F Kennedy Jr, canceled &lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/388/bmj.r389" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;its campaign&lt;/a&gt; encouraging people to get the shot. At the start of December, about 130m flu vaccines had been distributed in the US, 13m less than at the same point last year, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluvaxview/dashboard/vaccine-doses-distributed.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;according to the CDC&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s completely incredulous to me that after experiencing the worst flu season for kids on record that we could head into this flu season – with signs that it could be bad, based on the viruses circulating out there – with anything but a robust plan to encourage people to get vaccinated,” Nuzzo said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some US residents could also be concerned about how much protection the new round of vaccine shots offer against the latest variant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We have some reason to think that the protection may be lower, but I want to be careful by saying” that, Nuzzo said. “It may protect you less, but it’s likely still going to give you some important protection.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;People also might not be aware that they can pick up an at-home test from a pharmacy, Nuzzo said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“There are some people who might benefit from medication if they tested positive, but that medication needs to be given very soon after symptoms start,” Nuzzo said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 19:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQMDViMWVKYm1xc3FCalY1VVJ3cTF2NDRteHlJQWgwQl8zc3JMSWxGNTRVM09mSGZmYzZhdzl3MllTNDFRbG9FcGNhVjRrZTNnV0RkR1FaNVBoUnFPanl2TXBQUUlYekh6cDdkY2haUkpWMXVXZmpBRWxBNThUZVowdA</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法， 5种有助于降低血压的最佳减肥零食- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/snacks-for-weight-loss-with-high-blood-pressure-11874848</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Losing weight is often recommended for hypertension since extra weight raises blood pressure.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Protein- and fiber-rich meals boost fullness, while potassium and magnesium support heart health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;For snacks, dietitians suggest unsalted nuts, popcorn, yogurt with fruit, chia pudding and more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Weight loss is often recommended for people with hypertension because carrying excess weight is linked to higher blood pressure levels and increased strain on the heart.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Research shows that even modest weight loss can help lower blood pressure, making sustainable eating habits helpful for managing both.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; That's where snacking comes in. Foods that provide protein and fiber increase satiety and reduce cravings, while those that include potassium and magnesium help regulate blood pressure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Choosing nutrient-dense snacks can increase satisfaction between meals, supporting both weight loss and heart health. Ahead, dietitians share snack ideas that do just that.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-strained-greek-style-yogurt-with-fruit"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Strained (Greek-style) Yogurt with Fruit &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Dietitians agree that strained (Greek-style) yogurt is a great snack option for weight loss if you have high blood pressure, especially when paired with high-potassium fruits like bananas and kiwis.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "Greek yogurt is a good source of protein to keep you feeling full, while banana and kiwi provide potassium to help manage sodium levels in the body," says  &lt;a href="https://www.willowlabs.ai/products/nutu/team" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Dawn Menning, M.S., RD, CDCES&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Potassium helps the kidneys excrete excess sodium and supports the relaxation of blood vessel walls, both of which play an important role in blood pressure regulation.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Not a fan of bananas and kiwi? &lt;a href="https://www.mayazbites.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Maya Oueichek, M.B.A., RDN&lt;/a&gt;, recommends pairing strained (Greek-style) yogurt with berries and chia seeds. In addition to supporting satiety, strained (Greek-style) yogurt's protein helps preserve lean muscle mass during weight loss.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Berries contribute fiber and potassium, while chia seeds provide omega-3 fats and magnesium—nutrients that support healthy blood pressure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-hummus-with-veggies"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Hummus with Veggies &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Hummus is rich in plant-based fiber, protein and magnesium," says Oueichek, nutrients that are helpful for weight loss and managing hypertension.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; For veggies, she recommends carrots and bell peppers because they're a good source of potassium and naturally low in sodium.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "This combo promotes fullness, stable blood sugar and supports vascular function," Oueichek adds, all of which are important for weight loss and managing blood pressure.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It's important to keep sodium in check if you have high blood pressure, so choose low-sodium hummus options or make your own at home.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "Excess sodium intake is directly linked to elevated blood pressure," says Oueichek.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Try our&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/256571/garlic-hummus/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Garlic Hummus&lt;/a&gt; recipe, and enhance flavor with lemon juice, garlic and spices instead of salt.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-unsalted-nuts"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Unsalted Nuts &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Nuts support heart health by improving blood lipids, supporting healthy blood pressure and reducing inflammation. These benefits come from their mix of unsaturated fats, plant protein, fiber, phytosterols and minerals potassium and magnesium—nutrients linked to cardiovascular protection.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Enjoying nuts with a side of fruit can make an even more satisfying snack. "Fruit paired with a handful of nuts promotes satiety since fiber, protein and healthy fat slow digestion," says &lt;a href="https://sheridietitian.com/about-me/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Sheri Gaw, RDN, CDCES&lt;/a&gt;. She notes that this combination also provides potassium and magnesium, minerals that aid in blood pressure control.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The fiber and protein in nuts can also help reduce cravings, which may support weight loss, says Menning.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Go with unsalted varieties to best support your blood pressure.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-chia-pudding"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Chia Pudding &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Chia seed pudding provides healthy fat, protein, fiber, magnesium and potassium—nutrients that help slow digestion, regulate hunger and support heart health and blood pressure control," says Gaw. Research suggests chia seed consumption may help lower both systolic and diastolic blood pressure, likely due to its effects on vascular function and inflammation.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Chia seeds are also a source of omega-3 fatty acids, which have been linked to cardiovascular benefits, including reduced inflammation.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Preparing &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/chia-seed-pudding-8430793" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Chia Seed Pudding&lt;/a&gt; with cow's milk adds calcium and protein, further supporting heart health and satiety.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-air-popped-popcorn"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Air-Popped Popcorn &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Air-popped popcorn contains fiber, which has been linked to benefits for digestive health, blood sugar regulation, heart health and weight management.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; A fiber-rich snack helps slow digestion and promote fullness, which can keep you feeling full and satisfied between meals.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Dietitians recommend being thoughtful when seasoning your snacks. Oueichek suggests sprinkling popcorn with smoked paprika, cinnamon, cumin or chili powder instead of salt. "Or you can add nutritional yeast to give it a cheesy, savory flavor without adding sodium," says Menning. Nutritional yeast also provides B vitamins, fiber and a small amount of protein.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-ways-to-lose-weight-and-support-healthy-blood-pressure"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Ways to Lose Weight and Support Healthy Blood Pressure &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exercise regularly. &lt;/strong&gt;Physical activity helps lower blood pressure by strengthening the heart and improving blood vessel function, while also supporting weight loss.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Aim for 150 minutes of moderate aerobic activity plus 2 days of resistance training per week.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prioritize sleep. &lt;/strong&gt;Missing out on quality sleep is associated with increased appetite and energy intake.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; It can also negatively affect blood pressure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Aim for seven to nine hours of quality sleep each night. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limit alcohol intake. &lt;/strong&gt;Alcohol can raise blood pressure and add to overall caloric intake, making both heart health and weight loss harder to manage.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manage stress. &lt;/strong&gt;Chronic stress can elevate cortisol levels and blood pressure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "Simple practices like breathing exercises, mindfulness, yoga or regular walks can be effective," says Oueichek.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Snacks can help you lose weight and manage blood pressure when chosen thoughtfully. Balanced choices that combine protein and fiber increase satiety, while nutrients like potassium and magnesium support heart and blood vessel health. Rather than skipping snacks, aim to be intentional. Choose whole, nutrient-dense foods—like fruit, vegetables, yogurt, nuts and whole grains—to help you reach your goals.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 18:58:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNSnZRVWZ3LU01TS14WXVORkVCbm81Mkc2SVpIWGZuLUg2S3pISVVicHRCdGQ5REFNZmdZV3dhNG1STHQxODN2ZkRDelZNRWg2NjN5ZS1pSEVZTjdhNDFiSm9pWU5lVG1rS2NYSHF1Zlhia0M5WDNHeFJhNjlBM2N3MFYtbnpYWEJHNDc4</guid></item><item><title>在令人痛苦的研究中揭示了罗马边疆生活的恐怖- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/horror-of-life-on-roman-frontier-revealed-in-gut-wrenching-study</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Roman soldiers garrisoned at the fort of Vindolanda, located near Hadrian's Wall in northern England, were riddled with parasites that sapped their fighting fitness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In addition to lice-infested tunics and runny noses, Rome's military might have dealt with chronic gut infections that caused diarrhea, stomach cramps, and nausea, according to a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/parasitology/article/parasite-infections-at-the-roman-fort-of-vindolanda-by-hadrians-wall-uk/49A5CBC021F5C3D85D040D4FD1A9AD44"&gt;jointly performed archaeological study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; by researchers from Cambridge and Oxford.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"While the Romans were aware of intestinal worms, there was little their doctors could do to clear infection by these parasites or help those experiencing diarrhea, meaning symptoms could persist and worsen," says Marissa Ledger, an archaeologist at McMaster University in Canada who co-led the study while completing her PhD at Cambridge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These chronic infections likely weakened soldiers, reducing fitness for duty. Helminths alone can cause nausea, cramping, and diarrhea."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-reveals-british-history-s-most-worm-infested-people-and-it-s-not-who-d-imagine"&gt;Study Reveals British History's Most Worm-Infested People, And It's Not Who You Think&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers analyzed just under 60 samples of sewer drain sediments containing ancient poop and other detritus that washed away from the fort and nearby settlements, dating to the 3rd century CE. The glut of grossness originated from the fort's latrine drain, which carried waste to a stream north of the site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_187102" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-187102" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/parasite_eggs_roman_soldiers_642.jpg" alt="helminth eggs" class="wp-image-187102 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/parasite_eggs_roman_soldiers_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/parasite_eggs_roman_soldiers_642-600x374.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-187102" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;A significant percentage of the samples collected contained signs of worm eggs. (Ledger et al., &lt;em&gt;Parasitology&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous archaeological explorations in the area have unearthed a trove of organic materials that have been preserved in Vindolanda's waterlogged soil. These finds include more than &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/ancient-roman-bigfoot-unusually-large-shoes-puzzle-archaeologists"&gt;5,000 leather shoes&lt;/a&gt;, a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-wooden-phallus-might-be-a-rare-2000-year-old-dildo"&gt;wooden phallus&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vindolanda_tablets"&gt;over 1,700 thin wooden tablets&lt;/a&gt; inscribed with ink, which document day-to-day habits at the fort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This daily martial life would have revolved around guarding Hadrian's Wall, just north of the fort. Established in the early 2nd century CE, the wall is a defensive fortification running east-to-west from the North Sea to the Irish Sea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To ease occupation on this Roman-British frontier, the fort had baths, toilets, and drinking water. Regardless, the soldiers still suffered from intestinal infections, including roundworms, whipworms, and potentially &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/these-11-zoonotic-diseases-can-get-to-you-through-your-animal-friends"&gt;Giardia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, a &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/dpdx/giardiasis/index.html"&gt;diarrhea-causing&lt;/a&gt; microscopic single-celled animal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This latter pathogen is an exciting find for researchers, if not so much for those past soldiers, because it's the first evidence of &lt;em&gt;Giardia duodenalis&lt;/em&gt; in Roman Britain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite Vindolanda's bath complex, with its previously mentioned amenities, outbreaks occurred due to poor sanitary practices. Specifically, fecal contamination in food, water, and on the soldiers' hands helped spread these parasites throughout the fort and throughout time – samples collected from a fortification constructed in 85 CE also contained roundworm and whipworm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, parasite sufferers would have become severely ill from dehydration via chronic infections that could linger for weeks, "causing dramatic fatigue and weight loss." These conditions bred other severely deleterious intestinal pathogens, setting the scene for outbreaks of &lt;em&gt;Salmonella&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Shigella&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Written or uncovered evidence reveals many &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/roman-trade-routes-carried-tuberculosis-across-globe"&gt;other types of Roman-reared infections&lt;/a&gt;. On one occasion, 10 soldiers were deemed unfit for duty due to conjunctivitis, also known as pink eye, which &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/conjunctivitis-caused-by-poop"&gt;can occur&lt;/a&gt; when eyes come into contact with poop-laden fingers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the parasite profile at Vindolanda is similar to that from other Roman military sites, including those in Austria, the Netherlands, and Scotland. One reason may be the more-limited, pork-heavy diet, as described in preserved texts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, "Urban sites, such as London and York, had a more diverse parasite range, including fish and meat tapeworms."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, for all the modern romanticism surrounding Roman hygiene, the history is often dirtier and more fecal-infested than imagined. It's also worth noting that nearly 2,000 years ago, Vindolanda sat at Rome's northwestern frontier, and frontier settlements often faced the harshest hardships – made all the harsher when its defenders had 30-centimeter (12-inch) roundworms snaking through their guts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research is published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/parasitology/article/parasite-infections-at-the-roman-fort-of-vindolanda-by-hadrians-wall-uk/49A5CBC021F5C3D85D040D4FD1A9AD44"&gt;Parasitology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/parasitology/article/parasite-infections-at-the-roman-fort-of-vindolanda-by-hadrians-wall-uk/49A5CBC021F5C3D85D040D4FD1A9AD44"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 18:02:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxQVnFTVFozUU9hQmoxaXhpemdKVEtRNklRRnh5X2FfTjBQX1BXZGJfS2wxSEVtYWo5bjJXY3ZRWm1KZHNSc1NwOW1ib1Z3NFFKeF9UNzF0QjdvS3hsUGhTWDQ0UlZuWTdwbFprUTdocGhhY3lSNTZNUTZuZ1hUQnFsVXlGdmNibm1vSGRCVGJGLW1nRDlUZ21kTQ</guid></item><item><title>热门市中心餐厅、百思买和图书馆的麻疹暴露- WYFF新闻4</title><link>https://www.wyff4.com/article/measles-exposure-restaurant-best-buy-library-sc-greenville/69908010</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content--body-inner"&gt;
										&lt;div class="mobile"&gt;
													



																		&lt;div class="mobile"&gt;
							

&lt;section class="article-headline"&gt;
	
			&lt;p class="article-headline--title"&gt;Measles exposure at popular downtown restaurant, Best Buy, and library&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/section&gt;


							&lt;div class="article-branding"&gt;
						&lt;img data-src="https://kubrick.htvapps.com/htv-prod-media.s3.amazonaws.com/htv_default_image/site_branding/wyff.png" class="lazyload lazyload-in-view branding" alt="WYFF 4 logo"&gt;
								&lt;p class="article-headline--publish-date border-left"&gt;
			Updated: 11:17 AM EST Jan 3, 2026
		&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;a href="/article/hearst-television-news-policy-statements/14471973" class="editorial-standards border-left"&gt;Editorial Standards &lt;span class="info-icon"&gt;ⓘ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

							




						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
	
						
					&lt;p class="article-content--body-teaser"&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;p class="article-content--body-text-raw"&gt;
						South Carolina Department of Public Health (DPH) has identified three public places someone with measles may have exposed others to the disease.Thoe locations are:Nose Dive restaurant at 116 S. Main Street, Greenville, S.C. on Dec. 24 from 1:30 to 4:30 pmBest Buy at 1125 Woodruff Road, Suite 1201, Greenville, S.C. on Dec. 24 from 3 to 6 p.m.The Spartanburg County Public Library at 151 at S. Church Street, Spartanburg, S.C. for the Solar Superstorms planetarium show on Dec. 27 from 3:15 to 6:30 p.m. According to DPH, the person did not know they were infectious at the time. DPH is not aware of any risk for measles exposure at these locations beyond this period of time."People exposed at any of these locations who are not immune could begin developing early symptoms of measles now," a DPH official said Saturday. "DPH is asking anyone who was at any of these locations during those specific days and times to contact your health care provider if you believe you may have been exposed, if you do not have immunity to measles or if you develop symptoms.""People who were exposed, especially those without immunity through vaccination or previous disease, should monitor for symptoms through Jan. 17. Symptoms typically begin within 7-12 days (but up to 21 days) after exposure, and start with a cough, runny nose, and red eyes, along with a mild to moderate fever.""Two or three days later, the fever spikes, often as high as 104°F. At the same time, a red blotchy rash appears, first on the face and head, then rapidly spreads down the remainder of the body. A person with measles is contagious from four days before the rash appears through four days after its onset, so someone may be able to spread measles before they know they have the disease. It is important to stay home if you are ill.""If anyone who may have been exposed develops an illness with fever (101°F or more), cough, runny nose or red eyes, with or without rash, immediately call a health care provider and let them know about the exposure and symptoms so that they can tell you what to do next. Special arrangements will be needed to evaluate you without putting other patients and medical office staff at risk of exposure. You will be asked to stay at home until the doctor clears you.""The MMR vaccine is the most effective way of protecting oneself against measles. Anyone who is not up to date on MMR vaccination or does not have immunity from prior infection, is encouraged to receive a dose of MMR vaccine, unless there is a medical reason why you cannot receive it. The MMR vaccine is effective and safe. The DPH Recommendations for MMR Vaccination chart can help you understand if you need a dose of the vaccine. The MMR vaccine is available at a pharmacy or provider included on the DPH online vaccine locator or at DPH Health Departments."
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;div class="article-content--body-text"&gt;
						&lt;strong class="dateline"&gt;GREENVILLE, S.C. —&lt;/strong&gt; 													&lt;p&gt;South Carolina Department of Public Health (DPH) has identified three public places someone with measles may have exposed others to the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thoe locations are:&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nose Dive restaurant at 116 S. Main Street, Greenville, S.C. on Dec. 24 from 1:30 to 4:30 pm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Best Buy at 1125 Woodruff Road, Suite 1201, Greenville, S.C. on Dec. 24 from 3 to 6 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Spartanburg County Public Library at 151 at S. Church Street, Spartanburg, S.C. for the Solar Superstorms planetarium show on Dec. 27 from 3:15 to 6:30 p.m. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to DPH, the person did not know they were infectious at the time. DPH is not aware of any risk for measles exposure at these locations beyond this period of time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"People exposed at any of these locations who are not immune could begin developing early symptoms of measles now," a DPH official said Saturday. "DPH is asking anyone who was at any of these locations during those specific days and times to contact your health care provider if you believe you may have been exposed, if you do not have immunity to measles or if you develop symptoms."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"People who were exposed, especially those without immunity through vaccination or previous disease, should monitor for symptoms through Jan. 17. Symptoms typically begin within 7-12 days (but up to 21 days) after exposure, and start with a cough, runny nose, and red eyes, along with a mild to moderate fever."&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;"Two or three days later, the fever spikes, often as high as 104°F. At the same time, a red blotchy rash appears, first on the face and head, then rapidly spreads down the remainder of the body. A person with measles is contagious from four days before the rash appears through four days after its onset, so someone may be able to spread measles before they know they have the disease. It is important to stay home if you are ill."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="cream-inline-rec" class="cream-inline hidden"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"If anyone who may have been exposed develops an illness with fever (101°F or more), cough, runny nose or red eyes, with or without rash, immediately call a health care provider and let them know about the exposure and symptoms so that they can tell you what to do next. Special arrangements will be needed to evaluate you without putting other patients and medical office staff at risk of exposure. You will be asked to stay at home until the doctor clears you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The MMR vaccine is the most effective way of protecting oneself against measles. Anyone who is not up to date on MMR vaccination or does not have immunity from prior infection, is encouraged to receive a dose of MMR vaccine, unless there is a medical reason why you cannot receive it. The MMR vaccine is effective and safe. The &lt;a data-auth="NotApplicable" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://link.mediaoutreach.meltwater.com/ls/click?upn=u001.vYOEavOnxV2T5raErnqLQDNJhUM6JmZ0-2FKbEvFJhTByMyMirWxD6LVl8lFelFff8ASYPTQY1HrqgAtIkslOxA3eOvV99G-2Buk505vBOd5EPyVxK9hfX3qGRU33nIhwJLgBeP6-2FUpl4pQr75mLBLuOMA-3D-3DFg2e_uG4mCQLB9tukhJpN14mws0ZhzFFBDUdd-2F-2FjqRD3zCPIc6VZItOYVEpPELxBBVI52kOOmJaIcGXtH7I9-2FhWWSgULgs1Xa9kbc-2BoQp-2FBjHt8H57hXzUR6KmHQBwnAC58jzX7AijflPCamlePaNsjnrBYOtSHIB6bI7r9oo71VHMANtCIYQgr9JtPx-2BnsKpGWxOhaTQlX-2F-2BvdEJCw-2Bp-2B4vOslB0fFFnZrbPRVJxByIkgRz-2BkWrqGEetseF2HoHtunOfKiczqkt40DDV6YeQsoCN5c4nQsznFFTldWbwlKCBG7-2BEUnGpcFcl7D-2FjkdsnqP84Ii713RcF11YD7wUGqtkwAhnf-2FkKUETFgSx4rSDJbhvm0XeppXblzNl1fLERKHUQd" data-linkindex="0" title="https://link.mediaoutreach.meltwater.com/ls/click?upn=u001.vYOEavOnxV2T5raErnqLQDNJhUM6JmZ0-2FKbEvFJhTByMyMirWxD6LVl8lFelFff8ASYPTQY1HrqgAtIkslOxA3eOvV99G-2Buk505vBOd5EPyVxK9hfX3qGRU33nIhwJLgBeP6-2FUpl4pQr75mLBLuOMA-3D-3DFg2e_uG4mCQLB9tukhJpN14mws0ZhzFFBDUdd-2F-2FjqRD3zCPIc6VZItOYVEpPELxBBVI52kOOmJaIcGXtH7I9-2FhWWSgULgs1Xa9kbc-2BoQp-2FBjHt8H57hXzUR6KmHQBwnAC58jzX7AijflPCamlePaNsjnrBYOtSHIB6bI7r9oo71VHMANtCIYQgr9JtPx-2BnsKpGWxOhaTQlX-2F-2BvdEJCw-2Bp-2B4vOslB0fFFnZrbPRVJxByIkgRz-2BkWrqGEetseF2HoHtunOfKiczqkt40DDV6YeQsoCN5c4nQsznFFTldWbwlKCBG7-2BEUnGpcFcl7D-2FjkdsnqP84Ii713RcF11YD7wUGqtkwAhnf-2FkKUETFgSx4rSDJbhvm0XeppXblzNl1fLERKHUQd"&gt;DPH Recommendations for MMR Vaccination chart&lt;/a&gt; can help you understand if you need a dose of the vaccine. The MMR vaccine is available at a pharmacy or provider included on the DPH &lt;a data-auth="NotApplicable" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://link.mediaoutreach.meltwater.com/ls/click?upn=u001.vYOEavOnxV2T5raErnqLQBPccNkpqKgkcz-2Fho4eknp4kqMKdbQb6AXpyL95j2A7VJ-2BZ53WmokZqDtz-2Br3K2nFQ-3D-3DXwdM_uG4mCQLB9tukhJpN14mws0ZhzFFBDUdd-2F-2FjqRD3zCPIc6VZItOYVEpPELxBBVI52kOOmJaIcGXtH7I9-2FhWWSgULgs1Xa9kbc-2BoQp-2FBjHt8H57hXzUR6KmHQBwnAC58jzX7AijflPCamlePaNsjnrBYOtSHIB6bI7r9oo71VHMANtCIYQgr9JtPx-2BnsKpGWxOhaTQlX-2F-2BvdEJCw-2Bp-2B4vOsn4Tt9WNTdLWpkfM5m3S1K9TfeRNtA8JNRh8ds0V4-2F2uYYvqa-2FLm44dD6tvW6vy2FtXgV55MUwaaruiqfo7-2B0DXpqjUQnmcHgACopNMQDhnEfBMd6tCX55T5O2epMUnJSCG1FCz0fZY0wboAtaqph1E2eypiJGBAzyiQHO3qYEC2" data-linkindex="1" title="https://link.mediaoutreach.meltwater.com/ls/click?upn=u001.vYOEavOnxV2T5raErnqLQBPccNkpqKgkcz-2Fho4eknp4kqMKdbQb6AXpyL95j2A7VJ-2BZ53WmokZqDtz-2Br3K2nFQ-3D-3DXwdM_uG4mCQLB9tukhJpN14mws0ZhzFFBDUdd-2F-2FjqRD3zCPIc6VZItOYVEpPELxBBVI52kOOmJaIcGXtH7I9-2FhWWSgULgs1Xa9kbc-2BoQp-2FBjHt8H57hXzUR6KmHQBwnAC58jzX7AijflPCamlePaNsjnrBYOtSHIB6bI7r9oo71VHMANtCIYQgr9JtPx-2BnsKpGWxOhaTQlX-2F-2BvdEJCw-2Bp-2B4vOsn4Tt9WNTdLWpkfM5m3S1K9TfeRNtA8JNRh8ds0V4-2F2uYYvqa-2FLm44dD6tvW6vy2FtXgV55MUwaaruiqfo7-2B0DXpqjUQnmcHgACopNMQDhnEfBMd6tCX55T5O2epMUnJSCG1FCz0fZY0wboAtaqph1E2eypiJGBAzyiQHO3qYEC2"&gt;online vaccine locator&lt;/a&gt; or at &lt;a data-auth="NotApplicable" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://link.mediaoutreach.meltwater.com/ls/click?upn=u001.vYOEavOnxV2T5raErnqLQJAkGFKecHUg5p47VuEuKxUWTmLT-2BhO5pMXE7-2BCyZzaeC0-2FeS4dkstFKRZgQL5jNNQ-3D-3DR3-y_uG4mCQLB9tukhJpN14mws0ZhzFFBDUdd-2F-2FjqRD3zCPIc6VZItOYVEpPELxBBVI52kOOmJaIcGXtH7I9-2FhWWSgULgs1Xa9kbc-2BoQp-2FBjHt8H57hXzUR6KmHQBwnAC58jzX7AijflPCamlePaNsjnrBYOtSHIB6bI7r9oo71VHMANtCIYQgr9JtPx-2BnsKpGWxOhaTQlX-2F-2BvdEJCw-2Bp-2B4vOsrMV9cFLS2eGH3XIYhEEnDKHRC4KGdb0OLYqH-2BWgxn-2FIVdsbPUnzy2Dx-2Fwfvxc5WetURDq5L8AhLjF0oQzS0hwtM4e6CYUAvr8S-2FF4ggVyPfCVThI8URCWESjqk8SiLqSYyK9p8XHDs9XjIuhAA64S32D9QHaZQrXhQSH6jhB8Ru" data-linkindex="2" title="https://link.mediaoutreach.meltwater.com/ls/click?upn=u001.vYOEavOnxV2T5raErnqLQJAkGFKecHUg5p47VuEuKxUWTmLT-2BhO5pMXE7-2BCyZzaeC0-2FeS4dkstFKRZgQL5jNNQ-3D-3DR3-y_uG4mCQLB9tukhJpN14mws0ZhzFFBDUdd-2F-2FjqRD3zCPIc6VZItOYVEpPELxBBVI52kOOmJaIcGXtH7I9-2FhWWSgULgs1Xa9kbc-2BoQp-2FBjHt8H57hXzUR6KmHQBwnAC58jzX7AijflPCamlePaNsjnrBYOtSHIB6bI7r9oo71VHMANtCIYQgr9JtPx-2BnsKpGWxOhaTQlX-2F-2BvdEJCw-2Bp-2B4vOsrMV9cFLS2eGH3XIYhEEnDKHRC4KGdb0OLYqH-2BWgxn-2FIVdsbPUnzy2Dx-2Fwfvxc5WetURDq5L8AhLjF0oQzS0hwtM4e6CYUAvr8S-2FF4ggVyPfCVThI8URCWESjqk8SiLqSYyK9p8XHDs9XjIuhAA64S32D9QHaZQrXhQSH6jhB8Ru"&gt;DPH Health Departments&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;/p&gt;

							
											&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
						
						
																			

																				&lt;/div&gt;
	
																&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WYFF News 4</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:17:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQcEFXNmNGSGZPWllCd0xlQ1BzdHpWaGtQUGlncnIxV1V0dDQxOS1hMW9LOHduOTVwcXZvSW11WFpHQWZ0aFpPYlp6R0FxV1lDN1hFZU90S0FXcDRpOHoyVmltV29KcFRteGlLRUo5RGtLYmxJeWxWU3JEbWJZYlNpa014MFZkWlNFZ1UtcnEzTzdSM2hpZFVtWkRaN0RMZw</guid></item><item><title>16岁的俄亥俄州青少年死于流感： “这没有道理，”伤心欲绝的家人说-雅虎加拿大新闻</title><link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/ohio-teen-16-dies-flu-153152269.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A 16-year-old from Ohio died from the flu in late December&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ryleigh Spurlock's heartbroken family reacted to the teen's death, saying, "It doesn't make any sense"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ryleigh had not received her flu shot before her death&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;An Ohio teenager has died from the flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ryleigh Spurlock, 16, went to the doctor with “ordinary flu symptoms" on Dec. 23, but her condition quickly worsened, and she died in the hospital on Dec. 28, &lt;a href="https://www.cleveland19.com/2026/01/02/ohio-teen-dies-flu-marking-states-first-pediatric-death-this-season/?utm_source=taboola&amp;amp;utm_medium=organicclicks&amp;amp;tbref=hp" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cleveland 19 News;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Cleveland 19 News&lt;/a&gt; reported, citing Greene County officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“She went from a 98.5 temperature to a 105, she went septic, she had double pneumonia, all within 24 hours, all from the flu, and it doesn’t make sense,” Ryleigh’s stepmother, Brittney, said to the outlet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ryleigh Spurlock/Facebook&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Ryleigh Spurlock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Within hours of arriving at the hospital, Ryleigh was declared brain dead, her family told Cleveland 19 News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“She hadn’t had a pulse for 50 minutes. They were doing chest compressions, but she was brain dead,” Brittany said of Ryleigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The 16-year-old had not received her flu shot before her death, according to Cleveland 19 News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ryleigh’s sister, Kyleigh, recalled the teen's symptoms to Cleveland 19 News, stating that she had been “coughing and choking on her own blood."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When Ryleigh arrived at the hospital, Kyleigh told the outlet that doctors said "she was going to get worse before she got better.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-51.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC);elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC)&lt;/a&gt; recently &lt;a href="https://people.com/flu-deaths-rising-number-of-reported-cases-doubled-in-week-11878190" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:reported;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; that there have been over seven million cases of the flu this season, resulting in an estimated 81,000 hospitalizations and 3,100 deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;PEOPLE has contacted Greene County officials for comment.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/ohio-teen-16-dies-from-the-flu-heartbroken-family-reacts-11878682" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Canada</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:31:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE5iQTZmZ3ozdWFOX3lLRHJaSHVqT0w0UlRtWkthLW02dTM5TEo5TkpQT2Q1ZTNtM3JFNGpVbXlXXzBPeWFrQVhNZnB0dDVYRFlXT0k5WGF2YU9MRXg0bFRZaUNTcDNWX1lWNzFEczdQaw</guid></item><item><title>Fortis Delhi Gastroenterologist分享5个简单的方法来对抗餐后渴望和稳定血糖水平|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fortis-delhi-gastroenterologist-shares-5-easy-hacks-to-fight-post-meal-cravings-and-stabilise-glucose-levels-101767452608988.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/fortis-delhi-gastroenterologist-shares-5-easy-hacks-to-fight-post-meal-cravings-and-stabilise-glucose-levels-101767452608988.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Post-meal cravings are a common experience for individuals of all ages, and a serious cause of concern for those who are counting their calories.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2026/01/03/550x309/pexels-photo-434258_1767453078629_1767453100631.jpeg" alt="We should start our meals with vegetables, i.e., fibres, suggests Dr Vatsya.(Pexel)" title="We should start our meals with vegetables, i.e., fibres, suggests Dr Vatsya.(Pexel)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2026/01/03/550x309/pexels-photo-434258_1767453078629_1767453100631.jpeg" alt="We should start our meals with vegetables, i.e., fibres, suggests Dr Vatsya.(Pexel)" title="We should start our meals with vegetables, i.e., fibres, suggests Dr Vatsya.(Pexel)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;We should start our meals with vegetables, i.e., fibres, suggests Dr Vatsya.(Pexel)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It is often a result of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/diabetologist-says-these-7-dinner-foods-can-cause-a-sudden-spike-in-blood-sugar-levels-sugary-sauces-cereals-and-more-101766406004358.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="blood sugar levels"&gt;blood sugar levels&lt;/a&gt; crashing, and according to Dr Shubham Vatsya, a gastroenterologist and hepatologist at Fortis Hospital, Vasant Kunj, Delhi, it starts with how we eat our meals.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/does-your-heart-skip-beats-cardiologist-explains-real-causes-of-irregular-heartbeats-and-when-it-becomes-concerning-101767451329815.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Does your heart ‘skip’ beats? Cardiologist explains real causes of irregular heartbeats and when it becomes concerning"&gt;Does your heart ‘skip’ beats? Cardiologist explains real causes of irregular heartbeats and when it becomes concerning&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Taking to Instagram on January 3, Dr Vatsya shared five rules that can instantly stabilise glucose levels in our blood.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“When glucose keeps spiking and dropping, the body stays in stress mode, cravings increase, and ageing accelerates silently,” he wrote in the caption. “Simple sequencing, smart pairing, and short movement can keep glucose steady without cutting foods or calories.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Rule 1&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first step to prevent post-meal cravings is to start our meals with &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/aiims-trained-gastroenterologist-explains-different-fibres-warns-choosing-wrong-type-can-cause-more-bloating-101766562775125.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="fibres"&gt;fibres&lt;/a&gt;. “Veggies first, then protein, then fat, and carbs at the end,” stated Dr Vatsya, adding that this simple sequence reduces glucose spikes by 70 percent.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Rule 2&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We should avoid eating sugar on an empty stomach. This results in a sudden glucose spike in the bloodstream and guarantees a sugar crash.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Rule 3&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Always pair carbs with proteins and fats,” noted Dr Vatsya. “This slows down digestion and allows glucose to be steadily released in the bloodstream.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Rule 4&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Vatsya, post-meal movement should be mandatory. Studies have shown that walking for 10-12 minutes after every meal is more effective than a long workout, he claimed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Rule 5&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;By adding one spoonful of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/apple-cider-vinegar-for-weight-loss-nutritionists-guide-on-how-to-use-this-drink-before-bed-101766820243509.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="apple cider vinegar"&gt;apple cider vinegar&lt;/a&gt; to our salad at the start of meals, insulin response becomes smoother, shared Dr Vatsya.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Stopping sugar crashes is not difficult if eating habits and blood glucose are monitored with discipline,” he added.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:24:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAJBVV95cUxQc3RfeFJsUmdWdU5lZ1lYdndnWG52TEppM1lLRlJkbnUyMHRyaS14WVR2UkF2S3RyUjJiMWJDYkdfdVZnUFhXZ0lnSHdaRGRWbXl5blAzbjVUZFNaTWJMUVNmVWVNRy0tcXVJdV9FSjdmV3lyeEV4RlVpYmg5VHdSWkV3c1FRRlFOWnphM2lFeDA1LWR4MWExRnRNMUlZZGw0TlNicXZrMXJmelBfVWJKRDk5MUlrREJEaDBKV3M0S0pUd2J1Tlk3UzhjWEtSSVZWTjdSUUhnblUzV3JKSXdPRTU0WTJ2dTRkYmZDa2t0bEtnRmtEaU9FbkRsbW00dHN0WVoxTzlLd3LSAY4CQVVfeXFMUGxJeTZsdUdockdXUm81cW9reElmSTdYb29OUDFrR3dnRmNNSUdzNnNINTJuc08xc290eFduYmY2VU5VMzNzZDFHQjI0QzV1V1ZWLXdmQnRwcWVjV3FjOTNnQmxuTVpHVXlyVDc4bnVzMXB0cE1yRWlFaWFBZHJseTJTSFBYcVk1RXlMcV85MGZQbE9Ddnphaml4Uk9Ud05uaGpUNUU1OFlqdUczY0RfVFNMWTgzbU1Nb2YxRjlFRVlFSkw4Qnh4cy1CRW9fMm1ub3llT3dHaVdKdG0xTzMySzB6b1l6RjNOV1BYSFpXZWRpdTJ4ejZWWkFHZDlVc3NudXBPZXl6T1hDeC1yd0lR</guid></item><item><title>新研究探讨了与女性手淫习惯相关的因素- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/new-study-explores-factors-linked-to-womens-masturbation-habits/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study indicates that a woman’s knowledge of her own anatomy and her feelings toward her genitals are strong predictors of her solitary sexual behaviors. The research also suggests that women who engage in self-stimulation during adolescence may experience orgasms more frequently with partners later in life. These findings were published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/19317611.2025.2565374" target="_blank"&gt;International Journal of Sexual Health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solitary sexual activity is a normal aspect of human development and is widely practiced. Despite its prevalence, the subject often remains surrounded by silence and social stigma. This is particularly true for women, who have historically faced different social standards regarding sexuality compared to men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous scientific literature has established that masturbation can offer health benefits and improve sexual functioning. However, less is known about the specific psychological and social factors that influence this behavior in women. A lack of open discussion often leads to gaps in information regarding female biology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers Daniela Henriques, Pedro Alexandre Costa, and Ana Carvalheira sought to investigate these dynamics. Henriques is affiliated with the ISPA-University Institute in Lisbon, Portugal. The team aimed to assess how much women understand about their genital anatomy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They also wanted to identify which demographic and personal factors are linked to the frequency of masturbation. Another primary goal was to analyze the connection between early sexual experiences and adult sexual satisfaction. The researchers were particularly interested in how habits formed during teenage years might relate to the ability to reach orgasm with a partner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To gather this data, the scientists designed a web-based survey. They recruited 469 adult women of Portuguese nationality to participate. The participants ranged in age from 18 to 78 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The survey included a specialized questionnaire designed to measure knowledge of female anatomy. This section presented statements about the vulva, vagina, and clitoris. Participants had to identify whether these statements were true or false.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One section of the study assessed “genital self-image.” This concept refers to a woman’s feelings and beliefs regarding her own genitals. The survey asked participants to rate their agreement with statements about their comfort with and perception of their bodies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also collected detailed data on sexual behaviors. They asked about the age at which participants first masturbated. They also inquired about the frequency of this behavior during adolescence and within the past twelve months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results regarding anatomical knowledge revealed substantial gaps in understanding. The data showed that roughly 74 percent of the participants possessed a low or average level of knowledge about female genitalia. Misconceptions were particularly common regarding the clitoris.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The survey included specific questions about the size and shape of the clitoris. For example, it asked if the clitoris is an internal structure shaped like the wings of an airplane. A majority of the women did not identify this as a true statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many participants also held incorrect beliefs about the physical dimensions of the clitoris. Nearly half of the respondents provided incorrect answers regarding its length. These findings highlight a pervasive lack of education regarding the internal structure of the primary organ responsible for female pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these gaps in knowledge, the prevalence of masturbation was high. Approximately 96 percent of the women reported having masturbated at some point in their lives. The average age at which they began this behavior was just over 14 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The frequency of current masturbation varied among the group. The most common frequency reported was once a week. About one-quarter of the active participants selected this option.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers used statistical analysis to determine which factors best predicted how often a woman masturbates. They found that age was a strong predictor. Younger women tended to report higher frequencies of self-stimulation than older women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Place of residence also appeared to play a role. Women living in urban environments reported masturbating more often than those in rural areas. The researchers suggest that urban settings might offer more privacy or exposure to progressive views on sexuality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Relationship status was another determining factor. Single women reported engaging in solitary sexual activity more frequently than those in committed relationships. This finding aligns with the idea that some women use masturbation to replace partnered sex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Religious attendance showed a clear negative association with the behavior. Women who attended religious services more often were less likely to masturbate frequently. This likely reflects the influence of conservative moral teachings regarding autoeroticism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond demographics, the study found a strong link between anatomical knowledge and behavior. Women who scored higher on the anatomy quiz tended to masturbate more often. This suggests that understanding one’s body may facilitate sexual expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A similar pattern emerged regarding genital self-image. Women who felt more positive about the appearance and function of their genitals were more likely to engage in self-stimulation. Comfort with one’s body appears to remove barriers to sexual exploration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also uncovered an association between adolescent behavior and adult sexual response. Women who reported higher frequencies of masturbation during their teenage years experienced orgasms more often during partnered sex as adults. This correlation was observed specifically for orgasms achieved during vaginal penetration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors propose that early self-exploration serves a learning function. Through masturbation, adolescents may discover what types of stimulation they prefer. This self-knowledge can then be transferred to sexual interactions with partners later in life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the relationship between current masturbation and partnered sex showed a different pattern. For adult women, a higher frequency of masturbation was associated with a lower frequency of orgasm during partnered sexual activity. This suggests a compensatory dynamic for some individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This means that for some adult women, masturbation may serve to fill a gap left by unsatisfying partnered encounters. If a woman does not reach orgasm with her partner, she may turn to self-stimulation to achieve sexual release. The data supports both the idea of masturbation as a learning tool and as a compensatory act, depending on the context.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors noted several limitations that should be considered when interpreting these results. The study relied on a convenience sample recruited online. This method may attract participants who are more comfortable discussing sexuality than the general population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sample consisted entirely of cisgender women from Portugal. Cultural and religious specifics of the country may influence the findings. Consequently, the results might not fully apply to women in different cultural or legal environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The survey also relied on self-reported data. This introduces the possibility of recall bias, particularly when participants were asked to remember behaviors from their adolescence. Additionally, the study did not provide a rigid definition of masturbation, leaving it open to participant interpretation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these caveats, the research offers evidence that female masturbation is a multifaceted behavior. It highlights the importance of comprehensive sex education. The authors argue that education should go beyond reproduction to include anatomy and pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Better knowledge of the clitoris and other structures could help destigmatize female sexuality. Promoting a positive genital self-image could also improve sexual well-being. The researchers recommend that future studies investigate these relationships in more diverse populations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They also suggest that clinical interventions for sexual difficulties should consider masturbatory history. Understanding a patient’s comfort with their own body can provide context for treating sexual dysfunction. Ultimately, the study reinforces the idea that solitary sex is an integral part of a woman’s sexual health profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/19317611.2025.2565374" target="_blank"&gt;‘Ménage À Moi’: An Analysis of Factors Associated with Masturbation Among Women&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Daniela Henriques, Pedro Alexandre Costa, and Ana Carvalheira.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:10:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPdWx5ZndEWnd6dGZwaFdlTkUyUDg1MnZuZEs5TDY0NldwN09ycXBIT1RneWdNcFZNM2NsdW8xVkRDaVRDV0lmNlV5dkFZeVdQRVlHeUpOemU4dDlMRzI1UDhXVFdvNE5tSVU4Vnc2SmVBRmNxcEVmeFU5V2NlSFJBVU1OMUpYcjRuMEU3STZpTlpmdw</guid></item><item><title>全球最具传染性的疾病正在美国机场蔓延-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/most-contagious-disease-world-spreading-150000558.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In 2020, &lt;a href="https://www.explore.com/travel/coronavirus-flying-hotels-travel-safety/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:COVID-19 caused travel restrictions and other changes;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;COVID-19 caused travel restrictions and other changes&lt;/a&gt; to how people get around. &lt;a href="https://www.explore.com/travel/avoid-sick-traveling/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Avoiding getting sick while traveling;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Avoiding getting sick while traveling&lt;/a&gt; is tricky, as COVID-19, flu, and common colds easily spread when dozens of people sit shoulder to shoulder inside planes, trains, or buses. However, another disease has added itself to the list. Measles is on the rise, and health officials have detected it in airports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The New Jersey Department of Health sent a &lt;a href="https://www.nj.gov/health/news/2025/approved/20251226a.shtml" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:press release;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; stating that it detected measles in a traveler who was at the Newark Liberty International Airport on December 12, 2025. The department has undertaken contact tracing efforts in case the passenger infected others. Another case appeared in a passenger who flew to and from Boston Logan International Airport (&lt;a href="https://www.explore.com/1855227/oldest-airport-america-us-busiest-country-boston-logan-international-massachusetts/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:one of the busiest in the country;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;one of the busiest in the country&lt;/a&gt;) on December 11 and 12.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The Massachusetts Department of Public Health sent a &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/news/state-public-health-officials-alert-residents-about-potential-exposure-to-measles-in-multiple-locations-0" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:press release;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; of its own. The press release emphasized that measles is preventable through vaccines, making the nationwide rise in cases all the more surprising. Per the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Centers for Disease Control;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Centers for Disease Control&lt;/a&gt;, over 2,000 people in the U.S. tested positive for measles in 2025, numbers not seen since &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/preview/mmwrhtml/00020688.htm" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:1992;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;1992&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read more: &lt;a href="https://www.explore.com/travel/airport-security-secrets-you-need-to-know-gallery/?zsource=yahoo" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Airport Security Secrets You Need To Know;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Airport Security Secrets You Need To Know&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Why the measles resurgence is occurring&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Man in hazmat suit spraying an empty plane - David Silverman/Getty Images&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.gavi.org/vaccineswork/contagion-scale-which-diseases-spread-fastest" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Gavi;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Gavi&lt;/a&gt;, an organization working to increase medical vaccine access worldwide, explained that measles is the most contagious virus based on how many others just one person can infect, a measurement called R0. Like COVID-19 and the flu, measles spreads through particles in the air after someone carrying the disease coughs or sneezes. Its particles also linger in the air for up to two hours, meaning you can catch measles even without direct contact. After around two centuries of documented measles existence, researchers created a vaccine in the 1960s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Vaccine skeptics have long existed around the world, but recent years have seen a higher percentage of parents choosing not to vaccinate their children. Gavi attributes this to vaccine misinformation, the 2020 COVID-19 pandemic, and other global crises. Multiple health officials have publicly tried to ease people's minds by stating that vaccines are safe and effective as long as enough members of a population receive them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Getting measles despite being vaccinated is incredibly uncommon, but all travelers can take solace in the fact that cases are still fairly low nationwide. If you think you might be sick, wearing a mask can prevent you from spreading anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ready to discover more hidden gems and expert travel tips? &lt;a href="https://subscribe.explore.com/newsletter-syndicated?utm_source=yahoo&amp;amp;utm_medium=explore-NL-feed" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Subscribe to our free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Subscribe to our free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for access to the world's best-kept travel secrets. You can also &lt;a href="https://www.google.com/preferences/source?q=explore.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:add us as a preferred search source;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;add us as a preferred search source&lt;/a&gt; on Google.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the &lt;a href="https://www.explore.com/2066592/measles-most-contagious-disease-world-spreading-us-airports/?zsource=yahoo" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:original article on Explore;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;original article on Explore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxNT29RNE9GMnBaRjA5S1FhQTAwa1pzLTJpX3R6aU84cmEyT2Vtb2dWRHF1VHNVazg2RW11QksyZkhiN0ZkQ1FFWnVmbzNuMG9sZHNaVFhIeEs1Zi10cl81cE1uclhkTUFtU3lYZV9Bd1ZPZmZzNkZKcGZ6YS01YzZMQS1WaXRiZWNFbW5HLVVhV29EVmhr</guid></item><item><title>流行的止痛药几乎没有缓解和严重的风险- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/popular-painkiller-offers-little-relief-and-serious-risks/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a long time, one medication has become a quiet default for dealing with chronic pain: tramadol. It’s prescribed in clinics of all sizes and sits in medicine cabinets in homes across the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many doctors have viewed tramadol as a compromise. Stronger than over-the-counter options, yet thought to be easier on the body than other opioids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That reputation helped it spread fast. But a close look at the science tells a less comforting story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-tramadol-in-chronic-pain-care"&gt;Tramadol in chronic pain care&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A large review of existing research took a hard look at how well tramadol actually works for &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/chronic-pain-is-harder-to-treat-in-women-but-a-new-target-offers-hope/"&gt;chronic pain&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers pulled together results from many past studies and compared tramadol to a placebo, a dummy treatment with no active drug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team set out to answer a simple question: Does this medication truly help people feel better, and at what cost?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-tramadol-became-so-common"&gt;Why tramadol became so common&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tramadol is a dual-action opioid that eases pain through more than one mechanism. Doctors commonly prescribe it for moderate to severe pain, both short-term and chronic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because of this, tramadol appears in several &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/mindfulness-meditation-is-a-powerful-weapon-against-chronic-pain/"&gt;pain management&lt;/a&gt; guidelines. Over time, prescriptions climbed sharply, making tramadol one of the most frequently used opioids in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That rise did not happen by accident. Many doctors believed tramadol caused fewer side effects and carried a lower risk of addiction than other short-acting opioids. Patients often felt more comfortable taking it, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-earlier-studies-missed"&gt;What earlier studies missed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tramadol has been studied before, but earlier reviews did not fully answer the big questions. Most focused only on whether the drug reduced pain, not on safety. Others looked at limited types of pain. Important gaps remained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To fill those gaps, the researchers searched medical databases for randomized clinical trials published up to February 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trials compared tramadol with placebo in people living with chronic pain, including &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cannabis-may-ease-cancer-symptoms-like-pain-and-nausea/"&gt;cancer-related pain&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-a-closer-look-at-the-trials"&gt;A closer look at the trials&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final analysis covered 19 clinical trials with 6,506 participants. Five studies looked at nerve pain. Nine focused on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-confirm-the-best-treatments-for-osteoarthritis-are-not-medications/"&gt;osteoarthritis&lt;/a&gt;. Four examined chronic low back pain. One studied &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/fibromyalgia-pain-scientists-may-have-finally-solved-the-mystery/"&gt;fibromyalgia&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The average participant was 58 years old, with ages ranging from 47 to 69. Most studies tested tramadol tablets. Only one looked at a topical cream. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treatment lasted anywhere from 2 to 16 weeks. Follow-up periods ranged from 3 to 15 weeks. That matters because many side effects and long-term risks take time to show up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-small-relief-big-risks"&gt;Small relief, big risks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the researchers looked at all the results together, a clear picture emerged. Tramadol did ease pain, but only a little. The change was too small to meet the usual standards for meaningful relief. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People may have noticed some improvement, but it likely didn’t translate into better day-to-day function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eight of the trials also followed participants for serious side effects over periods ranging from 7 to 16 weeks. In those studies, tramadol was linked to roughly twice the risk of harm compared with a placebo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That higher risk was driven largely by heart-related problems, including chest pain, coronary artery disease, and congestive heart failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tramadol use was also linked to a higher risk of certain cancers, though the researchers noted that the short follow-up made this finding “questionable.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-common-side-effects"&gt;Common side effects &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across all trials, tramadol was tied to more common side effects like nausea, dizziness, constipation, and sleepiness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These issues may sound mild, but they can make daily life harder, especially for older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors also pointed out problems with the studies themselves. Many outcomes were at high risk of bias. That likely means the benefits of tramadol were overstated, while its harms were understated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-opioids-in-the-bigger-picture"&gt;Opioids in the bigger picture&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings land in the middle of a much larger opioid crisis. According to the authors of the study, approximately 60 million individuals worldwide experience the addictive effects of &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/brain-discovery-offers-hope-for-tackling-opioid-addiction/"&gt;opioids&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In 2019, drug use was responsible for approximately 600,000 deaths, with nearly 80% of these fatalities associated with opioids and approximately 25% resulting from opioid overdose,” wrote the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the United States, the number of opioid-related overdose deaths increased from 49,860 in 2019 to 81,806 in 2022.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Given these trends and the present findings, the use of tramadol and other opioids should be minimized to the greatest extent possible.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-pain-relief-that-comes-with-a-price"&gt;Pain relief that comes with a price&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After weighing the evidence, the team summed it up plainly. Tramadol may have a slight effect on reducing chronic pain while likely increasing the risk of both serious and non- serious adverse events. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The potential harms associated with tramadol use for pain management likely outweigh its limited benefits,” noted the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a drug so widely used and often trusted, that conclusion carries a lot of weight. It suggests that tramadol’s place in chronic pain care deserves serious rethinking, not because it does nothing, but because what it offers may simply not be worth the risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The full study was published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://ebm.bmj.com/content/early/2025/09/26/bmjebm-2025-114101"&gt;BMJ Evidence-Based Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:16:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNenZncy02LWllcHFtd1JEUkZoQ1RBblVmMEdiejRzWEUwV0NSX2RnX05qUU1YNG91eFU2bE5Na2p1N25wSkl0LWpsR01lX25STUNaaVhvRWNYNHVkQjBhN3VmQnVuUXJVWnowSDJsNmdrVElfNk9aSzdmdWxtYTdSUGI2QzFVM2tuRFVZWDNn</guid></item><item><title>难以入睡？美国医生揭示了一个简单的基于饮食的黑客，可以促进休息，优质的睡眠|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/struggling-to-fall-asleep-us-doctor-reveals-diet-based-hack-peanut-butter-which-can-promote-restful-quality-sleep-101767447911812.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/struggling-to-fall-asleep-us-doctor-reveals-diet-based-hack-peanut-butter-which-can-promote-restful-quality-sleep-101767447911812.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Struggling to fall asleep or waking up repeatedly through the night can be incredibly frustrating - and reaching for another &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/sleeping-pill-lowers-levels-of-alzheimer-s-proteins-study-101682044544011.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="sleeping pill"&gt;sleeping pill&lt;/a&gt; often feels like the easiest fix. But before turning to medication, there may be simpler, diet-based alternatives worth trying. Certain everyday foods contain nutrients that can naturally calm the &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/mumbai-neurologist-shares-best-brain-hack-to-manage-anxiety-and-calm-your-nervous-system-connect-with-your-body-101763469094420.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="nervous system"&gt;nervous system&lt;/a&gt;, relax the brain and support more restorative sleep, offering a gentler way to improve sleep quality without heavy reliance on pills.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2026/01/03/550x309/peanut_butter_1767448596549_1767448596884.jpeg" alt="The solution to restless nights might be lying inside a jar in your pantry!(Unsplash)" title="The solution to restless nights might be lying inside a jar in your pantry!(Unsplash)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2026/01/03/550x309/peanut_butter_1767448596549_1767448596884.jpeg" alt="The solution to restless nights might be lying inside a jar in your pantry!(Unsplash)" title="The solution to restless nights might be lying inside a jar in your pantry!(Unsplash)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;The solution to restless nights might be lying inside a jar in your pantry!(Unsplash)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read |&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/feeling-stressed-for-no-reason-us-doctor-shares-6-daily-habits-raising-your-cortisol-levels-caffeine-skipped-meals-101767349711212.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Feeling stressed for no reason? US doctor shares 6 daily habits raising your cortisol levels: ‘Caffeine, skipped meals…’"&gt;Feeling stressed for no reason? US doctor shares 6 daily habits raising your cortisol levels: ‘Caffeine, skipped meals…’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Kunal Sood, an anaesthesiologist and interventional pain medicine physician, is breaking down the science-backed benefits of an unlikely food that may help improve sleep quality - &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe/peanut-butter-5-creative-ways-to-add-this-protein-packed-spread-to-your-diet-101764135850151.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="peanut butter"&gt;peanut butter&lt;/a&gt;. In an Instagram video shared on January 3, the physician explains how specific compounds and nutrients in peanut butter work together to calm the mind and support more restful &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/tossing-and-turning-at-night-cant-sleep-psychiatrist-reveals-why-its-a-big-concern-for-your-mental-health-101766669383067.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="sleep"&gt;sleep&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Peanut butter and sleep&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to Dr Sood, there are three key reasons why peanut butter may help you fall asleep - supporting relaxation and promoting deeper, more restful sleep. He outlines the following:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;span&gt;Tryptophan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Sood states that peanut butter contains an amino acid called tryptophan, which supports serotonin production and helps calm the brain, making it easier to relax and drift off to sleep.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; He explains, “Peanut butter contains tryptophan, which is a precursor to serotonin, which can have a calming effect on your brain.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;span&gt;Healthy fats&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Peanut butter also contains healthy fats that help stabilise blood sugar levels, preventing sudden glucose spikes and crashes - a common reason why some people wake up during the night.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; Dr Sood highlights, “It is also high in healthy fats, which can help stabilise your blood sugar. It does this by slowing the absorption of carbohydrates. The reason you wake up at night sometimes is because of the sudden spike and crash of your blood sugar.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;span&gt;Magnesium&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It is also rich in magnesium - a mineral known to relax the nervous system and support deeper, better-quality sleep. The physician explains, “Peanut butter also contains magnesium, which has been shown to also relax you and improve your sleep quality.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;When to have it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Sood recommends consuming peanut butter at least two hours before bedtime to allow the body time to digest it and maximise its sleep-supporting benefits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;He also highlights that peanut butter can be effective for some people, but may not help everyone - but it is a low risk option you can try out to improve sleep.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He states, “If you are going to eat prior to bed it is recommended to eat two hours prior. It is worth noting, while peanut butter may help some people sleep, it is not for everyone.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. It is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:14:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwJBVV95cUxNcEpZWmgxbW1tMGpGSl9ZVWV6dEJvRlFvN3JBTk8wdjVsdjdFcmZvWVhEa3I0REpmazBxUGNPUHRoWVdyRnR5ektRTGRYLVBDczA0SWdtWnhHaXJRNWtFNGNrOF8zdDlwazhnejl6VnZ6TmdmVnVqVnNFek5JS01Hd2JBNUpPa0NveGxRNGx5UjVtMUx4M3BpcmVQWjA3aU03OWtpOGtVUHYyTHZvcW1pWGZzUGdiNnRkNDVvcWF3d3YwUjhUMlBiNWFaYU14WHNhdDBfZ2JxY2RtT2NSaERkYkdXUDBCQ1E0OGYxb2tQUzdQNlBJalpOdkY2dldqWkd2Nkc2ZVRTd2c5YjQ3TW1B0gGUAkFVX3lxTE16cEw4VnJpV0tRc01RbGNIQ0psVUJPT2QtYUZlc0JndW9rX3ZySHlpUEZtUVdPQlFIb1dkQnRPVXZzRDFLVmRkR2hTSFkxTENzdEt4M0hNYl9WNFFhejVQbklEQmdxTHpuZGhZUGJoemsxcTVZd3llYVAwRjVoRy1odjJSQmpjWmtvcnktcVZ6Z3dIRjR1bnBpNUVYRFI4YmhIOWd5RmU5ODk5TUViT243cGhFMmRWekxPS0tZeERiUjRBY1lnZnRCU1g5OHg5QkUwVDdYSjR5N2lXWDlVT01VSUwtaVVtemduRDU3Qnp1U3piRW9aeE9VSVhRUC1RSEZyRFlRQ0Q4WGdIN1FRMkgxd1FmaQ</guid></item><item><title>出生时双手比指尖小的小婴儿在一年后回到家中，并正常发育-好消息网络</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/tiny-baby-born-with-hands-smaller-than-a-fingertip-is-now-home-after-a-year-and-developing-normally/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_227569" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-227569" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-227569" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Preemie-baby-Gabriel-Golden-at-Vanderbilt-NICU-SWNS.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-227569" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Preemie baby Gabriel Golden at Vanderbilt NICU-SWNS&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A premature baby, born so tiny his hand was smaller than his dad’s fingertip, is finally home and healthy after a year in the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gabriel Golden was born weighing one pound in September 2024 after just 22 weeks gestation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He endured nearly a year in the Vanderbilt NICU in Nashville, Tennessee, battling chronic lung disease and multiple infections before his parents Caroline and Garreth were finally able to bring their son home three months ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Little Gabriel still faces respiratory challenges, but is thriving developmentally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was amazing that somehow, even though his finger was so small, I could feel his grip,” said his father Garreth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The strength those tiny fingers held left me speechless.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Caroline started hemorrhaging 14 weeks into the pregnancy, and for a harrowing eight weeks, doctors warned daily that she could miscarry at any moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She recalls bleeding constantly while on bed rest and stuck at home. When at 18 weeks, Caroline’s water broke. The preemie wasn’t considered viable, so the couple waited in limbo until 22 weeks, when Caroline was hospitalized with hopes of buying more time for their son’s development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The medical team presented stark statistics—and the numbers were devastating: a less than five percent survival rate, with greater than 90 percent odds of neurological problems, heart defects, and vision or hearing loss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The biggest thing is that their lungs are barely developed,” Caroline said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At 22 weeks and four days, Caroline went into labor during an emergency situation that put both their lives at risk. Garreth watched helplessly as medical staff rushed his wife to surgery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They’re having her sign paperwork that she could die from the surgery,” recalled Garreth, who spent a lot of time “not knowing what to think or what to do.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Against all odds, Gabriel was able to use the breathing tube and survived.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_227572" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-227572" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-227572" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Gabriel-Golden-is-finally-home-SWNS.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-227572" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Gabriel Golden is finally home -SWNS&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But he still had to battle severe broncho-pulmonary dysplasia—a chronic lung disease that left his lungs scarred and rigid. The couple said goodbye to their son on three separate occasions during his first six weeks of life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AGAINST ALL ODDS&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a title="Guinness Record Holder for Most Premature Baby is Thriving at 1-Year Old–and All Giggles After ‘Zero Odds’ to Live" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/guinness-record-holder-for-most-premature-baby-is-now-thriving-at-one-year-old-and-all-giggles-after-zero-odds-to-live/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Guinness Record Holder for Most Premature Baby is Thriving at 1-Year Old–and All Giggles After ‘Zero Odds’ to Live&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Multiple pneumonia infections also set him back, and doctors eventually determined he would need a tracheostomy to survive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Throughout the ordeal, Garreth traveled three hours each way to his job, continuing to work so they could pay their bills and Caroline tried to maintain a bedside vigil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their church community provided financial support, and four primary nurses at Vanderbilt became like family during Gabriel’s extended stay. “We couldn’t have done it without them,” Caroline said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One nurse specifically was with us for nine and a half months. I personally couldn’t have done it without her.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_227571" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-227571" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-227571" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Gabriel-Golden-family-at-Vanderbilt-NICU-SWNS.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-227571" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Gabriel Golden family at Vanderbilt NICU-SWNS&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Caroline, who had always dreamed of being a mother, says the experience transformed the couple’s faith and perspective on life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was thrust into a situation where my faith was the only thing I had to cling to. Now it’s stronger than I ever thought it could be.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GOOD NEWS BABIES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
• &lt;a title="Preemie Twins Given ‘No Chance’ of Survival Now Thriving Thanks to Revolutionary Co-Sleeping Cot" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/preemie-twins-given-no-chance-of-survival-now-thriving-thanks-to-revolutionary-co-sleeping-cot-that-promotes-bonding/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Preemie Twins Given ‘No Chance’ Now Thriving Thanks to Revolutionary Co-Sleeping Cot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
• &lt;a title="Baby Thriving After Doctors Removed Womb for Spinal Surgery–Then Put it Back Inside Mom at 26 Weeks" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/baby-thriving-after-doctors-removed-womb-for-spinal-surgery-then-put-it-back-inside-mom/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Doctors Removed Womb for Spinal Surgery–Then Put it Back Inside Mom at 26 Weeks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
• &lt;a title="British Woman Gives Birth After Receiving Transplant Womb from Sister and Pro Bono Surgery at Hospital" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/british-woman-gives-birth-after-receiving-transplant-womb-from-sister-and-pro-bono-surgery-at-hospital/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Woman Gives Birth After Receiving Transplant Womb from Sister–and Pro Bono Surgery at Hospital&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While Gabriel is home, he still requires a tracheostomy and faces respiratory challenges, but there’s good news, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“By the grace of God, Gabriel is completely developmentally appropriate, and has no brain issues,” Caroline told SWNS news agency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Other than his lungs, his body is in wonderful working condition.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The experience gave Garreth a new perspective when he walked through the children’s hospital and saw other families facing their own battles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“As complex as Gabriel is—and as precious as his life is—you walk into Vanderbilt’s Children’s Hospital, and it hits you like a wave of gratitude when you see some of the things going on with these children.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GIVE PREEMIE FAMILIES HOPE By Sharing This on Social Media…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:00:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizAFBVV95cUxNWnRrQUtDcHRXSmpsS3dtMU8xd0lTRkRDUkhXcWJqV0NyeldQMkg0ZWIwYnM3Y3luM1ktNmZPTWszS1NxQ2pERDhoV0tnUjJYTVFpV19YT2JDYk9XU01EZFA5TTFZR05QUTRmMzBQcUxuMVpGSlB3RGN5SmFjQXp2cW80SGJCTTVxR2hRYW5GQlFMYVllbUYyNlhQMDhtN0lFTlJvWEVMZXduREhfMmxDSTlTUEI1UG5sVWRMYWZFZExmZXJNaXBEcVQxOXU</guid></item><item><title>硅谷对JoyScore的追求-旧金山标准</title><link>https://sfstandard.com/2026/01/03/welcome-joyspan-hot-new-trend-longevity/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-grid article-content"&gt;&lt;div class="floats"&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;Luke Sequeira, a self-described nomadic autodidact, spent five days in early December preparing for an unusual rave. The protocols was strict: no psychedelics or other substances for 72 hours prior, no alcohol for 48 hours prior, no caffeine for at least six hours. In two mobile apps, he logged his mood, sleep quality, energy, sense of connectedness, and food and water intake. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;The 40-year-old headed to &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://sfstandard.com/2025/05/18/first-look-frontier-tower-san-francisco-vertical-village/" data-post-id="06cf79cc-deb7-4a51-b80c-5882d58fcf9a"&gt;Frontier Tower&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; on Market Street for the main event Dec. 9. His fingers were pricked and four blood samples taken to measure levels of GDF15, a stress-related biomarker, and cytokines, immune proteins that signal inflammation. Saliva was collected to track his cortisol and oxytocin, and a $195 electroencephalogram &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.awear.us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;wearable&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; was clipped to his ear to record his brain waves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;Finally, Sequeira and 12 other rigged-up participants headed to the dance floor, where a DJ played five techno tracks. The playlist was designed for the occasion by sound engineers, with each track lasting a precise length (eight to 12 minutes) with varying intensity measured in beats per minute. The dancers mostly bobbed on one spot; big moves were discouraged, lest the EEG sensor detach. After almost three hours, the rave was over. Sequeira, along with the others, had his blood and saliva retested before he left.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="mx-auto relative select-text break-words my-7 outline-none  grid-wide"&gt;&lt;div class="ColumnGroupBlock_container__DWhYM ColumnGroupBlock_stackOnMobile__EH9gN"&gt;&lt;p class="md:px-md max-w-full ColumnBlock_ColumnOverride__XqgIq "&gt;&lt;figure class="relative m-[0_0_1em] w-full"&gt;&lt;video class="w-full" src="https://assets.sfstandard.com/asset/994911177489/video_gqek6t1i5p7218r2qujnmc2r2c/?content-disposition=inline" autoplay="" loop="" muted="" playsinline=""&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;figcaption class="basis-full mt-[10px] text-xs text-gray-550 font-inter leading-[18px] "&gt;Joyspan is important to longevity but has the fewest metrics attached; there’s no Oura ring for belonging or Eight Sleep score for joy. 
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="md:px-md max-w-full ColumnBlock_ColumnOverride__XqgIq "&gt;&lt;figure class="relative m-[0_0_1em] w-full"&gt;&lt;video class="w-full" src="https://assets.sfstandard.com/asset/994911177489/video_3lb1n8nre50l12nig7538m9h76/?content-disposition=inline" autoplay="" loop="" muted="" playsinline=""&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;figcaption class="basis-full mt-[10px] text-xs text-gray-550 font-inter leading-[18px] "&gt;“It was more of a science experiment than the rave of my life,” said Karim Asry.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="floats"&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;The event was the &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://luma.com/longevity-rave-part-2" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Longevity Rave&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;, part of a project called the JoyScore Experiment. The project is the brainchild of Tina Woods, CEO of &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.colliderhealth.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Collider Health&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;, which has advised the U.K.’s National Innovation Centre for Ageing on longevity research and AI initiatives for the National Health Service. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though not a full-fledged clinical trial, the JoyScore Experiment is ambitious. If dance and music create feelings of joy and connection, could that be measured through biometric signals from brain activity, heart rhythms, or biomarkers like oxytocin and cortisol? Could that data then be converted into a “JoyScore,” providing a metric for induced happiness? “If you can measure it, then you can put a value to it [and] deliver increases in your health,” said Woods. “That’s a really big opportunity. Dancing tends to promote human joy. We’re trying to put science-backed rigor behind that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;That said, happiness is notoriously subjective and difficult to measure: How happy? For how long? And how often? This fuzziness, though, makes happiness the latest target for quantification. If we can put numbers to it, the thinking goes, perhaps we can optimize it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="mx-auto relative select-text break-words my-7 outline-none  grid-full"&gt;&lt;div class="ColumnGroupBlock_container__DWhYM ColumnGroupBlock_stackOnMobile__EH9gN"&gt;&lt;div class="md:px-md max-w-full ColumnBlock_ColumnOverride__XqgIq "&gt;&lt;figure class="ImageBlock_ImageFigure__ZnquR  inset-image mobile-grid-full mobile-grid-full" data-align="none"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="basis-full mt-[10px] text-xs text-gray-550 font-inter leading-[18px] "&gt;Josh Miller gives a saliva sample.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="md:px-md max-w-full ColumnBlock_ColumnOverride__XqgIq "&gt;&lt;figure class="relative m-[0_0_1em] w-full"&gt;&lt;video class="w-full" src="https://assets.sfstandard.com/asset/994911177489/video_ir1m5na5295ulahoe7u1lv541d/?content-disposition=inline" autoplay="" loop="" muted="" playsinline=""&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;figcaption class="basis-full mt-[10px] text-xs text-gray-550 font-inter leading-[18px] "&gt;Blood draw first, dance floor second, at the Longevity Rave.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="md:px-md max-w-full ColumnBlock_ColumnOverride__XqgIq "&gt;&lt;figure class="ImageBlock_ImageFigure__ZnquR  inset-image mobile-grid-full mobile-grid-full" data-align="none"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="basis-full mt-[10px] text-xs text-gray-550 font-inter leading-[18px] "&gt;Tracking joy, one techno track at a time.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="floats"&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;Attempts to quantify happiness date back to 1789, when the English philosopher &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.econlib.org/library/Bentham/bnthPML.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Jeremy Bentham&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; outlined a formula for measurement that factored in intensity, duration, and frequency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;By the mid 20th century, the research had moved from philosophy to psychology, with social scientists designing self-reporting tools that attempted to distinguish between immediate joy and a sustained state of happiness. These include the &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.gallup.com/poll/122453/understanding-gallup-uses-cantril-scale.aspx?" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Cantril Self-Anchoring Striving Scale&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; in 1965 (used by the U.N.-sponsored World Happiness Report and &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.worldhappiness.report/about/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;by Gallup&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; to track overall satisfaction) and, four years later, the Bradburn Affect Balance Scale, a multiple-choice scale that measures happiness as the balance of positive versus negative feelings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;Biologists, meanwhile, have attempted to measure happiness by tracking various signals and metrics, including &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9866883/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;heart rate variability&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;, &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2105.15029" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;mood&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; and &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hitachi-hightech.com/file/global/pdf/about/corporate/corp_archives/hitachireview/2015_64_no08_3.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;movement,&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; and blood and saliva biomarkers, and through the use of positron emission tomography (&lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6596504/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;PET)&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; scans to observe endorphin release during laughter. The common goal of the grab bag of approaches is to transform our somewhat squishy feelings of joy and happiness into something that can be detected and tracked with precision, physiologically. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;There has been some progress. Studies have found that people who self-report high levels of joy often have higher HRV, &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/15840727/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;lower&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/16213629/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;salivary cortisol &lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;and &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4258510/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;less inflammation.&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; But it’s also apparent that happiness cannot be forced; the very act of chasing happiness can &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/21517168/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;paradoxically&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; lead to unhappiness, since people start to obsess. Sample sizes in these studies have been typically small. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="flex flex-col p-md xl:px-lg bg-warm-gray-50 border border-warm-gray-200 rounded-xl" data-count="1"&gt;&lt;p class="border-t border-warm-gray-200 my-md"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="flex flex-col gap-y-xxs"&gt;&lt;div class="flex flex-row justify-between gap-x-sm"&gt;&lt;div class="flex flex-col gap-y-xs items-start"&gt;&lt;div class="relative"&gt;&lt;button type="button" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-expanded="false" aria-controls=":R4qmep6536:" class="button button-blue button-xxs text-sm text-semibold flex flex-row gap-x-xs items-center"&gt;Listen &lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 24 24"&gt;&lt;path fill="none" stroke="currentColor" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round" stroke-width="2" d="M17 7 7 17M8 7h9v9"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;div id=":R4qmep6536:" role="dialog" aria-hidden="true" hidden="" aria-labelledby=":R4qmep6536H1:" class="z-[1001] p-lg bg-white fixed md:absolute motion-safe:transition-all motion-safe:duration-300 md:motion-safe:duration-150 bottom-0 md:-bottom-xxs w-full md:w-[393px] flex-col gap-md shadow-default rounded-t-[40px] md:rounded-2xl hidden translate-y-full md:translate-y-none opacity-0 pointer-events-none md:scale-75 left-0"&gt;&lt;div class="flex items-center justify-between gap-md"&gt;&lt;h1 id=":R4qmep6536H1:" class="font-bold text-text-primary"&gt;Select Your Platform&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;button type="button"&gt;&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt;Close&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 20 20" fill="white" role="presentation" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M10 0C4.42857 0 0 4.42857 0 10C0 15.5714 4.42857 20 10 20C15.5714 20 20 15.5714 20 10C20 4.42857 15.5714 0 10 0ZM13.8571 15L10 11.1429L6.14286 15L5 13.8571L8.85714 10L5 6.14286L6.14286 5L10 8.85714L13.8571 5L15 6.14286L11.1429 10L15 13.8571L13.8571 15Z" fill="black"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="fixed top-0 bottom-0 left-0 right-0 transition-opacity bg-warm-gray-900 md:bg-transparent -z-50 opacity-0 pointer-events-none"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a href="https://sfstandard.com/pacific-standard-time/2025/12/10/wearable-ai-accessories/" class="block w-[100px] h-[100px] min-w-[100px] min-h-[100px] can-hover:hover:opacity-80" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;img alt="A person holds a round white object with their thumb and forefinger, with a colorful, partially torn overlay highlighting the hand's shape." loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" class="object-cover object-center rounded-lg h-full w-full !aspect-square lazyloaded" sizes="300px" srcset="https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S80x53-FPNG 80w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S120x80-FPNG 120w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S240x160-FPNG 240w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S350x233-FPNG 350w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S450x300-FPNG 450w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S512x341-FPNG 512w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S640x427-FPNG 640w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S750x500-FPNG 750w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S768x512-FPNG 768w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S828x552-FPNG 828w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S1024x683-FPNG 1024w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S1080x720-FPNG 1080w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S1200x800-FPNG 1200w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S1920x1280-FPNG 1920w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S2048x1365-FPNG 2048w, https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S3840x2560-FPNG 3840w" src="https://assets.sfstandard.com/image/994911177489/image_ershijg1jh0br6gueo9cm4da37/-C100.00%25x100.00%25%2C0.00%25%2C0.00%25-S3840x2560-FPNG"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="floats"&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;Suzanne Dikker, a neuroscientist and NYU professor who studies brain synchrony, noted that “it is very hard to infer directly from an [EEG] signal that people are indeed happy or not.” Dikker, who wasn’t involved in the JoyScore Experiment, also notes that correlation isn’t causation. “What you can do is show that a neural marker is correlated with people’s self-report of happiness or joy,” she said. “But you have to make sure it doesn’t co-vary with something else you didn’t intend to measure.”  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;Whether a readout of blood, saliva, and brain waves, coupled with self-reports, can lead to a joy metric is TBD, according to experts. “There’s no thermometer for happiness,” said Sonja Lyubomirsky, a psychology professor and happiness science researcher at UC Riverside. “I’m skeptical that you can measure something directly with a physiological or biological measure.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;Some physiological signals, including EEG patterns and cortisol and blood biomarkers, do correlate with happiness, she noted, “but not very highly.” Someone could be ecstatic, but that might not move any markers, due to cortisol levels or other “noise” in the body, Lyubomirsky added. “It’s a very, very messy, imperfect measure of happiness.”  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;One reason longevity seekers are focused on quantifying joy is the loneliness epidemic, which was deemed  a public health crisis in a 2023 &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/sites/default/files/surgeon-general-social-connection-advisory.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;report&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; by Dr. Vivek Murthy, the U.S. surgeon general at the time. According to the advisory, loneliness increases the risk of premature death by 26%, making social isolation comparable to smoking 15 cigarettes a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;For the tech crowd, loneliness stands as just another problem to solve, one potentially made worse by AI. In her study proposal, Woods argued that “in an age of AI‑driven techno‑isolation, we position raves as counter‑technology that restores human connection and preserves what makes us human.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="ImageBlock_ImageFigure__ZnquR grid-wide inset-image mobile-grid-full mobile-grid-full" data-align="wide"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="basis-full mt-[10px] text-xs text-gray-550 font-inter leading-[18px] "&gt;An ear-mounted EEG records brain activity as techno pulses through the room.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="floats"&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;“The holy grail of longevity science is to develop interventions that actually have application to you as an individual,” Woods added later. Prior research has failed to produce a universal joy score, but they didn’t have today’s tool kit, Woods said, noting developments in how “blood samples are collected, what can be measured, [with] labs developing new techniques all the time.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;This appealed to Sequeira, who, in addition to attending the rave, is conducting solo research on AI and well-being. “A joy score will create more awareness that joy is a factor to work toward, because what we don’t measure, we cannot manage,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="floats"&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;That notion — that anything worth caring about should be quantified — has long been axiomatic in Silicon Valley. It’s especially true in the longevity space, where tracking fundamentals like diet, sleep, and exercise is viewed as a baseline for extending both lifespan (years spent alive) and healthspan (the duration of life spent in good health).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;Those twin concepts have been joined of late by “joyspan,” a way to measure time with optimal social health. The term was coined last year by gerontologist Dr. Kerry Burnight as a shorthand for how relationships can extend &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/30-06-2025-social-connection-linked-to-improved-heath-and-reduced-risk-of-early-death" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;life and lower health risks&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;. Of the three “-span” concepts, joyspan has the fewest metrics attached; there’s no Oura ring for belonging or Eight Sleep score for joy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;The joyspan concept has growing support from experts. The quantification of flourishing “gives us a way to ground what can feel like abstract ideas, like joy, purpose, and connection, into something we can measure, track, and ultimately improve,” said Keith Comito, CEO of the &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="http://lifespan.io" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Lifespan Research Institute,&lt;span class="sr-only"&gt; (opens in new tab)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; a Mountain View nonprofit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;That’s why Karim Asry, 43, was at the Longevity Rave. The director of Espacio Open, a maker space in Bilbao, Spain, Asry spends half his time in San Francisco. He has long sought “actionable metrics” for his own happiness, and the rave promised to be at the forefront of developing those targets. Participants would be classic early adopters, helping to build “a new scientific metric of human joy and connection, using cutting-edge neuroscience and movement data,” according to the event flyer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;Still, Asry wasn’t convinced these specific markers would hold up. “How do you get metrics that are rigorous without oversimplifying the human experience to two to three KPIs?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;Asry, wearing the de facto rave uniform of a tee, jeans, and a hoodie, left feeling hopeful, if less elated than he feels after most raves. “It was more of a science experiment than the rave of my life,” he said. An app connected to the EEG sensor behind his ear allowed him to watch his brain waves seesaw in real time. “If I started reading something, it would go into a very calm state,” he said. But whether those fluctuations corresponded to joy was less clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;Sequeira also geeked out on the data during the event. “Every time the track changed, the [app showed] there was stress in my system — for a few minutes — and then my system came back to baseline,” he said.“The big takeaway for me is that sudden change results in stress. I’m rethinking what kind of music I listen to and how I go about listening to that.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;In the end, the experiment had some wins and some misses. Initially, the JoyScore team hoped to measure synchrony, a shared sense of rhythm and connection, among the attendees. But due to the slim turnout and some technical glitches with the EEG wearables, the synchrony measurement was dropped in order to focus on measuring individual happiness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;“The main thing is that we had enough people to actually give us some meaningful information for the next stage of the study,” said Woods, who is planning an Institutional Review Board-approved &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="https://sfstandard.com/2025/06/20/overseas-stem-cell-tourism/" data-post-id="91c9a121-22e0-4c17-8057-57702b626215"&gt;study this spring in a “network state”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;  in Roatan, Honduras, to test this formally. “This is a real punt into unknown territory,” she added, “but you have to experiment to get the data.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="mx-auto relative select-text break-words my-7 outline-none  grid-full"&gt;&lt;div class="ColumnGroupBlock_container__DWhYM ColumnGroupBlock_stackOnMobile__EH9gN"&gt;&lt;p class="md:px-md max-w-full ColumnBlock_ColumnOverride__XqgIq "&gt;&lt;figure class="relative m-[0_0_1em] w-full"&gt;&lt;video class="w-full" src="https://assets.sfstandard.com/asset/994911177489/video_la77qjvool1t3ead7m8l00l95l/?content-disposition=inline" autoplay="" loop="" muted="" playsinline=""&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;figcaption class="basis-full mt-[10px] text-xs text-gray-550 font-inter leading-[18px] "&gt;The future of longevity might look less like a lab and more like a rave.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="md:px-md max-w-full ColumnBlock_ColumnOverride__XqgIq "&gt;&lt;figure class="relative m-[0_0_1em] w-full"&gt;&lt;video class="w-full" src="https://assets.sfstandard.com/asset/994911177489/video_tghocg855l2834bhgt1pvjvk4g/?content-disposition=inline" autoplay="" loop="" muted="" playsinline=""&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;figcaption class="basis-full mt-[10px] text-xs text-gray-550 font-inter leading-[18px] "&gt;Ravers’ bodies become the data set.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="floats"&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;As for the rave, the participants’ neural activity data was time-stamped to specific music tracks and will be compared against their baseline data (pulled from a “control” rave held five days prior). Blood and saliva samples will be analyzed for biomarkers linked to inflammation and mitochondrial stress, then modeled alongside self-reports to see whether subjective spikes in joy can be mapped to bona-fide physiological changes. The analysis is expected by late spring. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;Even with the nebulous outcome, Lyubomirsky, the happiness researcher, said such studies matter. “Happier people are more likely to recover from surgery, they are less likely to have heart disease or cancer, have less pain, are less likely to get colds,” she said. “Happier people basically live longer.” Still, she cautioned against drawing firm conclusions. “I’m not sure that you could say this biological outcome, when it’s higher, means that you’re happier. … No one’s really been able to show that yet. Maybe in the future, but we’re just not there yet.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph-block article-body undefined text-left"&gt;Regardless of the scientific challenges, some ravers were just glad to be there. Serabeth Mullaney, 29, who lives in the Mission and works at a startup, left feeling upbeat. “I’ve always been really interested in neurology and how our brains affect our mood,” she said. And anyway, she added, “it’s hard to find people that are also passionate about the same things as you.” ”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The San Francisco Standard</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE5EVzkteV9YYzVXMXMwZ1luWkYzS0V6ODIzTzZvNmIxb2FrRDdiU1pTdlZJekphNjlOS3FLcGQtQi1XZm5UUEhvdnNWTld1Mm94amhfTXNndV9GSGJIel9RUi1FY2tEdEhkTGVtMW0weGZJclJfc3A4VjVCRm1fUnc</guid></item><item><title>据营养师称， 1月份有8种地中海饮食食品可供储备- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/mediterranean-diet-foods-to-stock-up-on-in-january-11875520</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Mediterranean diet gets top marks for supporting diabetes management, and heart, gut and mental health. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stock up on canned fish, beans and tomatoes, olive oil, nuts, kefir and frozen greens. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Enjoy these staple Mediterranean foods in smoothies, salads, pasta dishes, snacks or grain bowls. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In 2025, U.S. News &amp;amp; World Report rated &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-and-worst-diets-2025-8767671" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;the Mediterranean diet as the No. 1 diet&lt;/a&gt; for the eighth year in a row. Not only did it win best overall diet, it also won the top spot for managing diabetes, fatty liver disease and high cholesterol, supporting gut health and mental health, and got top marks for being easiest to follow.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This popular diet centers on plant foods including whole grains, fruits, vegetables, legumes, nuts, seeds, olive oil, herbs and spices. Fish is included a couple of times per week, while other proteins like meat, poultry, eggs and dairy are also included. It limits refined grains and added sugars.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you, like many people, are looking to refresh your health goals as we enter a new year, a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/longform/8046714/a-new-mediterranean-diet/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Mediterranean-inspired diet&lt;/a&gt; may be worth trying. Even if you don’t overhaul your whole eating pattern (let’s be real, that’s probably not realistic to do overnight, anyway), incorporating more fruits, vegetables, whole grains and fish into your days could have &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8050356/brain-benefits-mediterranean-diet/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;real health benefits&lt;/a&gt;. In this article, learn eight Mediterranean diet foods dietitians recommend stocking up on in January.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-canned-pulses"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Canned Pulses &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_1-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexandra Shytsman&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; After speaking with more than a dozen dietitians for this story, pulses were by far the most frequently recommended food. Pulses include beans, chickpeas and lentils. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Pulses are a top source of protein in the Mediterranean diet and an easy way to add more plant protein and fiber to your diet,” says &lt;a href="https://cravingsomethinghealthy.com/about/about-anne-danahy-nutritionist/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Anne Danahy, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;. They’re also a great way to &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7920421/what-is-iron-why-do-you-need-it/" class="pseudoStyle" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;get in iron&lt;/a&gt; if you’re cutting back on meat.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Thanks to their fiber, resistant starch, protein and micronutrients, “Pulses have several health benefits, including helping to stabilize blood sugar, optimizing heart health by lowering cholesterol, and supporting gut health,” says &lt;a href="https://www.coachsimranmd.com/about.html" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Simran Malhotra, M.D., DipABLM, CHWC&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://provider.faynutrition.com/book/sarah-nash/6ccedc" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Sarah Nash, M.S., RD, LDN&lt;/a&gt;, adds, “Lentils cook quickly, making them ideal for soups or salads, while canned chickpeas are versatile for grain bowls or roasting as a crunchy snack.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-artichokes"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Artichokes &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_2-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexandra Shytsman&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7961966/health-benefits-of-artichokes-according-to-a-dietitian/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Artichokes are high in prebiotic fiber&lt;/a&gt;, which acts as food for the good bacteria in your gut. Plus, they’re a good source of vitamins and minerals including magnesium, potassium, vitamin C, iron, copper and manganese.&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; You don’t have to go through the process of preparing fresh artichokes to reap the benefits of this vegetable. “Frozen or canned artichokes provide a convenient and easy source of fiber to add to pasta dishes, grain bowls or even protein dishes,” says &lt;a href="https://bebalancednutritionrd.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Meggie Connelly, M.S., RDN, LDN&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-canned-sardines"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Canned Sardines &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_3-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexandra Shytsman&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8058717/reasons-to-eat-canned-fish-according-to-a-dietitian/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Buying canned fish&lt;/a&gt; makes it so much easier to incorporate it into your week, whether it be for a snack, lunch or dinner. Fatty fish like &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8059288/are-canned-sardines-healthy/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;canned sardines are particularly beneficial&lt;/a&gt; because they’re rich in &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8076136/best-nutrient-for-lower-inflammation/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;omega-3 fatty acids&lt;/a&gt; and calcium. “Omega-3 fatty acids help to reduce inflammation and improve immune system function, heart health, skin health and brain health,” says &lt;a href="http://www.ginajonesnutrition.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="4" rel="nofollow"&gt;Gina Jones, M.S., RDN, LDN&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Not only are they a lean source of protein and rich in omega-3s, but sardines provide 38% of our calcium needs and a whopping 70% of our daily &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7950001/signs-you-might-have-a-vitamin-d-deficiency/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;vitamin D&lt;/a&gt; needs in just one serving,” says &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/mandy-enright-11733852" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Mandy Enright, M.S., RDN, RYT&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Plus, canned sardines are incredibly versatile. “You can make delicious sardine cakes or use them in a sardine salad, just like you would with tuna, but with all the benefits of sardines,” says &lt;a href="https://www.helpfuldietitian.com/about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Jessica Wilson, M.S., RD&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-frozen-greens"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Frozen Greens &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_4-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexandra Shytsman&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you can’t seem to use your fresh greens before they go bad or they are too costly for your budget, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/the-best-anti-inflammatory-frozen-veggies-8723520" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;buy them frozen&lt;/a&gt;! “Stocking up on frozen vegetables is a great way to make quick side dishes,” says Jones. Just because they’re frozen doesn’t mean they’re any less nutritious. They’re still a good source of fiber, vitamin K, vitamin C and iron. &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7891357/the-best-vegetables-for-gut-health/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Eating leafy greens&lt;/a&gt; like spinach and kale regularly can lower your risk of heart disease, certain types of cancer, osteoporosis and digestive illness. They’re also beneficial for managing diabetes.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-kefir"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Kefir &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_5-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexandra Shytsman&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Dairy is included in the Mediterranean diet. While Greek-style yogurt and feta cheese (which are also great options) may be the first dairy foods that come to mind, don’t overlook &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7664397/what-is-kefir/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;kefir&lt;/a&gt;. It’s a fermented milk product that’s enjoyed like drinkable yogurt.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Kefir is packed with probiotics to enrich the beneficial bacteria that make up your gut microbiota,” explains Danahy. Research shows that kefir can also improve blood pressure, inflammation and fasting blood sugars in people with metabolic disorders.&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; It’s also a source of high-quality protein. Danahy suggests using it in smoothies, salad dressings or to top your oatmeal.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-nuts"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Nuts &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_6-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexandra Shytsman&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8027688/are-nuts-good-for-you/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Nuts&lt;/a&gt; are some of the most nutrient-dense and versatile foods you can keep in your pantry, and whichever kinds you like best are worth incorporating into your day.&lt;span data-cite="5" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Nuts provide fiber, healthy fat, protein and antioxidants. For example, Brazil nuts help to support thyroid health, and walnuts have omega-3s that support brain health and reduce inflammation,” says Jones. Eating more nuts is linked with reduced risk of heart disease, cancer, hypertension and all-cause mortality.&lt;span data-cite="5" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; They can be eaten on their own, added to oatmeal, yogurt and even salads. Or for a dinner packed with omega-3s, try this &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/267223/walnut-rosemary-crusted-salmon/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Walnut-Rosemary Crusted Salmon&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-olive-oil"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Olive Oil &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_7-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexandra Shytsman&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; We can’t talk about the Mediterranean diet without talking about &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/is-olive-oil-good-for-you-8766002" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;olive oil&lt;/a&gt;. In fact, it sits at the base of the Mediterranean diet pyramid as a fat source to center every meal around.&lt;span data-cite="6" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Olive oil is rich in monounsaturated fats, which are the good healthy fats, and antioxidants. It helps to absorb fat-soluble vitamins and reduce inflammation,” says Jones. In fact, one study found that eating just ½ tablespoon (1½ teaspoons) of olive oil per day is linked with 19% lower risk of dying from cardiovascular disease, 17% lower risk of dying from cancer, and 29% lower risk of dying from a neurodegenerative disease.&lt;span data-cite="7" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-tomatoes"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Tomatoes &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_8-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexandra Shytsman&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Whether you prefer them fresh, jarred, canned or boxed, it’s worth keeping &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/are-tomatoes-good-for-you-8636976" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;tomatoes&lt;/a&gt; on hand. “Tomatoes are packed with nutrients and antioxidants like vitamins A and C. They’re an essential base for sauces, soups and pastas, offering rich flavors and anti-inflammatory benefits,” says Jones.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Both raw and cooked, tomatoes are a popular food in the Mediterranean region. Studies show that eating tomatoes can help prevent chronic diseases like cardiovascular disease and cancer because of their rich antioxidant content. Fun fact: Olive oil may help your body better absorb the main antioxidant in tomatoes, lycopene&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span data-cite="8" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_63-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_67-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Making dietary changes for your health doesn’t have to mean overhauling your whole diet overnight. By stocking up on just a few Mediterranean diet foods, you can start to add more nutrition to your days. Nuts are a great snack, canned legumes make a great base for an easy lunch, and olive oil can be used in just about any meal.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxQRjAtcnpEN21TMTlZTll0T0ZyYl90SW1yaE5qeHAzSFJyQnNNYjVlemdTV1R5bmFhcnM5NXBKU0cxcWhPZDA1dzZwcExpSU1NOEhtTU1JZ2xvbW45VnB2cWE3QldyZkRHZjlMYzRKRW11S2JQdkJVaFMxNlJiMXl6YU1hb2FlTm56YUpzbVFDaw</guid></item><item><title>宾夕法尼亚州报告高住院率导致22例流感相关死亡- WTAE</title><link>https://www.wtae.com/article/pennsylvania-reports-22-flu-related-deaths-amid-high-hospitalization-rates/69906110</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content--body-inner"&gt;
										&lt;div class="mobile"&gt;
													



																		&lt;div class="mobile"&gt;
							

&lt;section class="article-headline"&gt;
	
			&lt;p class="article-headline--title"&gt;Pennsylvania reports 22 flu-related deaths amid high hospitalization rates&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;div class="article-headline--subheadline"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials urging vaccinations and preventive measures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/section&gt;


							&lt;div class="article-branding"&gt;
						&lt;img data-src="https://kubrick.htvapps.com/htv-prod-media.s3.amazonaws.com/htv_default_image/site_branding/wtae.png" class="lazyload lazyload-in-view branding" alt="WTAE logo"&gt;
								&lt;p class="article-headline--publish-date border-left"&gt;
			Updated: 8:48 AM EST Jan 3, 2026
		&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;a href="/article/hearst-television-news-policy-statements/14471973" class="editorial-standards border-left"&gt;Editorial Standards &lt;span class="info-icon"&gt;ⓘ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

							




						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
	
						
					&lt;p class="article-content--body-teaser"&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;p class="article-content--body-text-raw"&gt;
						Pennsylvania has reported 22 flu-related deaths and over 35,000 confirmed cases since the flu season began in September, with hospitalizations reaching high levels."Just a reminder that people do die from flu every day," said Dr. Crawford Faucher, highlighting the ongoing impact of the virus.According to the health department, 552 adults and 142 children have been hospitalized due to the flu. Despite the concerning numbers, Dr. Faucher  noted that not as many people are getting their flu vaccines this season."It is not. It takes about two weeks for it to kick in and provide the maximum benefit," she said, emphasizing the importance of vaccination.Dr. Faucher  expressed concern over the skepticism surrounding the flu vaccine, saying, "I think there's continuing to be some skepticism, which is too bad because we're seeing the result of that."She also addressed common misconceptions, stating, "People say, 'Well, I've not gotten the flu shot, and I've never gotten the flu, and I say congrats that's great, but we still get outbreaks."To protect against the flu, Dr. Faucher  advised simple preventive measures: "Wash your hands, don't touch your face, sneeze into your elbow, not into your hand, and if you're in a crowded place, if you're traveling, you might want to bring out those face masks."With flu season lasting into March, health officials continue to urge vaccinations and adherence to preventive practices.
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;div class="article-content--body-text"&gt;
																			&lt;p&gt;Pennsylvania has reported 22 flu-related deaths and over 35,000 confirmed cases since the flu season began in September, with hospitalizations reaching high levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Just a reminder that people do die from flu every day," said Dr. Crawford Faucher, highlighting the ongoing impact of the virus.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;According to the health department, 552 adults and 142 children have been hospitalized due to the flu. Despite the concerning numbers, Dr. Faucher  noted that not as many people are getting their flu vaccines this season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is not. It takes about two weeks for it to kick in and provide the maximum benefit," she said, emphasizing the importance of vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Faucher  expressed concern over the skepticism surrounding the flu vaccine, saying, "I think there's continuing to be some skepticism, which is too bad because we're seeing the result of that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She also addressed common misconceptions, stating, "People say, 'Well, I've not gotten the flu shot, and I've never gotten the flu, and I say congrats that's great, but we still get outbreaks."&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;To protect against the flu, Dr. Faucher  advised simple preventive measures: "Wash your hands, don't touch your face, sneeze into your elbow, not into your hand, and if you're in a crowded place, if you're traveling, you might want to bring out those face masks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="cream-inline-rec" class="cream-inline hidden"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With flu season lasting into March, health officials continue to urge vaccinations and adherence to preventive practices.&lt;/p&gt;

							
											&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
						
						
																			

																				&lt;/div&gt;
	
																&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WTAE</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 13:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxNRzJRWWVSc2EtVHZrdDNYNXBjNTJCZll2d253TzdVX3lLejBoRFpJYThnRnhleGp4OGIwcjRoWE9vQVpNc0FpX2FxNGtPRUo0RWIzTjdOX2V1ZWhCSS04VFA0VnhPX3lMSWhpY0MzYzEtZXJ0T3g0V1FLdHVKWDF4cjZ2NVFsUUREblRXczNwX0g3QUpHc1Q5UVplM0FCdk5xU2FyX0xZOWNlZEZ2Y2g0X2hn</guid></item><item><title>一直都累吗？您的呼吸可能是罪魁祸首- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/tired-all-the-time-your-breathing-could-be-to-blame/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 13:40:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxOUUI5dGx0T2tYdW5EeTJWamszaHhYMjlfWFhTNUFhRGRpVWVsQUo0QWh2bUNwczdqUkJSbVl2YTQ4bGtFcUZVUnVGdWpZWlVGRmVSRzU2Vk4zWnhTQmxpZVNQTGd5QW16cGJ6RGZlcXVOdTJkaXNWODk3SWJZUFhQN3I1bw</guid></item><item><title>一位与产后抑郁症作斗争的新妈妈跳过了常规预约。不相关的访视导致意外诊断。- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/breast-cancer-surprise-diagnosis-new-mom-postpartum-depression/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Ameilia Boodoosingh Gopie didn't expect the deep depression after the birth of her first daughter in August 2022. In the months that followed, Gopie struggled to get out of bed and couldn't spend time with her daughter. Her husband was essentially "a single dad for eight months," she said. Routine appointments fell by the wayside. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After nearly a year, Gopie finally began to feel better. She was determined to make up for lost time. She took her daughter to visit family in New York, Canada and Trinidad. Soon, her daughter was walking and talking. Gopie was so distracted by "getting to love on my baby" that she continued skipping regular appointments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In December 2024, Gopie realized that a cut she had given herself while shaving had become infected. Her primary care physician reminded her of the importance of annual appointments, especially her mammogram. She said her &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/dense-breast-tissue-mammogram/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;dense breasts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; qualified her for earlier screenings. After their conversation, Gopie made an appointment. The results of her mammogram were abnormal, so her doctor ran another test. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Christmas Eve, she received the results: She had Stage III breast cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/03/0e838e9a-7e2a-46f9-b706-193763b38495/thumbnail/620x703/c4c59a8a3942c3528be2a75773fe24f9/screenshot-2026-01-03-at-6-35-54-am.png#" alt="screenshot-2026-01-03-at-6-35-54-am.png " srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/03/0e838e9a-7e2a-46f9-b706-193763b38495/thumbnail/620x703/c4c59a8a3942c3528be2a75773fe24f9/screenshot-2026-01-03-at-6-35-54-am.png 1x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Ameilia Boodoosingh Gopie and her daughter decorate for Christmas shortly before her diagnosis. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Ameilia Boodoosingh Gopie

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;"Just saying that C-word ripped me and my husband to pieces," Gopie, now 42, said. "I remember us both crying like two-year-olds. And my husband's holding my daughter. My daughter's like, 'It's OK, Dada. It's OK, Mama.' She didn't know any better, she was just trying to make her parents stop crying." &lt;/p&gt;

    
    &lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Coping with aggressive treatment &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gopie and her family celebrated that Christmas as normally as possible. On December 26, she said they "hit the ground running" to get a second opinion and figure out a treatment plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further testing determined that Gopie had triple-positive breast cancer. The subtype affects about 10% of breast cancer patients, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/triple-positive-breast-cancer" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;according to the Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. It has hormone receptors that make it more likely to respond favorably to treatment, but tends to be aggressive and present at a later stage, said Dr. Stuart Samuels, a radiation oncologist at the University of Miami Health System's Sylvester Comprehensive Cancer Center who treated Gopie. The disease had also spread to Gopie's lymph nodes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors recommended aggressive treatment beginning with chemotherapy. It had uncomfortable side effects, including pain, nausea and vomiting, Gopie said. Eventually, she lost her hair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Through it all, Gopie said it was hard to spend time with her daughter or stay focused at work. Gopie did what she could, prioritizing family time. When she was too sick to be with her daughter, she wrote letters to her and planned activities for when she was feeling better. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/02/d737f399-e7de-4505-b7a3-c50fef502a58/thumbnail/620x827/77c309d9ac9461d714e2ffa94874028e/1000213458.jpg#" alt="1000213458.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/02/d737f399-e7de-4505-b7a3-c50fef502a58/thumbnail/620x827/77c309d9ac9461d714e2ffa94874028e/1000213458.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/02/d737f399-e7de-4505-b7a3-c50fef502a58/thumbnail/1240x1654/0b4ce792444aeca5e0535dbbef1ea97c/1000213458.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Ameilia Boodoosingh Gopie and her daughter's toy.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Ameilia Boodoosingh Gopie

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;"As a mom, you just keep jumping through another hoop, and you're like, 'It's OK, as long as she's good,'" Gopie said. "You just keep going." &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A video diary, recorded before each treatment session, became a surprising source of strength, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I would tell that video how I felt, if I was happy, if I was sad, if I was nervous, what I think I'm going to expect that day, what I think I want for that day. I prayed every day and I still pray, but talking to myself every time before chemo helped a lot," Gopie said. "I realized doing those videos helped me to just release my feelings at that time." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;"It gets overwhelming" &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After finishing chemotherapy, Gopie underwent a double mastectomy. Samuels said surgeons found "quite a bit of cancer left in the breast," as well as in her armpit. That meant she would need radiation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samuels administered the treatment over the next three weeks. Gopie said the radiation had new side effects, including intense headaches and a burning feeling in her skin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Later tests showed she would need more chemotherapy. The treatment was exhausting, Gopie said, and made it hard for her to work and spend time with her family. Most of her focus went to just putting one foot in front of the other, she said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/02/a4dc33bf-4a41-4d56-a5a3-5bd6442a8e9b/thumbnail/620x827/fc2fe9378840d1b0ccf29390023fd9ce/1000213462.jpg#" alt="1000213462.jpg " srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/02/a4dc33bf-4a41-4d56-a5a3-5bd6442a8e9b/thumbnail/620x827/fc2fe9378840d1b0ccf29390023fd9ce/1000213462.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/02/a4dc33bf-4a41-4d56-a5a3-5bd6442a8e9b/thumbnail/1240x1654/7df0582e4db9a86db53badffca003dd2/1000213462.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Ameilia Boodoosingh Gopie, her husband and her daughter.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Ameilia Boodoosingh Gopie

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Gopie is still "in a limbo area," Samuels said, but "the hardest part is over." When Gopie spoke to CBS News, she was still undergoing radiation, taking a daily medication and receiving a regular hormone therapy infusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She still has an aggressive cancer, but she's just living her life," Samuels said. "Now it's really about recovery and enjoying her daughter." &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;"Learning to be the new Ameilia"&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gopie said she has been working on finding a new normal. She recently had reconstructive surgery and said she is beginning to feel more like herself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's interesting, you know, the life that I live. I'm trying to maintain the old Ameilia, but now to go through the new journey that I'm going through, I'm also learning to be the new Ameilia, who goes through pains and nausea and wakes up with huge headaches and has a three-year-old," Gopie said. "It gets overwhelming." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Throughout it all, the depression that haunted Gopie early in her daughter's life has never returned. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Thank goodness, I haven't gone through that," Gopie said. "I try my best to enjoy life. I know I'm going to be fine. I want to enjoy every second with my baby. I want to sing with her and laugh at her and dance with her and write things to her and leave it all over the house. I keep it positive."  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/03/3ff7d815-042a-42c9-887f-72ebe4edd056/thumbnail/620x825/8e7abe20225e09208f1d6405f6533068/545394444-10161487286392401-7745783308224515548-n-1.jpg#" alt="545394444-10161487286392401-7745783308224515548-n-1.jpg " srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/03/3ff7d815-042a-42c9-887f-72ebe4edd056/thumbnail/620x825/8e7abe20225e09208f1d6405f6533068/545394444-10161487286392401-7745783308224515548-n-1.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/03/3ff7d815-042a-42c9-887f-72ebe4edd056/thumbnail/1240x1650/ef474d9a6efa75e5ea3ec5556deb8327/545394444-10161487286392401-7745783308224515548-n-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;A recent photo of Ameilia Boodoosingh Gopie and her daughter.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Ameilia Boodoosingh Gopie

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  

    

                  
        
    
  
          
  
  



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

  
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 13:00:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQMWNDTk5GbDREeGlnOFNmcmk2YURqcWdWcXlYQmFBekZhYUw3THM1XzgyMzBnSXpqb0Z3Y0sxLUtGNzNRaHhwZ0VTNDJjUW9qd3h3T1FhY09naHRzMm15T2E3Z3U3WlNmYzBZSF9zcEFhUk10U1V2bEtuNHI1c0l3eWFvT19IbDg4S3FoQTdDZjFIRVg2NFNV0gGcAUFVX3lxTE1xSTFxel95Q215WFJER2dEUUM5Z2xnMHA3VUR3bnNTZXZGem9Lc2FGNWVSUkZOdmd6VGtyLU5vRzg0MHl5VUN4VWRoMVNpYTFsbGxlUTg5YXdFRkpOam9BOVNmS3lGOS1ha3VWQ1RjM2c5YW5WTDVnblVZcXZTQ3VnMnVhb1d4bnFOS0lTN1h5UGxTZXBlSTFpTnRWSw</guid></item><item><title>阻断一种蛋白质减缓小鼠癌症生长，科学家发现- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/blocking-one-protein-slows-cancer-growth-in-mice-scientists-discover</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;One of the ways scientists are trying to improve &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/breakthrough-breast-cancer-pill-extends-survival-in-7-year-trial"&gt;cancer treatments&lt;/a&gt; is by better equipping &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/surprising-immune-cell-discovery-wins-2025-nobel-prize-heres-the-science"&gt;the body's own immune system&lt;/a&gt; to fight off the disease – and a new study identifies a molecular switch that can do just that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Through an extensive screening process in which genes in  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="187392" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; cells in the lab were 'switched off' to pinpoint their effects, researchers found that a gene producing &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/cdd.2014.123"&gt;the TAK1 protein&lt;/a&gt; was crucial for cancer cells to evade immune attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further tests on &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-breakthrough-treatment-safely-kills-cancer-cells-with-light"&gt;cancer cells&lt;/a&gt; in mice with normal immune systems then confirmed how vital TAK1 is for cancer: Tumors in mice without this protein grew more slowly, and the mice survived for longer, on average.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/powerful-anti-cancer-drug-discovered-inside-japanese-tree-frog"&gt;Powerful Anti-Cancer Drug Discovered Inside Japanese Tree Frog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team from institutions in Australia and Ireland believes their findings could aid in the development of future treatments. Medications could potentially directly target TAK1 production, and 'flip' this molecular switch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_187395" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-187395" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/TAK1Effect.jpg" alt="TAK1 protein effect" class="wp-image-187395 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/TAK1Effect.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/TAK1Effect-600x557.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-187395" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The researchers looked at how the TAK1 protein affected cancer cells. (Djajawi et al., &lt;em&gt;Cell Rep.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is known that TAK1 promotes cancer cell survival and blocks cell death," &lt;a href="https://www.onjcri.org.au/news/research/onjcri-researchers-discover-molecular-safety-switch-shielding-cancers-from-immune-attack/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; cancer cell biologist Anne Huber, from the Olivia Newton-John Cancer Research Institute (ONJCRI) in Australia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"However, we didn't know that cancer cells use this tactic to avoid killing by the immune system."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huber and colleagues examined in greater detail the mechanisms underlying TAK1's effect. Specifically, it protects cancer cells from the activity of &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cytotoxic_T_cell"&gt;CD8⁺ T cells&lt;/a&gt;, immune cells that clear out damaged cells and kill deadly invaders like cancer cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One way these CD8⁺ T cells are effective is by releasing chemical signals called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cytokine" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;cytokines&lt;/a&gt;, which can more readily reach their targets when TAK1 is absent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowing how this process works in detail could help scientists better harness it for cancer treatments. When TAK1 is removed, cancer cells are essentially trying to survive without one of their best bodyguards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_180218" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-180218" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/c3ac86_ea1154e7cdc342f590b63a2d2771db07mv2-642x642.avif" alt="cartoon illustrating immune cells as characters " class="size-medium wp-image-180218" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/c3ac86_ea1154e7cdc342f590b63a2d2771db07mv2-642x642.avif 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/c3ac86_ea1154e7cdc342f590b63a2d2771db07mv2-675x675.avif 675w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/c3ac86_ea1154e7cdc342f590b63a2d2771db07mv2-768x768.avif 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/c3ac86_ea1154e7cdc342f590b63a2d2771db07mv2-600x600.avif 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/c3ac86_ea1154e7cdc342f590b63a2d2771db07mv2.avif 1290w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-180218" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;CD8+ cells and natural killer (NK) cells both play a role in killing deadly pathogens. (&lt;a href="https://www.synscicommics.com/mmunies?pgid=maufbuap-33a3cbff-8a32-4fff-82f4-d88566ceb4c4"&gt;SynSciCommics&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's worth emphasizing that this study involved cancer cells developed in the lab and tumors in mouse models. There's reason to believe the results can translate to humans, but that work still needs to be carried out and extended to a broader range of cancers (this study looked mainly &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/air-pollution-may-protect-people-from-skin-cancer-but-at-a-terrible-cost"&gt;at melanoma&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, these findings are encouraging. One of the benefits of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/boosted-natural-killer-cells-could-lead-to-off-the-shelf-cancer-immunotherapy"&gt;immunotherapy approaches&lt;/a&gt; to tackle tumors is that they lean more heavily on the body's own defences, rather than chemotherapy drugs or radiation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patient safety is always a crucial consideration whenever it comes to cancer-fighting treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stopping the production of TAK1 may be feasible in the future, but investigators will need to determine potential adverse health effects on the rest of the body and weigh them against the benefits.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Blocking TAK1 could make current immunotherapies more effective by stripping tumors of this protection," &lt;a href="https://www.onjcri.org.au/news/research/onjcri-researchers-discover-molecular-safety-switch-shielding-cancers-from-immune-attack/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; medical biologist Tirta Djajawi, from ONJCRI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"TAK1 is like a shock absorber that lets cancer cells survive the immune system's hardest hits. Remove it, and the tumor collapses under the force of immune attack."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.celrep.2025.116665"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cell Reports&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 12:02:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxNUVRCUjdIWDFvWm1pV2VrbXFBbVAwSWtQcWVQV2lRVnREdVc5VWxKZURUcl9CZlA3Y04xRGtNRGhZc0NjZ1NzNkNsaGNmNnpKbGFkanNMaE1QdzBPRkc2Y05hVDVvTVkyNHJDamJDTDhueDBGcGtFS3QzMEFPSDYydGZSZ2JwVkNXblNGOUlCQ0R5MnpHMGN3NEpkVWdmQQ</guid></item><item><title>主要医生透露，这不是油炸或加工食品，这实际上是对你的大脑最糟糕的食物-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/not-fried-or-processed-food-this-is-in-fact-the-worst-food-for-your-brain-reveals-leading-doctor/articleshow/126300311.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When we think of foods that are good for our brain, we naturally gravitate towards fruits, vegetables, nuts, and good fats. However, what about foods that slowly damage your brain? According to Dr. Austin Perlmutter, MD, it is not refined carbs, or fried food, but something you consume on a daily basis, almost every day—yes, we are talking about sugar, and specifically liquid sugar, aka sugary drinks. Let's take a look...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regular consumption of sugar-rich beverages and sweetened foods leads to brain &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902134/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;damage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; through gradual processes when these items are consumed every day. The brain functions through a few essential elements which include memory, mood, focus and dementia risk assessment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Unhealthy 5 letter foods you should avoid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;The process of sugar entering your brain system&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consumption of cola, packaged juice, energy drinks and sweet tea leads to fast sugar entry into the blood and brain. Your body needs to produce a large amount of insulin when blood sugar levels rise suddenly, and this process occurs multiple times throughout years which leads to brain insulin resistance. The brain depends on glucose for its operation but requires a continuous and controlled flow of this substance, instead of experiencing rapid increases and decreases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;High sugar intake over several years causes brain cell &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11446400/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;damage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; by triggering inflammation and oxidative stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Sweet drinks, kids’ brains, and attention&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early exposure to sugary drinks is especially harmful for young, developing brains. Studies connect high intake of sugar-sweetened drinks in babies and children with more attention and behavior problems later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A large Korean cohort study showed that children who consumed more than 200 ml of sugary drinks daily, before their second birthday developed ADHD at a higher rate than children who drank less. Other studies in Spain and China report that frequent soft drink intake in school-age children links to higher ADHD risk and poorer cognitive performance scores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Memory loss and thinking problems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prolonged intake of large sugar amounts results in detrimental effects that harm memory functions, learning abilities and information processing capabilities. Symptoms like brain fog and poor focus will appear first before the condition advances to its next stage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies based on cohort data show that children who drink too many sugary beverages at a young age, will achieve lower IQ levels as adults based on their cognitive test performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who drink too much sugar and sweetened beverages, face health dangers that harm their brain function because these drinking habits raise their risk of developing dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Artificial sweeteners&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt; do not help much&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Switching from sugar to “zero-calorie” sweeteners may not fully protect the brain. New studies suggest that some artificial and low- or no-calorie sweeteners may also speed up cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research on an 8-year Brazilian study revealed that people who consumed common sweeteners including aspartame, saccharin, acesulfame K, erythritol, sorbitol and xylitol, showed quicker deterioration in their memory abilities, verbal fluency and thinking performance, particularly among participants under 60 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research published in The Neurology journal demonstrated that people who consumed the most sugar substitutes developed mental performance decline at a faster rate than those who used these substances infrequently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Sweetened drinks prove more detrimental to health than sugary foods do&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liquid sugar is particularly bad for the brain because it is easy to overconsume and is absorbed very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drinks do not make you feel as full as solid food, so you can easily add hundreds of “free sugar” calories without noticing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="72"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/topic/world-health-organization" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; established two limits for sugar intake: free sugars at 10% of daily calories and 5% for maximum health advantages. One-liter soft drinks exceed the daily sugar limit people should not exceed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Mood swings, cravings, and addiction-like changes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="78"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brain's reward system reacts to sugar consumption through the same mechanisms that addictive substances trigger. This is one reason it is hard to stop at “just one” sweet drink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="81"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;After multiple sugar highs, your brain learns to search for sugar; this develops a pattern leading to a reward cycle that ends with a crash followed by strong hunger and irritability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="83"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The body experiences unstable mood, fatigue and concentration problems when sugar consumption remains high throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="85"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How to protect your brain from sugar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="87"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="88"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;People who drink fewer sweet beverages with added sugar, will protect their memory abilities and concentration skills, which will benefit their &lt;keyword id="20018982" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="brain-health" source="keywords"&gt;brain health&lt;/keyword&gt; in the long run.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The replacement of soft drinks, energy drinks and packed juices should be done by using water and unsweetened tea, along with lemon water, cucumber and herbs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep sweet treats small and occasional, and avoid giving sugary drinks to babies and toddlers to lower their future ADHD and cognitive risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="89"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is informational only and not a substitute for medical advice. Always consult a medical professional before making any new dietary changes. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="91"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="93"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="94"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="96"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="97"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="98"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:20:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogJBVV95cUxNNklNaDAtTXBLNDVIWXQ1SGhfNTRHLWx6cVdTMjhreWZZN0puc0J2VFFDQVpEdHI4cGZaVm1USWgySEpSU1VWN1h5M0tlVjA0M1FLYVV0bmNpZHl4bHBnVTFzT0FfX0dPTlowV2t5MHFLcDBHb3pBbTVIc2RESWY1WWhGcnprRVdQYnowMjlRTDRGZURDbTRvMGhnbXlMWk8tbEYyd1YydTU0VUtRcm9mYWQzWWUtNXg2cGc3SzY3cFViTjhiaWFOdmdFUzZTcFpUUFIyRmJMeTBiOHFIQ0hnNHV5NXpUSTZFN21TblFpYTNSMUZacGZvSzEzZnpiN084QlZpam15Mjh1NE90Uld0RXNsdWVDNkN0WEtNRVB4TFV6QQ</guid></item><item><title>疫苗对老年人的帮助超过我们所知道的-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/03/health/vaccines-dementia-heart-elderly.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 10:01:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxNdHd0THJVQ0Y2Z1ZHUjZwbzlmT2VzbkZuWl95SkJaVU1WNVl4RWVtWDZFWWVOYjhnLVY1YVZYNUdDeU1fOGhIU2dkalNuZF9tMVpMM1BicE5GaDA4Q3NtMmI5Nk8wY21uQ3ZhY2RRQWRZX2FtRVRjTm9jVmNRV1lIY2txREo</guid></item><item><title>随着流感病例激增，医生敦促接种疫苗- fox56.com</title><link>https://fox56.com/news/local/doctors-urge-vaccination-as-flu-cases-surge</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;DUNMORE, LACKAWANNA CO. (WOLF) — &lt;/span&gt;As the new year starts, doctors are urging the public to watch out for the flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every year it mutates and vaccine manufacturers try to account for the changes but since they’re developed in February to be available by the end of the year, experts say some years the vaccine is more effective than others as they try to anticipate and react to each year's individual strain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Influenza has eight different gene segments, and the H is one of them," explained Geisinger's medical director for infection prevention Dr. Mark Shelly. "And that’s the hemagglutinin. That’s the thing that attaches to us. So, and that’s also what our antibodies attack. So, if we’ve got a hemagglutinin that’s pretty recognizable, all the antibodies do a pretty good job. If it’s not as recognizable the old antibodies don’t help. And this one specifically has enough changes in the H to confuse some old antibodies.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pennsylvania Department of Health saying flu activity was increasing rapidly by the end of 2025 and with the increase of cases, comes an increase of shots. Local pharmacies saying that more people are coming in to get the flu shot than normal for this time of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“October was like, almost 20 to 30 flu shots a day," said Alexandra Riggleman, a pharmacist at DePietro's Pharmacy in Dunmore. "And like I said, it usually slows down right now but we’ve been getting like 10 to 20 a day.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though this year’s vaccine might not be able to stop somebody from getting the flu, doctors say it is still recommended as it lessens symptoms and keeps elderly and at-risk patients out of the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flu vaccine has been administered billions of times, has been tested tirelessly, and is considered one of the safest vaccines in the industry, with the chance that a patient leaves with something worse than a sore arm being close to zero. Getting the vaccine is the number one preventative method against the flu and it's so easy, I even got mine while covering this story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You wouldn’t have to force me to get a vaccine every year. I do it on purpose. I did it when I was 40, I’m doing it in my 60s. You know, I just do it," continued Shelly. "It’s not something I say: ‘you do it, so you protect me’, no. I do it because I protect myself, my family, and everybody else around me and my patients.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>fox56.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 09:47:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE55YThKemJJZklidndGblRKeGlkaE5nMTlaZ1dLeXBFc3I1YUxIeEJ5MjFrdXBkY05ra3dmVVFaWG1iX3JuS1dWcTJETWgxODBoNE5CSjM2OURDbFpYMHlRMm5kc29mVUVBZmZUcnNXQXBNdHdnUVhIUjR4WWo</guid></item><item><title>科学家测试了间歇性禁食而不减少进食，发现没有代谢益处- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251228020018.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A new study from the German Institute of Human Nutrition Potsdam-Rehbruecke (DIfE) and Charité -- Universitätsmedizin Berlin challenges a widely held belief about intermittent fasting. The research shows that time-restricted eating does not lead to measurable improvements in metabolic or cardiovascular health when calorie intake remains unchanged. However, the timing of meals did affect the body's internal clocks. These findings come from the ChronoFast study led by Prof. Olga Ramich and were published in &lt;em&gt;Science Translational Medicine&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time-restricted eating (TRE) is a form of intermittent fasting that limits daily food intake to a window of no more than ten hours, followed by a fasting period of at least 14 hours. The approach has become popular as a simple strategy to support weight management and metabolic health. Animal studies show that TRE can protect rodents from diet-related obesity and metabolic problems. In humans, earlier studies have reported benefits such as improved insulin sensitivity, healthier blood sugar and cholesterol levels, and modest reductions in body weight and body fat. As a result, TRE has been widely viewed as a promising tool for preventing insulin resistance and diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conflicting Evidence From Earlier Studies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite its popularity, past research on TRE has produced mixed results. Many studies have not been able to determine whether observed health improvements came from shorter eating windows, unintentional calorie reduction, or a combination of both. In addition, most earlier trials did not carefully track calorie intake or control for other factors that could influence metabolic outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To address these gaps, Prof. Olga Ramich, Head of the Department of Molecular Metabolism and Precision Nutrition at the DIfE and Professor at the Charité -- Universitätsmedizin Berlin, designed the ChronoFast trial. The goal was to test whether an eight-hour eating window could improve insulin sensitivity and other metabolic markers when calorie intake was kept constant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How the ChronoFast Study Was Conducted&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study used a randomized crossover design and included 31 women with overweight or obesity. Each participant followed two different eating schedules for two weeks at a time. One schedule involved early time-restricted eating between 8 a.m. and 4 p.m.(eTRE). The other followed a later schedule from 1 p.m. to 9 p.m. (lTRE). Throughout both phases, participants ate nearly identical meals with the same calorie and nutrient content (isocaloric).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers collected blood samples during four clinic visits and performed oral glucose tolerance tests to assess glucose and fat metabolism. Continuous glucose monitoring tracked blood sugar levels over 24 hours while food intake was recorded in detail. Physical activity was monitored using a motion sensor. In collaboration with Prof. Achim Kramer from the Charité -- Universitätsmedizin Berlin, the team also examined changes in the body's internal clock using isolated blood cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Measuring the Body's Internal Clock&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Human biology follows internally generated rhythms that roughly align with the length of a day, which is why they are known as circadian clocks (Latin: circa and dia). These rhythms help regulate nearly every physiological process, including sleep and metabolism. Almost all cells in the body contain their own internal clock, which can be influenced by light, physical activity, and food timing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To measure individual circadian phases, Prof. Dr. Achim Kramer developed the BodyTime assay. This test requires only a single blood sample and provides an objective snapshot of a person's internal timing. The ChronoFast study used this method and confirmed that eating schedules can shift internal clocks in humans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Metabolic Improvements Found&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite expectations based on earlier research, the ChronoFast study found no clinically meaningful changes in insulin sensitivity, blood sugar, blood fats, or inflammatory markers after the two-week interventions. "Our results suggest that the health benefits observed in earlier studies were likely due to unintended calorie reduction, rather than the shortened eating period itself," explains Ramich.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While metabolic measures remained largely unchanged, the timing of meals did affect circadian rhythms. Analysis of blood cells showed that the internal clock shifted by an average of 40 minutes during the late eating schedule compared to the early schedule. Participants following the later eating window also went to bed and woke up later. "The timing of food intake acts as a cue for our biological rhythms -- similar to light," says first author Beeke Peters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calories and Individual Timing May Matter Most&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings highlight the importance of calorie balance in achieving health benefits from intermittent fasting. "Those who want to lose weight or improve their metabolism should pay attention not only to the clock, but also to their energy balance," Ramich concludes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Future research will need to explore whether combining time-restricted eating with reduced calorie intake produces stronger benefits. Scientists also aim to better understand how individual factors, including chronotype and genetics, may influence how people respond to different eating schedules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 09:12:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE84YUsxR3ctbW1fSXJTTkxYQzdoc21KaUN0cmN5cnNwbGJPVW8xeWRwN3JaX3ZsYnp1eDM2NkU2WFRvWFRlOWRKSUJsclR0Q0pvbFNscEYxSlAweGw0NjY2QmdjdGtOUU9oUi15eklaNA</guid></item><item><title>根据专家建议，针对老年人的核心强化产品- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/tessaflores/core-strengthening-products-for-older-adults-according-to</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-8
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139929129" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title  "&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;Why Is Core Strength Important For Older Adults?&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“For older adults, a strong core helps prevent falls, supports proper posture, and facilitates the safe performance of daily activities such as standing, walking, and climbing stairs,” said Vesagas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brandon said that the term core may colloquially only apply to abdominal muscles, but it actually refers to all the deep muscle units of the “trunk” or torso like the pelvic floor, the deep spine muscles, and the lateral trunk muscles as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She explained that while generally these muscles are on all the time, as we get older, these muscles are less likely to be engaged due to limited mobility and less time spent standing, kneeling, or getting in and out of a variety of positions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Many people don’t realize they have to choose exercises that focus on these muscles ― their typical workout doesn’t target these muscle groups enough,” Brandon said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 09:01:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxOZjRsTnJ2Z3FiMUExeERrVTdPRENRbjRKa2tuZldQTlVhOFlGaXBCT1Zsek1VOFd2aWVxQlNmTXBRZF9ISEM4Sy1pQkV6YlpsbTJQN3V4d2ZLQnZtZERiWndPWS1qM3JuXzBfNHJIaHVnREhoS2xWMkZqWEU2RmZFRGFBLUp0SmM5WVJXZ3llNUo4dGZKM1R4YkZR</guid></item><item><title>在假期交通中，在美国两个主要机场检测到世界上传染性最强的病毒- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/worlds-most-contagious-virus-detected-193018261.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;During peak holiday travel, one of the most infectious diseases was detected at Newark Liberty International Airport in New Jersey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/measles" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:A case of measles was identified;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;A case of measles was identified&lt;/a&gt; in a passenger at terminals B &amp;amp; C on Dec. 12, according to a New Jersey Department of Health (NJDOH) press release. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Measles symptoms include a high fever, cough, runny nose, watery red eyes, &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/beauty-and-skin" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:and a rash;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;and a rash&lt;/a&gt; that usually appears between three and five days after symptoms begin," the release says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/travel/holiday-travel-plans-could-ruined-you-wear-particular-item-airport" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Your Holiday Travel Plans Could Be Ruined If You Wear One Particular Item To The Airport;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Holiday Travel Plans Could Be Ruined If You Wear One Particular Item To The Airport&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The rash usually begins as flat red spots that appear on the face at the hairline and spread downward to the neck, torso, arms, legs and feet."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The airborne virus can spread when someone coughs or sneezes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS/mvaj7wvj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read On The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Read On The Fox News App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Measles was detected at Newark Liberty International Airport on Dec. 12.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles can stay in the air for up to two hours after an &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/infectious-disease" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:infected person;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;infected person&lt;/a&gt; leaves the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials are asking those who suspect exposure or illness to &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/health-care" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:call their health provider;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;call their health provider&lt;/a&gt; before visiting a medical care center or hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Sign Up For Our Lifestyle Newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here To Sign Up For Our Lifestyle Newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"NJDOH is working in collaboration with local health officials on ongoing contact tracing and on efforts to notify people who might have been exposed and to identify additional exposures that may have occurred," says the release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New Jersey Department of Health says individuals at risk include those who have not been fully vaccinated or have not had measles in the past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Measles can stay in the air for up to two hours after an infected person leaves the area.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year, there have been &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/major-measles-outbreak-leads-hundreds-quarantined-us-county-officials-say" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:11 confirmed cases of measles;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;11 confirmed cases of measles&lt;/a&gt; in New Jersey, according to NJDOH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A record 8.03 million travelers are expected to &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/travel/general/travel-safety" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:fly across America this holiday season;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;fly across America this holiday season&lt;/a&gt;, according to AAA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here For More Lifestyle Stories;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here For More Lifestyle Stories&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Massachusetts Department of Public Health (DPH) also confirmed on Christmas Eve that a visitor from Texas was diagnosed with measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The traveler flew into &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/boston" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Boston Logan International Airport;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Boston Logan International Airport&lt;/a&gt; on American Airlines flight 2384 from Dallas-Fort Worth and was in terminal B, according to a DPH press release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;As of Dec. 23, there have been 2,012 measles cases in the U.S., the CDC says.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of Dec. 23, there have been 2,012 measles cases in the U.S., according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/lifestyle/quizzes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Test Yourself With Our Latest Lifestyle Quiz;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Test Yourself With Our Latest Lifestyle Quiz&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The single best way to protect your children and yourself from measles &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/major-measles-outbreak-leads-hundreds-quarantined-us-county-officials-say" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:is to be vaccinated;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;is to be vaccinated&lt;/a&gt;," Connecticut's DPH Commissioner Manisha Juthani, M.D., wrote in a statement, as Fox News Digital recently reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS?pid=AppArticleLink&amp;amp;af_dp=foxnewsaf%3A%2F%2F&amp;amp;af_web_dp=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.foxnews.com%2Fapps-products" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Download The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here To Download The Fox News App&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One dose of measles vaccine is about 93% effective, while two doses are about 97% effective."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Angelica Stabile of Fox News Digital contributed reporting.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Original article source:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/travel/worlds-most-contagious-virus-detected-two-major-us-airports-amid-holiday-traffic" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:World's most contagious virus detected at two major US airports amid holiday traffic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;World's most contagious virus detected at two major US airports amid holiday traffic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 08:01:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxPd2oyOXpmRUVsOTg2SXMtYm9mUU1sNWloWk85ZFpoRk1OZzJUWlM0dXRza05Cam93ZlN0ejRoUjk4M1o4bDN1ZF9iZzRmeWh0M29iNGExaGItU1dYYU1idnJKU0k4WXVhOF93c1AyVGFuOGdqSUhPcW5hdDd1R1V3ZEs4S21NNVNW</guid></item></channel></rss>