<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>对50万份医疗记录与阿尔茨海默氏症病毒一次又一次关联的研究- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/a-study-of-500000-medical-records-linked-viruses-with-alzheimers-again-and-again</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A study of around 500,000 medical records published in 2023 suggested that severe viral infections like encephalitis and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pneumonia" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73057" data-postid="176452" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;pneumonia&lt;/a&gt; increase the risk of neurodegenerative diseases like  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IYl" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73029" data-postid="176452" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Parkinson's&lt;/a&gt; and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="176452" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers found 22 connections between viral infections and neurodegenerative conditions in the study of around 450,000 people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People treated for a type of inflammation of the brain called viral encephalitis were 31 times more likely to develop Alzheimer's disease. (For every 406 viral encephalitis cases, 24 went on to develop Alzheimer's disease – around 6 percent.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-could-be-linked-to-a-common-virus-you-already-have"&gt;Alzheimer's Could Be Linked to a Common Virus You Already Have&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who were hospitalized with pneumonia after catching the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="176452" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt; seemed to be more susceptible to Alzheimer's disease, dementia, Parkinson's disease, and amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intestinal infections and meningitis (both often caused by a  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="176452" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;virus&lt;/a&gt;), as well as the varicella-zoster virus, which causes shingles, were also implicated in the development of several neurodegenerative diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176454" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176454" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/varicella_zoster-virus_toddler_642.jpg" alt="chicken pox on a toddler" class="wp-image-176454 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/varicella_zoster-virus_toddler_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/varicella_zoster-virus_toddler_642-600x374.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-176454" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Varicella-zoster virus is responsible for diseases such as chicken pox. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEI_oFb2NE/"&gt;Mixmike/Getty Images Signature/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The impact of viral infections on the brain persisted for up to 15 years in some cases. And there were no instances where exposure to  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="176452" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;viruses&lt;/a&gt; was protective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 80 percent of the viruses implicated in brain diseases were considered 'neurotrophic', which means they could cross the blood-brain barrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Strikingly, vaccines are currently available for some of these viruses, including  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="176452" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;influenza&lt;/a&gt;, shingles (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Varicella_zoster_virus"&gt;varicella-zoster&lt;/a&gt;), and pneumonia," the researchers &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/neuron/fulltext/S0896-6273(22)01147-3?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS0896627322011473%3Fshowall%3Dtrue"&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt; in their paper published last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although vaccines do not prevent all cases of illness, they are known to dramatically reduce hospitalization rates. This evidence suggests that vaccination may mitigate some risk of developing neurodegenerative disease."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176455" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176455" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/elderly_person_vaccine_642.jpg" alt="man getting vaccinated" class="wp-image-176455 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/elderly_person_vaccine_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/elderly_person_vaccine_642-600x374.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-176455" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Vaccinations may also help reduce your risk of dementia. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAE-eXD3E9s/"&gt;anontae/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2022, a study of more than 10 million people &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35025605/"&gt;linked the Epstein-Barr virus with a 32-fold increased risk of multiple sclerosis&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"After reading [this] study, we realized that for years scientists had been searching – one-by-one – for links between an individual neurodegenerative disorder and a specific virus," &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/news/could-viral-illness-increase-chances-developing-alzheimers-or-other-neurodegenerative-disease"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; senior author Michael Nalls, a neurogeneticist at the National Institute on Aging in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's when we decided to try a different, more data science-based approach," he &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/news/could-viral-illness-increase-chances-developing-alzheimers-or-other-neurodegenerative-disease"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;. "By using medical records, we were able to systematically search for all possible links in one shot."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, the researchers analyzed the medical records of around 35,000 Finns with six different types of neurodegenerative diseases and compared this against a group of 310,000 controls who did not have a brain disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This analysis yielded 45 links between viral exposure and neurodegenerative diseases, and this was narrowed down to 22 links in a subsequent analysis of 100,000 medical records from the UK Biobank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While this retrospective observational study cannot demonstrate a causal link, it adds to the &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/neuron/fulltext/S0896-6273(22)01147-3?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS0896627322011473%3Fshowall%3Dtrue"&gt;pile of research&lt;/a&gt; hinting at the role of viruses in Parkinson's and Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Neurodegenerative disorders are a collection of diseases for which there are very few effective treatments and many risk factors," &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/news/could-viral-illness-increase-chances-developing-alzheimers-or-other-neurodegenerative-disease"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; co-author Andrew Singleton, a neurogeneticist and Alzheimer's researcher and the director of the Center for Alzheimer's and Related Dementias.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our results support the idea that viral infections and related inflammation in the nervous system may be common – and possibly avoidable – risk factors for these types of disorders."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This study was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/neuron/fulltext/S0896-6273(22)01147-3?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS0896627322011473%3Fshowall%3Dtrue"&gt;Neuron&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in January 2023.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 22:08:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxNdU9ueUZaS0c3WVB3OGxpZ0MwQXRWeUcxaXY5aE5CNnBtNGQ1RThBT3hFa09YeExmaUU1amZ0V2d3dVY1RU4weXUtaTdRYV9odzJRbnJVU25rMV95YzM1cWx3Q3RycnhGNkFudUpnVnU4LXRKM0tQN0RYSGtLX2VtZnJuN2kxdUVGTHFJR0ZxV2JJQnZtOHgxcmx2ZTFlY0VpdzNVNlk5dDhlLU1fMHc</guid></item><item><title>听力障碍可能是一种脑调节障碍-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://neurosciencenews.com/misophonia-cognitive-emotional-flexibility-29770/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;A new study shows that misophonia, strong negative reactions to certain sounds, is closely linked to cognitive and emotional inflexibility. Participants with high misophonia severity struggled to shift between emotional tasks and reported rigid thinking in daily life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The condition was also strongly associated with rumination, or repetitive negative thinking, which may drive or exacerbate distress. These findings suggest that misophonia is more than sensory—it involves deeper issues of emotion regulation and executive function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Switching Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Individuals with misophonia showed reduced accuracy in tasks requiring emotional set-shifting, even when reaction times were unaffected.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cognitive Inflexibility:&lt;/strong&gt; Self-reported cognitive rigidity was significantly correlated with misophonia, independent of depression, anxiety, and hyperacusis.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rumination Link:&lt;/strong&gt; Multiple forms of rumination—general, brooding, and anger—were strongly associated with misophonia severity and mediated the link with cognitive inflexibility.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://neurosciencenews.com/?s=misophonia" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Misophonia&lt;/a&gt;, the intense emotional response to everyday sounds like chewing or sniffing, has long been viewed as a sensory condition. But new research reveals it may run much deeper—tied not just to sound sensitivity, but to how the brain regulates emotion, attention, and thought.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new pre-registered study has found that individuals with misophonia not only struggle with emotional reactivity to triggering sounds, but also exhibit significant impairments in both&lt;a href="https://neurosciencenews.com/?s=cognitive+flexibility" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt; cognitive and &lt;em&gt;affective flexibility&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;—the brain’s ability to shift focus, regulate emotional response, and move between mental tasks in the face of emotionally charged stimuli.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also found that this rigidity is closely linked to &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://neurosciencenews.com/?s=rumination" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;rumination&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, a repetitive pattern of negative thinking seen in many forms of mental distress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings offer a crucial window into misophonia’s cognitive profile, highlighting that what’s often assumed to be “just” a reaction to sound may in fact involve broader, transdiagnostic processes of emotional regulation and executive function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Beyond the Sound: The Brain’s Role in Misophonia&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Misophonia, affecting an estimated 5% to 20% of the population, is characterized by extreme discomfort or even rage triggered by specific sounds, often involving orofacial human noises (like chewing or throat-clearing). Though not yet listed in the DSM-5 or ICD-11, misophonia is increasingly recognized as a condition with serious life impacts—ranging from social avoidance to workplace difficulties and emotional distress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet, until now, misophonia has largely been approached through the lens of auditory processing or sensory hypersensitivity. What this new study reveals is that underlying cognitive and emotional traits—namely &lt;em&gt;inflexibility&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;rumination&lt;/em&gt;—may be critical in shaping misophonic responses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers used the &lt;em&gt;Memory and Affective Flexibility Task (MAFT)&lt;/em&gt;, a novel neurocognitive paradigm designed to measure how participants shift between memory-based and emotionally driven tasks. Unlike traditional tasks that use neutral stimuli, the MAFT incorporates emotionally evocative images to better capture real-world emotional demands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Affective Flexibility and the Cost of Switching&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the core findings was that individuals with clinically significant misophonia showed &lt;em&gt;reduced affective flexibility&lt;/em&gt;. Specifically, participants with higher misophonia severity performed worse on switch trials where they had to rapidly shift from one emotional evaluation to another—such as reappraising whether an image was emotionally positive or negative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This difficulty wasn’t simply about slow reaction times; in fact, reaction time was not correlated with misophonia severity. Instead, the impairment was in &lt;em&gt;switch accuracy&lt;/em&gt;—indicating a breakdown in the ability to shift cognitive sets in response to emotionally salient stimuli.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, these flexibility deficits persisted even after controlling for general cognitive rigidity, anxiety, depression, and hyperacusis, suggesting a specific and independent role for &lt;em&gt;affective switching&lt;/em&gt; in misophonia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Cognitive Inflexibility and Broader Mental Rigidity&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alongside behavioral task data, participants also completed the &lt;em&gt;Detail and Flexibility Questionnaire (DFlex)&lt;/em&gt;—a validated self-report measure of cognitive flexibility. Here too, the results were striking: misophonia severity was &lt;em&gt;strongly and positively associated&lt;/em&gt; with cognitive inflexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, individuals with misophonia not only struggled with moment-to-moment emotional shifts in a lab task—they also reported a &lt;em&gt;trait-like&lt;/em&gt; rigidity in daily life. These patterns mirror cognitive difficulties seen in disorders commonly comorbid with misophonia, such as OCD, autism spectrum disorder, and PTSD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet, affective flexibility and cognitive flexibility did &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; correlate with one another, reinforcing the idea that they are distinct processes—each contributing independently to the misophonic experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Rumination: The Mental Loop That Won’t Stop&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If affective inflexibility reflects difficulty shifting emotional gears, &lt;em&gt;rumination&lt;/em&gt; is the cognitive trap that keeps people stuck. Defined as repetitive, negative self-focused thought, rumination has long been implicated in depression and anxiety—but this study shows its unique relevance to misophonia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants completed three different rumination scales, measuring general perseverative thinking, brooding, and anger rumination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All three forms were significantly correlated with misophonia severity—even after controlling for anxiety and depression—suggesting that rumination is not merely a comorbid feature but a potential cognitive driver of misophonic distress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, rumination did &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; correlate with affective flexibility (as measured by MAFT), but did strongly correlate with cognitive inflexibility—suggesting a shared underlying mechanism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mediation analysis revealed that up to 43% of the link between cognitive inflexibility and misophonia could be explained by rumination, pointing to it as a key cognitive mediator.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Clinical Implications: More Than Sound Sensitivity&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This study offers a critical reframing of misophonia: not merely as a sensory disorder, but as a condition shaped by fundamental patterns of attention, flexibility, and emotion regulation. The findings raise important questions about how we classify and treat misophonia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Therapeutic interventions targeting cognitive flexibility and rumination—such as cognitive-behavioral therapy (CBT), mindfulness-based approaches, and metacognitive training—may hold promise for reducing misophonic distress. These methods could help individuals shift away from rigid thought patterns and develop greater emotional adaptability in the face of sensory triggers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also emphasizes the need for clinicians to assess for broader executive function difficulties and ruminative tendencies in patients reporting misophonic symptoms. Understanding this broader cognitive-affective profile may help prevent misdiagnosis and enable more tailored interventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Toward a New Understanding of Misophonia&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;By integrating behavioral tasks, self-report measures, and a robust pre-registered design, this study offers one of the most comprehensive looks yet at the cognitive underpinnings of misophonia. The evidence is clear: misophonia involves more than ears—it involves how the brain reacts, regulates, and &lt;em&gt;ruminates&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research should further explore these mechanisms using longitudinal designs and clinical samples, as well as investigate whether treating cognitive inflexibility and rumination can reduce symptoms over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those who live with misophonia, these findings may bring hope: not just for understanding, but for interventions that go beyond silencing the world—to helping the mind &lt;em&gt;let go&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Key Questions Answered:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq wp-block-yoast-faq-block"&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1759694517837"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: What is misophonia, and how is it usually understood?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: Misophonia is a condition where specific sounds trigger intense emotional responses, such as irritation, anxiety, or rage—most often viewed as a sensory processing issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1759694538120"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: What new insights does this study provide about misophonia?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: The study reveals that misophonia is also characterized by difficulty switching between emotional tasks, rigid thinking patterns, and high levels of rumination, suggesting a broader cognitive-emotional basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1759694553423"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: How could these findings impact treatment for misophonia?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: Targeting rumination and mental inflexibility through cognitive-behavioral or mindfulness-based therapies may help reduce misophonic distress and improve emotional regulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this misophonia and cognitive neuroscience research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://neurosciencenews.com/about-neuroscience-news/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Neuroscience News Communications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://neurosciencenews.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Neuroscience News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Neuroscience News Communications – Neuroscience News&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/bjop.70025" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Misophonia symptom severity is linked to impaired flexibility and heightened rumination&lt;/a&gt;” by Vivien K. Black et al. &lt;em&gt;British Journal of Psychology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Misophonia symptom severity is linked to impaired flexibility and heightened rumination&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Misophonia is a disorder involving sensitivity to certain sounds and related stimuli.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here, we explore the relationship between misophonia and affective flexibility, which describes cognitive shifting abilities in the face of emotion-evoking stimuli.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The secondary aim of this study is to test the potential association between misophonia and cognitive flexibility, building upon findings from previous research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The third objective is to examine the relationship between misophonia and rumination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One hundred and forty participants completed the Memory and Affective Flexibility Task (MAFT), designed to assess affective flexibility, as well as a battery of self-report measures to evaluate misophonia severity, cognitive flexibility, and rumination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Results suggested an inverse relationship between affective flexibility as measured by switch accuracy, but not reaction time, and misophonia severity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cognitive flexibility was also inversely associated with misophonia severity, but was not attributed to task-based affective flexibility, suggesting two independent constructs both involved in misophonia manifestation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rumination associated positively with misophonia severity and inversely with cognitive flexibility, but not affective flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taken together, these findings highlight a unique cognitive profile of misophonia, characterized by rigidity at the psychological level through cognitive inflexibility and rumination, as well as at the executive function level in terms of affective switching difficulties.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:19:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxNSG9zczVheGQzRWFpaFlPd1JqRkM3bXVObTM0RTJMSDhlcDN0MlNuUGxPSVdvMi13ZExmdmFrVUlucjYxN0NBeDBlbU9PRFNCS09NeGZaeEs5YkFsdFp5TEM4cjJNcThWZm5SMzR1U1hRNk41Zk93am9JR3VYbGg2SzlCRFM</guid></item><item><title>根据注册营养师的说法，您可以在超市找到的5种最健康的蛋白质棒- REAL SIMPLE</title><link>https://www.realsimple.com/healthiest-protein-bars-at-the-supermarket-11824355</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="realsimple-sc-page_1-0" class="comp realsimple-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--summary realsimple-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Not all protein bars are healthy—the best ones provide at least 12 grams of protein, minimal added sugar, and simple, whole food ingredients rather than additives or preservatives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Different types suit different needs, from nut- and seed-based bars packed with healthy fats, to whey or egg white bars that deliver complete proteins, to vegan-friendly plant protein options.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Smart shopping matters—look for short ingredient lists, at least 3 grams of fiber, and no more than 10 grams of added sugar per serving to ensure your bar supports energy, satiety, and overall health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/dietitian-favorite-sources-of-protein-11820661" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Protein&lt;/a&gt; remains incredibly popular within the health-focused community, leading to a booming protein-based product market—one of the most notable being the humble protein bar. Consumers reach for these bars as a snack, workout fuel, or even meal replacement (though that’s not recommended). “Protein bars are best used as a convenient snack, not a replacement for balanced meals. Whole foods should still be the foundation, with bars stepping in when you need something quick, portable, and reliable,” explains Stephanie Militano, MS, RD, CSSD, sports dietitian and owner of SM Nutrition.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In turn, the world of protein bars has become nothing short of overwhelming. In fact, the market is &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; saturated with options that you could try a new brand every day for an impressively long time. However, these convenience items can be incredibly deceiving when it comes to perceived health benefits. Some deliver what they advertise—clean protein with minimal unwanted ingredients—while others are no more than a glorified candy bar.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Here, we’ll explore what makes one protein bar more or less healthy than the next, and highlight five &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; nutritious options to look for on your next grocery store run.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-makes-a-protein-bar-healthy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What Makes a Protein Bar Healthy? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As with many packaged foods, the key to determining a protein bar's healthfulness (or lack thereof) lies in the &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/red-flags-on-food-labels-8781749" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nutrition facts panel and ingredients list&lt;/a&gt;. In protein bars, you primarily want to check for protein, fiber, and whole food-based ingredients—as well as fat sources, added sugar, additives, preservatives, and artificial ingredients.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; First, you (of course) want to check how much protein the bar contains. This macro helps us feel full after eating, stabilizes blood sugars, and supports the maintenance, growth, and repair of most tissues in the body&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;—most notably muscle—among many other important benefits. “Aim for at least 12 grams of protein per bar. If using it as a meal replacement or post-workout recovery, choose bars closer to 20 grams,” shares Jessica Clancy-Strawn MA, RDN, media and kidney wellness dietitian in Houston, Texas. Ideally the protein source of your protein bar will be whole food-based—like from &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/healthiest-nuts-to-eat-11686130" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nuts&lt;/a&gt;, seeds, legumes, dairy, or &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/recipe-collections-favorites/healthy-meals/healthy-egg-recipes" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;eggs&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Then, there are a few “nice to have” nutrients and ingredients in protein bars—namely &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/how-much-fiber-do-you-need-a-day-7564730" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;fiber&lt;/a&gt; and/or fruits and veggies. Fiber offers similar metabolic benefits as protein&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, boosting satiety after eating and managing the blood sugar response. However, it’s also tied to improved digestive regularity, cholesterol levels, and gut health as a prebiotic (or food for healthy bacteria) in the gut microbiome&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;—which supports several other elements of health like immune&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and brain health&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Three grams (or more) of fiber per bar is a major added bonus. Meanwhile, fruit and veggies add micronutrients like vitamins, minerals, and plant compounds to your protein bar for overall health support.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Paying attention to the type of fat found in your protein bar is also important. “Favor &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/healthy-fats-8740244" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;healthy fats&lt;/a&gt; such as polyunsaturated, monounsaturated, and &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-with-more-omega-3s-than-salmon-11784373" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;omega-3&lt;/a&gt; and -6 fatty acids from sources like &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/olive-oil-health-benefits-8754789" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;olive oil&lt;/a&gt;, nuts, and seeds. Avoid saturated&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and trans fats&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, especially those from partially hydrogenated or refined vegetable oils, which are not heart-friendly,” explains Clancy-Strawn. Zero grams of trans fat and three grams or less of saturated fat per bar is ideal.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Then, when it comes to other ingredients to be wary of, be on the look out for added sugar, additives, preservatives, or artificial ingredients. “Choose bars with short, recognizable ingredient lists. Avoid preservatives and additives—especially risky ones like erythritol, carrageenan, soy lecithin, and potassium sorbate,” shares Clancy-Strawn, as these additives have been linked with stomach upset&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, unwanted heart health events&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/signs-of-inflammation-7565179" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;inflammation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, and fatigue&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Plus, many additives and preservatives, while technically deemed safe for consumption, lack the long-term research&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; needed to truly gauge their health implications. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Meanwhile, added sugar is a major pro-inflammatory agent&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the body that can be found in high amounts in certain protein bars. “Opt for bars with 10 grams or less of added sugars. Lower sugar and higher fiber content help manage blood sugar spikes and crashes, and support sustained appetite control,” adds Clancy-Strawn. “Non-nutritive naturally-occurring sweeteners, such as stevia or monk fruit sweetener are better options to look for in a protein bar,” Maura Fowler, MPH RDN CPH, registered dietitian and founder of Healthy You by Maura notes.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Additionally, many allergens can be found in protein bars—like nuts, &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/healthiest-seeds-11688836" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;seeds&lt;/a&gt;, and dairy (or dairy-based components like whey and casein). If you or your loved ones have any food allergies or sensitivities, it’s important to carefully examine the food label and allergen statement prior to investing in a new protein bar option.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-healthiest-protein-bars"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Healthiest Protein Bars  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Thankfully, there are plenty of protein bar categories that meet these criteria. Here are five of the top better-for-you options:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Primarily Nut, Seed, or Nut-Butter Based Bars &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “I always want to encourage protein that comes from whole foods first,” says Fowler—and nut and nut butter-based protein bars definitely fit this bill. Plus, these bars often provide additional nutrients like fiber, healthy fats, and a variety of micronutrients naturally found in the nuts, seeds, and their butters. “Nuts and seeds offer numerous health benefits&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, including improved cardiovascular health and reduced risk of cancer, respiratory illness, infectious disease, and diabetes,” Clancy-Strawn adds. There are plenty of brands that offer nut, seed, or nut/seed butter-based bars. “A few of my favorite brands are Kind Bars and Larabar,” shares Militano.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Allergen-Free Bars &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For those allergic to any (or several) of the nine major allergens, there are a handful of allergen-free protein bars available. “It’s always important to be mindful of individuals who have allergies, and provide adequate options for those folks too. 88 Acres and Alio are made with simple ingredients and are free of all nine allergens,” says Fowler When searching for these bars, it’s essential to double check the food label and allergen statement before serving them to another with severe allergies or sensitivities.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Whey Protein-Based Bars &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Whey protein-based bars contain all of the essential amino acids, which make them a great choice if you are trying to support muscle health—and they are also typically &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-that-have-the-most-protein-8763731" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;higher in protein&lt;/a&gt;,” says Militano. Fowler agrees, adding, “Whey protein continues to prove it’s an ultimate source of protein that your body can better absorb&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.” Many of the protein bars that you’ll find in grocery stores fit within this category. “Rise bars are great options that feature simple ingredients including &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/health-benefits-of-cashews-7110031" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;cashews&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/almonds-health-benefits-6835790" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;almonds&lt;/a&gt;, or sunflower seeds, and natural sweeteners. They contain no hazardous additives, offer 16 grams of protein, a good amount of fruits and vegetables, and are low in sodium and saturated fat,” shares Clancy-Strawn.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Plant Protein-Based Bars &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you have dairy sensitivities or follow a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/recipe-collections-favorites/healthy-meals/easy-vegan-recipes" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;plant-based diet&lt;/a&gt;, vegan protein bars are a smart grab. “For those who prefer dairy free or a vegan/vegetarian lifestyle, these are their bars,” Fowler encourages. And there are plenty of brands offering exceptional plant-based protein bars. “Known for being gluten-free, dairy-free, seed oil-free, and free of sugar alcohols, Trubar was established in 2019 and is widely available at Target,” explains Clancy-Strawn. “Think! Plant Based Protein Bars are also low in added sugar, only 190 calories, and have minimal saturated fats,” Fowler adds.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Egg Protein-Based Bars &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Similar to whey-based protein bars, options that garner their protein power from eggs also offer all nine essential amino acids for a complete protein snack. Most of these bars use &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/egg-white-nutrition" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;egg whites&lt;/a&gt; as a protein source, which conveniently adds protein without affecting the flavor or texture. When it comes to brands to keep an eye out for within this category, Clancy-Strawn offers, “simplicity at its finest, RXBARs feature nuts, natural flavors, egg whites, and dates, with the ingredient list proudly displayed on the front.” &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-to-look-for-in-a-healthy-protein-bar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What to Look for in a Healthy Protein Bar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While these protein bar varieties and brands are a great starting point for finding healthy options, they only scratch the surface of what's available in grocery stores nationwide. To uncover other nutritious choices, keep the following guidelines in mind:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Look for protein content of at least 12 grams per bar&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fiber content of at least three grams per bar is a nice bonus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Choose options with whole food, recognizable ingredients &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Aim for bars with zero grams of trans fat and three grams or less of saturated fat per serving&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The shorter the ingredient list, the better. Select options with ingredients you recognize and can pronounce over bars with high amounts of additives and preservatives&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be sure there’s no more than 10 grams of added sugar in the protein bar you purchase&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you or your loved one has food allergies, be sure to thoroughly examine the ingredients list and allergen statement to avoid those triggering foods&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Real Simple</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxOQ1hNdU9QbEozYjBTNmx0YnZlQWR2c2JxRmlZMFpjdHNtNkpBU1NFX2FsUUhWRUREUEg3Y00wQjQydmR6TzQ5LWpSakZpd09EeGZqb3dtbWI1SG5EZmpzQ3BqT1hXYlZxNWQxczNQR0Rwb3VRTExBaHR2TWRtOENyV0V0OS0</guid></item><item><title>肠道中的细菌碎片可能会使我们的大脑在夜间睡眠- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/fragments-of-bacteria-in-our-gut-may-lull-our-brains-to-sleep-at-night</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Pieces of bacteria migrating from the gut to the brain may play &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/huge-accelerometer-study-suggests-the-best-sleep-time-for-heart-health"&gt;a key role in sleep&lt;/a&gt;, scientists have discovered, suggesting that the oldest and most basic microorganisms in our bodies are crucial in telling us when to nod off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These fragments are made of a chemical called peptidoglycan, which comes from bacterial cell walls in the digestive system. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/mp.2016.182"&gt;Previous animal studies&lt;/a&gt; have suggested peptidoglycan can infiltrate the central nervous system and influence behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this latest investigation, neuroscientists Erika English and James Krueger, from Washington State University (WSU), used tests on mice to establish that peptidoglycan levels in the brain change over the course of the day, and are &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/these-4-key-things-can-help-you-wake-up-feeling-great-scientists-say"&gt;lowest in the morning&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-rare-state-of-sleep-could-reveal-secrets-of-consciousness"&gt;This Rare State of Sleep Could Reveal Secrets of Consciousness&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the mice were &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-dangers-of-sleep-deprivation-are-very-real-expert-warns"&gt;deprived of sleep&lt;/a&gt;, the mix of peptidoglycan in different sections of the brain varied from typical levels. The activity of genes related to the chemical also changed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taken together, the patterns suggest substances pushed out by our gut bacteria could be influencing sleep, and are influenced by sleep in return. There's still a lot to explore and clarify here, but there's strong evidence of some kind of link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176104" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176104" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/BrainLevels.jpg" alt="Peptidoglycan levels" class="wp-image-176104 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/BrainLevels.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/BrainLevels-600x335.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-176104" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The researchers measured peptidoglycan levels in different areas of mice brains over time. (English &amp;amp; Krueger, &lt;em&gt;Front. Neurosci.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We have a whole community of microbes living within us," &lt;a href="https://news.wsu.edu/press-release/2025/09/24/key-to-the-riddle-of-sleep-may-be-linked-to-bacteria/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Krueger. "Those microbes have a much longer evolutionary history than any mammal, bird, or insect – much longer, billions of years longer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We think sleep evolution began eons ago with the activity/inactivity cycle of bacteria, and the molecules that were driving that are related to the ones driving cognition today."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results contribute to a hypothesis being tested at WSU that posits that our microbiome plays an important role in regulating sleep, along &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-body-has-a-built-in-weight-loss-system-you-may-not-know-about"&gt;with appetite&lt;/a&gt;, sex drive, and other motivations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's being called &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.smrv.2025.102145"&gt;the "holobiont condition" of sleep&lt;/a&gt;, the idea that both individual microbes in our body and the master control center of the brain have roles to play in telling us when we need to get some shut-eye and when we need to wake up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's not one or the other, it's both," &lt;a href="https://news.wsu.edu/press-release/2025/09/24/key-to-the-riddle-of-sleep-may-be-linked-to-bacteria/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; English. "They have to work together."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sleep really is a process. It happens at many different speeds for different levels of cellular and tissue organization, and it comes about because of extensive coordination."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An increasing number of studies are shedding light on how the gut and the brain collaborate to maintain healthy functioning. Microbial mixes are associated &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-of-over-400000-people-links-gut-bacteria-with-insomnia-risk"&gt;with insomnia&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/changes-in-gut-bacteria-are-present-long-before-signs-of-parkinsons-appear"&gt;neurodegenerative diseases&lt;/a&gt;, for example, demonstrating the complex interplay between these parts of the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Progress is also being made in understanding the different and varied factors that govern our urge to sleep and recharge at the right time, including peptidoglycan – from &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/exposure-to-daylight-predicts-when-youll-fall-asleep-study-shows"&gt;daylight exposure&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-shifted-peoples-day-by-just-5-hours-heres-what-happened"&gt;circadian rhythms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Now that the world has come to appreciate how important microbes are, not just for disease but also for health, it's a very exciting time to start to expand on our understanding of how we are communicating with our microbes and how our microbes are communicating with us," &lt;a href="https://news.wsu.edu/press-release/2025/09/24/key-to-the-riddle-of-sleep-may-be-linked-to-bacteria/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; English.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fnins.2025.1608302"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Frontiers in Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:01:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxQVUJVVHVSdnpha2ZfSXJHb2lOV0NaUG95ZGMzdFBHaEpkNHc4QzF4OGdqejRrQ0RJTFN2N1hiRHM4ejVlcS0zcGJLUFo1SUxyNDlNb1AxRWhnOHZJdG9rR2g5RlhabWxCR3lLYzI0cUVxYWhndW92V0xKNlBRanllblVSWmRiMXR5MWVhWnRKX0RuclI2LTZLeTU1VHFhNGx0</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，与朋友一起做几乎任何事情都会更好-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/10/05/friends-activities-happiness-research/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QN3BGEEWUNHOXAMDJ3IJONFIJY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Social interactions are essential for our well-being and happiness, research has shown. And now a large study supports that finding and suggests there are many ways to squeeze in more companionship — and happiness — into our busy lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxNQnZvaGhLRG1teHQ0RkN1Y1hzSVFmSzlZd0owVS1BLU54akJ4VWkxajE3VnR6SEZEWFBlc2dqY09GdldNcGFzMlU2dGQ0N01QZ08zenUtaU5RMjVkbk9CRlhKRnFwZzNOdlhpNkFJYi1LMFBkY0MtaHUycTZWYndoaVBQa1RycGNzRU9Qc1hlTDR2RW8</guid></item><item><title>引人注目的图像实时捕捉杀死细菌的抗生素- Live Science</title><link>https://www.livescience.com/health/medicine-drugs/striking-images-capture-an-antibiotic-slaying-bacteria-in-real-time</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto paywall-locker"&gt;
&lt;p id="dd6fde7e-fecb-437e-84e1-baadbc5d5640"&gt;Scientists have released new images showing, in incredible detail, antibiotics defeating disease-causing bacteria by piercing the microbes' membranes and infiltrating their innards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The antibiotics, called polymyxins, were observed forcing the armored membranes around &lt;em&gt;Escherichia coli&lt;/em&gt; bacterial cells to grow bumps and bulges. The bacteria then shed their outer membranes, leaving space for the antibiotic to enter the cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="dd6fde7e-fecb-437e-84e1-baadbc5d5640-2" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true"&gt;"It was incredible seeing the effect of the antibiotic at the bacterial surface in real-time," study co-author&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.hoogenboom-lab.com/carolina-borrelli.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.hoogenboom-lab.com/carolina-borrelli.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt; &lt;u&gt;Carolina Borrelli&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a doctoral student studying biophysics and microbiology at University College London (UCL), &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.imperial.ac.uk/news/269074/amazing-images-show-antibiotics-pierce-bacterial/amp/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.imperial.ac.uk/news/269074/amazing-images-show-antibiotics-pierce-bacterial/amp/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;said in a statement&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="a785aa11-374c-4ed5-890c-08581fef504e"&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/what-s-the-difference-between-gram-positive-and-gram-negative-bacteria" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/what-s-the-difference-between-gram-positive-and-gram-negative-bacteria"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Gram-negative bacteria&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are a broad class of microorganisms that have two membranes surrounding each cell; the two membranes sandwich a cell wall. &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/64436-e-coli.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/64436-e-coli.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;E. coli&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Salmonella&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Shigella&lt;/em&gt; — a type of bacteria that causes dysentery — are all examples of gram-negative bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Polymyxins can help treat infections caused by gram-negative bacteria that have gained &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/medicine-drugs/superbugs-are-on-the-rise-how-can-we-prevent-antibiotics-from-becoming-obsolete" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/medicine-drugs/superbugs-are-on-the-rise-how-can-we-prevent-antibiotics-from-becoming-obsolete"&gt;&lt;u&gt;resistance to other antibiotic drugs&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; they work by targeting the outer of the bacteria's two membranes, which act as a kind of armor that keeps antibiotics out. But exactly how the antibiotics slip past this armor isn't well understood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Polymyxins are an important line of defense against Gram-negative bacteria, which cause many deadly drug-resistant infections," study co-author&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.hoogenboom-lab.com/bart-hoogenboom.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.hoogenboom-lab.com/bart-hoogenboom.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt; &lt;u&gt;Bart Hoogenboom&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a biophysicist at UCL, said in the statement. "It is important we understand how they work."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the new study, published Sept. 29 in the journal &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=livescience_us_9719509356224894086&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fs41564-025-02133-1&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fstriking-images-capture-an-antibiotic-slaying-bacteria-in-real-time" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41564-025-02133-1" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="skimlinks" data-placeholder-url="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fs41564-025-02133-1&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fstriking-images-capture-an-antibiotic-slaying-bacteria-in-real-time" data-google-interstitial="false" data-merchant-name="nature.com" data-merchant-network="SkimLinks"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Nature Microbiology&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the team of researchers captured images of the antibiotic in action. Using a technique known as atomic force microscopy, the scientists passed a tiny needle back and forth over the bacteria to map out their shapes. This let them see how the bacteria changed as the polymyxin attacked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-Y5een5bVfw53pK8sPauUCi" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-Y5een5bVfw53pK8sPauUCi slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get the world’s most fascinating discoveries delivered straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Polymyxins forced &lt;em&gt;E. coli &lt;/em&gt;to quickly grow tiny bumps and protrusions on its outer membrane, the team found. As these bumps grew, the bacteria shed its armor, leaving gaps in that outer membrane through which antibiotics could enter and kill the cell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our images of the bacteria directly show how much polymyxins can compromise the bacterial armor," Borrelli said. "It is as if the cell is forced to produce 'bricks' for its outer wall at such a rate that this wall becomes disrupted, allowing the antibiotic to infiltrate."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="06e96628-98f1-4985-bdf0-5583aa6d6a72"&gt;Importantly, the polymyxins can only target bacteria that are actively growing, not those that have gone into a dormant state. Bacteria sometimes enter a state of dormancy to deal with difficult conditions, surviving years without eating, growing or reproducing, only to wake back up when conditions are more favorable. While dormant, bacteria can't grow their outer membrane armor, so the antibiotic couldn't ramp up production the same way it could in actively growing bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our next challenge is to use these findings to make the antibiotics more effective," Hoogenboom said. "One strategy might be to combine polymyxin treatment — counterintuitively — with treatments that promote armor production and/or wake up 'sleeping' bacteria so these cells can be eliminated too."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mb-6" id="9c130326-661e-4df5-8589-2af59cb02b5e"&gt;
&lt;div class="[&amp;amp;_a]:text-[#2f6e91] [&amp;amp;_a]:visited:text-[#09c] p-5 bg-[#F5F5F5] text-sm text-[#333]"&gt;

&lt;p class="infoDisclaimer tracking-[.02em] pt-2 font-normal"&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and is not meant to offer medical advice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxNOURqWVpzUzkta0w4SXFIWV9EcXAxVTAteXJ4Y1puaXRSS0JaRkpfSmgtTi0tNE16WW1CNmtrWjltbnV2MmtWS0xmaUxwTkV2Sk1SdVN5WU9Icm43d1Z3d0VxTlNkS1hCMzEyYm9HUEJOTDIyU1VrMGlJZTc4NTNicFRPbmxGamZpVExDWm0ta2ZaWHZsbHFBMnFGTWdSUXh2Mk9FYW8yWFROWjk4N2g4SjNuRV9lbndJ</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法， 6种碳水化合物可以帮助您减掉内脏脂肪- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/best-carbs-to-lose-visceral-fat-11824183</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Swapping refined carbs for fiber-rich complex carbohydrates may help you lose visceral fat.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oats, barley and quinoa may help reduce this fat by curbing appetite and changing gut bacteria.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sweet potatoes, beans and lentils are also great choices for reducing visceral fat.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Visceral fat lies deep within the abdominal cavity and wraps around organs like the liver and intestines. Unlike subcutaneous fat, which is the pinchable fat that’s right beneath the skin, visceral fat releases inflammatory compounds that can wreak havoc on your health. Over time, that inflammation can increase your &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7871737/inflammatory-foods-that-raise-heart-attack-stroke-risk/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;risk of chronic illnesses&lt;/a&gt; like type 2 diabetes, heart disease, metabolic syndrome and more.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The good news is that eating specific foods may make it easier to lose visceral fat, and that includes certain carbs. While you might have heard that carbs make you store more belly fat, that’s not entirely true. Yes, eating lots of sugary foods and simple carbs may prompt you to sock away extra belly fat. However, research has found that fiber-rich complex carbohydrates may help &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/things-to-help-lose-visceral-fat-11802059" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;reduce visceral fat&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; So, which &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7928306/healthiest-carbs-you-should-be-eating-according-to-a-dietitian/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;carbs should you be eating&lt;/a&gt; to fight visceral fat? To find out, we asked dietitians to share the best choices. Here are their six favorites.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-sweet-potatoes"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 1. Sweet Potatoes &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These starchy tubers get their deep orange color from beta-carotene. This antioxidant belongs to a larger family of plant compounds called carotenoids, which have been linked to lower levels of visceral fat.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Beta-carotene isn’t the only way sweet potatoes help fight visceral fat.  “Sweet potatoes also provide a healthy dose of fiber, which can help you feel satisfied after eating them,” says &lt;a href="http://www.tobyamidornutrition.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Toby Amidor, M.S., RD&lt;/a&gt;. “This can help minimize calorie intake later on, which indirectly can help with weight loss.” Plus, when you lose fat, you &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/bad-things-you-should-do-to-lose-visceral-fat-8736090" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;shed visceral fat&lt;/a&gt; along with it. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One cup of baked sweet potatoes gives you nearly &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/15696/is-fiber-good-for-weight-loss/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;7 grams of fiber&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; That’s 25% of the 28-gram Daily Value. What’s more, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-sweet-potato-recipes-11809009" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;sweet potatoes are tasty&lt;/a&gt;, versatile and convenient. Roast, microwave or bake them for a sweet addition to your next meal. Or, if you have a little more time on your hands, dice them up and add them to hash, or mash them with black beans and spices to pan-fry for a satisfying veggie burger. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 2. Oats  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Oats contain a unique type of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7962360/what-is-the-difference-between-insoluble-and-soluble-fiber-according-to-a-dietitian/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;soluble fiber called beta-glucan&lt;/a&gt;, which is best known for its &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-nutrient-to-help-lower-cholesterol-8399539" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;cholesterol-lowering properties&lt;/a&gt;. Beta-glucan has also been linked to a smaller waistline, less body fat and lower body weight, even among people who aren’t trying to cut calories.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This is likely due to several factors. For instance, soluble fiber, like beta-glucan, slows the passage of food through the intestines, helping you feel full. It also promotes the release of gut hormones that send satiety signals to the brain. So, you’re more likely to put your fork down faster. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This multitasking fiber may also reduce visceral fat by promoting &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7918818/gut-health-and-weight-loss/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;favorable changes in gut bacteria&lt;/a&gt;. Research shows that the gut bacteria of lean people often differ from those of people with obesity.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Scientists suspect that beta-glucan may lead to positive shifts in gut bacteria to more closely resemble those of lean people. In addition, when beneficial gut bacteria feed on beta-glucan, they produce compounds called short-chain fatty acids, which play a positive role in appetite and energy regulation.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Oatmeal or overnight oats are always simple and delicious ways to work more oats into your day. But don’t stop there. Stir them into pancakes or bake them into oat bars and cookies.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3-barley"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 3. Barley  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Barley delivers a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8024705/theprep-30-minute-high-fiber-dinners-to-help-you-poop/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;double dose of fiber&lt;/a&gt; to help blast visceral fat. Like oats, barley contains beta-glucan. When you cook and cool barley, it creates another type of fiber called resistant starch.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “Resistant starch resists digestion in the small intestine,” says&lt;a href="https://www.arugalyssa.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt; Alyssa Smolen, M.S., RDN, CDN&lt;/a&gt;. “Eating resistant starch can aid in reducing visceral fat because these starches are not fully broken down and are passed through our digestive system.”&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; So, it travels to your gut, where &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/2059033/best-and-worst-foods-to-eat-for-gut-health/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;good gut bacteria&lt;/a&gt;, that help maintain a healthy body weight, feed on it. This, in turn, helps them thrive. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re not sure exactly what to do with barley, it’s always a win in soups. You can also cook up a big pot of it to divide up and store in single-serve containers in the fridge or freezer. That way, you’ll always have some on hand to toss into salads or to reheat as a hearty side dish.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-4-quinoa"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 4. Quinoa &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you aren’t a fan of barley, quinoa is another standout carb to help you lose visceral fat, says &lt;a href="https://www.nutritionbybess.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Bess Berger, RDN&lt;/a&gt;. “Unlike most grains, it offers a solid dose of protein alongside fiber, which helps control appetite and prevent fat from accumulating around the midsection.” In fact, one cup of cooked quinoa delivers 5 grams of fiber and 8 grams of protein.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; If that weren’t enough, quinoa also contains magnesium. This mineral helps your body use the hormone insulin more effectively, which, in turn, helps protect against visceral fat storage, she says.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Don’t just save quinoa for side dishes. Use it as a protein and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/high-fiber-grain-bowl-recipes-for-summer-8674856" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;fiber-rich base&lt;/a&gt; for grain bowls, burrito bowls or a whole-grain quinoa risotto.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-5-lentils"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 5. Lentils &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Lentils are one of the best carb choices for targeting visceral fat because they bring both protein and fiber to the table,” says Berger. One cup of cooked lentils provides a whopping 16 grams of fiber, which gets you more than halfway to your daily goal, plus 18 grams of protein.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “That combo keeps you fuller for longer, steadies blood sugar and reduces the inflammation that often fuels belly fat storage,” says Berger. In fact, research has found that people who frequently eat legumes, like lentils, tend to have lower BMIs and carry less weight around their midsections.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One of the really nice things about lentils is that they cook up way faster than other legumes, with no soaking required. But if you’re really pressed for time, pop open a can. Either way, these tasty little legumes are delicious in soups, curries, or even mixed into ground beef to add more fiber and volume to Sloppy Joes or burgers.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-6-beans"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 6. Beans &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Not a fan of lentils? Try beans. One study found that women who consumed more beans had smaller waistlines and less body fat compared to women who rarely ate beans.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; What makes them so effective? “Beans pack the trifecta of weight management – fiber, protein and yummy taste,” says Amidor. “Due to the fact that they're a naturally rich source of fiber, beans help promote health and support weight management. In addition, their protein helps aid satiety and maintain muscle mass.” If you need one more reason to load up on beans, research has found that eating more protein, yet fewer calories, may help reduce visceral fat, while maintaining lean muscle mass.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The other nice thing about beans? There are &lt;em&gt;so &lt;/em&gt;many varieties to choose from. Whether you prefer black beans, navy beans, chickpeas or another bean, there are loads of options that can help you blast belly fat. So, stock your pantry with your favorites to toss into salads, tacos, pasta or to whip into a satisfying dip or hummus.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re trying to lose visceral fat, you don’t have to swear off carbs. The key to shedding this deep belly fat is choosing the right kinds of carbs. Replacing refined carbohydrates and sugary foods with fiber-rich complex carbohydrates can help you lose weight and visceral fat. Dietitians say the best carbs to help lose visceral fat are sweet potatoes, oats, barley, quinoa, lentils and beans. These carbs contain fibers like beta-glucan and resistant starch that slow digestion, increase fullness and promote the &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/283531/top-fiber-rich-foods-for-good-gut-bacteria/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;growth of good gut bacteria&lt;/a&gt;. In addition, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8061834/healthiest-beans-to-eat/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;whole grains, beans and legumes&lt;/a&gt; have a decent chunk of protein. That, paired with their fiber, spells even more satiety, helping you eat less overall. While choosing the right carbs is a solid strategy for reducing visceral fat, it’s not the only one. Exercising, getting good-quality sleep and managing stress may also help you lose visceral fat. Because in the end, it’s the big picture that counts!&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE9fV3dsTlVnZ3gtVnoyNnkyajhuMUQ2UFBFckFqcE1nRHVIRFY4YlRwLXkwaUtCbEd6Y1dDM3RIdkxfMmFmNnhHamI0V1BhOU9JU3FHUzNHMFBUanJGT1FJV3dBbnBVbWtnU0hpYkVBa3pjdk52M1E</guid></item><item><title>新的研究挑战治疗癌症的长期方法- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/new-research-challenges-long-standing-method-for-treating-cancer</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Removing lymph nodes during  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="175710" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; surgery has saved countless lives in many tumour types. Yet recent research is challenging parts of this long-standing practice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine your body's immune defences as a city, and lymph nodes as the hubs where police and firefighters gather fresh intel to launch their attack on criminals. What happens if you remove too many of these hubs? This is a new question at the centre of modern &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/cancer-14"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When surgeons remove lymph nodes, it's usually for two reasons: to find out whether cancer has spread, and to prevent further spread to other organs. For decades, this approach represented the best standard of care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-useless-organ-that-doctors-often-remove-could-actually-fight-cancer"&gt;A 'Useless' Organ That Doctors Often Remove Could Actually Fight Cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a tumour escapes its original site, cancer cells often travel through lymph vessels and settle in the nearest lymph nodes, which act as biological filters. Detecting cancer cells in lymph nodes signals that a patient's disease may be more likely to return after treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Removing these nodes allows doctors to &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/about-cancer/diagnosis-staging/staging"&gt;"stage"&lt;/a&gt; the disease accurately, and potentially increase the chances of eradicating all tumour cells – while also telling oncologists like me to treat the cancer more aggressively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But lymph nodes are not just passive waystations. They play an active role in the &lt;a href="https://www.aru.ac.uk/news/using-the-bodys-immune-system-to-combat-diseases"&gt;body's immune response&lt;/a&gt;, acting as meeting points for immune cells to share information about cancer. Recent scientific discoveries have led researchers to rethink how crucial these hubs are for sparking powerful, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/unlocking-the-bodys-defences-understanding-immunotherapy-226858"&gt;lasting immune reactions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41590-025-02276-7"&gt;newest studies&lt;/a&gt; shows lymph nodes help maintain a special type of immune cell called "CD8 positive T cells", which can destroy cancer cells. These immune cells are primed and kept ready to act by the environment inside the lymph nodes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without these hubs, the body's anti-cancer immune response, especially during &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-024-03083-7"&gt;immunotherapy&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39083809/"&gt;treatment&lt;/a&gt;, may be weaker than previously imagined. The &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41590-025-02276-7"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; shows how the specific cells in the lymph nodes make an initial anti-cancer burst of activity. However, this has only been demonstrated in the laboratory, not in humans as yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Removing lymph nodes is not without drawbacks. Patients can experience swelling (&lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/lymphoedema/"&gt;lymphoedema&lt;/a&gt;), increased risk of &lt;a href="https://www.jprasurg.com/article/S1748-6815(17)30492-8/pdf"&gt;infection&lt;/a&gt; in the affected limb, and sometimes chronic pain or mobility &lt;a href="https://www.cancerresearchuk.org/about-cancer/breast-cancer/treatment/surgery/remove-lymph-nodes"&gt;problems&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There's also concern that removing lymph nodes, while reducing short-term risks of cancer spread, might inadvertently weaken the body's &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10793742/"&gt;long-term immune defences&lt;/a&gt; – especially as modern treatments increasingly rely on the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/pancreatic-cancer-a-personalised-mrna-vaccine-may-boost-effects-of-treatment-205606"&gt;patient's&lt;/a&gt; natural immunity. This is in line with the new study findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;How lymph nodes work.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why do surgeons still remove lymph nodes, then?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For many types of solid tumour, the risk of metastatic spread remains high, and lymph node involvement is one of the best predictors of cancer recurrence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lymph node removal also provides vital information for choosing the most effective post-surgical treatments. In breast cancer, doctors often use a &lt;a href="https://www.macmillan.org.uk/cancer-information-and-support/treatments-and-drugs/surgery-to-the-lymph-nodes-for-breast-cancer"&gt;"sentinel node biopsy"&lt;/a&gt;. This means removing only the first lymph node that fluid from the tumour drains into. Checking just this sentinel node helps doctors see if the cancer has spread, while reducing the number of nodes removed and lowering the risk of side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical researchers are learning more about how lymph nodes work during long-term illnesses. The new study shows that lymph nodes aren't just passive filters; they're active training grounds where special immune cells grow, multiply and become powerful fighters. This is especially important during treatments that boost the immune system, such as &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41590-025-02276-7"&gt;checkpoint blockade treatments&lt;/a&gt;, which are now used for many types of &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/abs/10.1056/NEJMsb2300232"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These results suggest that taking out lymph nodes doesn't just block cancer's spread; it also removes important hubs where the immune system monitors the body and gets reactivated to fight disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the last decade, hospitals have adopted gentler, more &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7561013/"&gt;targeted&lt;/a&gt; lymph node surgeries. Instead of removing all the nodes in a region, the focus is now on minimising disruption: taking only the nodes most likely to harbour cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This approach reduces complications for patients and may help keep their immunity strong. Some patients with early-stage cancers may even avoid node removal altogether, instead relying on imaging and biopsies to monitor for spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those worried about the consequences of major lymph node removal, emerging therapies offer hope. Immunotherapy drugs, targeted treatments and even &lt;a href="https://www.aru.ac.uk/news/new-vaccines-could-transform-skin-cancer-treatment"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.aru.ac.uk/news/the-science-behind-the-new-mrna-cancer-vaccines"&gt;vaccines&lt;/a&gt; are being developed that can "re-educate" the immune system, even if some lymph nodes have been lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, there is growing evidence that patients do best when at least some hubs remain – preserving the body's ability to mount and sustain a defence against lingering cancer cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the future, cancer surgery may become even more &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38929782/"&gt;personalised&lt;/a&gt;. By mapping the activity inside lymph nodes – tracking which ones are essential for immune function and which are most likely to seed new tumours – doctors can &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/24833841/"&gt;tailor surgery&lt;/a&gt; so each patient gets maximum benefit with minimum harm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_175716" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-175716" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/personalised_cancer_treatment_642.jpg" alt="woman at a physician" class="wp-image-175716 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/personalised_cancer_treatment_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/personalised_cancer_treatment_642-600x374.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-175716" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Cancer surgery could one day be more personalised. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAGw8KXBzt4/"&gt;pixelshot/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent discoveries challenge surgeons and oncologists to weigh every decision carefully: not just for what is removed today, but for the immunity and future defences left behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is removing lymph nodes in cancer surgery a bad idea? The answer is complex. For many patients, it's still a good idea and can be lifesaving. But new science teaches us that lymph nodes are more than just staging posts; they may be indispensable for long-term immune protection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The future promises smarter, more strategic surgery, keeping more of the body's natural defence system intact while targeting cancer with precision.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/265557/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/justin-stebbing-1405462"&gt;Justin Stebbing&lt;/a&gt;, Professor of Biomedical Sciences, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/anglia-ruskin-university-1887"&gt;Anglia Ruskin University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/dont-cut-them-out-lymph-nodes-may-be-key-to-cancer-treatment-265557"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 14:01:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxQNTNTUlRZSlZvLUJzTDNKa0VjSllxdHpaU2xZYk0xTjFQZl9MOHpJRnlPYUhKZUtNNzNnVUdTWEU3eEg3TFAtSjRZUzI5NjlvZUdGQi1mSVkyQk9OcDMtQlFtd1EyNmtIM1F6VHlTTW9GTmlqLXpDQmhLS3pZRHNUUTFmOWZZYTJJNENmd3RTc05vMHRURFB5Nw</guid></item><item><title>人们对实验室培育的人类大脑感到震惊-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/lab-grown-human-brain-poll</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-wrapper" data-toc-container&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;Earlier this year, John Hopkins University scientists revealed that they had created something astonishing: a &lt;a href="https://hub.jhu.edu/2025/07/25/hopkins-researchers-develop-whole-brain-organoid/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;miniature whole human brain&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Specifically, it was a type of &lt;a href="https://www.hsci.harvard.edu/organoids" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;organoid&lt;/a&gt;, a small mass of human tissue grown from stem cells meant to mimic the function of our organs — and, most importantly, serve as a test bed to study diseases and new drugs for treatment.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The existence of this lab-grown brain and other similar organoids have gotten some scientists speculating that these little walnuts &lt;a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/can-lab-grown-brains-become-conscious/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;may become conscious in the future&lt;/a&gt; — essentially a soupçon&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;of human sentience in a petri dish — which, of course, carries immense ethical implications and icks a lot of people out.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;That was borne out by a &lt;a href="https://www.livescience.com/health/neuroscience/if-tiny-lab-grown-brains-became-conscious-would-it-still-be-ok-to-experiment-on-them" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;recent poll&lt;/a&gt; conducted by &lt;em&gt;Live Science&lt;/em&gt;, in which &lt;a href="https://www.livescience.com/health/i-honestly-am-not-sure-on-this-at-all-poll-reveals-public-uncertainty-over-experimenting-on-conscious-lab-grown-minibrains" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;657 readers responded&lt;/a&gt; to the question: “If brain organoids become conscious, should we experiment on them?”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Around 23 percent slammed the door shut on the whole idea, saying there’d be zero ethical justification for it. Even if rudimentary, a miniature conscious human brain could have the ability to think and feel pain and fear.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“I really don’t see a breakthrough here worth the literal lives of these created beings once they gain consciousness,” a reader wrote to &lt;em&gt;Live Science&lt;/em&gt;. “I have no mouth and I must scream…”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Another 25 percent said scientists shouldn’t test on organoids that are sentient, but that working on unconscious organoids is fine as long as they’re monitored for any sign of awareness.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Twenty-two percent said experimenting on conscious organoids are fine, but regulations governing their welfare is needed, and 19 percent of readers said no changes are needed in any current rules about handling these organisms. The remainder were on the fence about the question.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;It’s not clear how far along we are towards a brain organoid that has a shred of sentience, but there’s a sense that we’re tiptoeing towards that possibility; previous experiments on organoids were simpler, but now, like in the John Hopkins study, researchers can put together more complex organoids that link together different parts of brain matter. From there, it doesn’t take much to imagine a thought bubbling up from all those lab-grown neurons.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on brains:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://futurism.com/health-medicine/neuroscience-brain-consciousness"&gt;Neuroscientist Says We’re All Wrong About Root of Consciousness in Our Brains&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 13:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE5KWlZRSmNNdnJ5WjNrbTZNSnB3Tkw2SW0zVWJzOXdibnlEa0ZVLVBOLTFfQ2FDaVQ3Sm11Y3paRkxHYVpQX2tEdzA0cXotRkh4QU9ubldKV0hUTW5TMjBuVVkwdFZHb2lFUV8tdXRsMGQ</guid></item><item><title>新的研究发现，情绪健康对于长寿和身体健康同样重要- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/05/health/emotional-well-being-older-adults-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88nk3m007q26p5dfo2ai8d@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When it comes to aging and healthy living, we’re often given the same advice: Eat better, exercise every day and sleep more. But solely focusing on your physical health isn’t enough to achieve longevity, a new study has found.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000k3b6nof0249x6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Researchers looked at older adults’ optimal well-being, which they define as having social support; positive perceptions of aging, physical and mental health, happiness, and life satisfaction; and the ability to carry out daily activities without severe limitations.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000l3b6ngmo12kwt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Our study of over 8,000 older adults found that many who were not in optimal well-being at the start of the study were able to regain it within just three years,” said Dr. Mabel Ho, the study’s first author, in an email, referring to the 1 in 4 older adults whose health significantly improved. “These findings challenge the notion that well-being inevitably declines with age and highlight the potential for positive change later in life.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000m3b6nyzqknj8h@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The study, published on September 24 in the journal &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0329800" target="_blank"&gt;PLOS One&lt;/a&gt;, was a secondary analysis of data collected from the &lt;a href="https://www.clsa-elcv.ca/" target="_blank"&gt;Canadian Longitudinal Study on Aging&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000n3b6nfb2s1tc1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “These findings apply to older adults aged 60 and over who are not currently in optimal health or well-being,” said Dr. Esme Fuller-Thomson, the study’s senior author, in an email. “The study offers hope and practical insights for older adults, caregivers, and policymakers by showing that with the right supports and lifestyle choices, many older adults can regain a high level of well-being even after experiencing sub-optimal well-being.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000o3b6nuqv9zou1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            More than 1 in 5 Americans will be 65 or older by 2040, and nearly 3 in 5 of them will need long-term services and support, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/07/12/health/geriatrician-healthy-aging-wellness"&gt;previous CNN report&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000p3b6nji9la6s0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In 2023, about &lt;a href="https://www.ncoa.org/article/the-top-10-most-common-chronic-conditions-in-older-adults/" target="_blank"&gt;93% of adults&lt;/a&gt; age 65 or older in the United States reported having at least one chronic disease, such as heart disease and diabetes. While not all chronic conditions can be avoided, many can be &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/chronic-disease/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;prevented&lt;/a&gt; by altering your lifestyle.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000q3b6n9oj1tnnu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Individuals who began with strong psychological and emotional well-being were nearly five times more likely to reach optimal overall health by the end of the study,” said Ho, a recent doctoral graduate at the University of Toronto’s Factor-Inwentash Faculty of Social Work and the Institute of Life Course and Aging.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000r3b6n4ea4nlpd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The results “also underscored the critical influence of supportive relationships, socioeconomic conditions, and healthy lifestyle choices such as regular physical activity, not smoking, and good sleep,” she added.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000s3b6nyfut7jw0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But the study’s findings may not be applicable to all adults age 65 and older since the researchers focused their efforts in Canada, where patients have access to universal health care.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000t3b6nbaa7sh73@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “These findings provide valuable insight into aging and well-being in the context of a high-income country with universal healthcare,” Ho said via email. “However, it remains unclear how well these results translate to the United States, where life-long universal healthcare is not available; similarly, more research is needed to understand how older adults in diverse global settings experience and regain well-being in low- and middle-income countries, where healthcare access, social supports, and economic conditions can differ significantly from Canada.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  &lt;h2 class="subheader inline-placeholder subheader-elevate vossi-subheader vossi-subheader--size-h2" data-editable="text" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/subheader/instances/cmg88tyor00183b6nzrxb1w9l@published" data-component-name="subheader" id="taking-a-holistic-approach-to-health-and-aging" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
        Taking a holistic approach to health and aging
&lt;/h2&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000v3b6ntlwsmjie@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Physically, there are &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/05/28/health/live-long-healthy-life-eric-topol-wellness"&gt;three main lifestyle changes&lt;/a&gt; you can implement to achieve healthy aging: exercise, sleep and diet.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000w3b6nwm887ntw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            And while behaviors like &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/09/health/hobbies-social-longevity-wellness"&gt;nutritious eating and strength training&lt;/a&gt; are important, they won’t be as effective if you aren’t also addressing issues of loneliness and maintaining positive relationships.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000x3b6nf86b0dea@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “One of the things I always say to my patients is, believe it or not, there’s no disease, dis-ease or lack of ease, without your mind. The mind-body connection is unbelievably underestimated by Western medicine,” said     Dr. Andrew Freeman, director of cardiovascular prevention and wellness at National Jewish Health in Denver. He was not involved in the study.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000y3b6nbz2bkjpk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Chronically lonely adults age 50 and older have a 56% higher risk of stroke than adults lower on the loneliness scale, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/06/26/health/loneliness-stroke-wellness"&gt;previous CNN report&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya7000z3b6n1f09fp0v@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Stress reduction and frequent socialization were also associated with &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/28/health/cognitive-decline-pointer-study-wellness"&gt;improved cognition&lt;/a&gt; in adults experiencing early-stage Alzheimer’s disease.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700103b6n2czppi2i@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Cultivating strong social connections is an essential component of overall well-being. Lifestyle changes such as quitting smoking and addressing sleep issues like insomnia can also lead to meaningful improvements in health,” said Fuller-Thomson, professor and director of the Institute for Life Course and Aging at the University of Toronto’s Factor-Inwentash Faculty of Social Work.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg8ig0if000a3b6n6ub8ya03@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “By focusing on these key issues, older adults may be able to build resilience and enhance their quality of life, even when managing existing health challenges.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700113b6n523pfs0j@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The study highlights that it’s easier for younger adults to achieve optimal well-being, but that does not mean older adults can’t.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700123b6ns5zcwxeg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Our study shifts the narrative by showing that well-being in older adulthood isn’t static. Many older adults can recover and regain optimal health even after setbacks,” Ho said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700133b6n67dce5ck@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “While previous research has often focused on decline, this adds a new dimension by highlighting the potential for resilience, recovery, and improvement later in life. It emphasizes that aging can include periods of growth and renewed well-being, not just loss.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700143b6nksnkzakb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            And healthy living can start with increasing your steps, said Dr. Joyce Oen-Hsiao, a cardiologist at Yale Medicine, who was not part of the study.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700153b6n7nnb3vv2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “A lot of my elderly patients, their outing is going to the store. So, I’ll say, well, don’t park at the parking spot that’s close — maybe park at the parking spot that’s a little bit further. And then that way you increase your steps, you get a little bit more mobile,” said   Oen-Hsiao, who is also an associate professor of cardiovascular medicine at Yale School of Medicine.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700163b6nca5o60ml@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            No matter your age, you can start making choices to get physically and mentally healthier, experts say.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg88tya700173b6nncs8nn2o@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “If you put your mindset that you’re going to get better, that you’re going to feel better, that you’re going to do better, that you’re going to achieve whatever it is you’re trying to achieve, it makes the odds of that actually happening significantly more,” Freeman said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmg8hjtdu00073b6nw81h9gif@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    Get inspired by a weekly roundup on living well, made simple. Sign up for &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/newsletters/life-but-better?source=nl-acq_article"&gt;CNN’s Life, But Better newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for information and tools designed to improve your well-being.
&lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 13:00:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQcFpsQ1VVQkJISTRsZzNlYVRid3hhRnJDSHpxTjV5cU9RS0RPLWppMkJ6dGxsNl9mQ0ZyTzE5NlUwQmVRSVpvV0hrZWhrVGZHaEJMWTQ5U2hjUFJzQ05WQ3BSS3gzVjNtYS1hcFF1UUxYVFIyanRURTc4bHEwNkNSckZNRnZfZzg</guid></item><item><title>美国最主要的死亡原因，排名-视觉资本家</title><link>https://www.visualcapitalist.com/the-top-causes-of-death-in-the-united-states-ranked/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Visual Capitalist</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 12:12:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQTzNNd3BwRVJGNU0tWEVZekJvNmtlSnA2cnhBeTE2TXZGSGdCM3RCOXh2RkFmREtEZ255aGdkYlBzOWo3TGJ3ZHNZVlE4UlJHOF9HWkVpaWlYbHVpVDJPOThLa1loT2tKbDF2R2FQeUxZZGppb2Z4QWdheE5US0o5Ujc5SzZOd1JPUTBCRUN3</guid></item><item><title>这种“抗衰老”补充剂是新的健康热潮—但您应该服用吗？ -《旧金山纪事报》</title><link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/health/aging-longevity/article/nad-supplement-benefit-age-21055869.php</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="rel"&gt;&lt;section class="rel pb32 -mx20 sm:-mx40 lg:-mx56 x100vw sm:cw-80 lg:cw-112" aria-label="Carousel Gallery"&gt;&lt;div class="rel x100"&gt;&lt;figure role="group" aria-hidden="false" aria-label="Frame 1 of 3" class="rel m0 fdc top tdl300 td300 ttfeio rel o100 vv f x100"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel px20 sm:px0 td300 ttfeio tdl300 o100 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block oy-hidden mh46px"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Postdoctoral researcher Genesis Vega Hormazabal works Thursday in a lab at the Buck Institute for Research on Aging in Novato, which studies age-related disease. Its president and CEO, Dr. Eric Verdin, says the hype around NAD supplements has outpaced the science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 p4ywqby mnh24px"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lea Suzuki/S.F. Chronicle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure role="group" aria-hidden="true" aria-label="Frame 2 of 3" class="rel m0 fdc top tdl300 td300 ttfeio abs o0 vh f x100"&gt;&lt;p class="bgt rel vv o100 y32px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel px20 sm:px0 td300 ttfeio tdl300 o0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block oy-hidden mh46px"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientific manager Durai Sellegounder works in a lab at the Buck Institute for Research on Aging on Thursday in Novato.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 p4ywqby mnh24px"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lea Suzuki/S.F. Chronicle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure role="group" aria-hidden="true" aria-label="Frame 3 of 3" class="rel m0 fdc top tdl300 td300 ttfeio abs o0 vh f x100"&gt;&lt;p class="bgt rel vv o100 y32px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel px20 sm:px0 td300 ttfeio tdl300 o0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block oy-hidden mh46px"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0"&gt;&lt;p&gt;From left, Genesis Vega Hormazabal, postdoctoral researcher; Prasanna Vadhana Ashok Kumaar, associate director, Metalobics Core; Eric Verdin, president and chief executive officer; Durai Sellegounder, scientific manager; and Jingqi Fang, research scientist at the Buck Institute for Research on Aging in Novato on Thursday. The institute is an independent research organization that studies age-related disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 p4ywqby mnh24px"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lea Suzuki/S.F. Chronicle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may have seen wellness influencers touting the benefits of NAD on Instagram — or seen Kendall Jenner and Hailey Bieber getting IV infusions of the compound in an episode of “Keeping Up With the Kardashians.” Some swear NAD supplements give them extra energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers say NAD supplementation shows promise in animal studies, but urge caution because there have yet to be large clinical trials completed in humans that show proven benefits. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what to know about the latest longevity trend. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="A300" data-large-id="CONCERT1" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh600px ais lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh300px lg:ais"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is NAD?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAD, which stands for nicotinamide adenine dinucleotide, is a compound found in all cells of the body, particularly in the mitochondria, the energy centers of cells. NAD plays an important role in energy production, and is needed by sirtuins — proteins involved in cellular repair — to function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because NAD levels decline with age, the theory behind NAD supplementation is to restore NAD levels in the body, which then help sirtuins with cell function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="rel f m0 fdc -mx20 sm:mx0 x100vw sm:x100 mb32"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel pt8 px20 sm:px0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block ya"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buck Institute for Research on Aging research scientist Jingqi Fang, left, talks with Dr. Eric Verdin, the organization’s president and chief executive officer, on Thursday in Novato.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 mr48"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lea Suzuki/S.F. Chronicle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“NAD plays a key role in energy transfer in cells,” said Dr. Eric Verdin of the Buck Institute for Research on Aging in Novato, an independent research organization that studies age-related disease. He likens NAD’s role in the body to that of armored trucks in the economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="CONCERT1" data-large-id="CONCERT2" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh300px ais lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh300px lg:ais"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They take money from the stores and bring it to the bank,” said Verdin, who studies why NAD levels decrease with age. “If that stops, the whole economy grinds to a halt. NAD shuttles energy from one part of the cell to another.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What does research on NAD supplementation show?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAD supplementation appears to be safe, but hasn’t been studied in large controlled studies in humans, said Dr. Michael Fredericson, a sports medicine specialist and co-director of the Longevity Center at Stanford. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most studies on NAD supplementation have been conducted in animals, and have shown it can potentially help DNA repair, neurodegeneration, organ health, insulin sensitivity and metabolism, he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There’s a lot of promise here,” Fredericson said. “That’s why people are so excited about this.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="B300" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh600px ais lg:none"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings in animal studies were particularly exciting because they show that giving high levels of NAD precursors to mice appears to alleviate some diseases associated with aging, like heart attack, stroke, cancers, type 2 diabetes, macular degeneration, Parkinson’s and Alzheimer’s, Verdin said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAD precursors are the building blocks to making NAD. Because the body cannot absorb pure NAD, NAD supplements are given in the form of precursors called NR (nicotinamide riboside) and NMN (nicotinamide mononucleotide). Taking the precursors gives the body the components to make NAD. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some important limitations to these findings in animal studies. For one, animal studies used much higher doses of NAD precursors than the doses that are used for humans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;And second, animal studies don’t directly predict what will work in humans, Verdin said, pointing out that researchers have identified cures for Alzheimer’s and diabetes in mice, but those have not translated to successful therapies for humans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="CONCERT2" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh300px ais lg:none"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The field jumped ahead of itself by selling the supplements,” he said. “The evidence in humans is lacking. It’s not nonexistent, but it hasn’t been as positive as we had seen in animal studies. People have seen some promising effects, but nothing I’d take home to say, ‘Everyone has to now take NAD precursors.’”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What should you know if you’re considering it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s no specific agreed-upon dose for people, but supplement companies generally sell oral NAD supplements at doses around 125 mg to 250 mg per day, which are considered relatively low. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re shopping for a reputable supplement seller, look for companies that have an independent certification of analysis, Verdin said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some wellness centers also offer NAD IV infusions, which experts do not recommend because the body can’t absorb pure NAD, despite some celebrities like Jenner and Bieber extolling the health benefits. NAD infusions may cause more harm than benefit because they can elicit a major immune response, including chest pain, diarrhea and nausea, Fredericson said. This is because the infusion puts a huge amount of NAD straight into the blood serum, where it doesn’t belong, and the body treats it like a foreign substance, he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="S300" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh600px ais lg:none"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s not dangerous, you just feel horrible,” he said. “I’d stay away from the IV pure NAD because not only do you get that massive immune response, but you’ll pee most of it out. If you were going to try it, probably start with the oral forms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fredericson cautioned against taking NAD if you have a history of cancer because in some animal studies, very high doses of NAD may enhance tumor growth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though the doses in those animal studies were much higher than the doses you can find on the market for humans, “it’s just not worth the risk,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAD supplementation can also raise homocysteine levels in the blood, which can be a sign of dysfunctional metabolism. Verdin said this was the reason he stopped taking it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who might benefit?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fredericson has recommended NAD supplementation for some middle-aged and older patients who feel like they’re not healing as well as they used to, or who feel like their energy level is not what it used to be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’m prescribing it cautiously at this point,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main feedback he’s gotten from patients, he said, is that some feel like they have more energy — though that may be a placebo effect. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fredericson himself is taking 250 mg a day, and echoes that observation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s hard to tell. I think my energy’s been a little better than normal, but it’s just so hard to tell because there’s so many factors that go into it. Maybe I’m sleeping better. Maybe it’s in my mind. But I think there’s something to it.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;If research does in fact show that NAD is neuroprotective, “that’s going to be huge,” he said. “We have to wait and see on that. It’s one of those things where we still need more information. In five years it’ll be the biggest hit in the world, or we won’t even be talking about it anymore.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What anti-aging or longevity supplements should you consider instead?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Supplements in general are considered somewhat controversial, as studies have found that many supplements do not contain what the label on the bottle claims. Medical experts generally say supplements aren’t necessary for people who get proper nutrition from their diet.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There are dozens of supplements being touted or sold by different companies, and very few that have been shown to actually have an effect,” Verdin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among the most well-studied, he said, are &lt;a href="https://www.sfchronicle.com/health/article/vitamin-d-calcium-supplements-aging-longevity-20220319.php" data-link="native" class=""&gt;vitamin D&lt;/a&gt;, vitamin B-12 and omega-3 fatty acids. Verdin recommends getting tested to see if you’re deficient in these nutrients, and to consider taking supplements if your levels are too low. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of all, though, the most effective action you can take for aging well is to exercise, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People are looking for a magical pill that will solve their aging problem,” he said. “Physical activity is the magical pill we have today. That has an enormously protective effect. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’d urge people to look at all of this with some degree of circumspection and to not forget what does work, which is great nutrition, physical activity, stress mitigation,” he said. All the things your grandmother told you to do.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn top"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>San Francisco Chronicle</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 11:14:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxOMG9LNEtzTld4SF9IS2ViVTd3cjBGdGtQaVcwN0tQZmUtTzdXVjBsSnFSUXVaLUM4TS1taHFzY25GTnNGNUx6NmoyWWNwNzAzUjhqSllWcnQ2emh5RC1SZVF5XzBsLUYxWmxfV3lrY2VFWFNQd1o2U1YyOW1sWXpjdTdNX0hselZNT0hGTGxwMmRoV2lsWjh0WTJZdWdKaVU</guid></item><item><title>隐藏在大脑中的信号可能提前揭示阿尔茨海默氏症的岁月- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/a-signal-hidden-in-the-brain-may-reveal-alzheimers-years-in-advance</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A team of researchers from Florida International University (FIU) examined a brain protein previously &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.pharmthera.2007.12.004" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;associated with brain inflammation&lt;/a&gt; in Alzheimer's patients, in an effort to gain a deeper understanding of &lt;/span&gt;the relationship between the protein and the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What they discovered could translate into an early signal of neurodegeneration that could eventually lead to dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In mice models of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="175775" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;, elevated levels of &lt;a href="ttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Translocator_protein"&gt;translocator protein&lt;/a&gt; 18 kDa, or TSPO, were found in animals as young as six weeks, which is the equivalent of about 18-20 human years. The increase was found &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Subiculum"&gt;in the subiculum&lt;/a&gt;, a part of the brain crucial for memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/learning-one-word-could-help-prevent-a-third-of-alzheimers-cases"&gt;Learning One Word Could Help Prevent a Third of Alzheimer's Cases&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team found a similar TSPO pattern in human brain tissue taken postmortem from nine people in Colombia &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/man-identified-with-rare-mutation-that-protects-from-alzheimers-disease"&gt;with a genetic mutation&lt;/a&gt; that causes them to develop Alzheimer's disease relatively early, typically in their 30s or 40s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Neuroinflammation is a very early event in Alzheimer's that influences its onset," &lt;a href="https://news.fiu.edu/2025/can-we-detect-alzheimers-disease-decades-before-symptoms-start"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; neuroscientist Tomás Guilarte, from FIU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_175778" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-175778" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/BrainCells.jpg" alt="Brain cell analysis" class="wp-image-175778 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/BrainCells.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/BrainCells-600x288.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-175778" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Cell images showing microglia (blue), TSPO signals (red), and amyloid-beta plaques (cyan). (Martinez-Perez et al., &lt;em&gt;Acta Neuropathol.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If we can use TSPO to detect it early, right at the beginning stages of the disease, it could mean slowing progression or delaying symptoms by five or six years. That's five or six years where someone has a better quality of life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers found higher levels of TSPO in female mice, mirroring data that shows women are &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-is-more-common-in-women-and-this-may-help-explain-why"&gt;more likely to develop Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;. They also observed an increase in TSPO coinciding with the emergence of amyloid-beta plaques – protein clumps strongly associated with the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, the boost in TSPO was almost entirely in the form of immune cells &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Microglia"&gt;called microglia&lt;/a&gt; that were in contact with the plaques, which had both increased in number and produced more TSPO in response to the plaque build-up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The observations provide vital insights into the origins of Alzheimer's, providing clues on the kinds of chemical reactions that might be used to slow or even stop its progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We didn't see any TSPO increase in the other glial cells, like the astrocytes, which reveals the microglia are driving the majority of the inflammatory response," &lt;a href="https://news.fiu.edu/2025/can-we-detect-alzheimers-disease-decades-before-symptoms-start"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Guilarte. "What we believe is happening is something goes wrong with the microglia."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They stop doing their job in removing the plaques and just keep sending out TSPO signals. This constant signal of neuroinflammation is like adding wood to a fire."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's important to note that this study focused on early onset, genetic cases of Alzheimer's, which are in the minority overall. However, the researchers are already working on ways to expand on this study to further pinpoint the role of TSPO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As with many aspects of Alzheimer's, it can be difficult to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-cause-of-alzheimers-could-be-coming-from-within-your-mouth"&gt;untangle the causes&lt;/a&gt; from the consequences, but this brain biomarker may be a big help in getting a clearer picture – and ultimately, perhaps, giving us a vital early alarm bell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One of the biggest problems with Alzheimer's is people see it as a disease of aging, and that impacts when people get diagnosed," &lt;a href="https://news.fiu.edu/2025/can-we-detect-alzheimers-disease-decades-before-symptoms-start"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; neuroscientist Daniel Martinez-Perez, from FIU. "My hope is we can be part of helping people before they are too sick."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1007/s00401-025-02912-4"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Acta Neuropathologica&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 11:01:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxQcVZSVWVTQ3RXa0JwR3pwQVpsMWJYNmFVb2dsSDQwa3c1RXhTczk0S1cxWjc4QVJ4MktLLUdDOFVpTFlOdHFLZXVaYmpXSWFub19OeFpmTDhET2dBcG84RElKTHVxUGlIZ3Zha2NBSC11b3A2ODd4RWlYNElzOXhUQ0xQNmQySURwbDVlMzN6NHJZRTJKRUxUZEhtcXc</guid></item><item><title>他们的父母从未给他们接种过疫苗。作为年轻人，他们面临着一个选择。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/10/05/vaccines-skepticism-childhood-family-impacts/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QC5NMJTF3BHDVAQEYE3PEOPLKE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;At 30 years old, Lacie Madison just assumed she was fully vaccinated her entire life. But when she got a job at a hospital and was required to check her immunity, the doctor called with shocking news: It appeared she was barely vaccinated as a child, if at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HR22XK2CHRB3VPIUBJT6FL2U3E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“I just said, ‘Are you kidding me?’” recalled Madison, now 39.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 10:32:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxQMlRibnl0TlpHX2FXVkExd29EVF9SdU9BbDQtMjJxWEtvcUpyMEdrVVdERlFVSjZBbF9NSF9sZENmMVBhd25MemNaN1dPMVczUUo2X0xDaWtaUWZvVlljMlM5MDBOdXpMQzVvWlJ3QXJOSkZqUDFEdzR1cml4bDJtNlNYVHJ1RjBBeWlDM2NDN1NZdTFldVk3NUtR</guid></item><item><title>117岁的玛丽亚·莫雷拉（ Maria Morera ） ： “她没有魔法基因，这可能是她每天吃3次的零食-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/maria-morera-who-lived-till-117-ate-3-snacks-regularly-she-had-no-magic-gene-the-secret-was-in-her-gut/photostory/124318974.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;For over two decades, Maria enjoyed three servings of yoghurt daily, morning, afternoon, and night. It wasn’t part of a fad or diet trend; it was simply something she liked. But this small act turned out to have an enormous impact on her health.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers discovered that Maria’s gut microbiome, her inner ecosystem of bacteria, was similar to that of someone decades younger. It was rich in Bifidobacterium, a beneficial bacterium known for reducing inflammation and promoting better metabolism. These bacteria thrive in yoghurt containing strains like Streptococcus thermophilus and Lactobacillus bulgaricus, which she consumed regularly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Cell Reports Medicine (2024), this consistent intake of probiotic-rich yoghurt possibly reshaped her gut environment, keeping it youthful and resilient, a key factor in her healthy aging.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 09:43:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAJBVV95cUxPTzUxbkJVY0RySXRCdks1Tk9UZEczTEF5QzZRQVBGczJSOHhvU09hRkNOX0lKcnV4eUVCYjRQa1lnYVhGYkFha3FBLXBoRUtOSjZxX3hlbW93RnVCTzlJZnFmNW4zRWdyWElBcTJ4amZITUZRLXZwM093dlh2ZmpQLU9YZFlNNjR2WlBKRmtYbm1VTjZ4OXpnZWs2cEJFMmhZZVU1OWNycVB1dG51STVBZFJ2LUhQdmo5RU1VQ0ZHbTBpWlBzY2lyWXF4V2FXdWpFWE9BeWxVcTl3bkJIYWxyQTA5dGQycF84V2JxVW5JbldJT0tSSU9scU1VQnNEdUNqTERsNXpPVmJVb05KX25jRlgyVGdLeHQyRWx4X3JWbWxTVzdmUDUzSdIBsAJBVV95cUxNeGVfQWhaamRXRnNpM0lmSmI5QkdmYzNPX1ZfYWlsdG9oM0wtU3ZPc2w4ZVRKa2x0OXF1cGJkM1h0N25COFplMXVIY3NJSWs1Z2JlNnIwS0J6Y1VMOGtxQ0YyclFfVE9nQ2Zka3J2ZXlyQkJhRi1vamV5UGlwUVRHREVaRlFJdnNIdy1GNUhyTUU0NkxqalJFak84YmlQM09Mc1BWLXBIZGZ2Z1NvU2FNNkp3ME1PZTZxS0tvY0FOOEc2NFcxSFFjOXdkNGpwb0ZWTnVyWC1TQ1h3Tmsya3Rua0htd2sxU3M0YlN4c055c016NHh5dUZuX2doMVZHbDNFZUZybHAzWEJ2SjBBXzZGRnNNV0lSODlBM2trZE1pbU1TUTlfaE1taEhxVFd5Sjl2</guid></item><item><title>冠状病毒病例激增： “我确信自己会死” - Ynetnews</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/health_science/article/sytkc91plg</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-contents="true"&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="1p6s2-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1p6s2-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1p6s2-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“I’m a strong woman, but it just crushed me. I had a very high fever that wouldn’t go down, muscle aches and weakness. I couldn’t get out of bed,” said Dana Gabai, 39, of Ramla, who contracted COVID-19 last month. “I had a headache like I’d never had before, as if my head was swelling to giant proportions.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="fci7d-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="fci7d-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="fci7d-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Gabai says she had previously taken only one dose of a COVID-19 vaccine. “At the time people were saying these were experimental vaccines and that the long-term effects were unknown, so I decided not to get the follow-up doses,” she said. This was the first time she had COVID-19. “This is not a mild illness at all. I was sure I was going to die. I was in bed for eight days like a corpse.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="f750r-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide firstImageInArticle firstImageInArticleBody"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.BJexd4i1Teg" id="image_ArticleImageData.BJexd4i1Teg"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;4&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.BJexd4i1Teg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/05/BkfEMYJ6el/BkfEMYJ6el_0_165_731_836_0_x-large.jpg" alt="דנה גבאי חלתה בקורונה" title="Dana Gabbai contracted COVID-19 last month (Photo: Private album) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.BJexd4i1Teg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/05/BkfEMYJ6el/BkfEMYJ6el_0_165_731_836_0_x-large.jpg" alt="דנה גבאי חלתה בקורונה" title="Dana Gabbai contracted COVID-19 last month (Photo: Private album) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Dana Gabbai contracted COVID-19 last month&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Private album&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="8o2q0-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="8o2q0-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="8o2q0-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Gil Abraham, 42, of Hod Hasharon also caught COVID-19 a few weeks ago and describes a severe, prolonged illness. “I’m vaccinated and this was the third time I got it, and this time it hit me really hard,” he said. “For two days I had a high fever that wouldn’t break, and they called an ambulance because I felt I couldn’t breathe. I had strong heart palpitations and irregular breathing, and I writhed in body pain.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="db6u5-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="db6u5-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="db6u5-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;He said he encountered indifference when he arrived at the hospital. “They closed me behind a curtain. I vomited and felt like I was choking, but the doctor looked at me for a second and just said there was nothing to be done, that it was COVID, that I’d get fluids and painkillers — and sent me home,” he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="hpb1-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.BkgkT4okpeg" id="image_ArticleImageData.BkgkT4okpeg"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;4&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.BkgkT4okpeg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/05/SJxmj5yalg/SJxmj5yalg_0_309_961_540_0_x-large.jpg" alt="גיל אברהם חלה בקורונה" title="Gil Abraham lost his sense of taste (Photo: Private album) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.BkgkT4okpeg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/05/SJxmj5yalg/SJxmj5yalg_0_309_961_540_0_x-large.jpg" alt="גיל אברהם חלה בקורונה" title="Gil Abraham lost his sense of taste (Photo: Private album) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Gil Abraham lost his sense of taste&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Private album&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="enb0t-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="enb0t-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="enb0t-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Abraham continued to feel unwell in the days that followed. “My body hurt so much, even the pads of my fingers on my hands and feet,” he said. He also reported loss of taste. “Everything I ate tasted like rust. I lost a lot of weight.” He had difficulty walking even short distances because of breathing problems. He only began to feel better after about 10 days. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="2adk5-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2adk5-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2adk5-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“This is not a mild illness, and there isn’t enough awareness that there is a wave of illness,” Abraham said. “I didn’t believe in COVID before. The other times I said, ‘OK, it’s a mild flu,’ but this time it was a level up. I never imagined I’d need an ambulance. I have no underlying conditions. I’m healthy and I exercise.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="88m01-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="88m01-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="88m01-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Health funds are reporting a rise in cases. Maccabi said its September daily average was 219 diagnosed patients, up from 162 per day in August — an increase of 35%. It said the figures are based on weekdays only and reflect only patients who reported to their family doctor; some patients use at-home tests and do not report results to a physician.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="4ulag-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4ulag-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4ulag-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Leumit said cases rose 200% from July to September, with 300 COVID diagnoses in September compared with 100 in July. Clalit said relatively few people report COVID illness to community doctors, but it noted a rise in hospitalizations. Meuhedet reported a 10% increase in patients from August to September and a nearly threefold jump from July to September.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="46klp-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.ryl3kHjy6ex" id="image_ArticleImageData.ryl3kHjy6ex"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;4&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.ryl3kHjy6ex" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2023/09/06/ByDftiSRn/ByDftiSRn_0_73_1000_563_0_x-large.jpg" alt="בדיקת קורונה" title="Coronavirus test (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.ryl3kHjy6ex" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2023/09/06/ByDftiSRn/ByDftiSRn_0_73_1000_563_0_x-large.jpg" alt="בדיקת קורונה" title="Coronavirus test (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Coronavirus test&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="7k4tl-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7k4tl-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7k4tl-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The Health Ministry said there has been a moderation in the increase in COVID hospitalizations. “According to data received from 15 general hospitals, as of mid-September there was about a 10% rise compared with mid-August, versus a 40% rise in the previous month,” the ministry said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="61oai-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="61oai-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="61oai-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“We’ve seen a slightly more significant wave of COVID-19 over the past three months, and we are now in the midst of that wave,” said Professor Tal Brosh, head of infectious diseases at the Assuta Ashdod public hospital and head of the Health Ministry’s epidemic response team. He sought to reassure the public: “These are not the huge waves we saw in 2021-22 when hundreds of thousands of Israelis were infected one after another and hospital wards filled. Since the start of COVID there has always been ongoing illness, sometimes a bit more and sometimes a bit less. It comes in waves, and most of the time it simply doesn’t interest the public.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="nti8-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="nti8-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="nti8-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;He said the current rise is seen mainly among hospitalized patients, most of them older people with underlying illnesses. “We almost never see hospitalized COVID patients who do not have underlying conditions, and certainly we do not see young people hospitalized with COVID as we did before vaccines, when people in their 40s and 50s were hospitalized with severe COVID,” he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="7l5mk-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7l5mk-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7l5mk-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Still, he said, deaths are occurring among older people and other at-risk groups. Brosh noted that in 2024 COVID caused more illness and deaths than any other respiratory virus, including influenza. “It’s important to remember that COVID is not a seasonal disease, meaning infections occur throughout the year,” he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="afn77-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta wrapped"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleWrappedImageComponenta"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleWrappedImageData.B1xcXrsk6gx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/08/07/SyLVf11GOxg/SyLVf11GOxg_225_44_544_725_0_medium.jpg" alt="פרופ' טל ברוש" title="Professor Tal Brosh&amp;amp;nbsp; (Photo: Private album) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="caption" contenteditable="false"&gt;Professor Tal Brosh &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span disabled class="credit" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Private album&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="acflt-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="acflt-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="acflt-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;According to the National Center for Disease Control report for the week ending September 27, the number and percentage of positive COVID samples among hospitalized patients remain high compared with most of the past year. That week reported 92 new cases, about 8.3% of all hospitalized patients in 11 monitored hospitals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="4482u-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4482u-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4482u-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The prominent variants in the current wave are Nimbus (NB.1.8.1) and Stratus (XFG), from the JN.1 lineage, which are also seen globally and have become dominant. Dr. Efrat Wexler, head of primary care at Meuhedet, said the variants appear more transmissible but there is no evidence they are more aggressive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="77ruc-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="77ruc-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="77ruc-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“We hear from some patients that the illness is worse compared with previous infections, with marked weakness or increased mucus production, cough and runny nose, but we have not found that the current strains produce symptoms unusual beyond what we have known so far — high fever, dry or productive cough, fatigue and weakness, muscle and throat pain, and nasal congestion,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="6lu9r-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6lu9r-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6lu9r-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Brosh said new variants continue to evolve while immunity wanes over time. He noted that most young people were vaccinated with three doses about four years ago. “In those years they may not have encountered the virus, meaning they did not develop infection-derived immunity, and therefore they experience more significant illness.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="6t6n2-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6t6n2-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6t6n2-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Against the backdrop of rising cases, Brosh also pointed to falling COVID vaccination rates in recent years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="38qlc-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="38qlc-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="38qlc-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt; “If in 2020-21 Israel was a model for the world and we carried out the fastest, most comprehensive vaccination campaign, in the past year our figures are among the worst in Western countries,” he said. “Last year fewer than 50,000 Israelis were vaccinated, compared with 60%-70% of adults vaccinated in Scandinavia, and even in the United States, despite strong vaccine hesitancy, about 40% of at-risk people were vaccinated, whereas in Israel the figure is almost zero.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="bl1m4-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="bl1m4-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="bl1m4-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;He said the main reason for low vaccination uptake is a lack of public awareness and guidance. “We did a very poor job in the past two years. The Health Ministry and the health funds failed in outreach to at-risk groups about the need to get a COVID vaccine each year, similar to influenza. So even people who see the value in vaccines are not getting vaccinated because they don’t even know they should,” according to Brosh.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="76e2q-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="d2nbd-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="d2nbd-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="d2nbd-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;He also blamed rising anti-vaccine sentiment — a growing phenomenon in Israel and worldwide, especially regarding COVID vaccines. “During the pandemic many felt the vaccine was imposed on them, and at the same time a lot of misinformation against vaccines spread. I’m convinced that even if we run a very good campaign now, many people will still be afraid to vaccinate, and we must act on this,” he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="39fd-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="39fd-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="39fd-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Under updated Health Ministry guidance, COVID vaccination is recommended for people 65 and older and for those 6 months to 64 years who belong to risk groups: people with chronic illnesses including kidney disease, chronic lung disease and heart disease; smokers; and residents of geriatric institutions, nursing homes and assisted living.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="d6tsi-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="d6tsi-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="d6tsi-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Brosh said the updated recommendations align with other countries such as Britain, the United States and the Nordic countries. For people 65 and older who live in geriatric institutions, nursing homes or assisted living, an additional vaccine dose is recommended after six months — effectively two doses a year. Two doses a year are also recommended for people 75 and older regardless of health status. People who are not in risk groups may also be vaccinated if they wish to reduce their risk of infection and illness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="5ndu9-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5ndu9-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5ndu9-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Starting next month, the vaccines available through the health funds will be Novavax — a vaccine that uses the coronavirus spike protein produced in the lab. After injection the body recognizes the protein as foreign and learns to fight it. “This vaccine also underwent scientific trials and is very safe to use,” Brosh said. “There are also financial considerations that shouldn’t be ignored regarding the cost of vaccines and the choice of these vaccines.” The Novavax vaccine is authorized for people 12 and older, which will require the Health Ministry to find solutions for children in at-risk groups.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="cg12d-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="cg12d-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="cg12d-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;As last year, the vaccines to be administered target the JN.1 strain, in line with international organizations and the Health Ministry’s advisory committee on infectious diseases and vaccines. “The understanding is that the changes the virus made over the past year are not very dramatic, so it’s likely the vaccines will be effective against the strains currently circulating,” Brosh said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="3b8po" data-offset-key="5206k-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5206k-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5206k-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Wexler summed up: “The coronavirus is not going away soon, and vaccination significantly reduces the risk of severe illness, complications and hospitalization.” She stressed: “Anyone who is sick should avoid going to crowded places and participating in gatherings. That simple step of personal responsibility can reduce many infections.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 08:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE9yZnc1Zzl2TkdmN2JqcUF1R1BTRkNFVUJBREpEbzZsQ01ScW9RQk02MkZwQ3B2Qm5HQkVEcWx2MzJUSUNuMmd6TnEzZmNEdEw1cWdTRDNEdXFXN2lFN05jb1ROODdBTkpyeXc</guid></item><item><title>哈佛大学训练有素的胃肠病学家揭示了10种最佳的气体和腹胀食物-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/diet/harvard-trained-gastroenterologist-reveals-10-best-anti-bloating-foods/articleshow/124316547.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Has this ever happened to you that the stomach feels uncomfortable and heavy right after meals? Well you’re not the only one facing it. Bloating is a problem millions of adults are facing everyday, as per Harvard. However, small changes can help relieve the discomfort. Harvard trained gastroenterologist Dr. Saurabh Sethi suggests 10 best foods that can help reduce bloating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bloating occurs when excess air or gas buildup gets trapped in the digestive tract or when gut muscles fail to move food efficiently. This can be triggered by eating too fast and swallowing air, consuming gas-producing foods like beans, onions, or carbonated drinks or food intolerances. Sometimes hormonal changes can also lead to bloating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Bloated tummy woes? Common remedies to get rid of gas and bloating&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is that certain foods can actively soothe the digestive system by providing enzymes that break down food efficiently. Here’s a detailed list of 10 foods that can beat bloating, as per gastroenterologist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="Credits: Canva" msid="124316600" width="" title="Credits: Canva " placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-124316600,resizemode-4/credits-canva.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;Credits: Canva &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;10 foods to beat bloating:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Kiwi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kiwi is rich in fiber content and contains the actinidin enzyme, which aids protein digestion. A study published in the Journal of Nutritional Science found that consuming two kiwis daily improved bowel movements in individuals with mild constipation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-type="in_view" class="  "&gt;&lt;div class="EEW3_ timeline_pollWrapper_as " data-scrollga="scroll#poll_view"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="hLnAH"&gt;Poll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="KEEGr"&gt;Which of these foods do you think helps relieve bloating the best?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Papaya&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The papain enzyme is packed with digestive support. This enzyme helps break down protein and support digestion. Clinical studies suggest that a small serving of fresh papaya is a good option to reduce bloating after a protein-heavy meal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Pineapple&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A small serving of fresh pineapple after a big meal or added to salads can help digestion for some people. Pineapple is a food source of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11243481/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;bromelain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, a group of enzymes that digest protein. According to WebMD, bromelain can aid in digestion and reduce inflammation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="Credits: Canva" msid="124316607" width="" title="Credits: Canva " placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-124316607,resizemode-4/credits-canva.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;Credits: Canva &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Cucumber&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cucumbers are high in water content and contain fiber. Their hydrating effects also help flush out excess sodium, which can contribute to water retention and bloating. Add cucumber to meals in the form of salads to get benefits. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Chia seeds&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chia seeds are packed with fiber, and when consumed with water, these seeds form &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/nutrition/chia-seed-benefits-what-you-need-to-know?" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;gel-like consistency&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; in the gut that ultimately helps soften stool and maintain regularity. However, individuals with certain health conditions, such as low blood pressure or kidney disease, should consult a healthcare provider before consuming chia seeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Quinoa&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quinoa is a whole grain that contains prebiotic fibers. These fibers can promote the growth of beneficial gut bacteria. A study published in PubMed Central found that quinoa's bioactive compounds can improve intestinal microflora. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Oats&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study published in PubMed Central found that beta-glucan-rich oats or oat-based products in a diet significantly decrease the blood lipid profile and blood pressure by regulating insulin metabolism. One can enjoy Fennel seeds that have been traditionally used to relieve bloating and gas. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Ginger&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ginger has been used as an aid to digestion for ages. A study found that ginger significantly reduced gastrointestinal pain and improved digestion. These properties can help relieve bloating. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Peppermint tea or oil&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peppermint oil relaxes smooth muscle in the gut and can reduce spasms and trapped gas. Several clinical trials show benefits for abdominal pain and bloating, particularly in IBS. To consume, one can try peppermint tea or after consultation, may consume enteric-coated peppermint oil capsules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Fennel seeds&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fennel seeds have been traditionally used to relieve bloating and gas. A study by NIH found that fennel oil was effective in reducing symptoms of irritable bowel syndrome, including bloating and gas. To consume these one can chew some fennel seeds after meals or sip fennel tea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;These dietary adjustments can help alleviate mild bloating. However, individuals who feel constant bloating, accompanied with unintentional weight loss, persistent severe pain, blood in stool, or recurrent vomiting, must consult with a healthcare professional as these can indicate conditions like celiac disease, SIBO, IBD, ovarian pathology, or obstruction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and should not replace professional medical advice. Always consult a healthcare provider for persistent digestive symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 05:32:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9gFBVV95cUxQOFBoeVlKZk01VlBuY00zeVJIRU5xRHhuOGxYdUJlTzVSXzhnWktVSFNoeFlvYlI3SlJPMjFmRDJFVXhuX0UwLTFvOHl4c2RuV2NJeWRZTGlHd3hoU0RNWHk5R2ItekotYVA0bFE5WG4xQWFWSGxsU1RVVXdjRnRqTUFFeE1ETGE5cEFLR21qNUJ4UEJSVVMxbUg0U0RESEFBaC1GdmpPQ054a29qRFNHOVJQcDNJLUw1QWxFSWRIYll5bmd1aGtfODJpM2JTQ3lpVk1UQzJ6VlhHRXNlQ1poSlRONkNWN2tsdjZuOWdhcjQzQy1MVkE</guid></item><item><title>心脏病专家揭示了心力衰竭的惊人原因：不，不是高血压或动脉阻塞-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/cardiologist-reveals-surprising-cause-of-heart-failure-no-its-not-high-blood-pressure-or-clogged-arteries/articleshow/124315810.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart failure is one of the leading causes of death worldwide. When we hear of heart failure we often think of clogged arteries and heart attacks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, there is another uncommon factor that triggers heart failure. Recently, cardiologist Dmitry Yaranov, revealed a surprising risk factor that many do not know about. "It’s not blocked arteries. Not high blood pressure. Not a heart attack," he has posted on Instagram. "Most people are misdiagnosed for years. They’re told it’s “hypertension,” “age,” or “just back pain.” They bounce from clinic to clinic… while the heart quietly declines," he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/colon-cancer-this-simple-test-can-save-your-life-a-top-us-doc-says/photostory/124328295.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Colon cancer: THIS simple test can save your life, a top US doc says&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/scientists-find-excess-of-one-brain-protein-may-predict-alzheimers-years-in-advance/articleshow/124322962.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Scientists find excess of one brain protein may predict Alzheimer’s years in advance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/top-5-best-supplements-for-gut-health/photostory/124320096.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Top 5 best supplements for gut health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Heart Failure Warning: 4 Symptoms You Might Be Overlooking&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He then reveals the condition as amyloidosis, a protein that infiltrates the heart, stiffens it, and gradually shuts it down from the inside out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most Americans have never heard of cardiac amyloidosis, but this rare condition is becoming more recognized as an underlying cause of heart failure—especially in older adults. Simply put, amyloidosis happens when misfolded proteins (amyloid) build up in your organs, including your heart, and make it harder for your heart to pump blood effectively. Doctors are calling it an “underdiagnosed” condition that can mimic more common issues like heart failure with preserved ejection fraction (HFpEF), atrial fibrillation, or even hypertensive heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-type="in_view" class="  "&gt;&lt;div class="EEW3_ timeline_pollWrapper_as " data-scrollga="scroll#poll_view"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="hLnAH"&gt;Poll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="KEEGr"&gt;Were you aware of cardiac amyloidosis prior to reading this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is amyloidosis?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amyloidosis is a condition where abnormal proteins, called amyloid fibrils, fold incorrectly and deposit in tissues and organs. When these deposits build up in the heart, it’s known as cardiac amyloidosis. It can also affect the kidneys, liver, and nervous system, but when it hits the heart, things get serious fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two main types that affect the heart are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;AL Amyloidosis (Light Chain Amyloidosis): Caused by abnormal plasma cells in the bone marrow producing misfolded light chain proteins.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ATTR Amyloidosis (Transthyretin Amyloidosis): Caused by a faulty or unstable transthyretin (TTR) protein, either from a genetic mutation (hereditary ATTR) or from aging (wild-type ATTR).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How cardiac amyloidosis affects the heart&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think of your heart muscles like stretchy rubber bands that expand and contract with every beat. Amyloid deposits make those bands stiff and less flexible. The heart walls get thicker, not from muscle growth, but from sticky protein buildup. As a result, the heart struggles to fill properly (diastolic dysfunction) and eventually can’t pump out enough blood (systolic dysfunction).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Common cardiac amyloidosis symptoms include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shortness of breath, especially during activity or when lying flat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Swelling in the legs, ankles, or abdomen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fatigue or weakness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dizziness or fainting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Irregular heartbeat (atrial fibrillation is common)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chest pressure or fullness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fluid retention and “water weight” gain&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;These symptoms often mimic heart failure, which is why amyloidosis is frequently misdiagnosed, especially in older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This isn’t rare. It’s just rarely diagnosed. And for many patients, early recognition is the only shot at a better outcome," warns the cardiologist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 03:27:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgJBVV95cUxQVXhnTTBNZlEwMHl6WWVnV2QxZkhRY0ltY25qVFlmM0hBQl9VUkRjTFlwWlpJNUJ2ZFIxbHpRRTB3TVJDbXpKYy1ibTcxNE1odURhZlZheUc0YmZDeHl5blpFUC01YWRVNlF2OWVoMHFkY0pkTnpaTnhZSkt3UzJDQ3dLRXZkUWk2UHpKTDVLbFNISWlFTVBPUzNNcEtSZzRnX2dEOGd5TlA2UlhKRkdFQk9tQWhhb0NyVTh0ZzYyb1dYS2FFMFNTV1JubWZyanlhWEZ4anJJdGlKY3FiZEZOOC1vMFR5Y2NsWlltbkF2aDJQbGFLZUpWS0otNGktRGRtWG16cmZYTEhVeWo2dWhJX25JNnJpeUszMkE3MUJqUnMyQ3BCcWxNNlZhX1lCUdIBswJBVV95cUxNWGl0aGJyTnAtUjNHcVZVZUlETjZ5WXpValpEX2JuUUZoVGN4Y0IyVlhDYVhELWt3SFVIczdtQmNIOVNZNFdZckZKVHRmMlFLcld5T0Z3S0MzalU3SnAwYXh6NVlLZV80aTZYdERWeXpqNjdwMUtDaEpQclF2cTVnbVJvcTlIU1dXcjBoZUpXSlJWY2Rka0gyX0Z5YXp3N3ljY2gxZTJKc0tSWmJncGxOU2VzWXNXSnlxUkFJdWRpTUR0dnB5NVJkLUNFTVpMR0VEaVhsTjltNURuWmx6eUp3VTlFZ2daYnA2a2Z4ckF2OGZWc0IyZTMtTGdVSVIxSGZlb2d4YnNBYzV4RXdPX2pkRTJLcUZRaldpbERjMkRtMXlEX2c5NFlCZmhGUkk5Zm1nYWdj</guid></item><item><title>一位长寿专家表示，营养素缺乏可能对健康和寿命产生“深远影响” -需要注意以下五点- Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://www.fitandwell.com/nutrition/a-longevity-expert-says-nutrient-deficiencies-can-have-a-profound-effect-on-health-and-lifespan-here-are-five-to-watch-out-for</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p id="7b58b023-59ed-481e-be3b-38b2fa74acc7"&gt;Nutrient and mineral deficiencies can have a big impact on your day-to-day health, often making you feel more tired, weakening your immune system and generally preventing your body from working at full capacity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And according to Dr Matt Kaeberlein, a scientist, longevity expert and founder of healthtech company &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.optispan.life/" data-url="https://www.optispan.life/" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Optispan&lt;/a&gt;, nutrient and mineral deficiencies can also impact your long-term health. “Nutrient deficiencies may sound like a minor issue, but they can have profound effects on both healthspan and lifespan,” he tells &lt;em&gt;Fit&amp;amp;Well&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="7b58b023-59ed-481e-be3b-38b2fa74acc7-2"&gt;“Think of it this way: your body is a complex machine that depends on a steady supply of essential vitamins, minerals and amino acids to keep its systems running. When those inputs are missing, the machinery starts to wear down faster.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Kaberlein, most deficiencies are “partial and chronic”. This means that although they may not have a significant impact on daily life, they may be gradually affecting your health. “[This] quietly increases vulnerability to cardiovascular disease, dementia, infections and cancers. Over decades, these small cracks in the foundation can significantly shorten both lifespan and the years of life lived in good health,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kaberlein flagged five nutrient deficiencies that are both common and have particularly negative consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-1-iron" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-1-iron"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Iron&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check id="ef0760e7-1cd7-4dac-95f7-d290c155d345"&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images / bit245)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="732cfc11-3bea-4bf9-9804-d80ae023aa70"&gt;“Chronic iron deficiency causes anemia, reducing oxygen delivery. This not only causes fatigue but also forces the heart to work harder, increasing risk of heart failure and earlier death,” says Kaeberlein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iron-rich foods include red meat, poultry, fish, beans, lentils and dark leafy greens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-WXSgj9g3nnLxJZ8fBVrfTf" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-WXSgj9g3nnLxJZ8fBVrfTf slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a id="elk-2-vitamin-d" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-2-vitamin-d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Vitamin D&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="97571ec2-601d-4065-8283-db932662ac5f"&gt;“Low vitamin D or calcium accelerates bone loss, raising fracture risk and mortality,” says Kaeberlein. “Inadequate vitamin D accelerates bone loss, leading to osteoporosis and fractures. Hip fractures in older adults carry a 20-30% one-year mortality rate, so preventing this deficiency can literally save years of life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your skin is able to make vitamin D when exposed to sunlight, but you can also get it from some foods including oily fish and egg yolks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-3-folate" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-3-folate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Folate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check id="26be9de8-6446-484d-8a0f-0c90bb14bdb5"&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images / Ekaterina Goncharova)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="0c44b72a-9af2-4555-9a75-2fb1d6a9d20e"&gt;“Folate is essential for DNA synthesis and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DNA_methylation" target="_blank" data-url="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DNA_methylation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;methylation&lt;/a&gt;,” says Kaeberlein. “Low folate levels increase DNA damage and impair repair, raising risks for cancers and cardiovascular disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Populations with chronic folate deficiency consistently show higher mortality,” he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Folate is in foods like dark leafy green vegetables, beans, lentils and citrus fruits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-4-selenium" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-4-selenium"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4. Selenium&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="6faf310b-9445-401f-a742-3a8c33832ed7"&gt;“Selenium is a trace mineral that supports antioxidant defenses and thyroid function. Low selenium intake has been associated with higher rates of certain cancers and poorer survival outcomes,” says Kaeberlein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brazil nuts contain high amounts of selenium, as do some types of seafood and lean meats, such as beef and pork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-5-omega-3" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-5-omega-3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;5. Omega-3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="d3568ec9-2027-4a22-9c1a-50544d2f7bf7"&gt;“Deficiencies in marine omega-3s (EPA and DHA) are linked to increased risk of &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/arrhythmia/about-arrhythmia" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/arrhythmia/about-arrhythmia" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;arrhythmias&lt;/a&gt;, heart attacks and sudden cardiac death,” says Kaeberlain. “Even modest supplementation lowers cardiovascular mortality in multiple studies.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll mostly find omega-3 in oily fish, but you can also find it in flaxseeds and chia seeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-should-everyone-be-taking-supplements" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-should-everyone-be-taking-supplements"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Should everyone be taking supplements?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="04223a27-37bf-453d-be15-d7eaf0e3a127"&gt;It’s best to get the vitamins, nutrients and minerals you need from a varied diet, but given the risks of nutritional deficiencies, you’d be forgiven for thinking you should turn to supplements to play it safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, it’s not that simple. “Too much of some of these nutrients can be detrimental,” says Kaeberlein. “There’s a lower bound and an upper bound, and you want to be in that range. You don't want to be above the range, or that can have negative health consequences as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kaeberlein is an advocate of blood tests to establish whether you have any nutrient, vitamin or mineral deficiencies. Generally, you can acquire a blood test from your general health practitioner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You should know what your levels are, and if you are deficient or suboptimal, supplement into the optimal range,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9gFBVV95cUxNaU5jeW44RVIzaTJiWjdJdTNTdEpoelVLMlBvdWlqaE94NTl1VjI4OHFmYnRETktrb2lzMVhKSlRMM0NuOTBBRDFpdC1DdjkzVWh1LW81emYzcHRBeHYwNE9kU0Q3ZlRGOVV6eEE4RV82Unlmb1EwWndyOEtvQjZXMWFmMjZUQzJ3Uk13OWhiWm52RkdZQWlNN0h0R2lsMXdSUVlLa3hjQmd0ZTVHd2pzRUFoMjNUUEJWRjFHNWlBVVhNaWsxTERiUHBpd1lGa05MLU5mZVZGMTJUNWZ5OGxPbF9vUFpLM3g3UDFqbXowNTBhcS1jaXc</guid></item></channel></rss>