<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>帕金森病：常见咳嗽糖浆可减缓认知能力下降和痴呆症-印度时报 | Parkinson’s disease: Common cough syrup revealed to slow down cognitive decline and dementia - The Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimgJBVV95cUxOTUJKYVdoY1VCNG1HWV9iMXlNY0YxZ1Q0Ql9EQjRmNkZ5WXd2RWp3aFJGLVFtRFFkbFZtZXhFb0NWcFF6aXJKLUlLVzRXU0xwQktYN3ptYUpQa21xc3Bzam5QWEtSUFZUUmJLRFhfNjlwZUNZMEQ2RjEteGZRSXpuZDlIMXRsZnJ4Q2VxNHA2eDIwc1ctZzh1RXFwZ0oyS0RXNlpoNUNURUFoLU5vdkpXWWthcmZwTjBoNnBPQW9vUDBVbF9ueFRjS0FKRjZsOThHZ0FSVUFydWJrNlZUdUZXMldqLXhlTkdTYWNTNm1rNDVvR3NJUEQtZXUxbVVkZDRXSVFmRUp0aGg4TC16cWd5S3BGMUdBbUdqbFHSAZ8CQVVfeXFMT3BmM0JLUGFycXJjbGFWMGRvU3VXbTZaOTRpUmpWWVBEakZTTENCMy02VmtFR3l1N2hkQWp4TjZFRmtEcVI2YldUcTMtcFNvSW5mMEdqNkpSV1ExSG92UFFfZXNQMVo0QjhUY2Z0N3V1c3QwaTdFMG0wTVFOVFV6Z3dPYzlyNXhfbVZzYWJ3YVN2anZZUlNkdzd4SW9YMUlDTXNZUmdscjRQTXZnbEgtMUtVNktLdUNtcjJINGdjV24tOUZYbmlzWWxvaVRIY05tVy1La2xuV0kyR2h4SFg2Qlhpekl4T2RlNUYyZ2ZVaUdWWWtuaUt4VEVLQmFzZVdpblBueTJhSFl5cDRnT3lnZW85NW1fZEJJeHhNNjMzVjA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parkinson's disease (PD) is a progressive and complex neurodegenerative disorder that affects movement. It is narked not only by motor symptoms – such as tremors, stiffness, and bradykinesia – but also by cognitive decline. PD is also characterized by the degeneration and death of nerve cells in the brain that produce dopamine, a chemical messenger crucial for smooth and coordinated muscle movements. This loss of dopamine leads to a variety of motor and non-motor symptoms. Moreover, up to half of people with PD develop Parkinson’s disease dementia (PDD) within a decade, with symptoms ranging from memory loss and confusion to hallucinations and mood disturbances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, a groundbreaking phase 2 clinical trial has revealed that a common cough medicine can stabilize psychiatric symptoms and potentially slow cognitive decline in PDD patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read on to know more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The recent discovery&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a clinical trial, Ambroxol, a common cough medicine (used in Europe), has shown promise in slowing cognitive decline in people with Parkinson’s disease dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 12-month study conducted by researchers at Lawson Research Institute found that Ambroxol helped stabilise psychiatric symptoms, improved cognitive function, and protected against brain damage in genetically at-risk participants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaneurology/article-abstract/2835760" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;JAMA Neurology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; compared the outcome of the expectorant Ambroxol with a placebo among participants with Parkinson’s disease dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While primary and secondary outcomes were similar, participants on the placebo experienced worsening neuropsychiatric symptoms compared to symptoms remaining the same in the intervention group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results also showed a possible improvement in cognitive symptoms for people with variants of a particular gene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding Parkinson’s Dementia&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parkinson’s disease dementia is a progressive condition superimposed on the classic movement symptoms of PD. It typically manifests in the later stages of the disease and includes cognitive impairment – memory lapses, executive dysfunction, visual hallucinations, and mood disturbances like depression or apathy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approximately 153,000 people in the UK live with PD. There is currently no cure for PDD, but patients can take medications called cholinesterase inhibitors to help manage symptoms. Existing treatments, such as cholinesterase inhibitors (e.g., rivastigmine, donepezil) and memantine, may provide some symptomatic relief but fail to halt or alter the underlying neurodegeneration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Ambroxol: From cough syrup to neuroprotection&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ambroxol has been widely used in Europe for decades as a mucoactive agent – it helps clear phlegm and has an excellent safety profile. Its potential in neurodegenerative disease stems from its ability to enhance glucocerebrosidase (GCase) activity, a key enzyme encoded by the GBA1 gene. Reduced GCase activity leads to the build-up of alpha-synuclein, a hallmark of PD and PDD. By enhancing GCase, Ambroxol may promote the clearance of pathological proteins and reduce brain cell damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Key findings from the phase 2 trial&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers at Lawson Research Institute conducted a 12-month, randomized, placebo-controlled trial in 55 PDD patients, administering high-dose Ambroxol (525–1,050 mg/day). The major outcomes included:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Symptom stabilization:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Placebo participants experienced significant worsening in neuropsychiatric measures, while those on Ambroxol remained stable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Brain injury marker (GFAP):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Serum GFAP – a biomarker of neuronal damage – increased in the placebo group but remained stable with Ambroxol, implying neuroprotective action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Cognitive improvement in high-risk individuals:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Patients harboring GBA1 risk variants exhibited noticeable cognitive gains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Safety and tolerance:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Ambroxol was generally well-tolerated, with no serious adverse effects noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;One detailed report noted that high-dose Ambroxol recipients showed improved Montreal Cognitive Assessment (MoCA) scores by approximately 2 points, while placebo subjects declined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Limitations and the way ahead&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While findings are promising, they come from a small, single-center Phase 2 trial with limited diversity and may not be fully statistically conclusive. Certain dose‑response relationships remain unclear, and the subset of GBA1 carriers was small – about eight participants. Researchers are planning larger Phase 3 clinical trials in 2025 to specifically evaluate cognitive outcomes and determine optimal dosing strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The parting thought&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ambroxol’s success could inspire wider interest in repurposing safe, existing medications for neurodegenerative disorders. It also supports the hypothesis that enhancing GCase activity may combat alpha-synuclein pathologies – a concept applicable to Parkinson’s, dementia with Lewy bodies, and potentially Gaucher disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="78"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, this study draws attention to the value of targeted precision medicine – showing particular promise in patients with genetic risk factors (e.g., GBA1 variants). This could pave the way for more personalized neurotherapy approaches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="80"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Study: Slower memory decline in older adults linked to healthy lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="82"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="83"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 02:06:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgJBVV95cUxOTUJKYVdoY1VCNG1HWV9iMXlNY0YxZ1Q0Ql9EQjRmNkZ5WXd2RWp3aFJGLVFtRFFkbFZtZXhFb0NWcFF6aXJKLUlLVzRXU0xwQktYN3ptYUpQa21xc3Bzam5QWEtSUFZUUmJLRFhfNjlwZUNZMEQ2RjEteGZRSXpuZDlIMXRsZnJ4Q2VxNHA2eDIwc1ctZzh1RXFwZ0oyS0RXNlpoNUNURUFoLU5vdkpXWWthcmZwTjBoNnBPQW9vUDBVbF9ueFRjS0FKRjZsOThHZ0FSVUFydWJrNlZUdUZXMldqLXhlTkdTYWNTNm1rNDVvR3NJUEQtZXUxbVVkZDRXSVFmRUp0aGg4TC16cWd5S3BGMUdBbUdqbFHSAZ8CQVVfeXFMT3BmM0JLUGFycXJjbGFWMGRvU3VXbTZaOTRpUmpWWVBEakZTTENCMy02VmtFR3l1N2hkQWp4TjZFRmtEcVI2YldUcTMtcFNvSW5mMEdqNkpSV1ExSG92UFFfZXNQMVo0QjhUY2Z0N3V1c3QwaTdFMG0wTVFOVFV6Z3dPYzlyNXhfbVZzYWJ3YVN2anZZUlNkdzd4SW9YMUlDTXNZUmdscjRQTXZnbEgtMUtVNktLdUNtcjJINGdjV24tOUZYbmlzWWxvaVRIY05tVy1La2xuV0kyR2h4SFg2Qlhpekl4T2RlNUYyZ2ZVaUdWWWtuaUt4VEVLQmFzZVdpblBueTJhSFl5cDRnT3lnZW85NW1fZEJJeHhNNjMzVjA</guid></item><item><title>50岁之前非常简单的生活方式改变可显著改善大脑健康和衰老- Earth.com | Very simple lifestyle change before the age of 50 dramatically improves brain health and aging - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipwFBVV95cUxNclJtZzQtcFEzYmJfWFdXRWJ5b29pWngwbDFtRXUtbllqTTJRby12RUZIbmZCVFpxbE1UcU9BcUpKeVZ1cm5TUTBLV2xHVTlYQjB2WXNobFpvZU1OQkdFX19xZ0I0V3NfekZydmZPTlVJUWVRT1lfOXVfQXk4THFyS28xQUNjQ2Zqd3dtNHgxYVllYW1SdlQ3cU9fcTBIT3Zia2RWZzZZNA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to recent study, people who managed to fit regular exercise into their month while they were still under 50 now carry brains that look noticeably younger at 70. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The finding comes from &lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/drc/research-clinical-trials/insight-46" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Insight  46 project&lt;/a&gt;, which has tracked almost 500 members of Britain’s 1946 birth cohort for nearly eight decades. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://profiles.ucl.ac.uk/59397-sarah-james" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Dr Sarah-Naomi James&lt;/a&gt; of University College London’s &lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/drc/dementia-research-centre" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Dementia Research Centre&lt;/a&gt; led the work and calls it a reminder that, “staying active throughout your life, especially before turning 50, can help keep your brain healthy and delay early signs of Alzheimer’s.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-brain-activity-and-exercise"&gt;Brain activity and exercise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers looked at how often each volunteer reported leisure‑time activity between ages 36 and 69. One session a month was all it took to be classed as “active,” yet even that light commitment predicted larger volumes in the hippocampus, the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/human-brains-use-storage-trick-to-keep-your-memories-in-sequential-order/"&gt;brain’s&lt;/a&gt; chief memory hub. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team also compared cognitive test scores with early Alzheimer markers like amyloid build‑up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who kept moving scored higher even when those markers were present, suggesting exercise builds mental resilience rather than erasing the pathology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Older adults typically lose about one to two percent of hippocampal volume every year. Aerobic training can add roughly two percent back, effectively buying an extra year or two of neurological youth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Animal &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3072565/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; link that gain to boosts in blood flow, new neuron growth, and surges of brain-derived neurotrophic factor, a protein that primes synapses for learning. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human scans echo the trend, showing fitter seniors with denser hippocampal tissue and sharper spatial memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-exercise-and-hidden-alzheimer-s"&gt;Exercise and hidden Alzheimer’s&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Insight 46 scans did not find a direct link between activity and the amount of amyloid lodged in the brain’s cortex. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That matches other population &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31312836/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; where exercise softened the cognitive hit of amyloid without always lowering the plaques themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/23079557/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Researchers&lt;/a&gt; think movement may raise the threshold at which damage turns into symptoms, a concept known as cognitive reserve. Reserve acts like a backup network, letting healthy circuits pick up slack when disease strikes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-following-participants-for-70-years"&gt;Following participants for 70 years&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Insight 46 study is part of the world’s longest-running birth cohort, the 1946 &lt;a href="https://nshd.mrc.ac.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;British National Survey of Health and Development&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants have been assessed regularly since childhood, providing researchers with a rare, detailed view of their lifelong health, lifestyle, and socioeconomic background.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At age 70, five hundred and two of these individuals underwent memory testing, PET scans to detect amyloid, and MRI scans to assess brain volume and hippocampal size. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This combination of decades-long physical activity records and brain imaging allowed researchers to connect early-life exercise habits with structural and functional &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/your-brain-literally-changes-based-on-daily-activities-and-lifestyle/"&gt;brain&lt;/a&gt; markers nearly 40 years later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-women-show-bigger-benefits"&gt;Women show bigger benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women in the study saw the strongest benefits. Inactive women with amyloid deposits showed steeper memory loss than inactive men, yet a modest exercise habit erased much of that gap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hormonal shifts after menopause and higher baseline Alzheimer risk may make female brains more sensitive to lifestyle. That &lt;a href="https://bjsm.bmj.com/content/56/12/701" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;sensitivity&lt;/a&gt; means the upside of activity could be bigger too, offering a practical target for prevention campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exercise joins education, mentally demanding work, and social connection as major reserve builders. Each factor strengthens neural networks in different ways, so combining them multiplies protection over decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Nearly half of dementia cases can be prevented or delayed by addressing health and lifestyle risk factors,” notes researcher &lt;a href="https://www.alzheimersresearchuk.org/research/online-public-events/for-a-cure/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;David Thomas&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;a href="https://www.alzheimersresearchuk.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Alzheimer’s Research UK&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A separate 2020 &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7392084/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; estimated that up to forty percent of dementia cases could be delayed or avoided by tackling modifiable risks, with physical inactivity sitting near the top of the list. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-exercise-for-your-brain-before-50"&gt;Exercise for your brain before 50&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You do not need marathon medals to reap &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-discover-the-speed-at-which-the-brain-processes-information/"&gt;brain&lt;/a&gt; dividends. The study’s cutoff of one leisure session per month hints that consistency beats intensity for long‑term payoff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting after 50 still helped but earlier movers enjoyed the largest hippocampi at 70, implying that earlier habits leave a structural imprint. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cardiorespiratory-fitness-cuts-early-death-risks-by-53-percent/"&gt;Cardiorespiratory&lt;/a&gt; fitness later in life can still blunt the link between Alzheimer biomarkers and thinking decline, yet earlier routines give extra cushioning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public health guidelines call for at least 150 minutes of moderate activity each week, but any added movement counts. Regular walks, cycling to errands, or weekend dance classes all meet the threshold and most involve no special gear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s great to run with people because you keep each other accountable and stay connected,” said Graham Kent, a 74‑year‑old participant, while caring for his wife who lives with Alzheimer’s. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Engaging friends or pets can double as social enrichment, another pillar of reserve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The message lands clearly: move early, move often, and keep moving. A future cure would be welcome, but personal prevention starts with the next stroll.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/braincomms/article/7/1/fcae431/7933115" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Brain Communications&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 23:05:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxNclJtZzQtcFEzYmJfWFdXRWJ5b29pWngwbDFtRXUtbllqTTJRby12RUZIbmZCVFpxbE1UcU9BcUpKeVZ1cm5TUTBLV2xHVTlYQjB2WXNobFpvZU1OQkdFX19xZ0I0V3NfekZydmZPTlVJUWVRT1lfOXVfQXk4THFyS28xQUNjQ2Zqd3dtNHgxYVllYW1SdlQ3cU9fcTBIT3Zia2RWZzZZNA</guid></item><item><title>“自动对焦”规格可保证近距离或远距离的锐利视野- BBC | 'Autofocus' specs promise sharp vision, near or far - BBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE95bzBPb1NKS0ZfOVJBUzhEZTlKelQ1ZVpROTdKSVMwa2RkVTAwZTJQb3N3YUJyUHVEZm5ZeTVPSlM0bkdrZXAxZE1zZk5kWE1kakJhVlVxVGhyd9IBX0FVX3lxTE1qUXV6cXdEYkVOM3FuZEx3Y2hWb1hjdTMxUmJKM2I4Q3NJcGw5dnJpNFVXSldxVld2SkhkNjhhNl9JbmllV1E5Umh5cll1eEtJX1REN3JnWlhxVFNiVHJN?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 dfvxux"&gt;'Autofocus' specs promise sharp vision, near or far&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-801dd632-0 eSlECZ"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-801dd632-12 jSIeFi"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-801dd632-5 kRoBHa"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="sc-801dd632-7 lasLGY"&gt;Chris Baraniuk&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="sc-801dd632-8 hwLppI"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Technology Reporter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gyQxwn"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250701-150711-e3d94715db-web-2.24.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/a8d1/live/c37140d0-414a-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/a8d1/live/c37140d0-414a-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a8d1/live/c37140d0-414a-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/a8d1/live/c37140d0-414a-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/a8d1/live/c37140d0-414a-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/a8d1/live/c37140d0-414a-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/a8d1/live/c37140d0-414a-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a8d1/live/c37140d0-414a-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.png.webp" loading="eager" alt="IXI Niko Eiden, smiling and wearing IXI's autofocus specs." class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;IXI&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;"People don't want to look like cyborgs," says Niko Eiden&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;They look like an ordinary pair of glasses – but these are tech-packed specs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;On a Zoom call, Niko Eiden, chief executive and co-founder of Finnish eyewear firm IXI, holds up the frames with lenses containing liquid crystals, meaning their vision-correcting properties can change on the fly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;This one pair could correct the vision of someone who normally uses totally different pairs of glasses for seeing near or far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"These liquid crystals… we can rotate them with an electrical field," explains Mr Eiden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"It's totally, freely tuneable." The position of those crystals affects the passage of light through the lenses. A built-in eye-tracker allows the glasses to respond to whatever correction the wearer needs at a given moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;However, tech-laden eyewear &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-30830265" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;has a troubled history&lt;/a&gt; – take Google's ill-fated "Glass" smart glasses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Consumer acceptability is key, acknowledges Mr Eiden. Most people don't want to look like cyborgs: "We need to make our products actually look like existing eyewear."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250701-150711-e3d94715db-web-2.24.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/ea08/live/fcda8160-41e5-11f0-ae42-c9936551965a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/ea08/live/fcda8160-41e5-11f0-ae42-c9936551965a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/ea08/live/fcda8160-41e5-11f0-ae42-c9936551965a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/ea08/live/fcda8160-41e5-11f0-ae42-c9936551965a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/ea08/live/fcda8160-41e5-11f0-ae42-c9936551965a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/ea08/live/fcda8160-41e5-11f0-ae42-c9936551965a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/ea08/live/fcda8160-41e5-11f0-ae42-c9936551965a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/ea08/live/fcda8160-41e5-11f0-ae42-c9936551965a.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="IXI A pair of IXI glases. On one side you can see through to the electronics" class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;IXI&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;IXI glasses have lenses that can be manipulated with an electric field&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The market for eyewear tech is likely to grow. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Presbyopia, an age-related condition that makes it harder to focus on things close to you, is projected &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1367048424000493" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;to become more common&lt;/a&gt; over time as the world's population ages. And myopia, or short-sightedness, &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/ce8g4xpjz65o" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;is also on the rise&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Spectacles have remained largely the same for decades. Bifocal lenses – in which a lens is split into two regions, usually for either near- or far-sightedness – require the wearer to direct their vision through the relevant region, depending on what they want to look at, in order to see clearly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Varifocals do a similar job but the transitions are much smoother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;In contrast, auto-focus lenses promise to adjust part or all of the lens spontaneously, and even accommodate the wearer's changing eyesight over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"The first lenses that we produced were horrible," admits Mr Eiden, candidly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Those early prototypes were "hazy", he says, and with the lens quality noticeably poor at its edges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;But newer versions have proved promising in tests, says Mr Eiden. Participants in the company's trials have been asked, for example, to read something on a page, then look at an object in the distance, to see whether the glasses respond smoothly to the transition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Mr Eiden says that the eye tracking device within the spectacles cannot determine exactly what a wearer is looking at, though certain activities such as reading are in principle detectable because of the nature of eye movements associated with them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Since such glasses respond so closely to the wearer's eye behaviour, it's important the frames fit well, says Emilia Helin, product director.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;IXI's frames are adjustable but not to a great degree, given the delicate electronics inside, she explains: "We have some flexibility but not full flexibility." That's why IXI hopes to ensure that the small range of frames it has designed would suit a wide variety of faces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The small battery secreted inside IXI's autofocus frames should last for two days, says Mr Eiden, adding that it's possible to recharge the specs overnight while the wearer is asleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;But he won't be drawn on a launch date, which he intends to reveal later this year. As for cost, I ask whether £1,000 might be the sort of price tag he has in mind. He merely says, "I'm smiling when you say it but I won't confirm."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250701-150711-e3d94715db-web-2.24.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7b76/live/251892a0-414d-11f0-bace-e1270fc31f5e.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7b76/live/251892a0-414d-11f0-bace-e1270fc31f5e.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7b76/live/251892a0-414d-11f0-bace-e1270fc31f5e.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7b76/live/251892a0-414d-11f0-bace-e1270fc31f5e.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7b76/live/251892a0-414d-11f0-bace-e1270fc31f5e.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7b76/live/251892a0-414d-11f0-bace-e1270fc31f5e.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7b76/live/251892a0-414d-11f0-bace-e1270fc31f5e.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7b76/live/251892a0-414d-11f0-bace-e1270fc31f5e.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A mother tries on glasses in a store with her young daughter" class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Autofocus lenses could help people who struggle with varifocals or bifocals&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Autofocus lenses could help people who struggle with varifocals or bifocals, says Paramdeep Bilkhu, clinical adviser at the College of Optometrists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;However, he adds, "There is insufficient evidence to state whether they perform as well as traditional options and whether they can be used for safety critical tasks such as driving."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Chi-Ho To, an optometry researcher, at the Hong Kong Polytechnic University has a similar concern – what if the vision correction went wrong or was delayed slightly while he was, say, performing surgery on someone?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"But I think in terms of general use having something that allows autofocusing is a good idea," he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Mr Eiden notes that the first version of his company's lenses will not alter the entire lens area. "One can always glance over the dynamic area," he says. If wholly self-adjusting lenses emerge then safety will become "a much more serious business", he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;In 2013, UK firm Adlens released glasses that allowed wearers to manually change the optical power of the lenses via a small dial on the frames. These lenses contained a fluid-filled membrane, which when compressed in response to dial adjustments would alter its curvature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Adlens' current chief executive Rob Stevens says the specs sold for $1,250 (£920) in the US and were "well received by consumers" but not so much by opticians, which he says "strangled sales".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Since then, technology has moved on and the concept of lenses that refocus themselves automatically, without manual interventions, has emerged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Like IXI and other companies, Adlens is working on glasses that do this. However, Mr Stevens declines to confirm a launch date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Joshua Silver, an Oxford University physicist, founded Adlens but no longer works for the company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He came up with the idea of fluid-filled adjustable lenses back in 1985 and developed glasses that could be tuned to the wearer's needs and then permanently set to that prescription.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Such lenses have enabled roughly 100,000 people in 20 countries to  access vision correcting technology. Prof Silver is currently seeking investment for a venture called Vision, which would further rollout these glasses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;As for more expensive, electronics-filled auto-focus specs, he questions whether they will have broad appeal: "Wouldn't [people] just go and buy reading glasses, which would more or less do the same thing for them?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250701-150711-e3d94715db-web-2.24.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/881a/live/3756e680-414b-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/881a/live/3756e680-414b-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/881a/live/3756e680-414b-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/881a/live/3756e680-414b-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/881a/live/3756e680-414b-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/881a/live/3756e680-414b-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/881a/live/3756e680-414b-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/881a/live/3756e680-414b-11f0-835b-310c7b938e84.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Hong Kong Polytechnic University Prof Chi-Ho To holding up a lens." class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Hong Kong Polytechnic University&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Prof Chi-Ho To has developed a lens which slows short-sightedness&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Other specs tech is even slowing down the progression of eye conditions such as myopia, beyond just correcting for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Prof To &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-023-32700-7" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;has developed glasses lenses&lt;/a&gt; that have a honeycomb-like ring in them. Light passing through the centre of the ring, focused as normal, reaches the wearer's retina and allows them to see clearly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;However, light passing through the ring itself is defocused slightly meaning that the peripheral retina &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.myopiafocus.org/hyperopic-defocus-blur" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;gets a slightly blurred image&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;This appears to slow improper eyeball growth in children, which Prof To says cuts the rate of short-sightedness progression by 60%. Glasses with this technology are now in use in more than 30 countries, he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;British firm SightGlass has a slightly different approach – glasses that gently reduce the contrast of someone's vision to similarly affect eye growth and myopia progression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;While autofocus glasses and other high-tech solutions may have promise, Prof To has an even bigger goal: glasses that don't just slow down myopia but actually reverse it slightly – a tantalising prospect that could improve the vision of potentially billions of people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"There is growing evidence that you can do it," teases Prof To.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="links-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dHQIrb"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-666b6d83-0 sc-c4fb5674-0 gMiqnK iuHqSH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="links-title" class="sc-c4fb5674-2 jdmgui"&gt;More Technology of Business&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 23:05:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE95bzBPb1NKS0ZfOVJBUzhEZTlKelQ1ZVpROTdKSVMwa2RkVTAwZTJQb3N3YUJyUHVEZm5ZeTVPSlM0bkdrZXAxZE1zZk5kWE1kakJhVlVxVGhyd9IBX0FVX3lxTE1qUXV6cXdEYkVOM3FuZEx3Y2hWb1hjdTMxUmJKM2I4Q3NJcGw5dnJpNFVXSldxVld2SkhkNjhhNl9JbmllV1E5Umh5cll1eEtJX1REN3JnWlhxVFNiVHJN</guid></item><item><title>神经痛药物加巴喷丁与痴呆症、认知障碍风险增加有关- Medical Xpress | Nerve pain drug gabapentin linked to increased dementia, cognitive impairment risks - Medical Xpress</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigwFBVV95cUxNSHZNb1FNZVBQX2hPeVgyWFh4ckhmRzdBd1pNblh3TGhXMGpURHRHTFpqZE8xZzkxN0l5Rl8xYWNRUmp2YVJ6cElSV1NtMmp1eHVwNHZGRy1LVDk3UTZZU2tJZGd0WVNuV1VjT1lwelJERjJyelhrSk9ma1ZwZzhteTFFMA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
									    
&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2025/back-pain-1.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2025/back-pain-1.jpg" data-sub-html="Credit: Pixabay/CC0 Public Domain"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2025/back-pain-1.jpg" alt="back pain" title="Credit: Pixabay/CC0 Public Domain"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-darken text-low-up text-truncate-js text-truncate mt-3"&gt;
                Credit: Pixabay/CC0 Public Domain
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Receiving six or more prescriptions of the drug gabapentin for low back pain is associated with significantly increased risks of developing dementia and mild cognitive impairment (MCI)—29% and 85%, respectively—finds a large medical records study published online in the journal &lt;i&gt;Regional Anesthesia &amp;amp; Pain Medicine&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

                                        
                                                                                &lt;p class="w-100 my-4 d-print-none"&gt;
     
     
     &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="7587637799"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
     
&lt;/p&gt;  
                                         

                                                                                                                                    &lt;p&gt;What's more, these risks were more than twice as high in those normally considered too young to develop either condition—18–64-year-olds—the findings indicate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike opioids, gabapentin has relatively low addictive potential, and it has become increasingly popular for the treatment of chronic pain, especially &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/neuropathic+pain/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;neuropathic pain&lt;/a&gt;, as it offers potentially neuroprotective benefits, point out the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But concerns are beginning to emerge about its side effects, including a possible association with neurodegeneration, although the findings to date have been mixed, including whether particular age groups might be more vulnerable, they add.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a bid to shed more light on these issues, the researchers drew on &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/real-time+data/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;real-time data&lt;/a&gt; from TriNetX, a federated health research network, which contains &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/electronic+health+records/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;electronic health records&lt;/a&gt; from 68 health care organizations across the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They scrutinized the anonymized records of adult patients who had and hadn't been prescribed gabapentin (26,414 in each group) for chronic low pain between 2004 and 2024, taking account of demographics, co-existing conditions, and the use of other analgesic drugs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who had received six or more gabapentin prescriptions were 29% more likely to be diagnosed with &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/dementia/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt; and 85% more likely to be diagnosed with MCI within 10 years of their initial pain diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                        
    &lt;p class="w-100 mb-4 ads"&gt;
          
        
        &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="7099578867"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
        
    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                                                                                                                                                                &lt;p&gt;And when the records were stratified by age, 18–64-year-olds prescribed the drug were more than twice as likely to develop either condition than those who hadn't been prescribed gabapentin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While there was no heightened risk among 18–34-year-olds prescribed the drug, the risks of dementia more than doubled and those of MCI more than tripled among 35–49-year-olds prescribed it. A similar pattern was observed among 50–64-year-olds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Risks also rose in tandem with prescription frequency: patients with 12 or more prescriptions were 40% more likely to develop dementia and 65% more likely to develop MCI than those prescribed gabapentin between three and 11 times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/observational+study/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;observational study&lt;/a&gt;, and as such, no firm conclusions can be drawn about cause and effect. The researchers also acknowledge that their study was retrospective, and they weren't able to account for dose or length of gabapentin use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, they conclude, "Our findings indicate an association between gabapentin prescription and dementia or cognitive impairment within 10 years. Moreover, increased gabapentin prescription frequency correlated with dementia incidence."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They add, "Our results support the need for close monitoring of adult patients prescribed gabapentin to assess for potential cognitive decline."&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                                                    
                                                                                
                                        											&lt;div class="article-main__more p-4"&gt;
												                                                    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information:&lt;/strong&gt;
                                                    Risk of dementia following gabapentin prescription in chronic low back pain patients, &lt;i&gt;Regional Anesthesia &amp;amp; Pain Medicine&lt;/i&gt; (2025). &lt;a data-doi="1" href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1136/rapm-2025-106577" target="_blank"&gt;DOI: 10.1136/rapm-2025-106577&lt;/a&gt;
																								
																							&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                                        											
																					
                                                                                                                        
                                        
                                        &lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
                                                 &lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
                                                 Nerve pain drug gabapentin linked to increased dementia, cognitive impairment risks (2025, July 10)
                                                 retrieved 11 July 2025
                                                 from https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-nerve-pain-drug-gabapentin-linked.html
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
                                            This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
                                            part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                        &lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 22:30:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNSHZNb1FNZVBQX2hPeVgyWFh4ckhmRzdBd1pNblh3TGhXMGpURHRHTFpqZE8xZzkxN0l5Rl8xYWNRUmp2YVJ6cElSV1NtMmp1eHVwNHZGRy1LVDk3UTZZU2tJZGd0WVNuV1VjT1lwelJERjJyelhrSk9ma1ZwZzhteTFFMA</guid></item><item><title>女性服用10倍剂量的姜黄，因肝损伤住院- Ars Technica | Woman takes 10x dose of turmeric, gets hospitalized for liver damage - Ars Technica</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqwFBVV95cUxPdGlERENZMXJKTjdPdGpRc2JNV2RGdWR6REd6WU1IMW5vTENKTXZOMGdPaHJpZUVtLVd1RnppOFdyLW5KR1ZKQjhWb0VTTFBHUWZremg4T2RtTVpoQTB0NnhMenRqbzlYVjF5YWtwOURZdWtBNGpyTHQybmd4RFlzM1BVcU05ZUt1OVJvd3h5VWlPbW5PVmVmLUxocno4Ry1oY0JpX283a0dBX3M?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
                      
                      
          &lt;p&gt;A 57-year-old woman spent six days in the hospital for severe liver damage after taking daily megadoses of the popular herbal supplement, turmeric, which she had seen touted on social media, &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/liver-damage-turmeric-supplement-woman-hospitalized-rcna217578"&gt;according to NBC News&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The woman, Katie Mohan, told the outlet that she had seen a doctor on Instagram suggesting it was useful against inflammation and joint pain. So, she began taking turmeric capsules at a dose of 2,250 mg per day. According to the World Health Organization, an acceptable daily dose is &lt;a href="https://apps.who.int/food-additives-contaminants-jecfa-database/Home/Chemical/638"&gt;up to 3 mg&lt;/a&gt; per kilogram of weight per day—for a 150-pound (68 kg) adult, that would be about 204 mg per day. Mohan was taking more than 10 times that amount.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few weeks later, she developed stomach pain, nausea, fatigue, and dark urine. "I just did not feel well generally," she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After seeing a news report about the possibility of toxicity from turmeric, she connected her symptoms to the pills and went to urgent care. Blood tests revealed her liver enzyme levels were 60 times higher than the normal limit, suggesting liver damage. She was admitted to a local hospital and then transferred to NYU Langone in New York City. Her hepatologist there, Nikolaos Pyrsopoulos, said she was "one step before full liver damage, liver failure, requiring liver transplant."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Rare toxicity&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Generally, turmeric—a golden-colored staple of curries—is not harmful, particularly in foods. But, as herbal supplements have gained popularity and doses have gotten larger, doctors have reported &lt;a href="https://www.amjmed.com/article/S0002-9343(22)00740-9/fulltext"&gt;a rise in liver injuries from the spice&lt;/a&gt;. In fact, while rare overall, turmeric appears to have become the most common herbal cause of liver injuries in the US.&lt;/p&gt;

          
                      &lt;p class="ars-interlude-container in-content-interlude mx-auto max-w-xl"&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 22:19:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxPdGlERENZMXJKTjdPdGpRc2JNV2RGdWR6REd6WU1IMW5vTENKTXZOMGdPaHJpZUVtLVd1RnppOFdyLW5KR1ZKQjhWb0VTTFBHUWZremg4T2RtTVpoQTB0NnhMenRqbzlYVjF5YWtwOURZdWtBNGpyTHQybmd4RFlzM1BVcU05ZUt1OVJvd3h5VWlPbW5PVmVmLUxocno4Ry1oY0JpX283a0dBX3M</guid></item><item><title>这位网红分享了她积极的生活。离线后，她正在为治疗痛苦的病症而战。- NBC新闻 | This influencer shares her active life. Offline, she's fighting for treatment of a painful condition. - NBC News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxNMERacmRqOTBMVG1pRzMzc1ZxNF9aUVEzdE1UcVR4TXFGaHJTOFpqZVhHVVgzb2tTU3FTTWZhOHB4cV9CdjRtR3ZrM2F5ckpQZW9GQ0tXLVRaVTlXVGhraFVvV01rdEdmcXJFdVZQVlZwNURGTS0wRk04b2F5Nk1EdW9MMTRIQklQX2JzMmZLVkZIRU9CUzdxc0doVkxRQXAtU0hQSWR4WXg3c2RlNlHSAVZBVV95cUxOOVZxaHhHQmxSZjdrSUx5YjJYWGFUbjBsRktLb3Fpb3pJWkM4TElXSU1ROE9XQjhQQlVhNExOWGRCSFFjVnV3cUxybl9GVXczSUdUZ3JOdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b1d86f" class="body-graf"&gt;A scroll through Aurora McCausland’s wildly popular social media accounts — she has more than 300,000 followers across TikTok and Instagram — shows an active young mom dancing, cleaning and tackling major renovation projects in her Utah home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-ba300a" class="body-graf"&gt;Behind the scenes, though, is a painful reality: McCausland has lipedema, a progressive and debilitating disease that causes fat in connective tissue to build up disproportionately, most often in the legs, ankles and hips. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-ade5e9" class="body-graf"&gt;She said her &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/chronic-pain-more-common-diabetes-depression-study-rcna84470" target="_blank"&gt;legs throb with pain&lt;/a&gt;, swell unpredictably and feel heavy, like they’re filled with cement. It’s a major source of frustration for the mother of two young children. Standing up can cause her to black out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4e5cee" class="body-graf"&gt;“Things that I feel like I should be able to do cause pain pretty quickly, and then I kind of have to tap out,” said McCausland, 30, of West Valley City, Utah. “Getting down to play with my kids is really hard.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="styles_inlineImage__FvnTh styles_medium__MEKii styles_portrait__NEQhG" id="anchor-264ab6"&gt;&lt;picture class="styles_image__i32F7" data-testid="picture"&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 1000px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-07/250710-aurora-mccausland-beach-se-126p-cf452b.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-07/250710-aurora-mccausland-beach-se-126p-cf452b.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 320px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-07/250710-aurora-mccausland-beach-se-126p-cf452b.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-07/250710-aurora-mccausland-beach-se-126p-cf452b.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-07/250710-aurora-mccausland-beach-se-126p-cf452b.jpg" alt="Aurora McCausland."&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption styles_caption__TCewG" data-testid="caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption__container" data-testid="caption__container"&gt;Aurora McCausland first noticed symptoms of lipedema as a teenager. It took more than a decade for her to be diagnosed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="caption__source" data-testid="caption__source"&gt;Courtesy Aurora McCausland&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c6c335" class="body-graf"&gt;She’s tried to manage the pain with compression garments, lymphatic drainage and &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/anti-inflammatory-diet-may-help-colon-cancer-patients-live-longer-stud-rcna209539" target="_blank"&gt;anti-inflammatory diets&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-ec7e0d" class="body-graf"&gt;“Those are helpful at potentially slowing down the disease,” her physician, Dr. David Smart, said. “But really, only surgery helps to reverse the disease process.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-23c85b" class="body-graf"&gt;Smart is a dermatologic&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;surgeon at the Roxbury Institute in Murray, Utah. He performs a specialized type of liposuction that removes the diseased tissue to restore mobility. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5f7568" class="body-graf"&gt;The procedure isn’t cosmetic, and despite the buildup of fat, lipedema isn’t related to obesity. It’s not caused by overeating or inactivity. It’s a hormonally driven &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/heart-health/inflammation-how-protect-body-against-chronic-disease-rcna193856" target="_blank"&gt;inflammatory condition&lt;/a&gt;, one that’s largely resistant to diet and exercise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-470c1c" class="body-graf"&gt;“It goes against the more traditional health dogma that’s out there about normal fat,” Smart said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e611a1" class="body-graf"&gt;Lipedema is almost exclusively seen in women, but scientists don’t have a good handle on how many are affected. &lt;a href="https://lipedema.net/how-prevalent-is-lipedema-in-women/" target="_blank"&gt;Some estimates suggest&lt;/a&gt; it may affect up to 11% of women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-21ae88" class="body-graf"&gt;“There are no large-scale, population-based epidemiologic estimates. We don’t have blood tests. We don’t have imaging studies,” said Dr. Aaron Aday, co-director of vascular medicine at Vanderbilt University Medical Center in Nashville, Tennessee. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-7c7ae8" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Denied relief&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9bae22" class="body-graf"&gt;Many women first notice symptoms of lipedema at puberty, and the disease often worsens during major hormonal shifts like pregnancy or &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/non-hormonal-menopause-drugs-symptoms-insurance-hurdles-rcna152439" target="_blank"&gt;menopause&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-19305d" class="body-graf"&gt;McCausland said her symptoms first appeared during her early teens: leg pain, swelling and bruising from the slightest touch. “I thought it was just growing pains,” she said. Fat built up around her ankles. No matter how physically active she was — dancing and CrossFit were two hobbies — she couldn’t make the fat in her lower legs go away. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a72229" class="body-graf"&gt;Still, she was told it was just excess weight. “That if I worked out more, ate less, it would go away,” she said. “But no matter what I did, my legs just hurt more. I was doing everything right and getting worse.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-912ee4" class="body-graf"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you are dealing with bills that seem to be out of line or a denial of coverage, care or repairs, whether for health, home or auto, please email us at &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:Costofdenial@nbcuni.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Costofdenial@nbcuni.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a8e9f4" class="body-graf"&gt;McCausland’s five sisters experienced similar symptoms. She said none knew what the problem was until one of the sisters got liposuction to slim down her lower legs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-05cda9" class="body-graf"&gt;But lipedema fat isn’t the same as typical fat. Instead of feeling soft, it can feel like hard nodules under the skin. Regular liposuction can be risky to use on lipedema patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-2e569a" class="body-graf"&gt;It took far longer than it should have for her sister’s doctor to do the procedure, McCausland said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-818153" class="body-graf"&gt;“The doctor ended up giving her third-degree internal burns all on her legs, because he didn’t know that it wasn’t normal fat. He just kept going, having to go over and over and over trying to remove it,” she said. “It was just this horrible thing that happened. Obviously the doctor had no idea that she had this condition, and neither did my sister.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-244393" class="body-graf"&gt;Aday — who hasn’t treated McCausland — said that a specialized type of liposuction, performed by a surgeon with extensive knowledge of lipedema, is the most effective way to treat the disorder. It can reverse symptoms in many people. Some patients, he said, may have to have the procedure repeated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9dd69c" class="body-graf"&gt;The Roxbury Institute said that McCausland would need two liposuction surgeries, totaling more than $35,000. But her former insurance provider, Cigna Healthcare, denied coverage for the procedure twice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-fece8f" class="body-graf"&gt;In an emailed statement, a Cigna representative said: “Lipedema is a painful condition that disproportionately impacts women, and we cover a range of treatment options, including liposuction, for patients that meet evidence-based clinical criteria. Ms. McCausland’s case was carefully reviewed by multiple doctors, including a plastic surgeon with expertise in lipedema. Based on the information submitted by her doctor, she did not meet the clinical criteria for liposuction at that time.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-41d15e" class="body-graf"&gt;McCausland believes her coverage was denied because she didn’t look sick enough, adding that she suspects the denial was based on her social media posts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-99f394" class="body-graf"&gt;They said “that it’s not medically necessary,” McCausland said. “That’s absurd. They’re not looking at how I live. They’re looking at a photo and deciding I don’t look bad enough to be helped.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-648acd" class="body-graf"&gt;Cigna told NBC News that social media isn’t considered when it makes coverage decisions. “Our coverage decisions are based on the clinical information submitted by a patient’s treating physician in accordance with coverage policies and the patient’s plan design,” the representative said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-ffd6b5" class="body-graf"&gt;McCausland’s health insurance has since switched to MotivHealth, because of her husband’s new job. McCausland said MotivHealth has already suggested to her in a phone call that it’s not a procedure it usually covers but that she can submit additional documentation. A representative for the company didn’t respond to several requests for comment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-0ab819" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A long under-recognized disease&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9028cd" class="body-graf"&gt;Lipedema is categorized in four stages, based on visual appearance. Stage 1 looks like minor fat accumulation and Stage 4 appears as severe leg disfigurement. Appearance, however, doesn’t always match the severity of symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3eb303" class="body-graf"&gt;“You can have a Stage 1 patient that has very severe and crippling symptoms of pain and swelling, and somebody who is maybe more progressed visibly that doesn’t have such severe symptoms,” Smart said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-54aea0" class="body-graf"&gt;McCausland is a prime example. She doesn’t look sick, according to some commenters on her social media videos. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="styles_inlineImage__FvnTh styles_medium__MEKii styles_portrait__NEQhG" id="anchor-6d7e14"&gt;&lt;picture class="styles_image__i32F7" data-testid="picture"&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 1000px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-07/250710-aurora-mccausland-garden-se-126p-c38034.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-07/250710-aurora-mccausland-garden-se-126p-c38034.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 320px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-07/250710-aurora-mccausland-garden-se-126p-c38034.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-07/250710-aurora-mccausland-garden-se-126p-c38034.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-07/250710-aurora-mccausland-garden-se-126p-c38034.jpg" alt="Aurora McCausland."&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption styles_caption__TCewG" data-testid="caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption__container" data-testid="caption__container"&gt;McCausland said her legs throb with pain, swell unpredictably and feel heavy, like they’re filled with cement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="caption__source" data-testid="caption__source"&gt;Courtesy Aurora McCausland&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a20a36" class="body-graf"&gt;“I’ve gotten a handful of people saying, ‘Well, I’ve looked at your other videos, and I agree with your insurance company,’” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3c9791" class="body-graf"&gt;“This is very likely the reason why lipedema has been so under-recognized for such a long time,” Smart said. “So many people, so many insurance companies, so many physicians, have been telling lipedema patients for decades to just ‘work out, eat better, lose weight,’ when that’s not actually the problem.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-68ef4f" class="body-graf"&gt;He said waiting until the condition progresses is dangerous. Without treatment, lipedema advances, causing more inflammation, worsening pain and &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/knees-running-osteoarthritis-marathoners-orthopedic-rcna71270" target="_blank"&gt;permanent joint damage&lt;/a&gt;. The longer surgery is delayed, the harder it is to restore mobility in later stages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f28ea2" class="body-graf"&gt;“It’s really unfortunate for Aurora, because at that early stage, it is less likely that she gets insurance coverage,” Smart said. “They’re not looking at the severity of her symptoms. They’re not looking at the severity of her pain, the decrease in mobility, her lack of ability to be able to perform those daily activities of living.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bd97af" class="body-graf"&gt;Jonathan Kartt, chief executive officer of the Lipedema Foundation, said that the pain experienced by women with lipedema can be measured objectively. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d9476e" class="body-graf"&gt;Using a tool to measure how patients perceive stimuli like temperature and touch, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11013692/" target="_blank"&gt;researchers in Germany found&lt;/a&gt; that women with lipedema had a lower pain threshold compared with other women. The pain was specific to areas affected by the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-04efbb" class="body-graf"&gt;“The differences were so stark,” Kartt said, that it’s possible to use “this test to actually diagnose or confirm a diagnosis of lipedema.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bd26d1" class="body-graf"&gt;Aday, of Vanderbilt, is leading an effort to create a national biobank of information on lipedema patients. The team takes blood samples and urine, as well as fat and skin biopsies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-50e951" class="body-graf"&gt;“It’s meant to be a living research resource,” he said. “We want other investigators to use these data, build upon it and generate new data.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b26afd" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;There is also growing excitement in the lipedema field to see whether the blockbuster GLP-1 drugs, like Ozempic and Wegovy, might be useful. The drugs are mainly used to treat Type 2 diabetes and obesity, but have been shown to &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/semaglutide-linked-reduced-arthritis-knee-pain-people-obesity-study-fi-rcna177849" target="_blank"&gt;provide benefits for other diseases&lt;/a&gt;. Aday is working to secure funding for such a study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 21:22:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxNMERacmRqOTBMVG1pRzMzc1ZxNF9aUVEzdE1UcVR4TXFGaHJTOFpqZVhHVVgzb2tTU3FTTWZhOHB4cV9CdjRtR3ZrM2F5ckpQZW9GQ0tXLVRaVTlXVGhraFVvV01rdEdmcXJFdVZQVlZwNURGTS0wRk04b2F5Nk1EdW9MMTRIQklQX2JzMmZLVkZIRU9CUzdxc0doVkxRQXAtU0hQSWR4WXg3c2RlNlHSAVZBVV95cUxOOVZxaHhHQmxSZjdrSUx5YjJYWGFUbjBsRktLb3Fpb3pJWkM4TElXSU1ROE9XQjhQQlVhNExOWGRCSFFjVnV3cUxybl9GVXczSUdUZ3JOdw</guid></item><item><title>专家警告说，寄生虫正在美国“以人类为食”并传播致命疾病-每日邮报 | Experts warn parasites are 'feeding on humans' in the US and transmitting deadly disease - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisgFBVV95cUxPVlRiTEJ3RGRQRVpsT3J4U0pJYV81WHpPWFVCcFk2anJhNGNvZzEweFMxd01PLUZUUEhJaU5lV1JEczNmdHpsejZLSU8yQUpWUGxIenVsYlRzT09lSXZiaDd1T0RjYWotbEFPWDJHWVBUSzh2RGhuanBkNU91d24yOGxLRE9CZzNyZW1SX09TRTBmNnJIcFFFYzBVUnFTaEY4U2Z0Y2lFN0FlM2NpNHJQQW9B0gG3AUFVX3lxTE9lVmYzZEpBWFpjWGplNjhPWTJkT3Bod0gxR1lVcW1ROTYyazh1MlJ6WWVqa1dWcERLdUwwLUNUMnYyOHFjSFJpSzlzYUJPWHE3T19fWDZIbXpVTERqa09fQnBQbzVSYzdXQlk3bVlGVlNIOTlqYTlTOVhZUFVNWjh5Tk5GVFZIZF9MN3doZnFDN0dkZEg4SjdvUjZiQTF0Y2pfUEthWWRKMEJxWEZvNFJiWTNFYkthWQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bugs in the southeastern US may be spreading deadly, disease-causing parasites, experts warn. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/florida/index.html" id="mol-62c08910-5d99-11f0-843b-9fcbd1bac2c2"&gt;Florida&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/texas/index.html" id="mol-60d2a650-5d9a-11f0-843b-9fcbd1bac2c2"&gt;Texas&lt;/a&gt; spent 10 years tracking the transmission of Chagas disease, a dangerous condition caused by the parasite Trypanosoma cruzi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Trypanosoma cruzi is generally transmitted through feces of triatomine bugs, nicknamed 'kissing bugs,' which are known to bite humans and animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This leads them to passing on Chagas disease, which is currently infecting about 280,000 Americans, many of whom don't know they have it. Left untreated and &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14727773/Urgent-warning-blood-sucking-parasite-cases-double.html"&gt;living in the body for decades&lt;/a&gt;, it can lead to heart failure, blood clots and bowel damage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Based on 300 kissing bugs collected in 23 Florida counties, the researchers found more than a third of them were in people's homes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One in three bugs tested also carried Trypanosoma cruzi and infected people and animals in more than half of the counties examined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team believes the bugs come into homes as more people build property on previously undeveloped land, the insects' natural habitat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now, they are urging people in the 29 states where kissing bugs live - including Florida, Texas, New Mexico and Delaware - to reduce their exposure to them, which includes not keeping wood piles inside or near where pets sleep, as the bugs often are found there and can attach to pets and transfer to humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Triatomine bugs, nicknamed 'kissing bugs,' carry the parasite Trypanosoma cruzi, which causes Chagas disease&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Norman L Beatty, co-first author of the study and infectious disease physician at the University of Florida, said: 'We've done the groundwork to show that we have a vector in our state that is harboring a parasite, invading homes and feeding on humans and our pets.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Kissing bugs, which range from 0.5 to 1.25 inches long, are blood-feeding insects that tend to hide during the day in dark areas of homes like ceilings and cracks in the walls. They then come out to feed at night. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Study author Dr Samantha Wisely said: '[Triatomine bugs] are ambush predators, right? They wait for you to relax and then suck blood.'  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They spread Trypanosoma cruzi when humans or animals absorb or accidentally eat the bugs' infected feces. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Kissing bugs have been detected in 29 states, but Chagas disease is not closely tracked in the US. However, it has earned a reputation as a 'silent killer' because it lives in the body for decades without being detected. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers in the new study, published Monday in &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://journals.plos.org/plosntds/article?id=10.1371/journal.pntd.0012920"&gt;PLOS Neglected Tropical Diseases&lt;/a&gt;, collected 300 kissing bugs living in or around homes and analyzed their stomach contents to determine the source of their last meal and if they had the parasite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Of the one in three bugs living inside homes, most had been feeding on humans, whereas those outside homes had fed on other mammals, as well as reptiles and amphibians. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Infections were detected in 12 out of 23 Florida counties included in the study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers said kissing bugs may be invading homes because as Florida's population grows, more land is required for housing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Wisely said: 'I think that where we have seen transmission occurring in and around homes is in this, what I would call, peri-urban setting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'So, it's not quite suburbs, it's not quite rural … we're building into the Trypanosoma cruzi habitat, and so I think it increases the likelihood of people and companion animals becoming infected.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above map shows states where triatomine bugs have been detected&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above graph shows which food sources kissing bugs relied on, depending on where they were found. Bugs in homes most often fed on humans, while those outside focused on wild mammals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While many people with Chagas disease may be symptom-free, signs include fever, fatigue, body aches, headache, rash and loss of appetite. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Once it reaches the chronic phase, patients may suffer heart failure, abnormal heart rhythms, trouble eating and issues passing stool. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It can be treated with anti-parasitic medications and therapies for secondary issues like heart rhythm disorders. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Wisely said preventing Chagas infection involves keeping bugs from entering the home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She added: 'Don't keep those wood piles right next to your house. Don't keep them right next to where your dog sleeps. I think that's a huge part of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'That's the integrated part, not just using pesticides and insecticides. … Habitat management, as well as changing your behavior.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 16:38:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxPVlRiTEJ3RGRQRVpsT3J4U0pJYV81WHpPWFVCcFk2anJhNGNvZzEweFMxd01PLUZUUEhJaU5lV1JEczNmdHpsejZLSU8yQUpWUGxIenVsYlRzT09lSXZiaDd1T0RjYWotbEFPWDJHWVBUSzh2RGhuanBkNU91d24yOGxLRE9CZzNyZW1SX09TRTBmNnJIcFFFYzBVUnFTaEY4U2Z0Y2lFN0FlM2NpNHJQQW9B0gG3AUFVX3lxTE9lVmYzZEpBWFpjWGplNjhPWTJkT3Bod0gxR1lVcW1ROTYyazh1MlJ6WWVqa1dWcERLdUwwLUNUMnYyOHFjSFJpSzlzYUJPWHE3T19fWDZIbXpVTERqa09fQnBQbzVSYzdXQlk3bVlGVlNIOTlqYTlTOVhZUFVNWjh5Tk5GVFZIZF9MN3doZnFDN0dkZEg4SjdvUjZiQTF0Y2pfUEthWWRKMEJxWEZvNFJiWTNFYkthWQ</guid></item><item><title>简单的日常习惯可以帮助您降低血压- ScienceAlert | A Simple Daily Habit Could Help Lower Your Blood Pressure - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijwFBVV95cUxOT18xdXlUTmRYR01nMEd4NnVzOWF2VjE1MFROYWRReFlFUnFjdUFULTFSVENHU1lpZXVSZWJ0VHBCUGlESU5KSG82T3djU2dxdEJFc09KNkZpSlUxUHVneEJTbnlKUlBxX3NLNkZLak5SZFdEcG15Zkl0MldxZnFMSzB1SXVRd3BTWWVuYWVMbw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;We're constantly told to "eat healthy" – but what does that actually mean?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even doctors sometimes struggle to offer clear, practical advice on which specific foods support health, why they work and what real benefits people can expect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A growing body of research is starting to offer some answers. Along with colleagues, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40126033/"&gt;I have researched&lt;/a&gt; whether a group of plant compounds called flavan-3-ols could help lower blood pressure and improve blood vessel function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.surrey.ac.uk/news/new-study-finds-tea-and-chocolate-may-help-lower-blood-pressure"&gt;The results suggest&lt;/a&gt; these everyday compounds may have real potential for protecting heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-secret-to-better-sleep-could-be-as-simple-as-eating-more-fruit-and-veggies?utm_source=SA_article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related_link"&gt;The Secret to Better Sleep Could Be As Simple As Eating More Fruit And Veggies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flavan-3-ols – sometimes called flavanols or catechins – are natural plant compounds that belong to the &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5465813/"&gt;flavonoid family&lt;/a&gt;. They're part of what gives plants their colour and helps protect them from sunlight and pests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For us, they show up in some of our most familiar foods: cocoa, green and black tea, grapes, apples and even some berries. That slightly tart or bitter note you taste in dark chocolate or strong tea? That's flavan-3-ols at work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists have long been interested in their health effects. &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35294962/"&gt;In 2022, the Cosmos trial&lt;/a&gt; (Cocoa Supplement and Multivitamin Outcomes Study), which followed over 21,000 people, found that cocoa flavanols, but not multivitamin supplements, reduced deaths from cardiovascular disease by 27%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our study set out to dig even deeper, focusing specifically on their effects on blood pressure and endothelial function (how well blood vessels dilate and respond to blood flow).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We analysed data from 145 randomised controlled trials involving more than 5,200 participants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These studies tested a range of flavan-3-ol-rich foods and supplements, including cocoa, tea, grapes, apples and isolated compounds like epicatechin, and measured their effects on two key cardiovascular markers: blood pressure and flow-mediated dilation (FMD): a measure of how well the inner lining of blood vessels functions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The studies ranged from short-term (a single dose) to longer-term interventions lasting weeks or months. On average, participants consumed about 586 mg of flavan-3-ols daily; roughly the amount found in two to three cups of tea, one to two servings of dark chocolate, two tablespoons of cocoa powder, or a couple of apples.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regular consumption of flavan-3-ols led to an average drop in office blood pressure of 2.8 mmHg systolic (the top number) and 2.0 mmHg diastolic (the bottom number).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But for people who started with elevated blood pressure or diagnosed hypertension, the benefits were even greater with reductions of up to 6–7 mmHg systolic and 4 mmHg diastolic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's comparable to the effects of some prescription blood pressure medications and could significantly lower the risk of heart attacks &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/eight-ways-to-reduce-your-stroke-risk-no-matter-what-age-you-are-251524"&gt;and strokes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;We also found that flavan-3-ols improved endothelial function, with an average 1.7% increase in FMD after sustained intake. This benefit appeared even in participants whose blood pressure was already normal, suggesting these compounds may help protect blood vessels through multiple pathways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Side effects were uncommon and typically mild, usually limited to minor digestive issues, suggesting that adding flavan-3-ol-rich foods to your diet is generally safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Supporting cardiovascular health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the benefits were most pronounced in those with high blood pressure, even people with normal readings saw improvements in vascular function. This suggests flavan-3-ols may help prevent cardiovascular problems before they begin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High blood pressure is one of the major drivers of heart disease worldwide, even at levels that &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10243231/"&gt;don't qualify as full-blown hypertension&lt;/a&gt; (140/90 mmHg or higher). &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/abs/10.1161/CIRCULATIONAHA.124.072696#:%7E:text=The%202024%20European%20Society%20of,treat%20depends%20on%20the%20underlying"&gt;Recent guidelines&lt;/a&gt; from the European Society of Cardiology now recognise that even "elevated" blood pressure (120–139 systolic and 70–89 diastolic) carries increased risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lifestyle changes, particularly diet and exercise, are recommended by doctors as first-line strategies. But patients and even healthcare providers often lack clear, specific guidance on which foods truly make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our findings help fill this gap by showing that boosting flavan-3-ol intake through everyday foods may offer a simple, evidence-based way to support cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_167409" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-167409" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/TeaBerriesChocolate.png" alt="Tea in a cup next to berries and chocolate" class="size-full wp-image-167409" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/TeaBerriesChocolate.png 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/TeaBerriesChocolate-415x415.png 415w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/TeaBerriesChocolate-600x600.png 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-167409" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Eating certain foods could help support your heart health. &lt;/span&gt;(&lt;a href="https://www.pexels.com/photo/elegant-tea-setting-with-strawberries-and-chocolates-31583807/"&gt;İclâl Ağlamaz/Pexels&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What about supplements?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some studies tested supplements or isolated flavan-3-ol compounds, but these generally showed smaller effects than whole foods like tea or cocoa. This may be because other beneficial compounds in whole foods work together, enhancing absorption and effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At present, it appears both safer and more effective to focus on getting flavan-3-ols from foods rather than high-dose supplements, especially for people taking medications, since interactions are not fully understood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The studies we reviewed suggest that 500–600 mg of flavan-3-ols daily may be enough to see benefits. You could reach this by combining two to three cups of green or black tea, one to two servings (about 56g) of dark chocolate or two to three tablespoons of cocoa powder, two to three apples, plus other flavan-3-ol-rich fruits like grapes, pears and berries&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Small daily swaps, then, like trading a sugary snack for an apple and a piece of dark chocolate or adding an extra cup of tea, could gradually improve your heart health over time. Because flavan-3-ol content can vary between foods, monitoring your blood pressure at home may help you see if it's making a difference for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More research is needed, particularly in people with  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="167407" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, where the results were less consistent. We also need to better understand how flavan-3-ols interact with medications and whether even greater benefits can be achieved when combined with other healthy habits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the evidence is now strong enough to recommend flavan-3-ol-rich foods as part of a heart-healthy diet. As clinicians seek practical, affordable lifestyle strategies for patients, these findings bring us closer to the idea of using food as medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, flavan-3-ols aren't a magic fix. They won't replace medication for everyone. But combined with other healthy habits, they may offer a meaningful – and delicious – boost to cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And unlike many health fads, this isn't about exotic superfoods or expensive powders. It's about foods many of us already enjoy, used a little more intentionally.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/256631/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/christian-heiss-2393198"&gt;Christian Heiss&lt;/a&gt;, Professor of Cardiovascular Medicine, Head of Department of Clinical and Experimental Medicine, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-surrey-1201"&gt;University of Surrey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/how-tea-chocolate-and-apples-could-help-lower-your-blood-pressure-256631"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:05:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOT18xdXlUTmRYR01nMEd4NnVzOWF2VjE1MFROYWRReFlFUnFjdUFULTFSVENHU1lpZXVSZWJ0VHBCUGlESU5KSG82T3djU2dxdEJFc09KNkZpSlUxUHVneEJTbnlKUlBxX3NLNkZLak5SZFdEcG15Zkl0MldxZnFMSzB1SXVRd3BTWWVuYWVMbw</guid></item><item><title>联合国表示，如果美国对艾滋病项目的资助不被取代，到2029年将有数百万人死亡-美联社新闻 | UN says if US funding for HIV programs is not replaced, millions more will die by 2029 - AP News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqgFBVV95cUxPeHZ5S3VPb1dpQXM1SGpITlJwcVZ2cUx3Y3hHTld0eWxyUUo1N3ZPS21rWTFZb1pfZWVDWmptbllrLUhWLWJVSDNsRFFFUzRyUW1qemtNRUcyN1Z3ekhESEdTQ3huOThoS3dKSF9ud0hNSDNOakNxaGJwSVZTUXVLc3NGbXpmV0g2M0wtU2JYZ1gzNExWMnRWbmhfN05Ydk9XaDRzVXBJeGhuQQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:57:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxPeHZ5S3VPb1dpQXM1SGpITlJwcVZ2cUx3Y3hHTld0eWxyUUo1N3ZPS21rWTFZb1pfZWVDWmptbllrLUhWLWJVSDNsRFFFUzRyUW1qemtNRUcyN1Z3ekhESEdTQ3huOThoS3dKSF9ud0hNSDNOakNxaGJwSVZTUXVLc3NGbXpmV0g2M0wtU2JYZ1gzNExWMnRWbmhfN05Ydk9XaDRzVXBJeGhuQQ</guid></item><item><title>镁奇迹：新药即使在垃圾食品饮食中也能融化脂肪- SciTechDaily | Magnesium Marvel: New Drug Melts Fat Even on a Junk-Food Diet - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimwFBVV95cUxONWM4ZjlscVItcE5GMlVIUVZXc1FwQ1U3SmpySDQweXVPLVl1WUlzYV9FcU9nZXB2ZDcyRE5nanVrcWt6bjBxZ3M5ckgzc2hyTm5GQUFNZjFTTkdYS0pTaklfd18zUHVZbEQwamw2Z0x4X0k4UXVhbmljX2RiVHAyOTNMSUJ3S1FzeVF0X2dwQ0NoRzVHd1JCTG5fRQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:22:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxONWM4ZjlscVItcE5GMlVIUVZXc1FwQ1U3SmpySDQweXVPLVl1WUlzYV9FcU9nZXB2ZDcyRE5nanVrcWt6bjBxZ3M5ckgzc2hyTm5GQUFNZjFTTkdYS0pTaklfd18zUHVZbEQwamw2Z0x4X0k4UXVhbmljX2RiVHAyOTNMSUJ3S1FzeVF0X2dwQ0NoRzVHd1JCTG5fRQ</guid></item><item><title>帮助：许多跌倒是可以预防的。这些建议可能会有所帮助-《西雅图时报》 | Here to help: Many falls are preventable. These tips can help - The Seattle Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxPdVJwbjZFSUIzZzctT0JtQTJRZ09Ud281eTJPc3Q3cFJZSWcwTUJsSGNyVHNfVVhKUkxyREx4Vm54ZmNsZWZRd2hWUmpCWTFrdTFTZkpGaVJrd01rVExDX21yTXFwVW02ODlvOXpHMWVfR2tiVGpnNDVBdG5BclBJZDdoOHdTT19uUUFwTGZZbzdyZ0lxR1VZVlVfQ2t5eFdGZEowUlYzNnVUaC02bkE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxPdVJwbjZFSUIzZzctT0JtQTJRZ09Ud281eTJPc3Q3cFJZSWcwTUJsSGNyVHNfVVhKUkxyREx4Vm54ZmNsZWZRd2hWUmpCWTFrdTFTZkpGaVJrd01rVExDX21yTXFwVW02ODlvOXpHMWVfR2tiVGpnNDVBdG5BclBJZDdoOHdTT19uUUFwTGZZbzdyZ0lxR1VZVlVfQ2t5eFdGZEowUlYzNnVUaC02bkE?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Here to help: Many falls are preventable. These tips can help&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:00:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPdVJwbjZFSUIzZzctT0JtQTJRZ09Ud281eTJPc3Q3cFJZSWcwTUJsSGNyVHNfVVhKUkxyREx4Vm54ZmNsZWZRd2hWUmpCWTFrdTFTZkpGaVJrd01rVExDX21yTXFwVW02ODlvOXpHMWVfR2tiVGpnNDVBdG5BclBJZDdoOHdTT19uUUFwTGZZbzdyZ0lxR1VZVlVfQ2t5eFdGZEowUlYzNnVUaC02bkE</guid></item><item><title>您的生理年龄是？研究人员找到新的测量工具-《西雅图时报》 | What's your biological age? Researchers find new tool to measure - The Seattle Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikwFBVV95cUxPREhWdmhJTWttX3Vqa0NDUzR5U3M1ajhlTl9FRzc3OTlrZnVHQUdJTlhCUlQ3U29VeEotQ3RwMEs2NHQyRE01ajQ1a1ZBckVSWlo5NXY1VXU2UFhvZ2ZIMGQwVy03dGJEa3NJd2IzVXNXNGxzWldsaTNvaU50Um51Vzg5UFRUUGVrbzFjdGI4N1YyeXc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikwFBVV95cUxPREhWdmhJTWttX3Vqa0NDUzR5U3M1ajhlTl9FRzc3OTlrZnVHQUdJTlhCUlQ3U29VeEotQ3RwMEs2NHQyRE01ajQ1a1ZBckVSWlo5NXY1VXU2UFhvZ2ZIMGQwVy03dGJEa3NJd2IzVXNXNGxzWldsaTNvaU50Um51Vzg5UFRUUGVrbzFjdGI4N1YyeXc?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;What's your biological age? Researchers find new tool to measure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiX0FVX3lxTE1UcWc2TjdqUnlrZldoZG9SaldvOGliT1pJNUJuNExDc0FZV2w3UUpPZ29NX21nZ01aY3ZrSG9nUkRUV2lTMlltclhkRndTbWRrM1EzY1JsMVdEeG1lbVlJ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Plasma proteomics links brain and immune system aging with healthspan and longevity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Nature&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMidkFVX3lxTE85MDhMeUhpTjFYX05TSGJnSkU5cEhvZEZOcjN6bjhFTWRCMXhaak9nRk5kTVpoV094SkxNZEpYNFY4X2ZVY3lqS1p1a2NxQ3FGeWg2bHhBYjJZU1lSWXFEWkJkTDBfNzZOQW5XQXRyWUhBY2VSb1E?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;People with ‘young brains’ outlive ‘old-brained’ peers, Stanford Medicine scientists find&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Stanford Medicine&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinwFBVV95cUxNRUxHbFdNVE9MckNVQ1phSnp6WXJPaXlXYzhkRU1QRW16Nkw5WFQwYkZzc3pnZGx5VmlEWUNQelRhZFo0cVBCV3JyUzh5NXZVR1RoOW01TFdtTzlJZFZBY3ZoVWVKYnJXYWxtZ0sxVmxpOEpGcE40UUV3em9uaUF6MFFrbGdlVTFVNGhFTTlpTUcxdkNfRHlxQUlTR0xvVTA?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;New test could identify your body’s ‘weakest link’ as you age, Stanford research finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;San Francisco Chronicle&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqgFBVV95cUxOb2d5TnlfQXcyLXNzaWJFaWZsNXQ4MEtGeEtRRzJURUFZOVhSR2RMam1Tc2lHeFVTLUtnZUJZWEwtRkl1N3RTX3lZS1lSVndTYVNKMEUzZWc1Sk5fSEJNdTlZSHBTR1Awel9OS0tLTHRaWkxHcWp6OTU2dDBYTzhseU85MWRnX3A2MlVfTjhEVno5Y3hFZkx5VDlqdjlQVHJJbGVZTWdRcjlpdw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;A youthful brain and immune system may be key to a long life&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Scientist&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:00:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxPREhWdmhJTWttX3Vqa0NDUzR5U3M1ajhlTl9FRzc3OTlrZnVHQUdJTlhCUlQ3U29VeEotQ3RwMEs2NHQyRE01ajQ1a1ZBckVSWlo5NXY1VXU2UFhvZ2ZIMGQwVy03dGJEa3NJd2IzVXNXNGxzWldsaTNvaU50Um51Vzg5UFRUUGVrbzFjdGI4N1YyeXc</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法，食用这种水果可以延长寿命-雅虎 | Eating This Fruit Could Add Years to Your Life, According to Dietitians - Yahoo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijAFBVV95cUxNWVhFZWlMZi13RXNYNmRBWFUzRGFELWRfenhwYWNkekZuSllDMU9aa2dzMHhwNVpLQzlDTlB2NnhrQ2M0eHM4Sm9wVk9tMXlNalZHZV9kcWhQYVZsZEx2Vks2NEZaUzRxRTR0UU01RE50Y0NnLXhIQTB4ZzVGcHFJb1R3eFdSbjIzdm9wUw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reviewed by Dietitian Karen Ansel, M.S., RDN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty Images. EatingWell design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Key Points&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Fruit is filled with nutrients and antioxidants that may help you live longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Dietitians say sweet, juicy blueberries are one of the best fruits for longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;They’re rich in antioxidants and fiber for better long-term gut, heart and brain health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you’ve ever wondered if the food on your plate can make a difference in how long you live, the answer is a resounding yes! While there are lots of foods that may help you live longer, research has shown that &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.eatingwell.com/benefits-of-blueberries-11690014" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:blueberries are especially beneficial;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;blueberries are especially beneficial&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Of course, longevity is influenced by many factors. Genetics, socioeconomic status and health care access can all impact how long we live. However, food plays a central role in our health, and some foods—like blueberries—are especially powerful. Dietitians say these sweet, juicy berries are loaded with nutrients and plant compounds that may add years to your life. Ready to learn the details? Read on!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;How Blueberries May Add Years to Your Life&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Rich in Antioxidants&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Blueberries are particularly &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-as-many-antioxidants-as-green-tea-11761365" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:rich in protective antioxidants;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;rich in protective antioxidants&lt;/a&gt; called anthocyanins. “Anthocyanins in blueberries, which give them their beautiful color, have been associated with reduced risk of age-related diseases, including diabetes, cardiovascular disease and neurologic disease,” says &lt;a href="https://www.soundbitesnutrition.com/about-lisa" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Lisa Andrews, M.Ed., RD, LD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Lisa Andrews, M.Ed., RD, LD&lt;/a&gt;. They are believed to do this by &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8054507/best-antioxidant-rich-anti-inflammatory-fruits/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:fighting inflammation and reducing oxidative stress;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;fighting inflammation and reducing oxidative stress&lt;/a&gt;. If you’ve never heard of oxidative stress before, it occurs when there’s an imbalance of cell-damaging free radicals in the body. Over time, this can increase the risk of developing chronic diseases like cardiovascular disease, diabetes and cancer. Because blueberries are such a significant source of anthocyanins, you don’t have to eat mountains of them to reap their benefits. In fact, one study concluded that eating as little as ⅓ cup of blueberries daily can &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7898812/how-food-can-help-you-look-and-feel-more-youthful-heres-what-the-science-says/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:reduce the risk of many life-shortening chronic diseases;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;reduce the risk of many life-shortening chronic diseases&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;May Improve Gut Health&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Gut health isn’t just about smooth digestion. Research is finding that a &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-your-gut-health-impacts-your-body-8695122" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:healthy microbiome;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;healthy microbiome&lt;/a&gt; may impact nearly every aspect of our health. Enter blueberries. One cup of these powerful fruits provides &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7959854/ways-to-add-5-grams-of-fiber-to-your-meals/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:3.5 grams of fiber;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;3.5 grams of fiber&lt;/a&gt;,  or nearly 13% of the 28-gram Daily Value. “Fiber helps regulate bowel function and plays a role in appetite control and blood sugar management,” says Andrews.  “A recent systematic review of studies suggests that blueberries play a crucial role in &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8017087/things-you-should-do-every-day-for-gut-health/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:maintaining gut health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;maintaining gut health&lt;/a&gt;,” she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In addition to fiber, blueberries are also &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-foods-for-gut-and-heart-health-8771784" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:rich in gut-supporting compounds;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;rich in gut-supporting compounds&lt;/a&gt; called polyphenols. As encouraging as the positive impact of blueberries on gut health appears to be, research is still evolving, so more studies are needed. In the meantime, adding a cup of blueberries to your cereal, yogurt or smoothie certainly couldn’t hurt!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;May Lower Chronic Disease Risk&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Heart disease, type 2 diabetes and Alzheimer’s disease are among America’s leading causes of death. Studies have found that blueberries may reduce the risk of developing all of them. For instance, research that examined the link between blueberries and cardiovascular health found that &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7962766/are-blueberries-good-for-diabetes-heres-what-a-dietitian-has-to-say/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:frequent blueberry eaters;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;frequent blueberry eaters&lt;/a&gt; may be less likely to have high blood pressure, high cholesterol or have a heart attack. Encouraging research also suggests that blueberries may help the body use its own insulin more effectively, potentially reducing the risk of type 2 diabetes. Additionally, a smaller body of research has found that blueberries may &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.eatingwell.com/habits-to-avoid-for-cognitive-health-8786846" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:help preserve cognitive function;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;help preserve cognitive function&lt;/a&gt; and possibly protect against Parkinson’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Tips to Enjoy Blueberries&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Blueberries aren’t just a &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7900915/foods-associated-with-living-longer-according-to-research/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:top fruit for longevity;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;top fruit for longevity&lt;/a&gt;. They’re juicy, versatile and delicious. Try these tips to enjoy them every day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Snack on Them: &lt;/strong&gt;One of the best ways to eat fresh blueberries is as a snack. Simply wash and dry them, and you’re good to go. As delicious as they are on their own, they also pair beautifully with nuts or cheese for a satisfying, balanced snack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Try Frozen Blueberries: &lt;/strong&gt;“Fresh or frozen blueberries both offer nutritional benefits,” says Andrews. She’s a big fan of stocking up on frozen berries in the winter months when fresh ones aren’t readily available or are slightly more expensive than when they are in season. Pro tip: When buying frozen blueberries, check out the ingredient list to ensure they don’t contain added sugar or fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Them to Salads: &lt;/strong&gt;Tossing blueberries into a salad is a great way to add sweetness to an otherwise savory dish. Blueberries play well with many types of leafy greens, especially spinach and kale. Other add-ins like pecans, feta and avocado complement their sweetness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mix Them into Yogurt or Cereal: &lt;/strong&gt;No need to add sugar or syrup when you can top your favorite yogurt or cereal with fresh blueberries. If fresh berries are unavailable, try warming frozen blueberries in the microwave or on the stove. Then, let them cool and mix them into plain, unsweetened yogurt for a delicious treat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blend Them into Smoothies: &lt;/strong&gt;Looking for another way to use frozen blueberries? Toss a giant handful into a smoothie. They’ll make your smoothie even richer and thicker. Plus, they’ll provide fiber to slow the absorption of some of the sugars in your smoothie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Other Fruits That May Improve Longevity&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While regularly eating blueberries may add years to your life, they aren’t the only fruit that can help you live longer. These nutritious fruits also have &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8055902/healthy-habits-to-help-you-live-longer/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:life-extending benefits;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;life-extending benefits&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oranges: &lt;/strong&gt;These sweet citrus fruits are loaded with vitamin C and potassium, both of which support healthy blood pressure., ,  That, in turn, may help protect against heart attack and stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apples: &lt;/strong&gt;With roughly 4 grams of fiber per medium apple, apples are a great way to work more roughage into your day. They are also &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-antioxidant-drinks-11736079" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:rich in antioxidant polyphenols;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;rich in antioxidant polyphenols&lt;/a&gt; to combat oxidative stress, and they give you a potassium boost, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Avocados: &lt;/strong&gt;Yes, they’re fruits! And they’re packed with &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.eatingwell.com/underrated-nutrient-for-heart-health-11732192" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:heart-healthy fiber;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;heart-healthy fiber&lt;/a&gt;, says&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/lindsay-fencl-rd-cd-35a6251b2/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Lindsay Fencl, RD, CD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; Lindsay Fencl, RD, CD&lt;/a&gt;. In fact, one study found that eating two or more servings of avocado per week may reduce the risk of cardiovascular disease and coronary heart disease, especially when consumed in place of other high-fat foods like butter, margarine, processed meats and full-fat cheese or yogurt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cherries: &lt;/strong&gt;“They’re packed with antioxidants that help fight inflammation, support heart and brain health, and may even ease joint pain,” says&lt;a href="https://flavorfulnutrition.com/stacy-davis-registered-dietitian/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Stacy Davis, RD, LDN;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; Stacy Davis, RD, LDN&lt;/a&gt;. “They also have natural melatonin, which can improve sleep.” That’s key for a longer life, as research has found that sleeping too little (or too much) can shorten your lifespan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Our Expert Take&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The foods you eat play an essential role in helping you stay healthy, and some may even help you live longer. Like blueberries. These sweet, juicy berries are rich in antioxidants and fiber, which may help improve gut health and reduce the risk of chronic diseases like heart disease, type 2 diabetes and Alzheimer’s disease. Plus, they’re incredibly versatile. Whether you like them as a snack, or toss them in salads, yogurt, cereal or smoothies, there are countless ways to add blueberries to your day. Of course, blueberries aren’t the only fruit that may help you live longer. Cherries, oranges, avocados and apples are all loaded with nutrients that may add years to your life; plus, they’re filling and delicious. Now, that’s what we call a triple win!&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/eating-this-fruit-could-add-years-to-your-life-11768483" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:EATINGWELL;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;EATINGWELL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxNWVhFZWlMZi13RXNYNmRBWFUzRGFELWRfenhwYWNkekZuSllDMU9aa2dzMHhwNVpLQzlDTlB2NnhrQ2M0eHM4Sm9wVk9tMXlNalZHZV9kcWhQYVZsZEx2Vks2NEZaUzRxRTR0UU01RE50Y0NnLXhIQTB4ZzVGcHFJb1R3eFdSbjIzdm9wUw</guid></item><item><title>性激素也可能是心理健康药物-《经济学人》 | Sex hormones could be mental-health drugs too - The Economist</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxNb0RPVGUzeDJQZWlRdnhOdFdpV3htSldlYUQ3US03WUZFZUhFVjkwSng2dFV2cE5fU1lzY1Fna2pRUElzd3M2YmU5QkFuVkYyWF96QU4tNDk1SExsbDd3cXMyVnBtdkVXbjBKUHd0WktibTRCY0JCdkJmbUZ5bWtBdFhfNHpvRFZxbTM2Qnd5WW0wMVVQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="css-5nzj3w ei2yr3n1"&gt;&lt;p data-component="paragraph" class="css-1l5amll e1y9q0ei0"&gt;&lt;span data-caps="initial"&gt;P&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;OOR MENTAL&lt;/small&gt; health is a scourge. Prescriptions for anti-depressants and anti-anxiety medicines have soared in rich countries in recent decades. Yet they do not work for everyone. Perhaps a third of people with serious depression, for instance, report that drugs seem to have little effect. Doctors are therefore beginning to look further afield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Economist</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 12:54:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxNb0RPVGUzeDJQZWlRdnhOdFdpV3htSldlYUQ3US03WUZFZUhFVjkwSng2dFV2cE5fU1lzY1Fna2pRUElzd3M2YmU5QkFuVkYyWF96QU4tNDk1SExsbDd3cXMyVnBtdkVXbjBKUHd0WktibTRCY0JCdkJmbUZ5bWtBdFhfNHpvRFZxbTM2Qnd5WW0wMVVQ</guid></item><item><title>在临床试验中发现可缩小致命皮肤癌的改良疱疹病毒- ScienceAlert | Modified Herpes Virus Found to Shrink Deadly Skin Cancers in Clinical Trial - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipwFBVV95cUxPMDVsdzV5SkFyd0FXU0FTV1Q4VF9nWERfNllHZmcwOVBCZkVmTGd0dzd6d3pZTzQwdEFaNWROZ05JZFV1dElKMXNqemIzdjc0YWNPZUo2eC1nUjFjUm1zc3FlWWJ3M2NRMWk5SGFiVnFWaDlaN0dYSWE3bGtUbTFxZHJlRUFPY08xcWZlcTBXMUZuZi1zeUUybkkyYm15a2JQYjhUeTVGYw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Scientists have hijacked the herpes  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="167325" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;virus&lt;/a&gt; and turned it into a cancer-busting ally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A decade after the United States Food and Drug Administration (FDA) approved the &lt;a href="https://www.cancerresearch.org/immunotherapy-by-treatment-types/oncolytic-virus-therapy"&gt;first virus-based cancer therapy&lt;/a&gt;, another potentially life-saving treatment is on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A genetically modified herpes simplex virus, called RP1, has now been shown to destroy advanced &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Melanoma"&gt;melanoma&lt;/a&gt; tumors, even when they exist deep in the body, according to a phase 1/2 &lt;a href="https://www.clinicaltrials.gov/study/NCT03767348"&gt;clinical trial&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trial involved injecting RP1 into melanoma tumors on or just below the surface of the skin, or deeper in the body like in the lungs or liver. In patients who responded positively to the treatment, even tumors not directly injected with the medicine began to shrink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/plant-virus-fights-cancers-in-mice-with-widespread-effectiveness?utm_source=SA_article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related_link"&gt;Plant Virus Fights Cancers in Mice With 'Widespread Effectiveness' &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This result suggests that RP1 is effective in targeting  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="167325" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; throughout the entire body and not just the injected tumor, which expands the potential effectiveness of the drug because some tumors may be more difficult or impossible to reach," &lt;a href="https://news.keckmedicine.org/cancer-fighting-herpes-virus-shown-to-be-an-effective-treatment-for-some-advanced-melanoma/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; medical oncologist Gino Kim In from the University of Southern California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_167329" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-167329" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/Stage-4-diagram-2048x1350-1-642x423.png" alt="Advanced Melanoma" class="size-medium wp-image-167329" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/Stage-4-diagram-2048x1350-1-642x423.png 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/Stage-4-diagram-2048x1350-1-630x415.png 630w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/Stage-4-diagram-2048x1350-1-768x506.png 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/Stage-4-diagram-2048x1350-1-1536x1013.png 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/Stage-4-diagram-2048x1350-1-600x396.png 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/Stage-4-diagram-2048x1350-1.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-167329" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Melanoma stages. (&lt;a href="https://melanomafocus.org/melanoma-patient-treatment-guide/melanoma-info-by-stage/advanced-melanoma/"&gt;MelanomaFocus.org&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings are not yet peer reviewed, but they were &lt;a href="https://meetings.asco.org/abstracts-presentations/246581"&gt;recently presented&lt;/a&gt; at the 2025 American Society of Clinical Oncology (ASCO) meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intrigued by initial results, the FDA &lt;a href="https://www.onclive.com/view/fda-grants-priority-review-to-rp1-plus-nivolumab-for-advanced-melanoma-after-anti-pd-1-therapy"&gt;granted&lt;/a&gt; priority review to the RP1 therapy earlier this year, as long as it was in combination with the immune therapy &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nivolumab"&gt;nivolumab&lt;/a&gt; (brand name Opdivo).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Together, this drug duo seems to deliver a double punch to melanoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of the 140 patients enrolled in the recent phase 1/2  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="167325" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trial&lt;/a&gt;, roughly a third responded positively to the RP1 and nivolumab injections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At first, patients were given a combined therapy every two weeks. But after eight cycles, the patients continued with just nivolumab for up to two years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among patients who responded well, about 80 to 90 percent of their tumors shrank by more than 30 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The safety and efficacy of the herpes-based drug was considered similar for both the surface and deep injection sites. Although a version of the herpes virus is used as a carrier, it does not cause herpes in the patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These findings are very encouraging because melanoma is the fifth most common cancer for adults, and about half of all advanced melanoma cases cannot be managed with currently available immunotherapy treatments," &lt;a href="https://news.keckmedicine.org/cancer-fighting-herpes-virus-shown-to-be-an-effective-treatment-for-some-advanced-melanoma/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; In.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The survival rate of untreatable advanced melanoma is only a few years, so this new therapy offers hope to patients who may have run out of options to fight the cancer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To date, the FDA has approved just one virus-based cancer therapy – brand name &lt;a href="https://www.imlygic.com/"&gt;Imlygic&lt;/a&gt; – and it can only be &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/drugs-supplements/talimogene-laherparepvec-injection-route/description/drg-20165223"&gt;applied&lt;/a&gt; to advanced melanoma if the tumor exists on the skin or in the lymph nodes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The newest engineered version of HSV-1 therapy could get crucial medicine deeper into the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The drug research is being sponsored by a different biotech company, called Replimune Group, Inc., which is investing in oncolytic virus therapy – a clever technique that some think &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/first-patient-injected-with-experimental-cancer-killing-virus-in-new-clinical-trial"&gt;could change cancer treatment&lt;/a&gt; for good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After all,  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="167325" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;viruses&lt;/a&gt; evolved to invade our cells. And while this might often be considered a bad thing, researchers investigating oncolytic virus therapy have turned that skill into a blessing. They have designed common viruses, like the herpes simplex virus, to avoid healthy cells and directly destroy cancer cells by causing them to burst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upon breaking apart, the cell is thought to release a bunch of immune substances, called antigens, that trigger the broader immune system into attack mode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_167327" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-167327" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/fimmu-13-1012806-g001-642x362.jpg" alt="Engineered Herpes Virus" class="size-medium wp-image-167327" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/fimmu-13-1012806-g001-642x362.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/fimmu-13-1012806-g001-736x415.jpg 736w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/fimmu-13-1012806-g001-768x433.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/fimmu-13-1012806-g001-1536x866.jpg 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/fimmu-13-1012806-g001-2048x1154.jpg 2048w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/fimmu-13-1012806-g001-600x338.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-167327" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Oncolytic virus can selectively infect, replicate, lyse and kill cells. (Jafari et al., &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fimmu.2022.1012806"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Front. Immunol.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, 2022)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For cancers, like melanoma or &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/mammalian-orthoreovirus-brain-cancer-immune-system-trial"&gt;brain tumors&lt;/a&gt;, which are protected by an immunosuppressive environment, oncolytic viruses could prove particularly useful as therapies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, the FDA set a &lt;a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1737953/000110465925011851/tm256243d1_ex99-1.htm"&gt;target action&lt;/a&gt; date for its review of RP1 and nivolumab to 22 July 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the therapy proves up to snuff, it could be available to some patients with treatment-resistant advanced melanoma very soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I believe that oncolytic viruses will open up an important new approach to fighting cancer in some patients in the near future," &lt;a href="https://news.keckmedicine.org/cancer-fighting-herpes-virus-shown-to-be-an-effective-treatment-for-some-advanced-melanoma/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; In.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A phase 3 trial with more than 400 participants is now underway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trial findings were presented at the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1200/JCO.2025.43.16_suppl.9537"&gt;2025 ASCO Annual Meeting&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 12:05:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxPMDVsdzV5SkFyd0FXU0FTV1Q4VF9nWERfNllHZmcwOVBCZkVmTGd0dzd6d3pZTzQwdEFaNWROZ05JZFV1dElKMXNqemIzdjc0YWNPZUo2eC1nUjFjUm1zc3FlWWJ3M2NRMWk5SGFiVnFWaDlaN0dYSWE3bGtUbTFxZHJlRUFPY08xcWZlcTBXMUZuZi1zeUUybkkyYm15a2JQYjhUeTVGYw</guid></item><item><title>正如鲜为人知的副作用所揭示的那样，人们分享了“Ozempic sex”的经验- UNILAD | People share experiences with ‘Ozempic sex’ as little-known side effect revealed - UNILAD</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijwFBVV95cUxQNHppUEE3VFN6TEJJTE1rLUhPWllXYWdxMzhBYjRfWFAwRGxmQzYzb09rNGJacXU1SlVIVV85aFR1QTNjaHQyaHEtaVk2aU5kYlJ4MmZsYXVHQ1dIVktKOEFPN3lVaElOa3BDSE1YNlI3enJqU1hXOHZ4dC1RY0RmaEdYcGZmdzVsZGE0M09kRQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ozempic users have opened up about an unexpected side-effect of using the medication when it comes to the bedroom. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Falling into the category of GLP-1 medications, &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/ozempic"&gt;Ozempic&lt;/a&gt; is intended to be used by people with type two diabetes to help lower their blood sugar levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;However, it has also become a popular medication used by people who are trying to lose weight, with the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.ozempic.com/why-ozempic/what-is-ozempic.html"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; for the medication explaining: "Ozempic is a medicine for adults with type 2 diabetes that, along with diet and exercise, may improve blood sugar. While not for weight loss, Ozempic may help you lose some weight."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;As the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/drugs"&gt;drug&lt;/a&gt; becomes more popular, users have been opening up about some of the little-known side effects they've noticed, including &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/news/health/ozempic-side-effects-trapped-gas-wind-reddit-767921-20250620"&gt;gas&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/news/health/ozempic-face-mouth-weight-loss-364139-20250627"&gt;sagging skin. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Ozempic users have reported a whole host of side effects from the drug (George Frey/Bloomberg via Getty Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;In one &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/reddit"&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt; thread on the r/Ozempic page, one user reported an impact they'd noticed to their sex drive as they wrote: "My sex drive is completely gone."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Another thread on the site asked users if they'd noticed a change in libido, prompting one woman to reply: "Mine has left the building. I miss it!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;A second responded: "Same. Got nothing. It’s like it has totally just quit and left."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"I have been on Ozempic for about 3-4 months and I feel like my &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/sex-and-relationships"&gt;sex&lt;/a&gt; drive has disappeared. Anyone else found this?," another Redditor asked as they started a different thread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Interestingly, other Ozempic users have reported the opposite result, with one writing: "Mines definitely improved, my hubby loves it. Lol. I went years without any desire at all."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Mine has improved greatly, and it was good before," added another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Speaking&lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.wsj.com/health/wellness/weight-loss-drugs-ozempic-wegovy-side-effects-sex-0210c42b?st=es7rd6zzgxu9f2p&amp;amp;reflink=desktopwebshare_permalink"&gt; to &lt;/a&gt;The Wall Street Journal, Dr. James Simon, a reproductive endocrinologist, OBGYN and clinical professor at George Washington University, explained that the impact of GLP-1 mediations on sex drive may come down to biology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Some Ozempic users have reported a loss in libido (Getty Stock Photo)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;He said: “These drugs do work in the same places that pleasure and sexual interest are located in the human brain—male and female."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Dr. Taylor Kohn, a fellow in male reproductive medicine and surgery in the Department of Urology at Baylor College of Medicine, also told the publication that in the long run, the cardiovascular benefits associated with weight loss would likely have a positive impact on anyone experiencing erectile dysfunction, saying: “We know that if you reverse cardiovascular disease, erectile dysfunction improves as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;When contacted for comment, Novo Nordisk, which manufactures Ozempic, told UNILAD: "Patient safety is of the utmost importance to Novo Nordisk, and we recommend patients take these medications for their approved indications and under the supervision of a healthcare professional.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"We continuously collect safety data on our marketed GLP-1 medicines and work closely with the authorities to ensure patient safety. As part of this work, we continue to monitor reports of adverse drug reactions through routine pharmacovigilance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"We recommend that any patient experiencing side effects while taking GLP-1 RA medicines, including Wegovy and Ozempic (semaglutide injection), report them to their healthcare provider and via the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://yellowcard.mhra.gov.uk/"&gt;MHRA Yellow Card scheme. &lt;/a&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>UNILAD</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 10:58:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxQNHppUEE3VFN6TEJJTE1rLUhPWllXYWdxMzhBYjRfWFAwRGxmQzYzb09rNGJacXU1SlVIVV85aFR1QTNjaHQyaHEtaVk2aU5kYlJ4MmZsYXVHQ1dIVktKOEFPN3lVaElOa3BDSE1YNlI3enJqU1hXOHZ4dC1RY0RmaEdYcGZmdzVsZGE0M09kRQ</guid></item><item><title>ChatGPT博士将立即与您见面- WIRED | Dr. ChatGPT Will See You Now - WIRED</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxPd2l5NTVXYUx5dGZ1a2o1NFN1amVMWmNJSFk4UFppcW9pQzNoRE8xSGM0dThLNVZWNUw0SG40T0xBNnZCcGhOMktnRDJjVGF1TzFadk9zM3hqTHhHeHd2RVdtYXpJUjV0LVltRllNN3VKeWI1TklfaFg0dVJjbzdpT0MzQ3UzR014NE9FRDRzNW1BSW1BZGY0UW81S2RRSnIzTVRfMDRZSzJ6cjFUNlE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;And even if it is right, an AI agent can’t complement the information it provides with the knowledge physicians gain through experience, says fertility doctor Jaime Knopman. When patients at her clinic in midtown Manhattan bring her information from AI chatbots, it isn’t necessarily incorrect, but what the LLM suggests may not be the best approach for a patient’s specific case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;For instance, when considering IVF, couples will receive grades for viability for their embryos. But asking ChatGPT to provide recommendations on next steps based on those scores alone doesn’t take into consideration other important factors, Knopman says. “It’s not just about the grade: There’s other things that go into it”—such as when the embryo was biopsied, the state of the patient’s uterine lining, and whether they have had success in the past with fertility. In addition to her years of training and medical education, Knopman says she has “taken care of thousands and thousands of women.” This, she says, gives her real-world insights on what next steps to pursue that an LLM lacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Other patients will come in certain of how they want an embryo transfer done, based on a response they received from AI, Knopman says. However, while the method they’ve been suggested may be common, other courses of action may be more appropriate for the specific patient’s circumstances, she says. “There’s the science, which we study, and we learn how to do, but then there’s the art of why one treatment modality or protocol is better for a patient than another,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Some of the companies behind these AI chatbots have been building tools to address concerns about the medical information dispensed. OpenAI, the parent company of ChatGPT, &lt;a data-offer-url="https://openai.com/index/healthbench/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://openai.com/index/healthbench/"}' href="https://openai.com/index/healthbench/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; on May 12 it was launching HealthBench, a system designed to measure AI’s capabilities in responding to health questions. OpenAI says the program was built with the help of more than 260 physicians in 60 countries, and includes 5,000 simulated health conversations between users and AI models, with a scoring guide designed by doctors to evaluate the responses. The company says that it found that with earlier versions of its AI models, doctors could improve upon the responses generated by the chatbot, but claims the latest models, available as of April 2025, such as GPT-4.1, were as good as or better than the human doctors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“Our findings show that large language models have improved significantly over time and already outperform experts in writing responses to examples tested in our benchmark,” Open AI says on its website. “Yet even the most advanced systems still have substantial room for improvement, particularly in seeking necessary context for underspecified queries and worst-case reliability.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Other companies are building health-specific tools that are specifically designed for medical professionals to use. Microsoft says it has &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/microsoft-medical-superintelligence-diagnosis/"&gt;created a new AI system&lt;/a&gt;—called MAI Diagnostic Orchestrator (MAI-DxO)—that in testing diagnosed patients four times as accurately as human doctors. The system works by querying several leading large language models—including OpenAI’s GPT, Google’s Gemini, Anthropic’s Claude, Meta’s Llama, and xAI’s Grok—in a way that loosely mimics multiple human experts working together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;New doctors will need to learn how to both use these AI tools as well as counsel patients who use them, says Bernard S. Chang, dean of medical education at Harvard Medical School. That’s why his university was one of the first to offer students &lt;a href="https://cmecatalog.hms.harvard.edu/ai-clinical-medicine"&gt;classes&lt;/a&gt; on how to use the technology in their practices. “It’s one of the most exciting things that’s happening right now in medical education,” Chang says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The situation reminds Chang of when people started turning to the internet for medical information 20 years ago. Patients would come to him and say, “I hope you’re not one of those doctors that uses Google.” But as the search engine became ubiquitous, he wanted to reply to these patients: “You wouldn’t want to go to a doctor who didn’t.” He sees the same thing now happening with AI. “What kind of doctor is practicing at the forefront of medicine and doesn’t use this powerful tool?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 10:46:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPd2l5NTVXYUx5dGZ1a2o1NFN1amVMWmNJSFk4UFppcW9pQzNoRE8xSGM0dThLNVZWNUw0SG40T0xBNnZCcGhOMktnRDJjVGF1TzFadk9zM3hqTHhHeHd2RVdtYXpJUjV0LVltRllNN3VKeWI1TklfaFg0dVJjbzdpT0MzQ3UzR014NE9FRDRzNW1BSW1BZGY0UW81S2RRSnIzTVRfMDRZSzJ6cjFUNlE</guid></item><item><title>科学家成功逆转小鼠帕金森症状- WIRED | Scientists Succeed in Reversing Parkinson’s Symptoms in Mice - WIRED</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiswFBVV95cUxNNXhmZ0tRdDVXdFlERHVELVlzSWVmLWpyUVZLdy04YkRSc0Q0VkZfa2I5MDRRaTlESlhFR3pMUjE0VExuWXlKcUhFTkVpTHVtN0dwbG5ZNkJHLVZ4dGhJdDRPVHhjZlczcnZZY1BfOVFfTktfSmFDZmdiNzFZOGh0SlBtRF9qUWdPSTJfS3FRVXVZdDhsS0dCajRqNU9QYkgtRS01Q1UtblF3dmlkYWRCcDlXUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“All of the mice we treated showed dramatic improvement in their motor skills. The results exceeded our expectations and suggest that, after further study, this therapeutic approach could slow the progression of Parkinson’s in humans,” says Double.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;But experts caution that Parkinson’s is a complex condition that will likely require multiple combined interventions. A single treatment may have limited effect, but its efficacy may be enhanced by integrating it with other therapeutic approaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;In that context, Double’s team’s findings could be complemented by &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/07/250703230641.htm" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/07/250703230641.htm"}' href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/07/250703230641.htm" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;recent research&lt;/a&gt; from Stanford University focused on restoring communication between neurons in a subtype of Parkinson’s linked to mutations in the gene responsible for producing an enzyme called LRRK2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;In these cases, the mutation causes hyperactivity of the enzyme, altering the structure of brain cells and disrupting signaling between &lt;a href="https://es.wired.com/articulos/tu-cerebro-no-anticipa-un-solo-futuro-sino-varios-y-calcula-cual-es-el-mas-satisfactorio"&gt;dopaminergic neurons&lt;/a&gt; and those in the striatum, a deep brain region related to movement, motivation, and decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;It is estimated that about 25 percent of Parkinson’s cases are genetic in origin, and the LRRK2 mutation is one of the most frequent. The team led by Stanford neuroscientist Suzanne Pfeffer proposed that inhibiting the excessive activity of this enzyme could stabilize symptoms, especially if detected in early stages. The goal was to regenerate primary cilia, antenna-like structures that enable communication between cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The hypothesis was tested in mice genetically modified to exhibit LRRK2 hyperactivity and early symptoms of the disorder. For two weeks, these animals were administered with a compound called MLi-2, which binds to the enzyme and reduces its activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;In this first test, no relevant changes were observed, which the researchers attributed to the fact that the examined neurons and glia—another type of cell in the nervous system, which support neurons—were already mature and were not in the cell division phase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;However, a review of the scientific literature revealed that, even if mature, certain neurons can regenerate their primary cilia depending on their sleep-wake cycles. “The findings that other nonproliferative cells can develop cilia made us think that the inhibitor still had therapeutic potential,” Pfeffer explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The team then decided to extend the treatment to three months. After this period, they found that the percentage of neurons and glial cells in the striatum with primary cilia was comparable to that of healthy mice without the genetic mutation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;This restoration of cellular structures made it possible to reactivate communication between dopaminergic neurons and the striatum. As a result, neurotransmitters affected by the LRRK2 protein induced the production of neuroprotective factors at levels similar to those of a healthy brain, something that had been diminished as a result of LRRK2 hyperactivity. In addition, density markers of dopaminergic nerve endings were doubled, suggesting a possible recovery of previously damaged neurons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“These findings suggest that it is not only possible to stabilize the disease, but also to improve the condition of patients. This therapeutic approach has great potential to restore neuronal activity in Parkinson’s-affected circuits. There are currently several ongoing clinical trials with LRRK2 inhibitors, and we hope that these results in mice can be translated to humans,” says Pfeffer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The authors stress that, to maximize the effectiveness of this treatment, it is essential to identify &lt;a href="https://es.wired.com/articulos/el-parkinson-puede-predecirse-siete-anos-antes-con-una-nueva-muestra-mejorada-con-ia"&gt;early symptoms&lt;/a&gt;, which can occur up to 15 years before the characteristic tremors. The hope is that people with the LRRK2 mutation will be able to start treatment early. The next step would be to assess whether other Parkinson’s variants, not associated with this genetic mutation, could also benefit from this strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;It is estimated that the number of Parkinson’s cases worldwide could exceed 25 million by 2050, which would represent a 112 percent increase over 2021 figures, according to projections &lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/bmj/388/bmj-2024-080952.full.pdf"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in the British Medical Journal. Although these estimates are not definitive, the scientific community warns that they reflect a growing challenge for public health systems. For this reason, developing therapies capable of mitigating, stabilizing, and even reversing the progression of the disease is a global priority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story originally appeared on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://es.wired.com/articulos/cientificos-logran-revertir-sintomas-del-parkinson-en-ratones-podran-hacerlo-en-humanos"&gt;WIRED &lt;em&gt;en Español&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;and has been translated from Spanish.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxNNXhmZ0tRdDVXdFlERHVELVlzSWVmLWpyUVZLdy04YkRSc0Q0VkZfa2I5MDRRaTlESlhFR3pMUjE0VExuWXlKcUhFTkVpTHVtN0dwbG5ZNkJHLVZ4dGhJdDRPVHhjZlczcnZZY1BfOVFfTktfSmFDZmdiNzFZOGh0SlBtRF9qUWdPSTJfS3FRVXVZdDhsS0dCajRqNU9QYkgtRS01Q1UtblF3dmlkYWRCcDlXUQ</guid></item><item><title>世界贸易组织（ WTOP ）医学博士表示，缩口带的趋势带来了严重的健康风险 | Mouth taping trend poses serious health risks, says Md. doctor - WTOP</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxPRWMtUDBqWFNVdTJtZnZrM0RUb0w3c0ktTE5yWTM2SktWQnhSeGd1T2RhVC1zMnRoYTNVckNtcjJQZ2MwY2ZaN05ha1lqNi16UDNnUmtLU2xzLTN4MlJqRWpySnhtcTlkVG13QXdGakUxM0I3bmlYTEE3T3BWNDdwZUJ3V0dibzdObGRNTUYwNnhLYW1TTzN0OWZ1NHJOUFBRdkRJ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="schema-summary"&gt;Mouth taping trend to improve sleep quality, athletic performance poses serious health risks, says Maryland doctor.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;div id="Entry-content" class="entry-content Entry-content "&gt;
                                                
                                
                &lt;p&gt;The social media trend of mouth taping to improve sleep quality and ultimately boost athletic performance is largely unproven, and potentially dangerous, says Dr. Jennifer Gourdin, a sports medicine physician with Kaiser Permanente in Silver Spring, Maryland.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mouth taping is when you put a piece of tape across your lips to encourage nose breathing when you’re sleeping,” Gourdin told WTOP. “It’s currently trending on Instagram and TikTok, claiming to improve sleep quality, oxygen levels and reduce snoring.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gourdin, whose handle on Instagram and TikTok is @drjthesportsdoc, said many of those engaging in mouth taping are athletes. “This is a big deal in the sports field, because improved sleep quality is associated with improved muscle recovery and improved athletic performance.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The theory behind it is that nose breathing during sleep is more efficient, Gourdin said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When you breathe through your nose, you filter the air. It’s humidified and warm, so you’re less likely to wake up in the middle of the night with dry mouth or bad breath, and you’re less likely to wake up fatigued,” she said. “However, there’s not any strong evidence currently to suggest that this true.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And, the practice of mouth taping poses several risks to many people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If you have something like sleep apnea or some other underlying sleep condition, if you have nasal congestion, a deviated septum, or allergy symptoms, taping your mouth could lead to more restricted breathing,” said Gourdin. “It could also lead to dangerous drops in your oxygen levels while you’re sleeping, and in some individuals, it can also lead to panic attacks or anxiety attacks.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0323643" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;May study in the PLOS One journal,&lt;/a&gt; which reviewed 10 studies on mouth taping, found “very minor improvement in certain outcomes” for people with mild sleep apnea. But the research also found that “there are potential serious detrimental health outcomes to those with nasal obstruction,” who use oral taping as a means to ameliorate their mouth breathing, sleep apnea or sleep-disordered breathing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gourdin said there are currently no FDA-approved mouth tapes that are safe for people to use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of resorting to mouth taping, to improve sleep quality, Gourdin suggests trying a cool, calm, dark environment, limiting screen time, and turning of the television and putting your phone away before bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Have a sleep routine that you go through every night to help you wind down. Limit your intake of caffeine or alcohol before bed. And, for some patients, sleeping on your side can help improve your breathing,” Gourdin said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
                
                
                &lt;p class="After-content"&gt;
                                    &lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;p class="single-page__signature bottom"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Get breaking news and daily headlines delivered to your email inbox by signing up &lt;a href="https://wtop.com/newsletter-signup/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="single-page__signature bottom"&gt;© 2025 WTOP. All Rights Reserved. This website is not intended for users located within the European Economic Area.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WTOP</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:22:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPRWMtUDBqWFNVdTJtZnZrM0RUb0w3c0ktTE5yWTM2SktWQnhSeGd1T2RhVC1zMnRoYTNVckNtcjJQZ2MwY2ZaN05ha1lqNi16UDNnUmtLU2xzLTN4MlJqRWpySnhtcTlkVG13QXdGakUxM0I3bmlYTEE3T3BWNDdwZUJ3V0dibzdObGRNTUYwNnhLYW1TTzN0OWZ1NHJOUFBRdkRJ</guid></item><item><title>裸盖菇素能否成为长寿的神奇成分？ -研究发现 | Could Psilocybin Be The Magical Ingredient For A Longer Life? - Study Finds</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipAFBVV95cUxNSkU3em1DNjZHZU40VkxYQndncFpzOF9FMmhUNTlQT2ZyTjNYRzduTFlMREsydkpMZ05XTUV2cURXNVRUWlhscWtSVFE0WkVvRFNpYTRNT2ZWNzN4VEFyWHNhQ2FlVXNwNGM1MUxZbEtpVUluSENEd1VtUjBRc01yMVNiSFRFNzFBQ0ZKdUpveVpLanpOWG83NU1MMEc2R3hQcEx5TQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;&lt;div class="post-featured-image"&gt;&lt;picture&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocybin-magic-mushrooms-1200x800.jpg.webp"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocybin-magic-mushrooms-1200x800.jpg" alt="Psilocybin magic mushrooms"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;p class="post-featured-image-caption"&gt;(Photo by Cannabis_Pic on Shutterstock)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-breakthrough-mouse-study-hints-at-psychedelic-compound-yielding-possible-anti-aging-drugs"&gt;Breakthrough Mouse Study Hints At Psychedelic Compound Yielding Possible Anti-Aging Drugs&lt;/h2&gt;







&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-in-a-nutshell"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In A Nutshell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lab studies found that psilocin, the active form of psilocybin, extended the lifespan of human fibroblast cells by up to 57% while preserving telomere length.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Aged mice given monthly doses of psilocybin showed a 60% better survival rate than untreated mice, with signs of improved fur quality.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;The study suggests psilocybin may slow aging at the cellular level by boosting SIRT1, reducing oxidative stress, and preserving DNA stability.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Experts caution that these findings are preliminary and must be tested in humans to confirm safety and benefits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ATLANTA —&lt;/strong&gt; Magic mushrooms could be the unexpected fountain of youth. A groundbreaking study reveals that psilocybin, the mind-altering compound found in these fungi, might do more than produce psychedelic experiences. The research suggests it could actually help people live longer lives. Researchers have discovered this controversial substance extends cellular lifespan and improves survival rates in aging mice, opening an entirely new frontier in anti-aging research.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Most research has focused on &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/psilocybin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;psilocybin’s ability&lt;/a&gt; to treat &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/psychedelic-magic-mushrooms-psilocybin-depression/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/psychedelic-therapy-benefits-risks/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;anxiety&lt;/a&gt;, and other &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/psychedelics-mental-health-mysical-experience/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;mental health conditions&lt;/a&gt;. But this study reveals the compound might be working at a much more fundamental level, literally slowing down the aging process itself.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“There was overwhelming clinical evidence that it has benefits for multiple disease indications,” lead researcher Louise Hecker, PhD, tells StudyFinds. “But very little was known about how it affects the body outside the brain.” Our full Q&amp;amp;A with Dr. Hecker can be found at the end of our article.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41514-025-00244-x" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;npj Aging&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, the research represents the first experimental evidence that psilocybin could function as a “geroprotective agent,” essentially a substance &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/anti-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;that protects against aging&lt;/a&gt;. A drug already showing promise for treating mental illness might also help people maintain their health and vitality as they age.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Hecker, a former associate professor of medicine at Emory University, and her team tested what they call the “psilocybin-telomere hypothesis.” This theory suggests that psilocybin’s remarkable ability to treat a wide range of conditions, from depression to neurodegenerative diseases, might stem from its effects &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/cutting-calories-slow-cell-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;on cellular aging&lt;/a&gt; rather than just brain chemistry.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-142776"&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-1200x800.jpg.webp 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-475x317.jpg.webp 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-768x512.jpg.webp 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-400x267.jpg.webp 400w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-378x252.jpg.webp 378w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-276x184.jpg.webp 276w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-600x400.jpg.webp 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-1200x800.jpg" alt="Holding psychedelic psilocybin mushrooms" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-1200x800.jpg 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-475x317.jpg 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-768x512.jpg 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-400x267.jpg 400w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-378x252.jpg 378w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-276x184.jpg 276w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-600x400.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Researchers believe psilocybin could be used to treat numerous age-related conditions, if the study’s results are confirmed in human trials. (Photo by Cannabis_Pic on Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-laboratory-cells-live-57-longer-with-psilocin-treatment"&gt;Laboratory Cells Live 57% Longer With Psilocin Treatment&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The research team examined how &lt;em&gt;psilocin&lt;/em&gt;, the active form of psilocybin that forms when the body breaks down the original compound, affects human cells in laboratory conditions. Using human lung fibroblasts, which are cells that naturally age and stop dividing over time, scientists discovered something remarkable.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Cells treated with psilocin lived significantly longer than untreated cells. At a moderate dose (10 μM), psilocin extended cellular lifespan by 29 percent. When researchers increased the dose to 100 μM, cells lived 57 percent longer than normal.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers write that the psilocin-treated cells remained healthy and active for extended periods, continuing to divide and reproduce normally before eventually reaching the natural end of their lifespan. Importantly, the cells didn’t become &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/category/cancer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;cancerous&lt;/a&gt; — they simply &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/intermittent-fasting-slow-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;aged more slowly.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The mechanism behind this cellular age reversal involves several key biological processes. Psilocin increased levels of SIRT1, a protein crucial for regulating cellular aging, &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/metabolism/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;metabolism&lt;/a&gt;, and stress responses. It also reduced &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/oxidative-stress/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;oxidative stress&lt;/a&gt;, the cellular damage caused by harmful molecules called free radicals. And it helped preserve &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/telomeres/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;telomeres&lt;/a&gt;, the protective caps on chromosomes that naturally shorten with age.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Telomeres-1-1200x900.jpg" alt="Telomeres are found on both ends of chromosomes, 3d illustration." class="wp-image-130628" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Telomeres-1-scaled.jpg 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Telomeres-1-475x356.jpg 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Telomeres-1-768x576.jpg 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Telomeres-1-400x300.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Telomeres are “caps” found on both ends of chromosomes. Telomere length is affected by lifestyle and has direct impact on human health and lifespan. (Image by nobeastsofierce on Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-aging-mice-show-60-better-survival-rates"&gt;Aging Mice Show 60% Better Survival Rates&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Laboratory cell studies can be promising, but the real test came when researchers moved to living animals. The team studied female mice that were 19 months old, roughly equivalent to humans in their &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/older-adults/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;early to mid-60s&lt;/a&gt;. This age was deliberately chosen to test whether psilocybin could work as a realistic anti-aging intervention for older adults.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The mice received either psilocybin or a placebo once per month for 10 months. The dosing strategy started with a lower amount (5 mg/kg) for the first treatment, followed by higher doses (15 mg/kg) for the remaining nine treatments.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;By the end of the study period, 80 percent of the psilocybin-treated mice were still alive, compared to only 50 percent of the control group. That represents a 60 percent improvement in survival rates.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Beyond just living longer, the psilocybin-treated mice &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/how-magic-mushrooms-work/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;appeared healthier&lt;/a&gt;. Researchers observed visible improvements in the animals’ fur quality, including new hair growth and less graying compared to the control group.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocybin-mice-1200x600.jpg" alt="Psilocybin study on mice" class="wp-image-143525" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocybin-mice-1200x600.jpg 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocybin-mice-475x238.jpg 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocybin-mice-768x384.jpg 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocybin-mice-400x200.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Representative images of mice prior to treatment (19 month) and after the final treatment (28 month) with vehicle or psilocybin. Red arrows indicate regions where hair growth and/or hair color changes were observed. (Credit: Kato et al / npj Aging)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-psilocybin-slows-aging-at-the-cellular-level"&gt;How Psilocybin Slows Aging at the Cellular Level&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;How does a psychedelic compound manage to &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;slow aging&lt;/a&gt;? The answer likely lies in psilocybin’s interaction with serotonin receptors, particularly the 5-HT2A receptor. These receptors are distributed throughout the body in various cell types including fibroblasts, neurons, heart cells, immune cells, and blood vessel cells.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;When psilocybin activates these receptors, it appears to trigger an array of cellular changes that promote health and &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/category/longer-life/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;longevity&lt;/a&gt;. The compound increases production of antioxidant enzymes that protect cells from damage, while simultaneously ramping up SIRT1 activity, a key player in cellular maintenance and repair.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This systemic approach might explain why psilocybin seems effective against such a wide range of conditions. Rather than targeting specific diseases, it may be addressing the underlying aging processes that make people more susceptible to illness in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-major-questions-remain-before-human-use"&gt;Major Questions Remain Before Human Use&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Significant questions remain before this research could translate to human applications. The mouse study used only female mice, so researchers don’t yet know whether &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/anti-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;the anti-aging effects&lt;/a&gt; apply equally to males. The optimal dosing schedule, age of treatment initiation, and long-term safety of repeated psilocybin use for aging also need further investigation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Safety considerations are particularly important given that some research suggests delayed cellular aging could theoretically affect cancer risk, though the current study found no evidence of this problem. The researchers noted that treated cells eventually stopped dividing naturally rather than becoming cancerous.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;picture decoding="async" class="wp-image-143526"&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-1200x912.jpg.webp 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-475x361.jpg.webp 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-768x584.jpg.webp 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-400x304.jpg.webp 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-1200x912.jpg" alt="Psilocin molecule" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-1200x912.jpg 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-475x361.jpg 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-768x584.jpg 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-400x304.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Psilocin molecule. (Credit: Bacsica on Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/psilocybin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Psilocybin&lt;/a&gt; remains a Schedule I controlled substance in the United States, making research difficult and clinical use currently impossible outside of approved trials. The doses used in the mouse study were based on amounts given to humans in clinical trials for other conditions, but optimal anti-aging doses haven’t been established.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Despite these limitations, the research opens an entirely new avenue for &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;aging research&lt;/a&gt; and potentially therapeutic intervention. The idea that a single compound could address multiple aspects of aging — from cellular health to oxidative stress to DNA protection — is certainly a change to the typical approaches that target individual age-related diseases.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Given the plethora of positive clinical outcomes already observed for &amp;gt;150 clinical trials, I am very confident that these findings can eventually be translated to humans,” says Hecker, who is now an associate professor at Baylor College of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Rather than waiting for people to develop specific conditions and then treating those diseases individually, psilocybin could potentially be used to slow the aging process itself. &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/magic-mushrooms/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Magic mushrooms&lt;/a&gt;, once relegated to counterculture experimentation, may hold keys to helping humanity live longer, healthier lives.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/strong&gt; This article summarizes findings from an early-stage preclinical study. The results were obtained in laboratory cells and aged mice and have not yet been tested in humans. Psilocybin remains a controlled substance in many countries and is not approved for anti-aging use outside of regulated clinical trials&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-studyfinds-q-amp-a-with-lead-researcher-louise-hecker"&gt;StudyFinds’ Q&amp;amp;A With Lead Researcher Louise Hecker&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What first sparked your team’s interest in testing psilocybin for aging rather than psychiatric conditions?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; My workout buddy kept asking me questions about psilocybin. Non-scientists always think scientists know everything about all things science. But I initially knew nothing about psilocybin. So I told him I would do some reading on pubmed – the only acceptable platform for scientists to find information. I was immediately blown away by what was known and also what was not known about psilocybin. There was overwhelming clinical evidence that it has benefits for multiple disease indications. But very little was known about how it affects the body outside the brain. One paper (based on an idea) stood out on the “psilocybin-telomere hypothesis” – which postulates that psilocybin interventions may quantifiably impact telomere length. I thought that this could offer a potential explanation for its efficacy across a wide range of clinical indications. This hypothesis is based on a large corpus of studies linking mental health biological aging markers: positive psychological states are associated with longer telomeres and negative psychological states are associated with shorter telomeres. But this “theory” had no scientific evidence to support it. I realized, I can actually test this!&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What was the biggest surprise when you saw the cell lifespan results?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; That psilocybin treatment led to such a dramatic impact on cellular life extension and increased survival in aged mice, even when administered late in life. Also that the mice “looked” healthier – that grew back hair and white hair grew back in black.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How confident are you that these effects might translate to humans?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; Given the plethora of positive clinical outcomes already observed for &amp;gt;150 clinical trials, I am very confident that these findings can eventually be translated to humans.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image aligncenter size-full is-resized"&gt;&lt;picture decoding="async" class="wp-image-143529"&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler.png.webp 1158w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-316x475.png.webp 316w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-768x1154.png.webp 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-1022x1536.png.webp 1022w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-400x601.png.webp 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1158px) 100vw, 1158px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler.png" alt="Louise Hecker, PhD," srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler.png 1158w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-316x475.png 316w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-768x1154.png 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-1022x1536.png 1022w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-400x601.png 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1158px) 100vw, 1158px"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Louise Hecker, PhD, senior author and lead researcher, and former associate professor at Emory University, where the research was initiated and funded. Hecker is currently an associate professor at Baylor College of Medicine (Credit: Louise Hecker)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Could psilocybin’s impact on SIRT1 and oxidative stress explain its mental health benefits too?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you think the telomere-preserving effects could have side effects, such as increased cancer risk?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; This is certainly a risk and something that we need to carefully monitor moving forward. Additional studies are needed to evaluate this.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you respond to concerns about repeated psychedelic use in an aging population?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; An effective anti-aging treatment that could be administered to adults during late life could have significant clinical potential. The dose utilized in mice was modeled based on a clinical trial in patients ranging from 29 and 70 years (three patients were &amp;gt;65 years), where no serious adverse events were reported at the study endpoint or the post-study follow-up (98 days)&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41514-025-00244-x#ref-CR24" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;sup&gt;24&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; These findings support the feasibility of psilocybin treatment in older adults. Further, the FDA’s designation of psilocybin as a “breakthrough therapy” underscores its safety profile, as minimal adverse effects have been reported &lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41514-025-00244-x#ref-CR25" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;25&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41514-025-00244-x#ref-CR26" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;26&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41514-025-00244-x#ref-CR27" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;27&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41514-025-00244-x#ref-CR28" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;28&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. However, additional studies are warranted to identify optimized protocols for therapeutic efficacy, including the age of treatment initiation, frequency and dose of treatments, and to determine if treatment impacts maximal lifespan.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the biggest regulatory or funding barriers you face to moving this to a human trial?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; The schedule I designation remains a significant barrier for research and subsequently clinical development. Further, this impacts funding. The overwhelming majority of psilocybin studies have been from private funding or foundations rather than federal funding. This unfortunately limits research progress.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you wish the public would understand about the real state of psilocybin science?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH: &lt;/strong&gt;That what we already know about psilocybin is quite amazing! But there is so much more that we do not understand about how it works and it’s potential. It will be important for the federal government to recognize the importance of such work to help propel research progress forward.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anything else you’d like to add?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; This is such an exciting finding, and we hope to share more of our findings with the public soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-quaternary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-paper-summary"&gt;Paper Summary&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-methodology"&gt;Methodology&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers conducted both laboratory cell studies and animal experiments to test psilocybin’s effects on aging. In cell studies, they treated human lung and skin fibroblasts with psilocin at various doses and measured how long the cells continued to divide before reaching senescence. For animal studies, they gave 19-month-old female mice either psilocybin or placebo once monthly for 10 months, starting with 5 mg/kg for the first dose and using 15 mg/kg for subsequent treatments. The researchers measured survival rates, observed physical changes, and analyzed various cellular markers of aging.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-results"&gt;Results&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Psilocin treatment extended cellular lifespan by 29% at moderate doses and 57% at higher doses in laboratory studies. The treated cells showed delayed senescence, increased SIRT1 levels, reduced oxidative stress, and preserved telomere length. In mice, psilocybin treatment resulted in 80% survival compared to 50% in the control group, along with visible improvements in fur quality and reduced graying. The effects appeared to work through serotonin receptor activation and involved multiple anti-aging pathways.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-limitations"&gt;Limitations&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study used only female mice, so sex-specific effects remain unknown. The research was exploratory in nature, and researchers were not blinded to treatment groups due to logistical constraints with handling a controlled substance. The optimal dosing schedule, treatment duration, and long-term safety of repeated psilocybin use for anti-aging purposes require further investigation. The study also didn’t measure maximum lifespan effects or determine the ideal age for treatment initiation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-funding-and-disclosures"&gt;Funding and Disclosures&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The research was supported by the Imagine, Innovate and Impact (I3) Award from Emory School of Medicine, the Georgia CTSA NIH award, a grant from the Emory Woodruff Health Sciences Center for Health in Aging, and Veterans Administration Health System funding. The authors declared no competing interests. Psilocybin and psilocin were obtained from Cayman Chemical under a DEA license.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-publication-information"&gt;Publication Information&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41514-025-00244-x" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;npj Aging&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, volume 11, article number 55, in 2025. The paper was titled “&lt;em&gt;Psilocybin treatment extends cellular lifespan and improves survival of aged mice&lt;/em&gt;” and was authored by Kosuke Kato, Jennifer M. Kleinhenz, Yoon-Joo Shin, Cristian Coarfa, Ali J. Zarrabi, and Louise Hecker from institutions including Emory University, Baylor College of Medicine, and the Atlanta VA Healthcare System. The paper was received on December 9, 2024, and accepted on June 2, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Study Finds</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 06:58:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxNSkU3em1DNjZHZU40VkxYQndncFpzOF9FMmhUNTlQT2ZyTjNYRzduTFlMREsydkpMZ05XTUV2cURXNVRUWlhscWtSVFE0WkVvRFNpYTRNT2ZWNzN4VEFyWHNhQ2FlVXNwNGM1MUxZbEtpVUluSENEd1VtUjBRc01yMVNiSFRFNzFBQ0ZKdUpveVpLanpOWG83NU1MMEc2R3hQcEx5TQ</guid></item><item><title>布里奇沃特外展： “让女性失眠太难了” -英国广播公司 | Bridgwater outreach: 'It's so hard leaving women sleeping rough' - BBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBpUEhPck5oOFQ1QmM1Z0NQNlAwckhmVVFCYi10elFTNUtWU0FwLWZwTVVCT2ZYUXBTR1ZRSXN4RUx4UFl1QlJqNWJqSXRVVXcxT0R0c0dXZ1NIQdIBX0FVX3lxTE1SVkdHWWxtbU9HQklkVElVMGVmZzJCQUNHV1JSdjBjYk92bmRKaG8xNVowSXBBRUVfXzg2WXIza2NBOElybTMtZkVMWHlWSUlwel9JazBZbS1TbHU2NVJJ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 dfvxux"&gt;'It's heartbreaking leaving women sleeping rough'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-801dd632-0 eSlECZ"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-801dd632-12 jSIeFi"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-801dd632-5 kRoBHa"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="sc-801dd632-7 lasLGY"&gt;Ruth Bradley&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="sc-801dd632-8 fRRQoT"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BBC Politics Reporter, Somerset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gyQxwn"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250701-150711-e3d94715db-web-2.24.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/805e/live/d3880720-5bde-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/805e/live/d3880720-5bde-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/805e/live/d3880720-5bde-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/805e/live/d3880720-5bde-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/805e/live/d3880720-5bde-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/805e/live/d3880720-5bde-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/805e/live/d3880720-5bde-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/805e/live/d3880720-5bde-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC A woman in a white vest standing at the open boot of a van in a car park looking at the camera" class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;BBC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Dani says the women she works with are often "scared" of the risks they face while sleeping rough&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;&lt;b id="&amp;quot;to-go-home-and-know-you've-left-them---we've-had-to-tuck-women-into-foil-blankets-and-just-say-'see-you-later'---that-can-be-heartbreaking-sometimes.&amp;quot;" class="sc-d16436d-0 jpoiOL"&gt;"To go home and know you've left them - we've had to tuck women into foil blankets and just say 'see you later' - that can be heartbreaking sometimes."&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Dani Brown has just spent hours of her Wednesday evening driving and walking around the streets of Bridgwater, Somerset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;She's an outreach worker with the town's women's centre run by a charity, The Nelson Trust.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Every week she and a colleague go looking for homeless women who may need their help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;They load up a van with supplies from instant noodles and hot water, to underwear, panic alarms and sanitary products, and go out offering practical help and advice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;And Sarah, not her real name, knows what a difference this "brilliant" work can make.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;After five years using heroin, shoplifting, having her kids taken into care, and sleeping "in garages, on the streets, in alleyways", she has now been clean for 18 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;The team hands out supplies to women on the town's streets every Wednesday evening&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Now 38, Sarah "didn't feel quite so alone" once she found the Bridgwater Women's Centre team after one of many arrests for shoplifting, when she was sent to prison for her second time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"That's when I'd had enough. I really missed my kids, obviously I always miss my children, but that's when it clicked like nothing's gonna change until I got off the stuff. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"Now, being clean, everything else just falls into place," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;For the outreach team, Sarah's is a huge success story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;No longer sleeping rough, she is now in temporary accommodation and hoping to go to college later this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;She also sees her son everyday which she said is "amazing – I didn't ever think I'd get that back".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;And she's been been off methadone for the last six weeks: "I'm quite proud of that," Sarah admitted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Other women Dani and her colleague have seen are still in difficult situations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Dani collects donations from a local branch of Greggs at the end of their day&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"All the women I support are homeless, they also have complex needs regarding mental health, substance misuse, family breakdowns, they might be facing violence from a partner or another individual," said Dani.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;On this particular evening she'd managed to see ten women, three of whom were new or she hadn't seen for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"They were in parks, in town, we've seen women in tents, also outside the town centre who have made what they feel is a safe environment - but that's a risky situation to be in," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;As well as handing out food and supplies, Dani and her colleague have also given out advice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Once a month they're joined by sexual health nurses for the evening. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;On this occasion they've helped one woman get emergency accommodation for the night and sent emails to "many different professionals" to help others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 eOFjmw"&gt;Night-time 'most risky'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"We've got a GP coming in to the centre tomorrow so we were able to get four women to agree to come in and see the GP who don't currently access medical support - having that place of safety and that little prompt tonight has really helped," said Dani.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Dani said it's difficult leaving the women she comes into contact with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"In the evening, through the night-time, that's when women are at risk of violence - whether that's physical or sexual - because they're so vulnerable."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"The risks can women can be put into, and the risks that come to them when they're asleep - they're scared," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dHQIrb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 06:00:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBpUEhPck5oOFQ1QmM1Z0NQNlAwckhmVVFCYi10elFTNUtWU0FwLWZwTVVCT2ZYUXBTR1ZRSXN4RUx4UFl1QlJqNWJqSXRVVXcxT0R0c0dXZ1NIQdIBX0FVX3lxTE1SVkdHWWxtbU9HQklkVElVMGVmZzJCQUNHV1JSdjBjYk92bmRKaG8xNVowSXBBRUVfXzg2WXIza2NBOElybTMtZkVMWHlWSUlwel9JazBZbS1TbHU2NVJJ</guid></item></channel></rss>