<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>我们的大脑仍然可以使用一个巧妙的技巧来超越人工智能- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/our-brains-can-still-outsmart-ai-using-one-clever-trick</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Despite the rapid advances in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/artificial-intelligence"&gt;artificial intelligence&lt;/a&gt; in recent years, the humble human brain still has the edge over computers in its ability to transfer skills and learn across tasks. A new study reveals how we likely do this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Led by a team from Princeton University, the researchers behind the new study didn't actually run tests on humans, but instead used animals that are very close to us in terms of biology and brain function: rhesus macaques &lt;span&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rhesus_macaque"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;Macaca mulatta&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These monkeys were asked to identify shapes and colors on a screen, and to look in particular directions to give their answers. While this was happening, brain scans were used to check for overlapping patterns and shared areas of activity in the animals' brains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/computers-made-from-human-brain-tissue-are-coming-are-we-prepared"&gt;Computers Made From Human Brain Tissue Are Coming. Are We Prepared?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those scans showed the monkey brains using different blocks of neurons – 'cognitive Legos', in the words of the researchers – across tasks. Existing blocks can be repurposed and recombined across new tasks, showing a neural flexibility that even the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/does-using-artificial-intelligence-ruin-your-actual-intelligence-scientists-investigated"&gt;best AI models&lt;/a&gt; can't compete with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"State-of-the-art AI models can reach human, or even super-human, performance on individual tasks," &lt;a href="https://pni.princeton.edu/news/2025/cognitive-legos"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; neuroscientist Tim Buschman, from Princeton University. "But they struggle to learn and perform many different tasks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We found that the brain is flexible because it can reuse components of cognition in many different tasks. By snapping together these 'cognitive Legos', the brain is able to build new tasks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you can see in the video below, the animals had to discriminate between shapes and colors in three separate but related tasks that required the animals to continually learn and apply what they knew from one task to the next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cognitive Lego blocks the researchers identified were concentrated in the brain's &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prefrontal_cortex"&gt;prefrontal cortex&lt;/a&gt;. The region is linked to higher cognition – solving problems, planning, making decisions – and seems to play an important role in cognitive flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also found that when certain cognitive blocks weren't needed, activity in them was reduced, suggesting the brain can file away the neural Legos that it doesn't immediately need to better focus on the task at hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think about a cognitive block like a function in a computer program," &lt;a href="https://pni.princeton.edu/news/2025/cognitive-legos"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Buschman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One set of neurons might discriminate color, and its output can be mapped onto another function that drives an action. That organization allows the brain to perform a task by sequentially performing each component of that task."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It explains how monkeys and possibly humans can &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-brain-has-a-hidden-rhythm-and-it-may-reveal-how-smart-you-are"&gt;adapt to challenges&lt;/a&gt; and tasks they haven't seen before, and use &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-critical-boom-in-technology-traced-back-more-than-half-a-million-years"&gt;existing knowledge&lt;/a&gt; to tackle them – something that  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/artificial-intelligence" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73092" data-postid="185062" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;artificial intelligence&lt;/a&gt; in its current form struggles with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further down the line, the researchers suggest their findings could help train AIs to be more adaptable to new tasks. Their work could also be useful in developing treatments for neurological and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/several-psychiatric-disorders-share-the-same-root-cause-study-reveals"&gt;psychiatric disorders&lt;/a&gt; where people struggle to apply skills to new settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, these cognitive Legos show, on a fundamental level, how our brains are more flexible and adaptable than AI models, which exhibit so-called &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.1611835114"&gt;catastrophic forgetting&lt;/a&gt;: a weakness that means neural networks can't learn consecutive tasks without forgetting how to perform the last one they trained on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/heres-why-multitasking-gets-trickier-and-even-dangerous-as-we-age"&gt;task-switching&lt;/a&gt; isn't exactly great &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-multitasking-drains-your-energy-reserves-and-what-you-can-do-about-it"&gt;for our brains,&lt;/a&gt; applying what we know from one task to another can be a useful shortcut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If, as suggested by our results, the brain can reuse representations and computations across tasks, then this could allow one to rapidly adapt to changes in the environment, either by learning the appropriate task representation through reward feedback or by recalling it from long-term memory," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09805-2"&gt;conclude&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09805-2"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:02:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxPWFNBLWJ3VzNKaW9oY0xGS3Bpc1Vrc0prY1ZINWgzM3p6T3BOR0kxVUg1bGhWNnhBNUJ6SWF0VGMwRzFHQ055bnNTQTRWQjRqSnNyNHBDa2JsRFEtM3UtU3djNTNweEJNWGhrQ1FLZjZFRVdDajlocDRtOWx2dHd0WXB6OVRfRDlaQmRsZw</guid></item><item><title>这位RFK Jr.的疫苗顾问对他的批评者有一些选择-Politico</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2025/12/14/vaccine-adviser-retsef-levi-acip-rfk-kennedy-00688979</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Politico</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxOMGJYVDBwc01LUWwxMjk0REcxZXlQRUFpanZrRHZnRHdEbnR3M19rTTBsY1lLLVhRLW5jbnRMaFpwZlk5WEdGUVZMMWtHQXNFLWdZR3k3ZWpTT3VETWFORVh0V0VVQWpFZ2laOW1CQ0ZTbWk4SEVsMHFwV243UEdCa3phZUdVWVJ2YUhfNXNvQWlfWWQxdk42Tm93</guid></item><item><title>首次使用3D打印的人类角膜移植，实验室培养的组织在数百万盲人的“游戏规则改变者”中恢复视力-好消息网络</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/first-human-cornea-transplant-using-3d-printed-lab-grown-tissue-restores-sight-in-a-game-changer-for-millions-who-are-blind/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_226802" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-226802" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-226802" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash.jpg 1400w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-326x182.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-1024x571.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-768x428.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-696x388.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-1068x595.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-754x420.jpg 754w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-530x295.jpg 530w" sizes="(max-width: 1400px) 100vw, 1400px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-226802" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;File photo – credit: Maria Maximova&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first successful human implant of a 3D-printed cornea made from human eye cells cultured in a laboratory has restored a patient’s sight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The North Carolina-based company that developed the cornea described the procedure as a ‘world first’—and a major milestone toward its goal of alleviating the lack of available donor tissue and long wait-times for people seeking transplants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Precise Bio, its robotic bio-fabrication approach could potentially turn a single donated cornea into hundreds of lab-grown grafts, at a time when there’s currently only one available for an estimated 70 patients who need one to see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This achievement marks a turning point for regenerative ophthalmology—a moment of real hope for millions living with corneal blindness,” Aryeh Batt, Precise Bio’s co-founder and CEO, &lt;a href="https://www.fiercebiotech.com/medtech/precise-bio-completes-first-human-cornea-transplant-using-3d-printed-lab-grown-tissue" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;said in a statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“For the first time, a corneal implant manufactured entirely in the lab from cultured human corneal cells, rather than direct donor tissue, has been successfully implanted in a patient.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company said the transplant was performed Oct. 29 in one eye of a patient who was considered legally blind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is a game changer. We’ve witnessed a cornea created in the lab, from living human cells, bring sight back to a human being,” said Dr. Michael Mimouni, director of the cornea unit at Rambam Medical Center in Israel, who performed the procedure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JUST WOW&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a title="Tooth Is Implanted in 34-year-old’s Eye to Restore His Vision After Two Decades" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/tooth-is-implanted-in-34-year-olds-eye-to-restore-his-vision-after-two-decades/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Tooth Is Implanted in 34-year-old’s Eye to Restore His Vision After Two Decades&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was an unforgettable moment—a glimpse into a future where no one will have to live in darkness because of a shortage of donor tissue.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dubbed PB-001, the implant is designed to match the optical clarity, transparency and bio-mechanical properties of a native cornea. Previously tested in animal models, the company said its graft is capable of integrating with a patient’s own tissue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The outer layer of the eye—covering the iris and pupil—can end up clouding a person’s vision following injuries, infections, scarring and other conditions. PB-001 is currently being tested in a single-arm phase 1 trial in Israel, which aims to enroll between 10 and 15 participants with excess fluid buildups in the cornea due to dysfunction within its inner cell layers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Precise Bio said it plans to announce top-line results from the study in the second half of 2026, tracking six-month efficacy outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIGHT RESTORED WITH STEM CELLS&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a title="Sight Restored to People Blinded in Eye Accidents Using New Stem Cell Treatment" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/sight-restored-to-people-blinded-in-eye-accidents-using-new-stem-cell-treatment/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Sight Restored to People Blinded in Eye Accidents Using New Stem Cell Treatment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The corneas are designed to be compatible with current surgery hardware and workflows. Shipped under long-term cryopreservation, it is delivered preloaded on standard delivery devices and unrolls during implantation to form a natural corneal shape.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“PB-001 has the potential to offer a new, standardized solution to one of ophthalmology’s most urgent needs—reliable, safe, and effective corneal replacement,” said Anthony Atala, M.D., co-founder of Precise Bio and director of the Wake Forest Institute for Regenerative Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;STAR POWER&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a title="Kate Winslet Makes Dreams Come True for Girl Losing Her Sight–Bringing Her to the Theater and Funding a Safari" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/kate-winslet-makes-dreams-come-true-for-girl-losing-her-sight-bringing-her-to-the-theater/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Kate Winslet Makes Dreams Come True for Girl Losing Her Sight–Bringing Her to the Theater and Funding a Safari&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The ability to produce patient-ready tissue on demand could lead the way towards reshaping transplant medicine as we know it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Edited from &lt;a href="https://www.fiercebiotech.com/medtech/precise-bio-completes-first-human-cornea-transplant-using-3d-printed-lab-grown-tissue" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt; by Conor Hale)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 18:00:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7AFBVV95cUxNSUg3Qld5d0RRRklLV1kxWmd3M2MzYnVUZG9ValpNQ3BNQWp5Sm1IeVUzdGJpWWpIdWhIY2JwMVhYTHVjaTFDN3lqME9fNFZxNVVWQnNZcDVaNTQ0TDl0eTNnNnFvZDBTUEZLYlkyMnBaRk94SHNhRDlVR2NrZVRlamR4VFNSYmlZRjBWcGc1ZklfZXVtMlBrRmladFhPS0JQSVhrVlZzQTVjQmdmOTRGVXdMYTZuTlRUWkxZMFh6Zk1tQ0pxUUtSOXpvaENFRXlvYnBqVFBvbHNPcG9jbEprMkFCQm1Db2pVT2h2dQ</guid></item><item><title>我丈夫在未经我允许的情况下向我释放了他的幻想。我不知道我们的婚姻能否幸存下来。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/12/sex-husband-bed-advice-bathroom-fight.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4iu6hd005pyum21bx5p45j@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Stoya and Rich here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhbih001v3b786hv4re0b@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do it,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="103" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs3y001y3b78pxeqfuzt@published"&gt;My husband recently surprised me with something unexpected when we were in bed. We had just finished having sex when he stood up and gave me a golden shower. I was shocked and disgusted and fled the room. After I had washed off, I angrily demanded to know why the hell he would do such a thing. He said he had been fantasizing about it for more than a year and needed to “get it out of his system.” I’m not sure if I can trust him again and we haven’t had sex or slept in the same room since. Is it worth trying to save my marriage?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs3z001z3b78t4ttc906@published"&gt;—Pissed Off&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs3z00203b78t4uw0fs2@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Pissed Off,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="111" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs3z00213b78tumkn8xt@published"&gt;It’s worth doing what you’re doing now—refusing sex and sleeping in separate rooms—while you sort out your feelings. Sometimes, it’s unfair to judge people based on their worst behavior; at other times, the worst behavior is so scarring that it ends up defining the relationship for us, like it or not. Now is the time to take stock. Is the relationship otherwise loving, with open communication and a strong sense of equality/both partners’ needs being met? Or was this a leak from a torrent of domineering behavior that disregards your ability to consent in favor of his comfort/pleasure? That is, is this plausibly a one-time thing, or part of a pattern?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="237" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs4100223b78wvgjqh7i@published"&gt;His peeing on you without discussing it with you first was not OK. Though there are plenty of piss enthusiasts out there, many people are disgusted by the notion for good reasons: Most of us are taught from an early age that such waste is dirty and should be avoided at all costs. As with any kink or fetish, though, regardless of the cultural associations around it, it should have been discussed ahead of time and you should have been given the opportunity to voice your disinterest. You had no reason to expect that your husband would do this, especially because you were still in bed. Those who are into piss tend to arrange for such play to be carried out in a manner that is easy to clean after—they may love it, but they typically don’t want to live in the smell of it. This may involve doing it in the shower/bathtub or putting special sheets on the bed that contain the liquid without absorbing it. There was an overall lack of consideration on your husband’s part by not discussing his interest with you ahead of time and by then &lt;em&gt;pissing in the bed you sleep in&lt;/em&gt;. It’s “out of his system,” fine—just make sure that’s true and make clear that these kinds of surprises are not welcome. If you have a hard time moving forward, you may want to enlist the help of a counselor.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmj4jhx7s00243b78jryngibu@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class="prudie-google-form" data-form-response-uri="https://docs.google.com/forms/u/0/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/formResponse" data-uri="slate.com/_components/prudie-google-form/instances/cmj4ji4e900263b78l6izgfzo@published"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="prudie-google-form__disclaimer"&gt;
      Please keep questions short (&amp;lt;150 words), and don‘t submit the same question to multiple columns. We are unable to edit or remove questions after publication. Use pseudonyms to maintain anonymity. Your submission may be used in other Slate advice columns and may be edited for publication.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="slate-notification--success js-success-message" hidden&gt;Thanks! Your question has been submitted.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmj4jibbn00293b78wxw6ghli@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jierp002b3b783453xkof@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="145" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs8002e3b78c5wh6h76@published"&gt;I am pretty happy in my marriage of over 30 years. My question is how to deal with the fact that my husband loves to have sex early in the morning and before we go to sleep. I wouldn’t mind but, our sex is hindered by the fact that it’s hard for my husband to maintain an erection. If he takes a pill, it will get hard but he says it gives him headaches. I hate to say this, but without the pill, his penis is either half hard or gives out in the middle of us making love—so I am very seldom satisfied. Afterward, he just goes to sleep. He thinks it’s great. I don’t want to hurt his feelings. It’s funny because I used to be the one with a low sex drive, but now I want more sex! How can I make this better?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="6" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs9002f3b78q8sgo572@published"&gt;—Somebody Tell Me What to Say&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="7" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs9002g3b78si2t2fgk@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Somebody Tell Me What to Say,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="114" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs9002h3b78fd08yj98@published"&gt;Definitely prioritize not hurting your husband’s feelings. This does not mean letting him off the hook for not being a thoroughly considerate partner, but you want to communicate so that he can hear you. I think first, you must determine what it is that you want. You are “dealing” with your husband’s penchant for early morning and late night sex. What would be better for you? Figure it out and ask for it. You’ve been doing it his way as a matter of default—that has bought you leverage. “I think it would be really hot if we …” is a positive way to frame this as a potentially pleasurable experience for both of you.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="127" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs9002i3b787n3ychj7@published"&gt;Other people’s erections are, uh, hard to manage. He’s talked about getting a headache from pills before, so maybe that’s your way in. I don’t know how extensively he’s sampled the different PDE5 inhibitors on the market, but sometimes people tolerate them differently. So if sildenafil (Viagra) gave him a headache, he may want to try tadalafil (Cialis) and/or vardenafil (Levitra) to see if he has better results. He could also try a cock ring. This is a delicate topic and you should handle it as sensitively as possible. It is fair for you to want a more reliable dick, but in attempting to achieve that, don’t insult him. You might ask him if he’s satisfied with his erection quality. If he’s not, there’s an in, too.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="84" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivsa002j3b78yvb1qf7z@published"&gt;Say he has no designs to do anything about the erections that underwhelm you. Are there other means of getting off that would suit you? If so, request them: oral, manual, toys, etc. You have every right to ask him to help you orgasm before he turns over and falls asleep. You can say something like, “I’m happy that you find our sex so satisfying—can you help me get off, too?” And then tell him how you want him to do that. Be specific.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmj4jizb4002l3b78t0u6t4yc@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmj4jj5le002n3b7874c91s3q@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Send Us Your Questions About the Workplace!

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="36" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jjgqg002q3b78r8o3cucc@published"&gt;The columnists behind our advice column, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/advice/good-job"&gt;Good Job&lt;/a&gt;, want to help you navigate your social dynamics at work. Does your colleague constantly bug you after hours? Has an ill-advised work romance gone awry? &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/DEVPsiDdnLHQVX7h7"&gt;Ask us your question here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmj4jjkks002t3b782uirr9pd@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jjobl002w3b78qu4voslp@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="43" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g300303b78bcyxmonb@published"&gt;I am a newly married gay man, and I thought my husband and I were going to be spending Christmas with my sister and her family. Except, she just added a condition that has me wondering whether to speak to her ever again.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="109" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g300313b78foq8tbk1@published"&gt;She and her husband have a son who just turned 3, and she said that she wants my husband and me to sleep in separate bedrooms while we stay over. Her claim is that he’s “too young to understand” why we would be sharing a room. My brother and his wife have stayed over at their place before, and when I asked him, he said they have never been faced with this sort of request (luckily he’s on my side). I have a suspicion that my sister’s husband is behind this, as he’s very Catholic.  This feels like a slap in the face to put it mildly. Is it worth reconsidering our relationship?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="7" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400323b785fpqtwnf@published"&gt;—I Thought I Had a Supportive Sister&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="8" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400333b78nh9uv866@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear I Thought I Had a Supportive Sister,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="222" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400343b78svsjulg9@published"&gt;Your sister’s condition is rude and discriminatory. I think it is also based on a fallacy. Her son is not too young to understand why you’d be sleeping in the same room. If he notices at all, which is unlikely as he is 3 and still exists mostly in his own head, all his parents would have to say to him is that his uncle is staying in the same room as another man because they are married. Unless a huge deal is made about something like this, kids tend to roll with the punches. Some uncles marry women, others marry men, still others marry people who don’t fit neatly into either category. Some never get married. Easy. If for some reason, this isn’t easy, there are several picture books made for kids that explain LGBTQ+ identities—&lt;a href="https://www.readbrightly.com/30-great-lgbtq-books-kids/"&gt;here’s a big list of them&lt;/a&gt;. Gay people are a part of the world this kid lives in, and shielding it from him is an exercise in futility. In fact, your presence in his life and household gives his parents the opportunity to explain that some people are gay, which may be different than what he is used to, but makes you no less worthy of familial bonds and love. That your sister and her husband seem to want to bury this truth is very disappointing.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="106" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400353b78f90gejd5@published"&gt;I don’t know if this is worth completely burning a bridge, though. There’s a middle ground to explore where you refuse discriminatory boarding terms but keep your sister in your life. It seems like this is the first time you’ve come up against something so overtly steeped in homophobia from this family member—you haven’t yet pushed back nor seen her reaction to the pushback. I don’t think you should tolerate sustained bigotry, but I also know that sisters are hard to come by and it’s worth finding a solution to keep family members in your life. It’s not always possible, but you should at least try.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="103" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400363b78q3b4h2eq@published"&gt;I would tell her that you and your husband will not be sleeping in separate rooms, nor should you have to change your way of life for the sake of a 3-year-old. (Incidentally, I have no time for people who talk about how queerness risks confusing children. To be a child is to be in a state of perpetual confusion, and as detailed above, this one’s particularly easy to clear up.) But you could get a hotel/Airbnb nearby so that you can spend time with your family during the holidays. This way you don’t have to compromise your marriage &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt; your holiday plans.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk8g400393b78xm7r1qlp@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Rich&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmj4j7mih001n3b786vzo892s@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="108" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4j7ukn001r3b78q1f4mlo8@published"&gt;Growing up, I was really into kink. When I met my late husband, it was a big part of my life, and he and I were heavily involved in our local BDSM scene. When he died in 2019, I felt like that part of my life died with me. I’ve gotten back into sex and dating, and I’ve mostly been having vanilla sex. It’s … not satisfying. I find myself missing kink, but it’s also caught up in missing my husband. My friends think I’m just mourning and confused, but I’m not so sure. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/12/new-sex-interests-friends-grief-advice.html"&gt;Is there a way to get back into kink after what I’ve been through?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmj4iu6hd005syum2ar5pu42m@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQbnJJUm9lRHhwZ3FCQ1JqSjZxZ3pnbFJJckZidmhCSTg0UDRlVDhTYkI1QTZLbWFMWkJZVi1ZUlZtVkt0ZjI4Q2t1UTlMeXIwUDVjSUpFS3hxcGdINWo3OFp6UzJwcVRwNndkeDNwVFNkcUV0Y1BVTmp2NDd2S1B0MQ</guid></item><item><title>哈佛肠道发现可能会改变我们治疗肥胖和糖尿病的方式- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251214100926.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A research project supported by FAPESP and carried out at Harvard University in the United States has identified a set of metabolites that move from the intestine to the liver and then on to the heart, which distributes them throughout the body. These circulating compounds appear to influence how metabolic pathways function within the liver and how sensitive the body is to insulin. The findings point to potential new strategies for treating obesity and type 2 diabetes. The study was published in &lt;em&gt;Cell Metabolism&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The hepatic portal vein drains much of the blood from the intestine to the liver. Therefore, it's the first place to receive products from the gut microbiome. In the liver, they can be conjugated, transformed, or eliminated, and then enter the systemic circulation," explains Vitor Rosetto Muñoz, first author of the study and postdoctoral researcher at the Ribeirão Preto School of Physical Education and Sports at the University of São Paulo (EEFERP-USP) in Brazil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"By analyzing the blood leaving the intestine and the peripheral blood circulating throughout the body, we were able to more accurately observe the enrichment of these metabolites derived from the gut microbiome in each location and, consequently, how they can modify hepatic metabolism and metabolic health," adds Muñoz. He completed this work during an internship at the Joslin Diabetes Center at Harvard Medical School in the United States with support from a FAPESP scholarship under the guidance of researcher Carl Ronald Kahn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gut Microbiome Diversity and Metabolic Disease Risk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the past several years, scientists have increasingly recognized that the gut microbiome acts as a key link between genetics, environmental factors, and the development of metabolic disorders. Studies have shown that people and animals with obesity, type 2 diabetes, glucose intolerance, or insulin resistance often have distinct gut microbial compositions compared to those without these conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even so, researchers still struggle to determine which specific bacteria or microbial products drive these differences or how they interact with intestinal tissues. To explore this question, the recently published study examined metabolites in the blood of mice that varied in their susceptibility to obesity and diabetes. Samples were taken from the hepatic portal vein, which carries blood from the intestine to the liver, and from peripheral blood, which travels from the liver to the heart before circulating through the body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Normally, studies tend to look at metabolites present in fecal material or peripheral blood, but they don't accurately reflect what's first reaching the tissue of the liver, which is an important metabolic organ linked to different diseases," says the researcher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environmental and Genetic Effects on Metabolite Profiles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In healthy mice, the team detected 111 metabolites enriched in the hepatic portal vein and 74 in peripheral blood. When mice genetically predisposed to obesity and type 2 diabetes were fed a hyperlipidemic diet (rich in fat), the number of metabolites enriched in the hepatic portal vein dropped from 111 to 48. This finding indicates that environmental factors, such as diet, can strongly influence the distribution of these compounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The metabolite profiles in these susceptible mice also differed from those observed in a strain of mice naturally resistant to metabolic syndrome. This contrast suggests that genetic background plays a central role in shaping which metabolites appear in the hepatic portal vein.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This shows that both the environment and the host's genetics can interact in complex ways with the gut microbiome. As a result of these interactions, different combinations of metabolites may be sent to the liver and subsequently to the peripheral circulation. These metabolites likely play an important role in mediating the conditions that lead to obesity, diabetes, and metabolic syndrome," says Muñoz.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Testing Microbiome Disruption and Metabolite Effects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To identify which bacteria and microbial byproducts contribute to these metabolite patterns, the researchers treated obesity and diabetes susceptible mice with an antibiotic designed to target specific intestinal microorganisms. As expected, the treatment altered the microbiome and changed the balance of metabolites in both peripheral blood and the hepatic portal vein.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One outcome was an increase in metabolites such as mesaconate, which participates in the Krebs cycle, a fundamental energy-producing pathway in cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using this insight, the scientists exposed hepatocytes (liver cells) to mesaconate and its isomers, which are chemical compounds with the same molecular formula but different structures. The treatments improved insulin signaling and regulated genes involved in hepatic fat accumulation (lipogenesis) and fatty acid oxidation, both of which are crucial processes for maintaining metabolic health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The metabolites found in the blood of these two sites, therefore, play important roles in mediating the effects of the microbiome on liver metabolism and the pathogenesis of type 2 diabetes insulin resistance, which is related to eating a high-fat diet," says Muñoz.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next Steps in Mapping Gut Driven Metabolic Pathways&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scientists now aim to characterize each metabolite in greater detail and determine how they are produced. This deeper understanding of microbial influences on metabolism may eventually lead to the identification of molecules that could serve as new therapeutic options for metabolic diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:24:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE1iRllkR2I3OE8yX1daRkFMV3J2ajcwZDktc3ZGekVKMEVBSnlKYV85TWVYbzBQY1lzZUlQWXBFX2dwYlNzOExPN2dsMUxJZllHVm5kdGE1bE5Zek43ZnU0RG5UcTNXMzhQWEozY0hsbw</guid></item><item><title>心脏外科医生分享了您应该“绝对避免”的四种食物，这些食物会“积极毒害”您的身体- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/lifestyle/food-and-drink/food-drink-to-avoid-christmas-997708-20251209</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p class="loading-bar_loader__2fNms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;main&gt;&lt;template id="B:0"&gt;&lt;/template&gt;&lt;p class="article-page-skeleton_background__h2J4n"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/main&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:15:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxQclRiZnJwSDVLVDdoQTZkLUJzR0dmOExUZ2JudDNvU05qVy10Y3dQclNmeWZIQUZBdEliOTJSOHlac1Y1UV8tSWVMRExad1FzeDZFMWFPVHFaak90aXdiWVp3UVlPZkdQT1ROLU9JVzZVV1UxUmdWY0hfVXh0SnJ4VEU0VnBGX2J5R3hXZ25EOVFVa1RQWmlpRjF0Yw</guid></item><item><title>简单的饮食，是一种天然的Ozempic ，并诱使您感到饱腹感-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15257157/Nutrition-Twins-natural-ozempic-weight-loss-GLP-1.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Forget needles and prescriptions, one of the hottest trends in health right now is using nutrition and lifestyle to hack your body into making more of its own natural 'Ozempic.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The key behind Ozempic and similar name-brand medications is their mimicking of a hormone produced naturally in the body called glucagon-like peptide-1, or GLP-1. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Your body already produces GLP-1, which is responsible for appetite, feeling full and supporting metabolism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The more GLP-1 you have, the easier it is to control cravings and &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/weight_loss/index.html" id="mol-8c6cea70-b991-11f0-b9f6-9f861087316c" class="class"&gt;lose weight&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, &lt;a target="_self" class="class" href="/wellness-us/nutrition/article-13265507/best-hacks-lose-weight-fast-easy.html"&gt;weight-loss drugs&lt;/a&gt; can cost more than $1,000 a month and require injecting yourself weekly with a needle. Many users also report undesirable side effects like diarrhea, vomiting and even suicidal thoughts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About one in eight adults (12 percent) report ever having taken a GLP-1 inhibitor. T&lt;span&gt;his includes the six percent of adults who say they are currently taking one of these drugs, according to a KFF poll.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But more and more people are exploring ways to naturally increase the hormone and harness its weight-loss abilities by eating the&lt;span&gt; right foods and following gut-supporting habits that can significantly boost how much and how often the hormone is released.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As registered dietitian nutritionists and personal trainers with more than 15 years of experience, we reveal the top foods to eat for boosting your natural GLP-1 without using the drugs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The Nutrition Twins (pictured) reveal the top foods to eat for boosting weight loss, along with some of their favorite products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-medium health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Fiber is the foundation of natural GLP-1 support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Fiber slows digestion, stabilizes blood sugar and naturally encourages GLP-1 release, all of which support fullness and weight management. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox floatRHS health" data-version="2" id="mol-6a168fb0-d5d1-11f0-9789-efd82214dd7b" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15257157/Nutrition-Twins-natural-ozempic-weight-loss-GLP-1.html"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;Fiber options for turning on your body’s natural 'Ozempic'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt; &lt;ul class="mol-bullets-with-font"&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Garlic&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Onions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Leeks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Green Bananas&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Jerusalem artichokes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Oats&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Cooked and cooled grains and potatoes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Lentils&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Chickpeas&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Beans&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Apples&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Asparagus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Root vegetables&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Prunes &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;High-fiber foods also add volume to meals, keeping you satisfied while managing calories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Prebiotic fibers are non-digestible carbs that feed beneficial gut bacteria. These bacteria ferment prebiotics into short-chain fatty acids (SCFAs), which signal your gut to release GLP-1 and peptide YY, another hormone that helps you feel full and regulate appetite. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Garlic and onions are two examples of prebiotic-rich foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Resistant starch is a special type of prebiotic fiber that resists digestion in the small intestine and reaches the large intestine intact, where it then feeds gut bacteria to produce SCFAs. This stimulates GLP-1 and PYY release, promoting fullness and helping with calorie control. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Good sources of resistant starch include lentils and cooked-and-cooled potatoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another type of fiber known as fermentable fibers are found in beans, oats, apples, root vegetables and prunes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These fibers also encourage SCFA production, reduce inflammation, and enhance GLP-1 signaling, contributing to appetite regulation and supporting weight management.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-medium health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Protein: Satiety hormones in action&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Protein-rich foods naturally stimulate hormones that help you feel full, including GLP-1 and PYY, which signals to your brain that you have eaten enough. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Pairing protein with fiber slows digestion, prolongs satiety and helps curb cravings, supporting weight management and steadier energy levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Research shows that protein-rich meals - often containing around 20 to 30g or more, raise GLP-1 and PYY - though responses can vary depending on the rest of the meal and individual biology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Our top protein options to boost natural GLP-1 include eggs, fish, poultry, beans, lentils and yogurt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Prunes are a good source of fiber, which slows digestion, stabilizes blood sugar and naturally encourages GLP-1 release, all of which support fullness and weight management (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-medium health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Healthy Fats: Sustained fullness and GLP-1 support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Healthy fats slow digestion and help support GLP-1 release, keeping you fuller longer and helping curb cravings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Pairing these fats with fiber and protein maximizes satiety and steadies blood sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Even small amounts - ideal for calorie control, like a drizzle of olive oil, a few nuts or a slice of avocado - can make a meaningful difference in meal satisfaction while supporting your body’s natural GLP-1 response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Our top choices include olive oil, avocados, nuts, seeds and fatty fish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-medium health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Polyphenols &amp;amp; Antioxidants: Nourish your gut and GLP-1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Polyphenols are plant compounds that feed beneficial gut bacteria and help support GLP-1 release. Foods rich in polyphenols also act as antioxidants, reducing inflammation that can interfere with hormone signaling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Top polyphenol- and antioxidant-rich choices include blueberries, raspberries, strawberries, pomegranate, dark chocolate with 70 percent cocoa or higher, green tea, grapes and apples.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Healthy fats, which include those found in nuts, slow digestion and help support GLP-1 release, keeping you fuller longer and helping curb cravings (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-medium health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Live Probiotics: live support for your gut and GLP-1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Live fermented foods provide beneficial bacteria that support GLP-1 and PYY signaling. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Key strains include Bifidobacterium, Lactobacillus and Akkermansia muciniphila, and they’re linked to increased GLP-1 production.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Akkermansia thrives when paired with polyphenol-rich foods, prebiotic fibers and omega-3s. Preclinical studies show it produces a protein called P9 that signals gut cells to make more GLP-1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some of our favorite probiotic and gut-supporting foods include yogurt with live cultures, kefir, sauerkraut, kimchi, tempeh and miso, among others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox health" data-version="2" id="mol-bbb0a5d0-d5d2-11f0-9789-efd82214dd7b" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15257157/Nutrition-Twins-natural-ozempic-weight-loss-GLP-1.html"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;How to easily add more GLP-1-boosting foods to your meals &lt;/h3&gt; &lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt; &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Breakfast&lt;/span&gt;:  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Top oatmeal or whole-grain cereal with berries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sprinkle with nuts or seeds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Enjoy Greek yogurt with fruit and a pinch of chia or flaxseeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Add a few slices of avocado or a light drizzle of olive oil to scrambled eggs or savory toast. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Try a smoothie with kefir, spinach, frozen berries and a scoop of protein powder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Lunch&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Toss beans, lentils or chickpeas into salads or grain bowls with a teaspoon of olive oil–based dressing for healthy fats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Include lean protein such as grilled chicken, turkey or tofu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Dinner&lt;/span&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Roast a mix of colorful vegetables and drizzle lightly with olive oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Include fiber-rich sides like quinoa, barley or lentils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Choose fatty fish like salmon or anchovies and rotate with lean proteins like chicken, turkey or plant-based options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Add miso soup or fermented vegetables like kimchi or sauerkraut for gut support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Snacks and drinks&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Include small portions of fruit, nuts, seeds and fermented foods daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sip green or black tea.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:08:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNa3dGNWNuTHpZYmE1MGdrSnpsNlpJNlhyVWxfTGFDN1ZQT3JGcnNfcWZ4Vjlqc0wxWktQemQ1QkIyb2ZfY09rR1hsUkpMcW9CRUdMMmdTYUpvazhVejV6Y2pEdFFORjZCVF9iMEwwQkJJSHNtQWVGUnVlNHFyYlVVWDJkb0w4a1prR1FRS2ZEWWpzdmtJZHY4MDNfa3FOZEExS0ZUX21aVmVKZw</guid></item><item><title>一个研究生的疯狂想法引发了一个重大的老龄化突破- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251213032625.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;One potential strategy for treating a wide range of illnesses involves targeting senescent cells. These cells -- also known as "zombie cells" -- stop multiplying but fail to clear themselves from the body as healthy cells normally do. They appear in many conditions, including cancer, Alzheimer's disease, and throughout the aging process. Although scientists are working on ways to eliminate or repair these cells, a major challenge has been detecting them within living tissue without disturbing nearby healthy cells.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers at Mayo Clinic, writing in the journal &lt;em&gt;Aging Cell&lt;/em&gt;, describe a new method for labeling senescent cells. Their approach uses "aptamers" -- short pieces of synthetic DNA that fold into three-dimensional structures. These structures can attach to proteins found on the outer surfaces of cells. In experiments with mouse cells, the team identified several rare aptamers, selected from more than 100 trillion random DNA sequences, that were able to recognize specific surface proteins and mark senescent cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This approach established the principle that aptamers are a technology that can be used to distinguish senescent cells from healthy ones," says biochemist and molecular biologist Jim Maher, III, Ph.D., a principal investigator of the study. "Though this study is a first step, the results suggest the approach could eventually apply to human cells."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How a Chance Conversation Sparked a Collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The idea that led to this project began when a Mayo Clinic graduate student shared an offbeat thought during a casual discussion with a classmate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keenan Pearson, Ph.D. -- who recently received his degree from Mayo Clinic Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences -- had been working with Dr. Maher on how aptamers might be used for neurodegenerative diseases or brain cancer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, several floors above, fellow graduate student Sarah Jachim, Ph.D., was studying senescent cells and aging in the lab of researcher Nathan LeBrasseur, Ph.D.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their paths crossed at a scientific gathering, where they exchanged ideas about their thesis projects. Dr. Pearson wondered if aptamers could be adapted to detect senescent cells. "I thought the idea was a good one, but I didn't know about the process of preparing senescent cells to test them, and that was Sarah's expertise," says Dr. Pearson, who became lead author of the publication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mentors Back a Bold Student Idea&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The students brought their concept to their advisors and to researcher Darren Baker, Ph.D., whose work centers on senescent cell therapies. Dr. Maher recalls that the idea initially struck him as "crazy" but worth exploring. All three mentors supported the proposal. "We frankly loved that it was the students' idea and a real synergy of two research areas," says Dr. Maher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As early experiments produced promising results, the pair enlisted more students from their labs. Then-graduate students Brandon Wilbanks, Ph.D., Luis Prieto, Ph.D., and M.D.-Ph.D. student Caroline Doherty added new techniques, including advanced microscopy and additional tissue types. "It became encouraging to expend more effort," Dr. Jachim says, "because we could tell it was a project that was going to succeed."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revealing New Clues About Senescent Cells&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond providing a tagging method, the research offered insight into the biology of senescent cells. "To date, there aren't universal markers that characterize senescent cells," says Dr. Maher. "Our study was set up to be open-ended about the target surface molecules on senescent cells. The beauty of this approach is that we let the aptamers choose the molecules to bind to."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team found that several aptamers attached to a variant of a protein called fibronectin on the surface of mouse cells. Scientists do not yet know how this fibronectin variant relates to senescence. However, its discovery suggests that aptamers may help identify features unique to senescent cells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potential Applications for Human Health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More work will be needed to find aptamers that can reliably detect senescent cells in human tissue. If aptamers can be adapted for this purpose, they could eventually be used to deliver treatments directly to these cells. Dr. Pearson notes that aptamers are less costly and more flexible than traditional antibodies, which are commonly used to distinguish one cell type from another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This project demonstrated a novel concept," says Dr. Maher. "Future studies may extend the approach to applications related to senescent cells in human disease."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE9tYzI4Y2Zzd3BRZFNJY0t3eGlzWVR1SmpqMjJFTkx5SkV5bzlTUzZfRllIdGFPUFVEUGFmUmRvUTBPWDJnLS1rR1VvMlZOVEgtMkt2TlAyU1dvY2xZYlFOeTFYMk9VMjBWSU0wWjFfdw</guid></item><item><title>我尝试了“每天超过10,000步”的步行方法–这就是为什么我是一个粉丝-独立报</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/health-and-fitness/japanese-walking-workout-iwt-10000-steps-weight-loss-b2884233.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 gIQPHK sc-jbiisr-1" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 dFpFuY"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 iBibVd"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 jVZWGn"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 juUDRT"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 cqPbFA"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 rAFIl sc-hez36s-16 jZSKtc"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 PdmgT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 eZqxmv"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 tawua"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 gZmYS"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 cglitp"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 keLMOw sc-aja53j-7 eMEmGu"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 dHXFkr"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 dIsmaL"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 hUgQwJ sc-culv3z-0 eifaJK sc-a5wy94-0 hyKPon"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="big-letter"&gt;W&lt;/span&gt;alking is an accessible form of movement with impressive health-boosting credentials; I think there is enough research available to safely make that statement. Treating &lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/10k-steps-a-day-walking-b2735565.html"&gt;10,000 steps per day&lt;/a&gt; as the gold standard for a healthy lifestyle is far more contentious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number stems from a 1960s Japanese marketing campaign for a pedometer called the Manpo-Kei, or “10,000 steps metre”. It’s a nice round number, but it’s not one identified by science as the holy grail for health – a 2023 study by the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.ugr.es/en/about/news/how-many-steps-take-each-day-reduce-risk-premature-death8000"&gt;University of Granada&lt;/a&gt; suggests that, while more is better, 8,000 is sufficient “to significantly reduce the risk of premature death”​​. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/topic/walking"&gt;Walking&lt;/a&gt; 10,000 steps also takes a fair old while. Even at a decent nick, this task is likely to take you upwards of 90 minutes each day, making it a struggle for busy folks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-31azim-0 eBMXOi nextSwipeIgnore sentry-block"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU sc-wlmftc-0 ccDPKb"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-hKDTPf hmBpZX"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/K7Ehvq-bm6I"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, an alternative walking protocol – colloquially termed “Japanese walking” due to its country of origin – has stepped into the spotlight online. It takes just 30 minutes per day, with fitness coach and content creator &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.instagram.com/coacheugeneteo/?hl=en"&gt;Eugene Teo&lt;/a&gt; claiming it offers “10 times the benefits” of walking 10,000 steps per day in his viral video above. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a fitness writer, I’ve covered walking extensively, finding it’s one of the best ways to help people of all fitness levels introduce more movement into their regular routine. So, intrigued, I endeavoured to try “Japanese walking” and find out if the impressive health claims around it held water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to try the ‘Japanese walking’ method&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complete the sequence below five times without any breaks:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-kk992l-0 sc-1k7glnk-1 dDVXDN irZnNR"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Three minutes of walking at a low intensity (40 per cent peak aerobic capacity, or a relaxed pace) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Three minutes of walking at a high intensity (70 per cent peak aerobic capacity, or a brisk pace) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Benefits of Japanese walking&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The “Japanese walking” protocol comes from a study published in the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17605959/"&gt;Mayo Clinic Proceedings&lt;/a&gt; journal in 2007. It was designed to test whether high-intensity interval walking training (IWT) can offer greater benefits than moderate-intensity continuous walking training, in terms of improving thigh muscle strength, peak aerobic capacity (the maximum amount of oxygen you can take in and use during exercise) and blood pressure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over five months, 60 men and 186 women with an average age of 63 were divided into three groups; no walking training, IWT and CWT (continuous walking training). The CWT group was instructed to walk at 50 per cent of their peak aerobic capacity (a fairly slow pace) and take 8,000 or more steps per day at least four times per week. The IWT group was told to complete the protocol above, four or more times per week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among participants who met these conditions, those in the IWT group saw a 13 per cent increase in isometric knee flexion, a 17 per cent increase in isometric knee flexion, and an eight per cent increase in peak aerobic capacity for walking. This was “significantly greater than the increases observed in the moderate-intensity continuous walking training group”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research also found a greater reduction in resting systolic blood pressure in the IWT group, despite the fact they didn’t spend as much time walking each week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The conclusion states: “high-intensity interval walking may protect against age-associated increases in blood pressure and decreases in thigh muscle strength and peak aerobic capacity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/life-style/japanese-walking-trend-weight-loss-b2759539.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The latest walking trend that could help burn more calories and lower blood pressure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 htsIMX"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/04/8/36/Walking-is-one-of-the-most-accessible-forms-of-movement-offering-impressive-health-benefits.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/04/8/36/Walking-is-one-of-the-most-accessible-forms-of-movement-offering-impressive-health-benefits.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/04/8/36/Walking-is-one-of-the-most-accessible-forms-of-movement-offering-impressive-health-benefits.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Walking is one of the most accessible forms of movement, offering impressive health benefits" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-263151"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Walking is one of the most accessible forms of movement, offering impressive health benefits&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (David Lovelady)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What happened when I tried Japanese walking&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don’t have a full science lab set up at home; what I do have is two legs, a &lt;a href="/extras/indybest/outdoor-activity/sports-equipment-accessories/best-garmin-watch-b1903982.html"&gt;Garmin watch&lt;/a&gt; and a lot of walking experience, so I decided to put these to good use. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During my Monday lunch break, I took my dog for a 30-minute walk as normal. Then, at 1pm the following day, I tried the “Japanese walking” method on the same looped route, setting my Garmin Vivoactive to record both sessions and taking note of any subjective changes I felt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My usual 30-minute walk saw me accrue nearly 3,000 steps, covering 2.12km at an average speed of 14min 10sec per kilometre. My heart rate averaged 85bpm, remaining fairly constant throughout, and I burned an estimated 157 calories. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As anyone who has owned a dog might expect, there was a good deal of stopping and starting to inspect particularly interesting trees and bollards, and I defaulted to a fairly casual pace amid a busy work day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the Japanese walking protocol, my numbers looked a bit different, with my fast pace falling just below 120 steps per minute and my slow pace a few shy of 100 steps per minute. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I travelled significantly further, covering 2.94km and 3,500 steps at an average speed of 10min 12sec per kilometre. My average heart rate came out very similar (86bpm) but there were noticeable peaks (104bpm) and troughs in line with the high- and low-speed intervals. My estimated calorie burn was also significantly higher: 211. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/life-style/health-and-families/how-many-steps-a-day-cancer-risk-b2756669.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How many steps to take each day to slash your risk of cancer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Benefits of the Japanese walking method&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea that walking faster, or sprinkling more intensity into your exercise, holds greater benefits is nothing new. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Specialist in walking for health, &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://education.ua.edu/about/directory/faculty-directory/elroy-aguiar/"&gt;Dr Elroy Aguiar&lt;/a&gt;, is an assistant professor at the University of Alabama’s department of kinesiology. He was the lead author on a 2024 paper published in the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/sms.14762"&gt;Scandinavian Journal of Medicine and Science in Sports&lt;/a&gt;, which correlated as little as one minute of high-intensity activity with improved health outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One of the really interesting findings from our paper was that, if you look at people’s highest one minute of activity across each day, averaged across the monitoring period, that was a very strong signal for whether they had one or more metabolic syndrome risk factors [elevated waist circumference, high triglycerides, low HDL (or “good” cholesterol), high blood pressure and high blood sugar] present,” he tells me. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another series of studies he worked on, featured in the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29858465/"&gt;British Journal of Sports Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, pointed to the fact that “if you walk at a cadence of about 100 steps per minute, that’s equivalent to what’s called ‘moderate-intensity’, and all of the research in this area suggests that most of the benefits [of walking] accumulate at a moderate or higher intensity”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond this, completing the Japanese walking method four times per week leaves you half-an-hour away from the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/physical-activity"&gt;World Health Organisation’s&lt;/a&gt; “global recommendations of at least 150 minutes of moderate-intensity physical activity per week”. Add a couple of short full-body &lt;a href="/topic/strength-training"&gt;strength training&lt;/a&gt; sessions into the mix and you have a decent &lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/short-workouts-plan-fitness-dan-john-b2737277.html"&gt;minimalist workout plan&lt;/a&gt; for beginners. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/life-style/step-count-walking-benefits-10000-day-b2739534.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How your step count became the ultimate modern humblebrag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 cztisH"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/09/13/09/Untitled-design-%2889%29.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/09/13/09/Untitled-design-%2889%29.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/09/13/09/Untitled-design-%2889%29.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Completing the ‘Japanese walking’ method a few times each week sets you well on your way to hitting the World Health Organisation’s weekly physical activity guidelines" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-263152"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Completing the ‘Japanese walking’ method a few times each week sets you well on your way to hitting the World Health Organisation’s weekly physical activity guidelines&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Harry Bullmore/The Independent)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Potential drawbacks of the Japanese Walking method&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of the information above paints the Japanese walking method in a favourable light – as it should, with the protocol delivering impressive results in a non-intimidating time-span. However, if we are questioning the claim that it is “better” than walking 10,000 steps a day, there are a few further areas to consider. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Firstly, Dr Aguiar’s 2024 paper supported the idea that the “best” walking method for reducing metabolic risk factors involves a combination of high volume (number of steps) and high intensity (walking speed). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Accumulating a high volume of walking throughout the day [8,000-plus steps], then focussing on at least 30 minutes of faster walking or jogging, would be a way to move the metrics in a positive direction and lower your metrics for each of the [metabolic syndrome] risk factors,” he says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I racked up a little over 3,500 steps when trying the Japanese Walking method – less than half of the 8,000 daily steps research has repeatedly linked to many favourable health outcomes, and short of the 5,000 mark often viewed as the threshold for a sedentary lifestyle. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using this method as part, rather than all, of your daily steps could be a better approach for achieving your health goals. However, if you only have 30 minutes per day free, it still offers dramatically more benefits than not moving at all, and improved return on investment over a regular 30-minute walk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another area where the Japanese walking method loses out to walking 10,000 steps per day is movement regularity. While the former involves a concentrated 30-minute dose of activity, the latter can be spread throughout the day, encouraging you to abandon your office chair and sofa more often. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 10-year study of 8,000 people, published in the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30551177/"&gt;American Journal of Epidemiology&lt;/a&gt;, found that those replaced 30 minutes of daily sitting with light activity had a 17 per cent lower risk of dying in that period. This even applied if they accrued these 30 minutes across short intervals throughout the day – hence why your smartwatch is constantly sending you reminders to stand up and move. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regular movement can also help maintain mobility and reduce stiffness in our joints and muscles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When we’re dealing with an adaptation from stillness, movement is the answer, so any movement is better than just being still,” movement mechanics expert and &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.thetrainingstimulus.com/"&gt;The Training Stimulus&lt;/a&gt; founder Ash Grossmann summarises. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final factor to consider is enjoyment. By adding a rigid framework, Japanese walking ensures intensity. However, it also meant I was unable to stop and chat to people in the park or appreciate my surroundings to the same extent. For me, this lowered the stress-busting potential of my walk, sacrificing some of the usual mental health benefits of walking for physical ones. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/news/health/fart-walk-benefits-type-2-diabetes-cancer-b2744886.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What the heck is a fart walk? Why this practice is being hailed as the secret to healthy aging&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 cztisH"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/04/8/50/I-found-the-Japanese-walking-method-was-more-effective-at-raising-my-heart-rate-potentially-offering.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/04/8/50/I-found-the-Japanese-walking-method-was-more-effective-at-raising-my-heart-rate-potentially-offering.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/04/8/50/I-found-the-Japanese-walking-method-was-more-effective-at-raising-my-heart-rate-potentially-offering.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="I found the 'Japanese walking' method was more effective at raising my heart rate, potentially offering greater physical benefits, but I preferred the calming effects of a standard walk" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-263153"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;I found the 'Japanese walking' method was more effective at raising my heart rate, potentially offering greater physical benefits, but I preferred the calming effects of a standard walk&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Harry Bullmore/The Independent)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The Japanese walking method: the verdict&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In my time writing about health and fitness, the net positive effect of regular movement has been one of the most striking common denominators. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those looking for a minimum effective dose: any movement will do you a lot of good, particularly if your starting point is a sedentary lifestyle. But if you can fit one or two quick full-body strength training sessions, regular aerobic activity (like walking) and an occasional dash of more intense exercise into each week, it will stand you in very good stead. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walking is among the most accessible forms of exercise there is, lowering the barrier to entry for exercise for billions of people, which is why I’m always keen to promote it. However, in the modern world, even finding time for a quick walk can be tricky for particularly busy individuals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Japanese walking method provides a time-savvy way to enjoy many of the benefits of a greater volume of daily walking. Sure, you could enjoy higher-intensity exercise in any number of other forms, from cycling to a HIIT workout, but walking remains the most efficient – you don’t even need a change of clothes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So should you try it? Yes, especially if you’re short on time and looking for a way to squeeze health-boosting movement into your day. And should you stick with it? This depends. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you enjoy this framework, or find it’s something you can stick to with a good degree of regularity, that’s the ticket to a sustainable movement habit and the many health benefits that come from it. If not, look for an alternative form of moderate- to high-intensity exercise that you find fun, and commit to this instead – consistency is the key to long-term results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/walking-10000-steps-a-day-calories-fitness-b2650416.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walking 10,000 steps day might not matter if you don’t do this one thing, according to an expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:33:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxOc0RPQ042dmZvckQ4eDdDMVNvZWk5YmtKcHJBQWhRbEU0c1UxaVk1OUw5dTRSdy1KeV92Qi1rNnZSQWM2aHFjQy1nT1F3eldId25VUWVlTGc0WUZ6X2tVWDh4VzBQZzRFakkycHpmSVg2Q3NETW9CMjBKdFdqWkVfNFRoMzV4ZlRpdkROa3pHZ3VkazFITGVFSXpwQUw4ZXNnWVdYWXFfdVZGbXhiT1RhRnQ1cTdZUQ</guid></item><item><title>阿托伐他汀召回可能会影响数十万患者–并反映出FDA在检查海外生产的药物时遇到的麻烦-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/atorvastatin-recall-may-affect-hundreds-152027420.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you take cholesterol-lowering drugs called statins, you may have noticed a flurry of &lt;a href="https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2025/10/23/generic-statin-atorvastatin-calcium-recall/86861216007/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:news coverage;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;news coverage&lt;/a&gt; since &lt;a href="https://www.aarp.org/health/conditions-treatments/atorvastatin-recall-october-2025/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:late October 2025;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;late October 2025&lt;/a&gt; about an extensive recall of thousands of bottles of atorvastatin, the generic version of Lipitor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Both generic atorvastatin and brand-name Lipitor contain the same active ingredient, atorvastatin calcium, and are considered bioequivalent by the Food and Drug Administration. This medication is the &lt;a href="https://clincalc.com/DrugStats/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:No. 1-selling drug;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;No. 1-selling drug&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S., with over 115 million prescriptions going to more than 29 million Americans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I am a &lt;a href="https://pharmacy.uconn.edu/person/c-michael-white/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:clinical pharmacologist and pharmacist;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;clinical pharmacologist and pharmacist&lt;/a&gt; who has assessed the manufacturing quality of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10600280251343626" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:prescription;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;prescription&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10600280241233255" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:over-the-counter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;over-the-counter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/87551225251326811" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:illicit drugs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;illicit drugs&lt;/a&gt;, as well as &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/1060028019900504" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dietary supplements;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;dietary supplements&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This atorvastatin recall is large, potentially affecting hundreds of thousands of patients. But it’s only the latest in a &lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/fda-drug-loophole-sun-pharma" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:series of concerning manufacturing issues;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;series of concerning manufacturing issues&lt;/a&gt; that have come to light since 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;What pills are being recalled, and why?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ascend Laboratories, based in New Jersey, originally issued the recall for &lt;a href="https://www.accessdata.fda.gov/scripts/ires/?Event=97639" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:about 142,000 bottles;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;about 142,000 bottles&lt;/a&gt; of its generic atorvastatin on Sept. 19. Each bottle contained 90, 500 or 1,000 tablets, enough to fill prescriptions for three, 17 or 33 patients, respectively, for one month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;About three weeks later, on Oct. 10, the FDA quantified the risk of using these poor-quality tablets and gave the recall a &lt;a href="https://www.accessdata.fda.gov/scripts/ires/?Event=97639" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Class II status;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Class II status&lt;/a&gt;, which means that the medication could cause “&lt;a href="https://pharmacyfreak.com/drug-recalls-in-the-usa-what-happens-when-the-fda-recalls-a-drug-understanding-class-i-ii-and-iii-recalls/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:temporary or medically reversible;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;temporary or medically reversible&lt;/a&gt; adverse health consequences.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Manufacturers &lt;a href="https://pharmaeducation.net/quality-control-tests-of-tablets-or-evaluation-of-tablets/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:must conduct quality tests;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;must conduct quality tests&lt;/a&gt; on random samples of tablets from every batch they make. These tests make sure the pills contain the correct dosage of the active ingredient, are made to the proper physical specifications and are not contaminated with heavy metals or microbes. If the samples test &lt;a href="https://www.gmpsop.com/what-are-the-elements-of-quality-control-process-in-pharmaceuticals/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:“out of specification”;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;“out of specification”&lt;/a&gt; for any feature, the company must conduct further testing and destroy defective batches, losing the cost of manufacturing them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In this case, sample pills &lt;a href="https://www.usp.org/sites/default/files/usp/document/harmonization/gen-method/stage_6_monograph_25_feb_2011.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:failed to dissolve properly;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;failed to dissolve properly&lt;/a&gt; when they were tested. Batches manufactured from November 2024 through September 2025 all had this defect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As with other drugs, when you swallow atorvastatin, it must &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK557405/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dissolve before the active ingredient can be absorbed;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;dissolve before the active ingredient can be absorbed&lt;/a&gt; by the body. It then goes to the liver, where it reduces the blood concentrations of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/1060028017722009" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:low-density lipoproteins;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;low-density lipoproteins&lt;/a&gt; – also called LDL, or “bad cholesterol.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If the drug doesn’t dissolve properly, the amount absorbed by the body is substantially reduced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1056/NEJMoa050461" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Lowering LDL with atorvastatin;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Lowering LDL with atorvastatin&lt;/a&gt; has been shown to reduce cardiovascular events like heart attacks and strokes after a few years by 22%. When almost 30,000 people in a 2021 study stopped taking their &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamanetworkopen.2021.13186" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:atorvastatin or other statin for six months;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;atorvastatin or other statin for six months&lt;/a&gt;, the risk of cardiovascular events, deaths and emergency room visits increased between 12% to 15%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So, while patients wouldn’t immediately feel a difference if their atorvastatin tablets didn’t dissolve properly, their risk of cardiovascular events would significantly rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;What should patients on generic atorvastatin do?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;First, don’t stop taking the medication without talking with your pharmacist or prescriber. Even if you have the recalled pills, taking them is still better than not taking the medicine at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;You can determine whether your medication came from Ascend Laboratories by looking at your prescription label.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Search for the abbreviations &lt;a href="https://www.printablelabeltemplates.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/prescription-label-template-microsoft-word-prescription-label-template-best-business-template-within-prescription-label-template-RfKgMc.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:MFG or MFR;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;MFG or MFR&lt;/a&gt;, which stand for “manufacturing” or “manufacturer.” If it says “MFG Ascend” or “MFR Ascend,” that means that Ascend Laboratories supplied the medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The first five letters of a National Drug Code, abbreviated as NDC on the prescription label, also reveal the manufacturer or distributor. &lt;a href="https://ndclist.com/ndc/67877-513/package/67877-513-10" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ascend products have the number 67877;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Ascend products have the number 67877&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If Ascend Laboratories is the distributor, a pharmacist can cross-reference your prescription number to obtain the lot number and compare it with the &lt;a href="https://www.accessdata.fda.gov/scripts/ires/?Event=97639" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:posted lot numbers;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;posted lot numbers&lt;/a&gt; on the FDA website for recalled atorvastatin. If your product has been recalled, your pharmacy may have other generic versions of atorvastatin in stock that are not part of this recall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;You should be able to tell from the prescription label whether your atorvastatin comes from the manufacturer that announced the recall. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.gettyimages.com/detail/photo/elderly-woman-examining-a-medicine-bottle-in-a-royalty-free-image/2194995487" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:benixs/Moment via Getty Images;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;benixs/Moment via Getty Images&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Alternatively, the pharmacist can get a new prescription from your health care provider for another &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/009127000204200902" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:generic statin drug, such as rosuvastatin;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;generic statin drug, such as rosuvastatin&lt;/a&gt;, which &lt;a href="https://www.pharmacypracticenews.com/Clinical/Article/06-22/Using-National-Guidelines-to-Determine-Hyperlipidemia-Treatment/67209" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:works similarly;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;works similarly&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;A pattern of lapses for overseas manufacturers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While the defective atorvastatin is distributed by a U.S. company, it is actually manufactured by &lt;a href="https://www.accessdata.fda.gov/scripts/ires/?Event=97639" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Alkem Laboratories in India;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Alkem Laboratories in India&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In fact, many aspects of pharmaceutical drug manufacturing are now occurring overseas, primarily in China and India. This has limited the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/1060028019881692" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:FDA’s ability to provide the oversight;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;FDA’s ability to provide the oversight&lt;/a&gt; required for drugs sold in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the 1990s and early 2000s, the FDA &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/1060028019881692" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:performed routine surveillance inspections;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;performed routine surveillance inspections&lt;/a&gt; of U.S. manufacturing plants every three years, but seldom conducted them overseas. In the wake of several high-profile manufacturing quality lapses, including at &lt;a href="https://oig.hhs.gov/fraud/enforcement/generic-drug-manufacturer-ranbaxy-pleads-guilty-and-agrees-to-pay-500-million-to-resolve-false-claims-allegations-cgmp-violations-and-false-statements-to-the-fda/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:the Indian generic drug giant Ranbaxy Laboratories;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;the Indian generic drug giant Ranbaxy Laboratories&lt;/a&gt;, Congress &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/about-fda/fda-track-agency-wide-program-performance/fda-track-generic-drug-user-fee-amendments-gdufa-performance-reports" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:established a funding mechanism;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;established a funding mechanism&lt;/a&gt; and the FDA established a universal standard for inspecting both U.S. and overseas manufacturers every five years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;However, the U.S. fell behind with international inspections after COVID-19 shut down international travel, and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10600280251343626" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:it has yet to catch up;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;it has yet to catch up&lt;/a&gt;. Additionally, overseas manufacturers generally get warning of an upcoming inspection, making the process potentially less rigorous than in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A lack of inspections for eye drop manufacturers, especially in India, led to massive recalls in 2023 after a wave of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10600280241233255" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:rare eye infections;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;rare eye infections&lt;/a&gt; caused some people to lose their eyesight. The problem was traced to widespread unsanitary manufacturing conditions and improper testing for sterility at overseas facilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In 2024, &lt;a href="https://www.medpagetoday.com/publichealthpolicy/fdageneral/114762" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:eight deaths and multiple hospitalizations;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;eight deaths and multiple hospitalizations&lt;/a&gt; led an Indian manufacturer, Glenmark Pharmaceuticals, to recall 47 million potassium chloride extended-release capsules that did not dissolve properly. In February 2025, inspectors found that the company had falsified quality results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The FDA recently started &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10600280251343626" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:laboratory spot testing;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;laboratory spot testing&lt;/a&gt; of prescription and over-the-counter drugs arriving in the U.S. to compensate for these limitations. Outside laboratories such as &lt;a href="https://www.valisure.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Valisure;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Valisure&lt;/a&gt; also do independent testing. Independent testing has caught several dangerous products, but due to limited resources, only a few products can be tested each year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In 2023, Alkem Laboratories, which manufactured the currently recalled atorvastatin, had to recall 58,000 bottles of the blood pressure drug &lt;a href="https://www.hmpgloballearningnetwork.com/site/pln/news/beta-blocker-recalled-1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:metoprolol XL;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;metoprolol XL&lt;/a&gt; because the pills also did not properly dissolve. Spot testing also led to widespread recalls after FDA and Valisure laboratories found cancer-causing chemicals called nitrosamines in some &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/1060028019892222" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:blood pressure, diabetes;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;blood pressure, diabetes&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jama.2021.10043" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:indigestion drugs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;indigestion drugs&lt;/a&gt; tested between 2019 and 2020, as well as benzene in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10600280251343626" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:numerous sunscreen and antibacterial gel products;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;numerous sunscreen and antibacterial gel products&lt;/a&gt; tested between 2020 and early 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Raising consumer vigilance&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;With these growing gaps in oversight, it’s reasonable to be mindful of changes in how a particular medication affects you. If your prescription drug suddenly stops working, it might be because that particular batch of the medication was not manufactured properly. Alerting the FDA &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/safety/medical-product-safety-information/medwatch-forms-fda-safety-reporting" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:about sudden loss of drug effectiveness;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;about sudden loss of drug effectiveness&lt;/a&gt; could help the agency more quickly identify manufacturing issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In 2024, the FDA started &lt;a href="https://www.ema.europa.eu/en/partners-networks/international-activities/bilateral-interactions-non-eu-regulators/united-states" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sharing the inspection burden;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;sharing the inspection burden&lt;/a&gt; with other regulatory agencies like the European Medicines Agency for the European Union. Such coordinated efforts could lead to less duplication and a bump in inspections of overseas manufacturers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the meantime, however, consumers are largely at the mercy of spotty inspections and testing, and rarely hear about problems unless poorly manufactured drugs cause widespread adverse events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="http://theconversation.com/us?utm_source=Yahoo&amp;amp;utm_medium=related-link&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related-link-0&amp;amp;utm_content=article-268364" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The Conversation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt;, a nonprofit, independent news organization bringing you facts and trustworthy analysis to help you make sense of our complex world. It was written by: &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/c-michael-white-382205?utm_source=Yahoo&amp;amp;utm_medium=related-link&amp;amp;utm_campaign=byline-link&amp;amp;utm_content=article-268364" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:C. Michael White;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;C. Michael White&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-connecticut-1342?utm_source=Yahoo&amp;amp;utm_medium=related-link&amp;amp;utm_campaign=byline-link&amp;amp;utm_content=article-268364" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:University of Connecticut;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;University of Connecticut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;C. Michael White does not work for, consult, own shares in or receive funding from any company or organization that would benefit from this article, and has disclosed no relevant affiliations beyond their academic appointment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:20:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQQUVyNU1zdVBRblhLN1I0M3ZjdWF0Q1l0ZUwyaURTenpGeGdxUW9zTHR1Zk5LWWJfMkRqSkZBTEZsUXdVOTF3VkVqVmJuNTViNW1MUWVBdjRIM2tFT2wzSm9OVUVFQzZleTdWNmJYU3VpaGxQVVh0U0NOZ1JfQU9PbFRaRmNiS2k5TjB5LVYydWJFeVFW</guid></item><item><title>25岁的认证营养和健康教练的首选早餐： “它让我成功，它让我感觉良好” - CNBC</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/12/14/certified-nutrition-and-health-coachs-go-to-breakfast.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-articleBody--AEqcE" id="MakeItRegularArticle-ArticleBody-5" data-module="ArticleBody" data-test="articleBody-1" data-analytics="MakeItRegularArticle-articleBody-5-1"&gt;&lt;span class="HighlightShare-styles-makeit-hidden--MFwCR"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;From how much &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/16/4-energy-boosting-foods-according-to-nutritionists.html"&gt;energy you have first thing in the morning&lt;/a&gt;, to how &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/23/a-nutritionist-shares-the-best-grocery-foods-to-boost-mood-brain-energy-happiness.html"&gt;your mood&lt;/a&gt; ebbs and flows throughout the day, the foods you eat have a significant impact on how you feel. It's why doctors and nutritionists alike consider the first meal of the day to be most important. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://healthwithhunter.shop/pages/about-me" target="_blank"&gt;Hunter Stoler&lt;/a&gt;, a NYC-based certified nutrition and health coach, has a go-to breakfast that he eats just about every day to feel his best. Known as "&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/healthwithhunter/" target="_blank"&gt;Health with Hunter&lt;/a&gt;" on social media, the 25-year-old also recommends this breakfast to his more than 400,000 followers on Instagram and 300,000+ followers on TikTok. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll say six out of every seven days a week, I have a yogurt bowl just because I know it's balanced," Stoler tells CNBC Make It.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His yogurt bowl recipe is high in fiber and protein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="withOneTrustPlaceholder-placeholderDimensions OneTrustLoadingPlaceholder-container"&gt;&lt;span class="DynamicLoadingIndicator-spinnerParent" data-test="DynamicLoadingIndicator" data-testid="DynamicLoadingIndicator"&gt;&lt;span class="DynamicLoadingIndicator-spinner"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It sets me up for success, it makes me feel good and I'm full for a few hours after that," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The breakfast allows him to up his fiber intake, which, research shows, many people often lack in their diets. Less than 10% of U.S. adults get the recommended daily intake of fiber, according to a study which was presented at &lt;a href="https://nutrition.org/n24/" target="_blank"&gt;Nutrition 2021 Live Online&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are the key ingredients in Stoler's daily yogurt bowl. Plus, some of his other healthy breakfast options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Health with Hunter's go-to high-fiber, high-protein breakfast&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just about every morning, Stoler mixes together these five ingredients:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Non-fat Greek yogurt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Half a serving of protein powder&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Frozen organic wild blueberries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Healthy cereal or granola&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spices (cinnamon, pumpkin spice or a pinch of salt)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's flexibility in that, but the structure of the meal is the same," Stoler says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That combination of protein from the protein powder and Greek yogurt, fiber from the blueberries, and potentially a little bit from the cereal or granola, is what's going to keep me really full and just satisfied."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research shows that the antioxidants found in blueberries can help &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/01/14/holy-grail-of-longevity-foods-that-this-doctor-eats-every-day.html"&gt;reduce inflammation, improve your brain health&lt;/a&gt; and lead to more positive health outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-container--Gwv2j" data-test="Pullquote"&gt;&lt;div class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-pullquote--yciaK Pullquote-styles-makeit-pullquoteBase--I6tb3"&gt;&lt;p class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-quotemark--wOJVx"&gt;&lt;span class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-quotemark1--_xuDE"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-quotemark2--Fbxk0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-wrapper--J7kni"&gt;&lt;p class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-quote--PKfrc"&gt;The opportunities are endless, but remember, it's about the structure with flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-sourceWrapper--_Vvz3"&gt;&lt;p class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-sourceAccentWrapper--Ubl5i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-source--S2oO1"&gt;Hunter Stoler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-info--K2Jz_"&gt;Nutrition and health coach&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Stoler's other go-to morning meals that's high in fiber and protein is overnight oatmeal. He mixes together almond milk or whole milk with a cup of glyphosate-free oats and a scoop of protein powder. He stores it in his fridge until the following day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Then the next morning, you have delicious oats that you could top with fruit, a nut butter, which is really great, cinnamon and maybe a little bit of Greek yogurt for more protein," Stoler says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If he's craving a warm, healthy breakfast, he toasts high-fiber bread and tops it with savory foods like scrambled eggs and avocado, or yogurt for a sweet option. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The opportunities are endless, but remember, it's about the structure with flexibility," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to give your kids the ultimate advantage?&lt;/strong&gt; Sign up for CNBC's new online course, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://smarter.cnbcmakeit.com/p/how-to-raise-financially-smart-kids?utm_source=cnbc&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=makeitarticle&amp;amp;amp;utm_campaign=bottom" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Raise Financially Smart Kids&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Learn how to build healthy financial habits today to set your children up for greater success in the future. Use coupon code EARLYBIRD for 30% off. Offer valid from Dec. 8 to Dec. 22, 2025. Terms apply.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-relatedContent--nvEkA" id="MakeItRegularArticle-RelatedContent-1"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-container--UeiCK"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-nonCollapsibleContent--jmjdo"&gt;&lt;h2 class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-header--DqhoP"&gt;Take control of your money with CNBC Select &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CNBC Select is editorially independent and may earn a commission from affiliate partners on links.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="ArticleBody-MobileAdhesion" class="MobileAdhesion-container" data-module="mps-slot"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOWnZWVjlqSlZoOUNOZWVmR3R1WGx1Tzh5QTdIR3BGbHhWR09BQzRERDVjXzQ5WDd0VGhGdWpzQVNvSDc0akJJcHdZc1RUbERGSnBlekx5LUE4Z0duZVVjQ1pDNndjNTNQNElsMEJtRVY0cFM2ZzRKWm1nUVdIR2VtRkktd0dYak85R3hyNjRoR0d3TEVC0gGaAUFVX3lxTE1mVGNIeXN3cGFpU0trTU5xNHRrMjV5MTNackRuMXZ4dzNiMHRVendEa2w4Wl9UUXRDSFotZ2RnXzNCdHVVaVNsTXdSY3N0aFVVa3JFU2RkVG9oVHIxUnYzSExqXzEyb25GeWdFS1UzUFVHYnZ6RnVTemg3cjRKS2xfNnBHT1F1cENZTDF6Sld6emdpczRWbDhkVXc</guid></item><item><title>如何在圣诞节前接种流感疫苗-《每日电讯报》</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/conditions/cold-flu/how-get-a-flu-vaccine-before-christmas-jab/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;p&gt;Her message was echoed by Nick Thayer, the head of policy for the Company Chemists Association. He said there is “no national shortage of flu vaccines, but the bulk of them are administered in October and November”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This means that “by the time you get to December, some places are running low, and some will have none left from their original allocation”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may therefore need to shop around for your flu vaccine. “Look on the websites for pharmacies, look on the NHS website, if you are eligible for a free jab or talk to your local pharmacy and ask,” Thayer advises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are unable to get the vaccine before Christmas, stick to the basics to reduce your risk of catching the flu. These include handwashing, avoiding crowded indoor gatherings, staying home when unwell, and self-isolating within families where possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flu jab remains a valuable layer of protection, according to Dr Clarke. It is safe and generally thought to achieve maximum protection for an individual after 10 to 14 days. Whilst there is still a chance you might get the flu after having the jab, it is likely to be milder and not last as long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protection from the flu vaccine goes down over the year and the types of virus it protects against are updated annually, which is why it is important to stay up to date with your inoculations, according to the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whilst this year’s dominant strain is thought to be a mutated version of the influenza A virus, data shows that the flu vaccine still provides good protection against it. The UK Health Security Agency found it has been &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/flu-vaccine-providing-important-protection-despite-new-subclade"&gt;70 to 75 per cent effective at preventing hospital attendance in children aged 2 to 17, and 30 to 40 per cent effective in adults&lt;/a&gt;. This is broadly in line with effectiveness in previous flu seasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost 17 million vaccines have been delivered this autumn, which is 350,000 more compared to this time last year, although Dr Clarke wishes more of us would choose to be inoculated. The latest National Flu and Covid-19 Surveillance Report shows that only 70.9 per cent of over-65s have received their flu jab this season. Rates amongst eligible under-65s are far lower, hovering around 35 per cent. “It really would make a difference,” says Dr Clarke.&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 14:44:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxPNWQ1LWRLd0ExNlM4ZXh6NFhzd01aZUI3S2d3d0gwNXNraC1nNWdUSm9SaHhzeWZMS3pveFNtNzVKUEVTUHk4WHhOTzZYZHdKM1ZNTFdQdGdyOGRlZUszMkRBX21JbTBwZjJEM25XNjd2Ui1QLUZSSFlManRLUmFGWnRYbHJvZjdCcXFWTWd1T0hjZXlqaHdvMlFidXRXWWFDdlpBS0cya3Rwdw</guid></item><item><title>大量研究发现医用大麻患者非常令人担忧的结果-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/huge-study-medical-marijuana</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="article-featured-image-figure"&gt;
			
			
	&lt;p class="article-featured-image-caption-container"&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="article-featured-image-caption"&gt;
			Illustration by Tag Hartman-Simkins / Futurism. Source: Getty Images
 		&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/figure&gt;
	
	
	
	
	
	&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;In a blow to the medical cannabis establishment, a team of psychiatrists performed a detailed analysis on 15 years of cannabis research — and found not only that medical marijuana doesn’t seem to help people with acute pain or insomnia, which proponents often tout, but that almost of third of medical weed users are abusing the drug.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The findings, published in the medical journal &lt;em&gt;JAMA&lt;/em&gt;, will likely further fuel an ongoing debate on &lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2025/01/marijuana-legalization-drawbacks/681519/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;whether the states went too far with legalization&lt;/a&gt;. And it comes at a wild moment: just as &lt;a href="https://www.axios.com/2025/12/12/marijuana-thc-cannabis-laws-state-federal-trump" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;president Donald Trump signaled&lt;/a&gt; this week he’ll loosen federal restrictions on weed.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“While many people turn to cannabis seeking relief, our review highlights significant gaps between public perception and scientific evidence regarding its effectiveness for most medical conditions,” said Michael Hsu, lead author and addiction psychiatrist at the University of California, Los Angeles, in a &lt;a href="https://www.uclahealth.org/news/release/evidence-lacking-medical-cannabis-most-conditions" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; about the study.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Clear guidance from clinicians is essential to support safe, evidence-based decision-making when discussing medical cannabis with their patients,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The team looked over more than 2,500 clinical trials that studied the efficacy of medical marijuana products and also certain cannabinoids, which are isolated cannabis compounds, approved by the Food and Drug Administration for use in “HIV/AIDS-related anorexia, chemotherapy-induced nausea and vomiting, and certain pediatric seizure disorders.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;On the question of pain management, the team found very little sign that cannabis help&lt;strong&gt;s&lt;/strong&gt; with acute pain. They found the same for insomnia, and sleep trials that studied whether cannabis helped with getting a restful night of slumber came up with very little evidence of its effectiveness as well.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Researchers also found that 29 percent of medical marijuana users showed evidence of “cannabis use disorder,” a catch-all term for people who show a problematic usage pattern with the drug.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;But the team did find&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;that FDA-approved cannabinoids had a “small but significant reduction in nausea and vomiting” for people going through chemotherapy for cancer and other situations where people have difficulty keeping food down. They also helped people with AIDS/HIV retain or increase body weight when up against a placebo.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“There are some legitimate purposes for these compounds,” Kevin Hill, one of the study authors and an addiction psychiatrist at Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center in Boston, &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/12/health/medical-cannabis-benefits.html?partner=slack&amp;amp;smid=sl-share" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;told &lt;em&gt;The New York Times&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. “And there’s a whole other group of people who are saying they’re using it medically, but they’re really not. They’re just rationalizing their recreational use.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Related to that point, the team found that high-potency cannabis was associated with increased risk for developing signs of psychosis compared to the low-potency stuff, while smoking weed daily increased the risk for heart complications, such as coronary heart disease, myocardial infarction, and stroke.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;It’s clear that there are people who abuse medical marijuana, judging from the evidence — but something tells us that this study will not stop the growing clout of the cannabis industry, a $32 billion sector and growing.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on cannabis:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/scientists-weed-cognitive-decline"&gt;If You Blazed Massive Amounts of Weed as a Youth, Scientists Have Interesting News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 13:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE9DZHFUQ3JBSEFNQ29TOG5nVlhESlJkamJaMkdqRDhwSjhONnVfRG5IX3RoTTZvXzh5NnpEQlF3bUhXcGpkR3V5SE5Vc2NVM1c5X2NoZ2RxdjFFZGdDY1FZR0tRNHlaX1hlODhGNnB1UEMtc1E</guid></item><item><title>一个女孩在等待名单上一年后说“爸爸，我得到了一颗心”的那一刻-好消息网络</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/the-moment-a-girl-says-daddy-im-getting-a-heart-after-a-year-on-the-waiting-list/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_226782" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-226782" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-226782" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Girl-tells-dad-shes-getting-heart-SWNS.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-226782" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Girl tells her dad she’s getting a new heart – SWNS&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The emotional moment an 11-year-old girl broke the news to her father that she’s getting a heart transplant was captured on video.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Daddy, I’m getting a heart!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ava was born in 2014 with several heart defects, and was just six days old when she had her first open heart surgery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year when she was ten, a sinus infection escalated, pushing her into heart failure—so she was put on the transplant list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ava spent more than 200 days waiting for an organ donor at the Cleveland Clinic Children’s Hospital in Ohio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in March 2025, her mom, Jamie, received the news that Ava would be getting a new heart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ava immediately wanted to call her dad, Sean, who was at home with his younger daughter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_226781" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-226781" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-226781" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Girl-and-mom-in-hospital-vertical-SWNS.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-226781" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Ava with her doctor – Credit: SWNS&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was so excited and couldn’t believe it was actually happening,” Ava recalled later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The heart transplant took place that month, performed by pediatric and congenital heart surgeon Dr. Hani Najm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And, Ava was able to return home after eight months in the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hearing Ava say those words, ‘I’m getting a heart’, was overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“After everything she’d been through, we were finally one step closer to coming home for good.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LOOK&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a title="Infant’s Organ Donation Creates Lifelong Bond for Two Families, Lets Mom Hear her Late Daughter’s Heart" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/infants-organ-donation-creates-lifelong-connection-for-two-families-lets-mom-hear-her-late-daughters-heart/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Infant’s Organ Donation Creates Lifelong Bond for Two Families, Lets Mom Hear her Late Daughter’s Heart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WATCH the heartwarming moment below…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1s4qEY3VzX4?si=pajDAl76zxCj4RTr" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SHARE THE GOOD NEWS With Organ Donors on Social Media…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 13:06:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxPbWdQLVU1TS1SanhrbWtaWHFEbWdwcmNSS2Y5QUtuTHJhNGMxVWZYX3BpXzFDWXBXYlIzQ2hFT21xd1pWbmtzZWtmVmFtakNIbGJJaVhzSGlyaUxrQ1hKc2FWMGZ0XzJYRVZzS1BaZFBZQkJ0STBHOG9xMXVOeEJXcWVtVEh4OGtrTTZaU09EWXNqYW1GZTExVl9ZbFNRWVJBNjVEaHNmdGcwRFRvczAyTWtINA</guid></item><item><title>特朗普吹捧的自闭症药物现在很受欢迎，但医生们看到了一个困境-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/13/trump-leucovorin-autism-treatment/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="43COSOCEHJETBCZHM7YVJLWN3U" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Pediatrician Kristin Sohl has lost count of how many times parents of children with autism have asked her for a &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/09/22/leucovorin-autism-treatment-rfk/"&gt;prescription for leucovorin &lt;/a&gt;— the drug thrust into the spotlight after President Donald Trump touted it at a White House event this fall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 13:01:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxORWJWZUpBaklBWTh1Uk5jZXRWN0RYRkU4LVYtTHdnOHgwMW14YkJwNlIzUy15UFJIbzFCQms2SGk2cEZ4ZlVDQWpTaTlvQlZvQUJDMmw4WlFhelJJUFp5ZUJCR21MZ2NTd1FwSzk0aGY0TmJqeGJXUXhwNV9lb2dXMFN2b1lucHk3eFpV</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr.将疾病预防控制中心变成了“僵尸组织” - thehill.com</title><link>https://thehill.com/opinion/healthcare/5646842-rfk-kennedy-cdc-zombie-organization/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>thehill.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPR1dqQVpXRU9GYUZvT0JLSndGUTNpd2VfWWNxcXJ4eWdsTzNwTUhsNlE1TnE3SDFwdlFzWHJOVDF2ZllBVDNvSFZKcEdnakgxcjQ0Sm00aE9McjdtLWJEeFVtVHhVVGpjS2x5bkRQNGdZSnZ4M2FzMzlvdGlOT3NBbU5uQkxBUWs1VUQ00gGQAUFVX3lxTE81RU9vVnFiNXEyVHl6WWU1akxFYVQtMmxwbWFEOUVPUE9Jd0c5N3pZQlVKVUJ1dGY1Z25ZOHRrakRsdlFXNVpuTFZ2c0VfaUs1YTc1Szczdm16UXlBcjBCSWZGNGVKTGpVTW14b0pQanNRZjE3YWJYTnpoVUF2TUxKRUFnSngtUnR2WHczc0lzRA</guid></item><item><title>加州大学旧金山分校的医生在老年人中看到更多这种慢性病的病例。于是他们开了一家新诊所--《旧金山纪事报》</title><link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/health/aging-longevity/article/bowel-disease-ibd-longevity-clinic-21231425.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>San Francisco Chronicle</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 12:07:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxQRmhwRzdkV1JkTkhZc3JEbmw4ZVZ6dHVFUWIyX3BERGNXVGI5Q1pIaXhVdTNVbk9NQ2NnVDNNdHlVWHZWLTFKSEZ0TWhoVkllaER6OHlNbXBRdHZFbVpfM2VrWEtTVUM5Mkp1dEVPQ0NDMmh3c3BnWkRIN3A5OUo0RlAxa2FVd3NKeVNaNTZzbW9ma3B1bzVYYjNfWS0xMlFxaFgybDZDUG5VZw</guid></item><item><title>带状疱疹疫苗对痴呆症的惊人影响揭示-推出</title><link>https://rollingout.com/2025/12/14/shingles-vaccines-impact-on-dementia/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="elementor-element elementor-element-93bad64 elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-id="93bad64" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="text-editor.default"&gt;
									New research shows the routine shot may reduce Alzheimer’s risk and slow cognitive decline in older adults								&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;div class="elementor-element elementor-element-27a7d87 elementor-widget elementor-widget-theme-post-content" data-id="27a7d87" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="theme-post-content.default"&gt;
					&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;A routine vaccine that millions of older adults receive to prevent painful shingles outbreaks may offer an unexpected bonus: significant protection against dementia. Recent research has uncovered a compelling connection between the shingles vaccine and reduced risk of cognitive decline, with findings suggesting the shot may not only prevent dementia but also slow its progression in people already facing diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;The discovery emerged from a unique natural experiment in Wales that allowed researchers to conduct rigorous analysis typically only possible in randomized clinical trials. The results have captured the attention of geriatric specialists and neurologists who see potential for a readily available intervention that could impact millions of lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 class="font-claude-response-subheading text-text-100 mt-1 -mb-1.5"&gt;How researchers discovered the connection&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;The foundation for these findings came from a shingles vaccine program launched in Wales on September 1, 2013. The program allowed residents aged 79 and older to receive the &lt;a href="https://rollingout.com/2025/12/08/trump-vaccine-childhood-immunization/"&gt;vaccine&lt;/a&gt;, creating distinct groups of vaccine-eligible and vaccine-ineligible individuals based purely on birth date. This setup provided researchers with conditions similar to a randomized trial, where the groups should be essentially identical except for vaccination status.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;Dr. Pascal Geldsetzer, a senior author of the study and assistant professor of medicine at Stanford University, emphasized the significance of this natural experiment. The design allowed researchers to draw meaningful conclusions about cause and effect rather than simply observing correlations that might result from other factors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;A major study published in April 2025 revealed that individuals who received the shingles vaccine experienced a 20 percent reduction in &lt;a href="https://rollingout.com/2025/10/28/trump-mistakes-dementia-screening-for/"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt; risk over a seven-year period. This finding alone would have been noteworthy, but follow-up research published in the journal Cell took the implications even further.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 class="font-claude-response-subheading text-text-100 mt-1 -mb-1.5"&gt;The vaccine may help those already diagnosed&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;The follow-up study analyzed health records to track cognitive decline from earliest signs through late-stage dementia. Researchers discovered that participants who received the shingles vaccine showed lower likelihood of being diagnosed with mild cognitive impairment over the subsequent nine years compared to unvaccinated individuals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;Perhaps even more encouraging, vaccinated people proved significantly less likely to die from dementia after receiving a diagnosis. This suggests the shingles vaccine may play a role in slowing disease progression, offering hope not just for prevention but also for those already facing cognitive challenges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;Geldsetzer noted that the research now provides evidence likely showing a cause-and-effect relationship between shingles vaccination and both dementia prevention and treatment. This distinction between correlation and causation represents a critical advancement in understanding how the vaccine impacts brain health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 class="font-claude-response-subheading text-text-100 mt-1 -mb-1.5"&gt;Why the vaccine might protect the brain&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;Researchers are actively investigating the mechanisms behind these protective effects. Two primary pathways appear most promising based on current understanding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;The shingles virus, known scientifically as varicella-zoster, can cause substantial inflammation in the nervous system when it reactivates decades after initially causing chickenpox. This neuroinflammation is thought to contribute to dementia development. By preventing the virus from reactivating, the vaccine may shield the brain from inflammatory damage that accelerates cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;Additionally, the vaccine may enhance the immune system’s ability to clear abnormal proteins associated with dementia, particularly those linked to Alzheimer’s disease. This immune boost could help the body address one of the fundamental biological processes underlying cognitive deterioration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 class="font-claude-response-subheading text-text-100 mt-1 -mb-1.5"&gt;Medical experts weigh in&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;Geriatric specialists have responded with cautious optimism to these findings. Dr. Zeeshan Khan, chief of geriatrics at Hackensack Meridian Jersey Shore University Medical Center, highlighted the profound impact dementia has on patients and their families. He noted that a routine preventative measure already recommended for shingles could have powerful effects on brain health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;Khan also praised the study’s design, which minimized biases frequently encountered in observational research. The quasi-randomized nature of the Wales program eliminated many confounding factors that typically complicate interpretation of vaccine effectiveness studies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;Neuropsychologist Dr. Raphael Wald described the findings as further confirmation that the shingles vaccine decreases dementia risk. He emphasized the need for additional investigation to determine whether the immunological response serves as the primary factor in risk reduction, which could inform development of new treatments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 class="font-claude-response-subheading text-text-100 mt-1 -mb-1.5"&gt;What this means for older adults&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;The emerging evidence linking the shingles vaccine to lower &lt;a href="https://www.alzheimers.org.uk/about-dementia/managing-the-risk-of-dementia/risk-factors-for-dementia" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;dementia risk&lt;/a&gt; and slower disease progression offers tangible hope for the millions affected by cognitive decline. The findings reinforce the importance of vaccination in older adults while presenting an accessible option for enhancing brain health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;As research continues, scientists may unlock new avenues for dementia prevention and treatment based on understanding how this vaccine protects cognitive function. For now, the message remains clear: a shot already recommended for preventing painful shingles may deliver benefits extending far beyond its original purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="font-claude-response-body break-words whitespace-normal "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; Medical research on shingles vaccine and dementia&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Rolling Out</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 12:03:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTFBCZXlpdEpSUi1HcDlZcFNaNjg1cDBreDdhTkZ1dzJOaHhfdEZIMTA2RTIxUFJjM195SU5heTJ2ZEVqM191VE1VNmh1d2doTWs5bHpMRnFZcGFFSUJxU1l6RjBIQXZCU1dZVFl4UjFrRDhsc05kbXlYc1BHRQ</guid></item><item><title>当医生警告“立即停止”时， “将痴呆和中风风险提高300 ％”的饮料-爱尔兰之星</title><link>https://www.irishstar.com/culture/drink-raises-risk-alzheimers-stroke-36398799</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="article-body" class="ArticleBody_article__AwrJE" data-testid="body"&gt;&lt;h1 class="HeadingOne_heading-one__mmNWJ  __className_1d6fbb"&gt;The drink that 'raises dementia and stroke risk by 300%' as doctor issues warning to ‘stop now’&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 class="LeadText_lead-text__wd_PA __className_2d8d76" data-testid="leadtext"&gt;Dr Clint Steele has issued a stark warning about diet soda drinks, referencing research that links daily consumption to significantly increased risks of stroke and dementia&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="Byline_byline-container__K_Owl" data-testid="byline"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-content" class="Byline_byline-content-wrapper__Imque"&gt;&lt;div class="Byline_author-badge-date-wrapper__Q7jj1"&gt;&lt;div class="Byline_author-and-badge-wrapper__2dsv1"&gt;&lt;p class="Authors_authors-container__wVWas" data-tmdatatrack="author" data-testid="byline-author"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35 __className_fdd245"&gt;Neil Shaw&lt;/strong&gt; Assistant Editor (Money and Lifestyle)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;, &lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35 __className_2d8d76"&gt;Ruairi Byrne&lt;/strong&gt; Deputy editor&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35 __className_f59809"&gt;Myriam Toua&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="Byline_dates-container__Rqzf2"&gt;&lt;span class="" data-testid="byline-publishedDate"&gt;06:41 ET, 14 Dec 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="Byline_updated-date__8vEV8 Byline_updated-date-with-published__ApG_G" data-testid="byline-updatedDate"&gt;Updated 06:54 ET, 14 Dec 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="SlideViewerButton_slide-viewer-button__BDJoG" aria-label="Open image viewer" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-controls="image-lightbox"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX ImageEmbed_image-lead__Ti3qQ" data-testid="leadimage" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="36398798"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Diet sodas can increase the risk of strokes and Alzheimer's&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: Getty)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;A leading doctor has issued a stark warning about a widely consumed beverage that could dramatically heighten your risk of dementia. Dr Clint Steele cautions that diet soda increases the likelihood of stroke by 300% and dementia by 290%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;The 56 year old &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.irishstar.com/all-about/health" target="_self" aria-label="" rel="follow" tabindex="0"&gt;specialist in brain and nervous system health,&lt;/a&gt; whose practice centers on optimizing cognitive function and preventing or &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.irishstar.com/culture/blood-test-dementia-alzheimers-disease-36363081" target="_self" aria-label="" rel="follow" tabindex="0"&gt;potentially reversing dementia and Alzheimer's disease, has highlighted research that's garnered&lt;/a&gt; more than two million views on social media. He points to extensive studies linking daily intake of the drink to serious health risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;His advice is simple – &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.irishstar.com/news/us-news/alzheimers-early-symptom-can-spotted-35166695" target="_self" aria-label="" rel="follow" tabindex="0"&gt;make the switch to water or tea before it's too late&lt;/a&gt;. "There have been numerous studies to prove that this type of drink can be damaging to your brain and also to your body," said Dr Steele, reports &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.irishmirror.ie/news/world-news/neurologist-issues-warning-over-popular-36395889" target="_self" aria-label="" rel="follow" tabindex="0"&gt;the Irish Mirror&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span data-testid="readmore" class="ReadMore_readmore-prefix__xS44r __className_2d8d76"&gt;READ MORE: &lt;span class="ReadMore_readmore-link__eF9pN"&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.irishstar.com/news/world-news/alzheimers-blood-test-trial-news-35878828" data-tmdatatrack="read-more" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="35878828" data-tmdatatrack-source="editorial" tabindex="0"&gt;Major Alzheimer's diagnosis breakthrough as new blood test to be trialled&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="readmore" class="ReadMore_readmore-prefix__xS44r __className_2d8d76"&gt;READ MORE: &lt;span class="ReadMore_readmore-link__eF9pN"&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.irishstar.com/news/us-news/one-alzheimer-warning-sign-your-35578668" data-tmdatatrack="read-more" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="35578668" data-tmdatatrack-source="editorial" tabindex="0"&gt;One Alzheimer warning sign your body might be giving you&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"Specifically, your cardiovascular system. But this specific study was very interesting because what they did was that they tracked people's eating and drinking habits over the course of seven years."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image-group"&gt;&lt;button class="SlideViewerButton_slide-viewer-button__BDJoG" aria-label="Open image viewer" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-controls="image-lightbox"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX false" data-testid="imageembed-36398797" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="36398797" data-tmdatatrack-type="image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Dr Clint Steele says even one a day will damage your health and you should swap it for something else&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;He added: "And then what they did was they tracked them 10 years after that - to see who developed stroke and dementia symptoms. They found the people who drink diet soda on a daily basis, at least one a day, had an increased risk of stroke by 300%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BoxStyles_box-container__Qk3WH BoxStyles_non-commercial__aiWwo undefined" data-testid="non-commercial-1" data-position="6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"And an increased risk of dementia by 290%. These are chemicals that are damaging your body and brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"Instead, replace it with good stuff like water and tea. You don't need these sugary drinks. Soda is just as damaging, but what we're seeing in the research is that diet soda and these chemicals that are used for sweeteners are more damaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"Even if you drink it multiple times per week, it's still damaging. Give it up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Dr Steele has spent 34 years focusing on brain health and preventing dementia, driven by a deeply personal tragedy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image-group"&gt;&lt;button class="SlideViewerButton_slide-viewer-button__BDJoG" aria-label="Open image viewer" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-controls="image-lightbox"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX false" data-testid="imageembed-36398806" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="36398806" data-tmdatatrack-type="image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;People are urged to swap out diet soda drinks for water or tea&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;He shared: "My grandmother passed from dementia, and it is one of the saddest things I've ever seen, her not knowing me or even my mum, her daughter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"She was in a care facility, and they would show her flash cards of various fruits and animals - she would have no idea what they were. Even though she did not know who I was, she would whisper in my ear, 'Please, help get me out of here. I just want to go fishing'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"It broke my heart, and I knew I needed to do something so others did not have to go through this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;The physician delivered his sobering message in a video captioned: "Drinking this regularly increases your risk of stroke by 300% and dementia by 290%."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;For all the latest news straight to your inbox, sign up for our FREE newsletters &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.irishstar.com/newsletter-preference-centre/?utm_source=newslettersignupfooter" target="_blank" aria-label="[object Object]Link opens in a new tab." rel="follow" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;&lt;u&gt;here&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;The disclosure shocked numerous viewers. One commenter, Billy, admitted: "I'm on way out then as I drink a minimum of 10 cans of Diet Coke per day everyday."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Another user, Caz, responded: "No diet drinks and artificial sweeteners in my house ever, real butter and real milk nothing artificial it's bad for you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BoxStyles_box-container__Qk3WH BoxStyles_commercial__Wo6Z4 undefined" data-testid="commercial-8" data-position="10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Missy shared: "Husband has had diet sodas daily for many years. He was just diagnosed with dementia."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Jenny responded: "At least it wasn't coffee! I'm good I hate diet soda."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Pam observed: "I'm the weirdo that only likes water and sparkling water, can't stand syrupy flavoured soda and diet soda in particular."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;However, the doctor's claims didn't convince everyone. Ette pushed back: "My mother had dementia and barely ever drink pop at all, so there's that so."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Brix noted: "My dad has dementia and never drank a diet drink in his life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Another commenter offered: "My grandmother lived to be 94. Drank Diet Coke everyday and never had any health problems."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;A different user challenged: "So why is my 92 year old mother in law still kicking it? All I have ever seen her drink for the last 40 years is Diet soda!".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;For the latest local news and features on Irish America, visit our homepage&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.irishstar.com/" target="_blank" aria-label="[object Object][object Object]Link opens in a new tab." rel="follow" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Irish Star</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 11:54:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxOejVBNmVpVC02dmZHekVGYUZMU3B3dEpXa2FROE04TFNuSENDc0VrQmVJd2RZcVo5TENMSU5rVzlQX0wtUHFTeVdWUnpuZk1fcm9PM04wVmpzMVNZalBYT2htbnlCa05CZXNnS3ZEdkotTHJpbTNzUjlJZ2R1cTRuekRfajQ</guid></item><item><title>改善性健康的3种科学支持的食物-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/3-science-backed-foods-to-improve-sexual-health-and-libido/articleshow/125960439.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s be honest: passion has left the chat long before many of us realised. Busy schedules, constant stress and chaotic personal lives have somewhat become the norm. In between demanding jobs, family responsibilities and poor lifestyle choices, health takes a back seat. This includes &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/topic/sex" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;sex&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;ual health; however, it is one area that is constantly overlooked. Most of us are running on fumes by the time we make it to bed, and libidos become collateral damage. While several factors contribute to this, eating the right foods can enhance your sex life. Here are three science-backed foods that may act as aphrodisiacs. Take a look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Oysters&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Oysters are more than a delicacy. They have long been considered an aphrodisiac. This seafood is rich in zinc, a compound linked to increased blood flow. Zinc can regulate testosterone levels and also improve male fertility. A 2018 review found that &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30009140/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;zinc deficiency can affect testosterone levels.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; Interestingly, oysters contain more zinc than other foods. In fact, one serving alone provides &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="http://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Zinc-HealthProfessional/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;291% of your recommended daily value of zinc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Berries&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Most of us know that berries are superfoods, but did you know that they can enhance your sexual health? A 2016 study from the University of East Anglia (UEA) and Harvard University, published in The American Journal of Clinical Nutrition, found that &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0002916523121575?via%3Dihub" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;berries are linked to reduced erectile dysfunction&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. The researchers found that eating foods rich in certain flavonoids is associated with a reduced risk of erectile dysfunction in men, with the greatest benefit seen in those under 70. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The anthocyanins found in blueberries, cherries, blackberries, radishes and blackcurrants offered the greatest benefits, even in preventing the condition. The researchers also found that a higher total fruit intake was associated with a 14% reduction in the risk of erectile dysfunction. When flavonoid-rich foods are combined with exercise, the risk is reduced by 21%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Nuts&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Go nuts, quite literally. Nuts can help improve sexual function. Eat your walnuts, almonds and hazelnuts. A 2019 study from Universitat Rovira i Virgili, published in the journal Nutrients, found that consuming &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/11/6/1372" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;60 grams of nuts a day improves sexual function&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. Yes, that’s right. The researchers found that adding walnuts, hazelnuts and almonds to your diet can improve sexual desire and orgasm quality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; These foods are not miracle cures, but adding them to your diet may help. To get things going, it is also important to address the risk factors for sexual and erectile dysfunction, such as smoking, excessive alcohol consumption, a lack of physical exercise, stress and an unhealthy diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment, or before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7wFBVV95cUxOSkRyaTk5U0VLSXZkMkNTejBGTGlpZ0VkSjN6MW5FYW5NNDFKa1QtX2tvbGhtNXJ6RnNJRzRjaUlxUkdUUjdJRE5VU1RzUU1XTnE4c2NFb0lFc3FFU1hWWU5wUS1qWTRjVTBodmlSVUI4TGwzMk1oRzFLNERHZWdoM1ZfQ3Bwamp1Vk5vWkw1eUNCMkswdjcxSHhKQjAtYmpjbEFtZ2Q4clVQQkVFYXNSazVTSlEzWlJFT1dEYzkwUk5RcXFTbU5hOUlDV2JxRV9NZGVqb1h2dzdkVWRnUVZnTlkzMkZqVnZRM1JyTEdnYw</guid></item><item><title>我写的是超加工食品，但我仍然无法告诉你如何避免它们。原因如下- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/14/health/ultraprocessed-food-definition-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1l1t79002r26p416cd6w86@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As I push my cart into my favorite grocery store, I stop and look at the shoppers — my neighbors — around me. Do they realize that nearly &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/news-events/press-announcements/hhs-fda-and-usda-address-health-risks-ultra-processed-foods" target="_blank"&gt;70% of the food&lt;/a&gt; available to purchase for their families is &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/02/28/health/ultraprocessed-food-health-risks-study-wellness"&gt;ultraprocessed&lt;/a&gt;? And if they did, would they know how to avoid those foods?
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000k3b6nxmpsncs5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            I’ve been trying to answer that question for more than two years now, as part of my beat for the CNN Wellness team. Not only does my team report on the latest lifestyle news, we also provide expert-vetted guidance on how to improve your health —  we like to say it’s “news you can use.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000l3b6nox73futj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Yet after reading countless studies, talking to dozens of experts and exploring all sorts of trendy apps, I still can’t help you &lt;em&gt;reliably&lt;/em&gt; avoid ultraprocessed foods, also known as UPFs.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000m3b6n5fwlwser@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Come with me to the snack aisle, and I’ll explain why.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000n3b6nhcwyhjsd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As I pass by all the colorfully packaged candies, cookies and chips, my stomach starts to rumble with anticipation. Typically made of refined grains and overflowing with sugar, salt and fat, these products — which we used to call “junk foods” — are calorie-laden, nutritionally bad for us, and deliciously addictive.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000o3b6ndbetrfr8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The appeal of junk food hasn’t changed — in fact, experts say it’s only gotten worse as the food industry &lt;a href="https://stateofchildhoodobesity.org/sugary-drinks-and-tobacco-different-industries-same-playbook/#:~:text=According%20to%20Kelly%20Brownell%2C%20PhD%2C%20and%20Matthew,tobacco%20and%20food%20industries%20have%20decades%2Dlong%20connections." target="_blank"&gt;refined its algorithms&lt;/a&gt; to target our “&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2019/03/19/health/bliss-point-addictive-food"&gt;bliss point”&lt;/a&gt; — creating the absolute &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6550161/" target="_blank"&gt;yummiest combinations&lt;/a&gt; of sugar, salt and fat to make it nearly impossible to “eat just one.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000p3b6nyhlsw0xq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Today,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;many of those same junk foods — as well as the majority of other ultraprocessed foods such as ready-to-eat meals, processed meats, instant and boxed mixes, breakfast cereals, and more — contain newly created synthetic favors, textures, dyes and preservatives.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000q3b6n7p1c5xnf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In fact, today’s preservatives can keep foods looking fresh and tasty for days and weeks, even years — much longer shelf lives than in your great granny’s day.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000r3b6n0uuqis7u@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There’s no doubt that the safety and convenience of such long-lasting, affordable foods has been life-changing. Today, we can make meals from our cabinets without stopping by the store for fresh ingredients or stirring sauce for hours over the stove. We have more of our precious time to spend on other pursuits.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000s3b6nh4ztevfm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Yet it’s those preservatives and other additives, however, that can make a food ultraprocessed, according to the food classification system &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10261019/" target="_blank"&gt;NOVA,&lt;/a&gt; the most widely used definition of UPFs to date.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000t3b6nsa4ljt63@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            NOVA was &lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/public-health-nutrition/article/nutrition-and-health-the-issue-is-not-food-nor-nutrients-so-muchas-processing/0C514FC9DB264538F83D5D34A81BB10A" target="_blank"&gt;created in 2009&lt;/a&gt; by Brazilian nutritionist Carlos Augusto Monteiro,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;who coined the term “ultraprocessed.” Monteiro is an emeritus professor of nutrition and public health in the School of Public Health at Brazil’s University of São Paulo.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000u3b6nzwm5vwr7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            NOVA splits food into four categories. First are  &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/04/health/weight-loss-ultraprocessed-food-wellness"&gt;minimally processed&lt;/a&gt; foods — whole foods which we may slightly “process” by cutting (slicing up an orange or apple) and cooking (sautéing vegetables). The second group includes processed culinary items used to prepare, season and cook whole foods — think spices, herbs and oils. Group three consists of processed foods that combine groups one and two — canned or bottled veggies and fruits, salted nuts, and unpackaged, freshly baked breads are examples.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000v3b6n3uo2dcp1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Group four are ultraprocessed foods — which now make up to 53% of an American adult’s diet and 62% of foods eaten by an American child, according to &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/07/health/ultraprocessed-food-calories-average-diet-wellness"&gt;a recent report&lt;/a&gt; by the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000w3b6nrtd92o9y@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            According to Monteiro, the products in group four contain little to no whole food. Instead, they are manufactured from “chemically manipulated &lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/384/bmj.q439" target="_blank"&gt;cheap ingredients&lt;/a&gt;” and often use synthetic additives to make them “edible, palatable and habit-forming.”
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000x3b6ngzi7wfre@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Additives often used in ultraprocessed foods include preservatives to resist mold and bacteria; emulsifiers to keep incompatible ingredients from separating; &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/01/17/health/red-40-food-dyes-wellness"&gt;artificial colorings&lt;/a&gt;; fragrance and flavor enhancers; and anti-foaming, bulking, bleaching, gelling and glazing agents.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000y3b6n26gf0jtk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “No reason exists to believe that humans can fully adapt to these products,” Monteiro  cowrote in a &lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/384/bmj.q439" target="_blank"&gt;2024 editorial in the journal The BMJ&lt;/a&gt;. “The body may react to them as useless or harmful, so its systems may become impaired or damaged, depending on their vulnerability and the amount of ultra-processed food consumed.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde000z3b6na9kq87tw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The stakes are high: &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/04/28/health/ultraprocessed-food-death-wellness"&gt;Studies&lt;/a&gt; have shown that eating just 10% more calories a day from &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/11/22/health/ultraprocessed-food-cancer-wellness/index.html"&gt;ultraprocessed food&lt;/a&gt; — that’s about one serving — may be associated with a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/02/28/health/ultraprocessed-food-health-risks-study-wellness/index.html"&gt;50% higher risk&lt;/a&gt; of cardiovascular disease-related death. There is also a 55% greater chance of obesity and a 40% higher probability of developing type 2 diabetes. The risk of &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/05/22/health/ultraprocessed-food-stroke-cognitive-decline-wellness/index.html"&gt;cognitive decline and stroke&lt;/a&gt; also rises, as does the chance of &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/11/22/health/ultraprocessed-food-cancer-wellness/index.html"&gt;developing cancers&lt;/a&gt; of the upper digestive tract.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00103b6n7qad1tso@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            However, the Consumer Brands Association, which represents major food manufacturers, told me in an email “there is currently no agreed upon scientific definition of ultra-processed foods.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00113b6nsomxpp2h@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Attempting to classify foods as unhealthy simply because they are processed, or demonizing food by ignoring its full nutrient content, misleads consumers and exacerbates health disparities,” said Sarah Gallo, CBA’s senior vice president of product policy. “Americans deserve facts based on sound science in order to make the best choices for their health.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00123b6n4nyo6y4r@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In addition, she said, food and beverage manufacturers have long invested in product labeling, “so that consumers can review product ingredients and nutrition information and make decisions best for them.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00133b6njujkc39t@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            To manufacture cheap, delicious food that is packaged for convenience, experts say basic food crops such as potatoes, corn, wheat and soybeans may be disassembled into their molecular parts — starchy flours, protein isolates, fats and oils — to create what manufacturers call “slurries.” (How do they do it?  &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BsKsrCGfxLY" target="_blank"&gt;Watch this video.&lt;/a&gt;)
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00143b6nbub2x0tb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The cell&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;walls of the plants are destroyed, dispersing micronutrients that often need to work together to nurture our bodies. Insoluble &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/10/health/high-fiber-diet-weight-loss-mortality-study-intl"&gt;plant fiber&lt;/a&gt; we need to be healthy may also &lt;a href="https://www.cspi.org/article/high-fiber-foods-ultra-processed-pretenders-what-know" target="_blank"&gt;be lost&lt;/a&gt;. What’s left is a substance some scientists call “&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/02/01/health/predigested-food-wellness"&gt;predigested&lt;/a&gt;” — not unlike the regurgitated food a mama bird feeds her babies.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00153b6nzr7utecv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Barry Popkin, the W.R. Kenan Jr. Distinguished Professor at the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill’s Gillings School of Global Public Health, has seen the process firsthand.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00163b6nt3px83m2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “In the early 2000s, I went into some food plants and I saw the stuff — it was supposed to be granola bars, shredded wheat cereal,” Popkin said. “It was colorless, odorless. I scooped some up in a spoon and tried to taste it — it was like sawdust or something.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00173b6n4q1rdmkd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Here’s why eating “predigested” food can be a problem: When we eat whole foods as our bodies are meant to do, we absorb micronutrients throughout the entire digestive process. If they are exploded into smithereens in an ultraprocessed food, do we still have access to them? If we do, are they absorbed by the body in the ways nature meant them to be?
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00183b6n3tsoljqg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            I’m not aware of any studies that answer that question, although research is underway. But according to some food scientists I’ve spoken to, it doesn’t matter — manufacturers just add back missing vitamins, fiber and protein during manufacturing and voilà! It’s as good as new.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00193b6nleu4wng0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Or is it? Is a patched-up Humpty Dumpty really the same Dumpty that fell off the wall?
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001a3b6nyn1c2bhr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Let’s get back to the slurries: Next, with the help of artificial colorings, flavorings, texturizers and glue-like emulsifiers, ingredients are mixed, heated, pounded, shaped or extruded into any food a manufacturer can dream up.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001b3b6njp8au3qt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It’s an illusion of food,” Dr. Chris van Tulleken told me &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/02/01/health/predigested-food-wellness"&gt;last year.&lt;/a&gt;  He is a BBC contributor and professor of infection and global health at University College London.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001c3b6n7n0sshmb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It’s really expensive and difficult for a food company to make food that is real and whole, and much cheaper for food companies to destroy real foods, turn them into molecules, and then reassemble those to make anything they want,” said van Tulleken, author of the 2023 book “&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Ultra-Processed-People-Cant-Stop-Eating/dp/1324076267" target="_blank"&gt;Ultra-Processed People&lt;/a&gt;: Why Do We All Eat Stuff That Isn’t Food … and Why Can’t We Stop?”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001d3b6nbb42n16l@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            I’m still wandering around the snack aisle, so let’s put our knowledge to the test by looking at one of my kids’ old favorites — ranch-flavored veggie straws. As a conscientious mom, I always reached for the organic version.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001e3b6ny3pe1vsh@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Of the more than 30 ingredients, three are additives: sodium caseinate, used as an emulsifier; calcium chloride, which extends shelf life; and potassium chloride, a flavor enhancer used to treat low blood pressure and low potassium levels.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001f3b6n28jra10y@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            All are designated GRAS (&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/10/03/health/food-supply-safety-loopholes-wellness"&gt;generally regarded as safe&lt;/a&gt;) for use in food by the US Food and Drug Administration. Yet by NOVA’s standards, those veggie straws are definitely ultraprocessed.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001g3b6njp87d70s@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Let’s look at the nutrition label. The top ingredient is potato starch, followed by potato powder. Then come various oils, dehydrated vegetable powders (such as bell peppers, carrots, spinach), turmeric and beetroot powders (for color), and dried milk products (for the ranch taste). There are some vitamins and minerals. Oh, and salt and sugar, of course.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001h3b6n6rtu9zzv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            None of that sounds dangerous, but all those powders? That’s a red flag that these kid-friendly straws may not have been made from my “Mom” vision of sautéed veggies pureed in a blender, poured into a mold and baked until puffy. Instead, it’s possible they were created from a potato-based sludge, colored and flavored with vegetable powders, and enriched with vitamins before being squeezed through a tube and baked.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001i3b6ni71kk8i7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            That’s something scientists can’t determine. In fact, none of us can, because how these foods are made is proprietary to each manufacturer, which closely guards recipes and “bliss point” algorithms from competitors and the public.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001j3b6ngw2fnsb4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            I tried to obtain access to a major food company’s production site on several occasions to understand how potato chips and other foods are made. Six months later, I gave up.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001k3b6ns8ged0rc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Food companies today, they’ve closed off their processing plants,” Popkin said. “So we’ve never been able to have a clinical study studying what happens if you eat real corn versus deconstructed corn.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001l3b6n5n36zzj7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But wait — I buy organic versions of the veggie straws, doesn’t that help? Unfortunately, no. Buying organic does reduce pesticide levels, but that’s not part of ultraprocessing. Turning even an organic vegetable into refined flakes and powders may destroy the plant’s food matrix — cell walls that hold nutrients — and like our Humpty Dumpty, that food must be put back together again.
    &lt;/p&gt;



  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001m3b6nbjbp60vq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Many experts have tried to simplify the chore of avoiding ultraprocessing by advising consumers to choose foods with no more than five ingredients or avoid foods with ingredients you can’t pronounce or can’t find at home.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001n3b6n2tgqodqq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Those are great suggestions if you have time to read labels. It’s also not a complete solution. Let’s look at my favorite potato chip, which only has three ingredients on the label: potatoes, salt and oil. Does that mean this potato chip is now good for me? Or is it still a junk food even though it isn’t ultraprocessed by the NOVA definition?
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001o3b6nikvrvi5a@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Those convenient, kid-friendly frozen chicken nuggets are easy to identify as ultraprocessed. And here’s a startling fact: Nuggets typically contain &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8537092/" target="_blank"&gt;transglutaminase,&lt;/a&gt; which the industry calls “meat glue.” It’s an enzyme that helps combine parts of an animal or different animals into one product — hot dogs, sausages and deli meats are common examples. (Hint: If the food packaging reads “formed” or “reformed,” it likely contains transglutaminase.)
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001p3b6nzqngyr8e@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Transglutaminase isn’t easy to pronounce, and it’s not an ingredient you’ll have at home. Yet the &lt;a href="https://ific.org/resources/articles/what-is-transglutaminase/" target="_blank"&gt;FDA&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://ask.usda.gov/s/article/Is-Transglutaminase-Enzyme-TG-Enzyme-Safe#:~:text=Yes%2C%20Transglutaminase%20Enzyme%20(TG%20enzyme,products%20for%20over%2010%20years." target="_blank"&gt;US Department of Agriculture&lt;/a&gt; have no problem with it because it dissipates when cooked.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001q3b6nhntxbie0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            This next challenge is harder: Are most breads on grocery store shelves ultraprocessed by NOVA standards? Unless it’s freshly baked from scratch, the answer is “most likely,” although experts disagree.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001r3b6njw5rlwzm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            From the NOVA perspective, if a bread lasts longer than a week or so without mold, it may have a synthetic preservative in it. Common additives in bread include calcium propionate, an artificial preservative linked to &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/12173999/" target="_blank"&gt;behavior problems in children&lt;/a&gt;;  &lt;a href="https://www.foodchemadditives.com/side_effects_info/781#:~:text=General%20Side%20Effects,review%20it%20and%20respond%20soon." target="_blank"&gt;potassium sorbate&lt;/a&gt;, another synthetic preservative linked to skin and respiratory issues in people who are sensitive to it; and BHA (butylated hydroxyanisole) and BHT (butylated hydroxytoluene), two more artificial preservatives that &lt;a href="https://www.ewg.org/news-insights/news/2025/04/despite-health-harm-concerns-bha-and-bht-remain-food-and-cosmetics" target="_blank"&gt;may be linked&lt;/a&gt; to hormone and reproductive disruption and cancer.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001s3b6nlpm4fhbv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But what if the bread is made with whole wheat or whole grains you can actually see and taste? It may still be ultraprocessed, but isn’t it better for you? That is still a fiercely debated question.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001t3b6n0sps4a7u@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Now, here’s a tricky one: plant-based meat substitutes. Ultraprocessed to their core, many experts say these alt meats are still better for us than red and processed meats full of saturated fats or nitrates.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001u3b6ntpuo6uzk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The fat composition of beef is so undesirable for health that it’s very easy to be better than that,” leading nutrition researcher Dr. Walter Willett told me &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/21/health/plant-based-meat-benefits-wellness"&gt;earlier this year.&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001v3b6naa4ks2q8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Animal products not only have too much saturated fat but lack polyunsaturated fat, fiber and many of the minerals and vitamins available in plants,” said Willett, professor of epidemiology and nutrition at Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health and professor of medicine at Harvard Medical School in Boston.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001w3b6nnu98pqg0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Many of the alt-meat products have dramatically improved their nutritional profiles since they first hit the market. Recent studies &lt;a href="https://gfieurope.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Guide_-Where-does-plant-based-meat-fit-in-the-UPF-conversation_19-May.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;analyzed&lt;/a&gt; by the Physicians Association for Nutrition, or PAN International, found plant-based meats were dramatically lower in saturated fat, a little lower in overall calories, equal in protein, dramatically higher in fiber (beef has no fiber), and a bit higher in salt and sugar than conventional meat.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001x3b6n1vb8dx5n@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There’s also the role of plant-based meat in saving the planet. According to the &lt;a href="https://gfi.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Good Food Institute&lt;/a&gt;, which &lt;a href="https://gfi.org/resource/environmental-impacts-of-alternative-proteins/" target="_blank"&gt;promotes alternative proteins&lt;/a&gt; and coauthored the report, replacing a beef burger with a plant-based patty can reduce greenhouse gas emissions by up to 98%&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;and land use by up to 97%.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001y3b6ng9goqqba@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            I could go on and on, but here’s the bottom line: Deciding what is “ultraprocessed and bad for your health” and “ultraprocessed, but OK to eat” is really complicated — especially for a society unwilling or unable to give up inexpensive, convenient food.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subheader inline-placeholder subheader-elevate vossi-subheader_elevate vossi-subheader_elevate--size-h2" data-editable="text" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/subheader/instances/cmj1llnjb00373b6nv990gvau@published" data-component-name="subheader" id="a-lot-of-huffing-and-puffing-going-on" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
        A lot of huffing and puffing going on…
&lt;/h2&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde001z3b6nqktiftvo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Fortunately, the world is taking action. In mid-May, the World Health Organization put out a &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/articles-detail/call-for-experts-to-develop-a-who-guideline-on-consumption-of-ultra-processed-foods" target="_blank"&gt;global clarion call&lt;/a&gt; for scientists to help define and create guidelines for ultraprocessed food consumption. Once the panel is chosen, the work is expected to take two years.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00203b6n34x02gt9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A week later, the Trump Administration released its first “Make America Healthy Again” report, calling for action on &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/05/22/politics/maha-rfk-report-medicines-processed-foods-pesticides#:~:text=The%20report%20states%20that%20children,Kennedy%20told%20reporters%20on%20Thursday"&gt;ultraprocessed foods&lt;/a&gt; they say are a danger to our children’s health&lt;strong&gt;. &lt;/strong&gt;An August 15 &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/15/health/maha-report-draft-pesticide-ultraprocessed-food"&gt;leaked version&lt;/a&gt; of the second report — which was supposed to announce specific policy actions — instead called for the government to “continue efforts to develop a U.S. government-wide definition.” The final report, &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/maha-commission-report-childhood-disease-strategy.html" target="_blank"&gt;released in September,&lt;/a&gt; provided no additional action.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00213b6nk5k303vo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Unfortunately, the final MAHA report is all promises and has no teeth,” University of Carolina’s Popkin &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/10/health/maha-report-children-health-response-wellness"&gt;told me at the time&lt;/a&gt;. “In my opinion, it shows the food, agricultural, and pharmaceutical industries got to the White House and won the day.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00223b6nxphulf9y@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Andrew Nixon, deputy assistant secretary for media relations at the US Department of Health and Human Services, told me in an&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;email the administration is confronting the UPF challenge, which is a “major driver of the nation’s chronic disease epidemic.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00233b6n76o0g9we@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Replacing them with real, whole foods is one of the most effective ways to Make America Healthy Again,” Nixon said. “We remain committed to serving the American people, not special interests or outside critics, by delivering radical transparency and upholding gold-standard science.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00243b6njra0ps5f@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Other groups have stepped into the void. The American Heart Association, for example, divided ultraprocessed food into &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/CIR.0000000000001365" target="_blank"&gt;three categories&lt;/a&gt; — least healthy, moderately healthy and healthy.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00253b6nkypfpr5w@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Understandably, the AHA is most concerned with how foods impact the heart. High-fat red and processed meats fall within the “least healthy” category in the AHA report — as they should, considering their role in heart disease and colon cancer. However, red meat is also the &lt;em&gt;least &lt;/em&gt;processed food in that category.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00263b6nbxck5sk5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            And yet, that’s the point: Regulating ultraprocessed foods by additives alone — without also addressing the health concerns of too much sugar, salt and saturated fat (hello, &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/03/25/health/beef-tallow-healthy-seed-oils-rfk-wellness"&gt;beef tallow&lt;/a&gt;!) — won’t improve the nation’s food supply and our deteriorating health.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00273b6nbt273vwu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In an effort to fix that, Monteiro is campaigning for researchers and government officials to add more ingredients to the NOVA definition often used in creating food policy.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00283b6n9f4i7pxj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Our proposal now is to target any food with an excess of sodium, saturated fat or sugar, along with synthetic colors, flavors and non-nutritive sweeteners,” Monteiro told me when I reported on a recent &lt;a href="http://www.thelancet.com/series-do/ultra-processed-food" target="_blank"&gt;three-part series&lt;/a&gt; in the journal The Lancet. He and Popkin coauthored the articles with 41 other internationally known scientists.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00293b6nieju32em@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            However, there is a missing element, according to Harvard’s Willett: “The huge blind spot of refined grains, which is the largest source of calories in the US and most countries at this time — this is not considered to be an UPF.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002a3b6non1c1zpt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The Lancet series blasted the food industry, claiming global corporations continued to aggressively market and extensively profit from new and existing UPF products despite increasing evidence of harm to public health.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002b3b6n5tey3pfn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The food industry doesn’t want to lose their cash cow, so they’re willing to put millions into fighting government restrictions on ultraprocessed food as well as funding nutritionists who’ll say there’s no evidence of harm,” Popkin said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002c3b6noxi9dtdn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The International Food &amp;amp; Beverage Alliance, founded in 2008 by leading food and nonalcoholic beverage companies, told me in an email when the Lancet series published that health authorities worldwide have rejected the concept of ultraprocessed food due to its lack of scientific consensus.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002d3b6nm2z8rndk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The policy and advocacy recommendations of this series go far beyond the available evidence — proposing new regulatory action based on ‘processing’ or additive ‘markers’ and calling for the exclusion of industry from policymaking,” said IFBA Secretary-General Rocco Renaldi.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002e3b6nmdm6mfmt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            California made history in early October by enacting the &lt;a href="https://legiscan.com/CA/text/AB1264/id/3248161" target="_blank"&gt;first law in the United States&lt;/a&gt; to define and ultimately ban problematic ultraprocessed foods in public schools.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002f3b6nloi6vmlf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Not only does the California legislation define ultraprocessed food — not an easy task as you have seen — it requires public health officials and scientists to decide which UPFs are most harmful to human health. An “ultraprocessed food of concern” would then be phased out of the school food supply. That’s impressive, considering California is projected to serve &lt;a href="https://a46.asmdc.org/press-releases/20250603-california-advances-first-nation-legislation-phase-out-harmful-ultra" target="_blank"&gt;over 1 billion meals&lt;/a&gt; to schoolchildren in the 2025–26 school year.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002g3b6nkpnqn2tf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/10/09/health/california-governor-bans-red-dye-no-3-wellness/index.html"&gt;California&lt;/a&gt; has also led the way in laws banning &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/06/26/health/food-dyes-maha-ultraprocessed-foods-wellness"&gt;food dyes&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://nj.gov/health/eoh/rtkweb/documents/fs/1559.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;potassium bromate&lt;/a&gt;, a possible carcinogen once widely used in breads, &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/11/10/health/food-additives-dye-brominated-vegetable-oil-wellness/index.html"&gt;brominated vegetable oil&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://efsa.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/epdf/10.2903/j.efsa.2004.83" target="_blank"&gt;propylparaben&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002h3b6nxnrl4lqp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Here in California, we are actually doing the work to protect our kids’ health, and we’ve been doing it since well before anyone had ever heard of the MAHA movement,” said Jesse Gabriel, the Democratic California Assemblymember who introduced several of the bills, in an October 9 press conference.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002i3b6nhobwcthy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            What’s so promising about the legislation is the scope of the effort. California lawmakers have considered many of the ways in which both junk and ultraprocessed foods may be harmful to human health — ingredients such as nonnutritive sweeteners; additives such as emulsifiers, stabilizers and thickeners; flavor enhancers; a host of &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/01/17/health/red-40-food-dyes-wellness"&gt;food dyes&lt;/a&gt; and more.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002j3b6noq80rasu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            American scientific research on the harms of UPF additives is in its infancy, but the new law has taken that into account. Additives banned, restricted or required to carry a warning by other local, state, federal or international jurisdictions will be in the analysis. That’s key, as the European Union and other countries have already regulated many additives still allowed in the US.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002k3b6nej52qhrp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Food modified to contain high amounts of saturated fat, sodium and added sugar can also be rejected, according to the law. This will help target industry strategies that may contribute to &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/06/27/health/child-addiction-ultraprocessed-foods-wellness"&gt;an addiction to ultraprocessed foods&lt;/a&gt; — an increasing concern for American children &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/08/health/ultraprocessed-food-ban-california-wellness"&gt;raised on UPFs&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002l3b6nvciqv3hs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The downside? The law won’t provide final details on which UPFs are most concerning until June 2028, and it won’t have all UPFs out of school lunches until 2035. I’m hopeful there will be useful updates as the process rolls along.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002m3b6ngkrhfqwx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            While we wait for definitive action (don’t hold your breath), we still have to navigate the grocery store. Of course, the best way is to buy everything fresh and cook at home. But like you, I’m far too busy to do as much of that as I would like — plus my kids are grown and the pressure to set a good example is gone (although my new grandson may change that).
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002n3b6ny3yjvcio@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Instead, I stock up on frozen veggies — many are flash frozen and have the same nutrients as when first picked. Low-sodium canned beans and other legumes keep me from having to cook dry beans from scratch.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002o3b6nkqwrufzr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When I buy fresh produce, I try to buy organic if my budget allows. That’s especially true for crops in the 2025 “&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/06/11/health/2025-dirty-dozen-pesticide-wellness"&gt;Dirty Dozen&lt;/a&gt;,” an annual list of foods with the most (and least) &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/24/health/pesticides-produce-fruits-vegetables-toxins-wellness"&gt;pesticides&lt;/a&gt; created by the Environmental Working Group, a health advocacy group.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1yx38u00013b6px32naneu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            I also do my best to avoid veggies and salad greens packaged in &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/09/16/health/food-packaging-chemical-toxins-study-wellness" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;chemical-laden plastics&lt;/a&gt; (that’s a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/06/24/health/microplastics-food-packaging-study-wellness" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;whole other problem&lt;/a&gt; I write about). I especially stay away from precut veggies (&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10969708/#:~:text=The%20B%20vitamins%20are%20highly,in%20small%20losses%20of%20iron." target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;loss of nutrients&lt;/a&gt;) and foods sold in black plastic containers (&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/10/01/health/flame-retardant-black-plastic-wellness" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;read about those here&lt;/a&gt;.) That’s really hard because they are &lt;em&gt;everywhere!&lt;/em&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002p3b6nhq5m92np@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When it comes to ready-to-heat-and-eat meals, I look for whole chicken breasts, sliced beef and pork, chicken or steak kebabs, and stews with real chunks of meat. (Here’s a tip: If the package says the meat is cooked “sous vide,” I’ve found it’s more likely to be whole meat.)
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002q3b6n2rarfqbt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As for the rest of the grocery store — the nearly 70% which is ultraprocessed — I do my best. I don’t know all the names of additives — much less which are harmful or beneficial — so that’s not very helpful to me. I could just as easily discard a food enriched with pantothenic acid (vitamin B5), pyridoxine (vitamin B6) or cobalamin (vitamin B12) as I could one with azodicarbonamide, a bleaching agent in bread &lt;a href="https://eur-lex.europa.eu/LexUriServ/LexUriServ.do?uri=OJ:L:2004:007:0045:0046:EN:PDF" target="_blank"&gt;banned in the EU&lt;/a&gt; due to cancer concerns.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002r3b6n28d0ky1l@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Instead, I put on my detective hat, turn the product over, and read — starting with the nutrition label. Many people go straight to carbohydrates, but carbs are not necessarily the enemy — in whole foods they come naturally, along with fiber, vitamins and minerals. Foods which are overly processed, however, may need to increase levels of added sugars, salt and fat to make the food “&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31689013/" target="_blank"&gt;hyperpalatable&lt;/a&gt;” and hard to resist.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002s3b6njdl1dj2j@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A tablespoonful of ketchup, for example, can contain 4 grams (1 teaspoon) of added sugar, while spaghetti and pizza sauces are notoriously high in added sugar as well. If you search the shelves, however, there are low-salt, no sugar and no artificial sweetener options.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002t3b6n2b9ueek0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            And this is important&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;— the percentages on the nutrition label are only for &lt;em&gt;one &lt;/em&gt;serving. Let’s take honey peanut butter, part of a typical PB&amp;amp;J lunch for my kids while they were growing up.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002u3b6nnxt2741m@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The label says one serving — two tablespoons of peanut butter — has 13 grams of sugar (2.5 teaspoons). So if I put 3 servings on the sandwich — that’s an incredible &lt;em&gt;39 grams &lt;/em&gt;or&lt;em&gt; 7.3 teaspoons &lt;/em&gt;of sugar&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;(not counting the jelly) in what many of us consider a healthy meal for a child.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002v3b6n42x3n26z@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            (OK, you may know this, yes. But truthfully, how often do you stop and look at serving size? Yeah, me neither.)
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002w3b6nofpy0pxo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            I then move to the ingredients listed in the order of prevalence. I look for signs of overprocessing (powdered veggies, of course). Additives are always at the bottom, but other culprits rise to the occasion. If sugar is first, second or third on the list, I tend to consider the food a dessert. If ingredients at the top are healthy and sugar is toward the bottom of the list, I’m not overly concerned.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002x3b6n173ijfkn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Here’s a great example: An extremely popular organic bread in grocery stores has 35 ingredients — the first 21 are whole grains and seeds. The loaf has no synthetic additives, but it does have 4 grams of added sugar per serving in the form of organic molasses. Would you consider that a junk food? An ultraprocessed food overly laden with sugar? Or is it healthy? You decide.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002y3b6nwkqz3hbz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Yet you shouldn’t have to decide, experts say. You should be able to go to your grocery store and buy foods that are good for you without having to play detective.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde002z3b6nxx0hb3hn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The rise of ultra-processed foods (UPFs) in human diets is being driven by the growing economic and political power of the UPF industry,” wrote&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;the authors of the &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(25)01567-3/fulltext" target="_blank"&gt;third Lancet paper&lt;/a&gt;. “Curbing corporate power in food systems begins with governance reform.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00303b6nlc6kevoa@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Otherwise, they added, UPFs may well “replace all other food groups” in the not-so-distant future.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00313b6nxgooe932@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Yes, there will always be junk food, and yes, we will all succumb at times. But if the majority of our food was regulated to be as whole, fresh, and devoid of added sugar, salt, fat, additives and processing as possible, we would be a much healthier nation — and world.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj1lllde00323b6nywol4qay@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            I’m not holding my breath.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 11:00:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQeVlFeGlQb3g1T1Qtdl82NF9GRVVwcTRPNThZamw4emZYb3NlSWdFdmxpMXlDWUhFRk40VktsRllVOHZadVZPaHhmeGUyUUdpQVNXOTk3dDhOV0JvcExOXzZ3alpSZHhhaDBONGlnWVR6dzBFRU1XUDdIdnhCM0FpQWdhUQ</guid></item><item><title>医生警告说，流行饮料“使中风风险增加300 ％ ，痴呆症增加290 ％” -镜报美国</title><link>https://www.themirror.com/news/health/neurologist-warning-stroke-dementia-drink-1560815</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="article-body" class="ArticleBody_article__AwrJE" data-testid="body"&gt;&lt;h1 class="HeadingOne_heading-one__mmNWJ  __className_0bd3f9"&gt;Doctor warns popular drink 'raises stroke risk by 300% and dementia by 290%'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 class="LeadText_lead-text__wd_PA __className_fdd245" data-testid="leadtext"&gt;A doctor has warned that a popular drink could significantly increase your chances of developing stroke and dementia, with studies showing those who consume it daily face dramatically higher risks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="Byline_byline-container__K_Owl" data-testid="byline"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-content" class="Byline_byline-content-wrapper__Imque"&gt;&lt;div class="Byline_author-badge-date-wrapper__Q7jj1"&gt;&lt;p class="Byline_dates-container__Rqzf2"&gt;&lt;span class="" data-testid="byline-publishedDate"&gt;06:00 ET, 14 Dec 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="Byline_updated-date__8vEV8 Byline_updated-date-with-published__ApG_G" data-testid="byline-updatedDate"&gt;Updated 07:08 ET, 14 Dec 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="SlideViewerButton_slide-viewer-button__BDJoG" aria-label="Open image viewer" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-controls="image-lightbox"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX ImageEmbed_image-lead__Ti3qQ" data-testid="leadimage" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="1366389"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Experts have recommended drinking teas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;A brain doctor has issued a stark warning about a widely consumed beverage that could dramatically heighten your risk of dementia. Dr Clint Steele cautions that diet soda increases stroke risk by 300% and dementia risk by 290%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;The 56-year-old expert, &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.themirror.com/all-about/health" target="_self" aria-label="" rel="follow" tabindex="0"&gt;who specializes in optimizing brain health and preventing or potentially reversing&lt;/a&gt; dementia and Alzheimer's disease, has published findings that have garnered more than two million views online. He cites longitudinal &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.themirror.com/news/health/manage-ibs-easy-healthy-diet-1475127" target="_self" aria-label="" rel="follow" tabindex="0"&gt;research linking daily intake of the drink to serious health issues&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;His advice is simple – &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.themirror.com/news/health/making-one-small-change-your-1185369" target="_self" aria-label="" rel="follow" tabindex="0"&gt;make the switch to water or tea before it's too late&lt;/a&gt;. "There have been numerous studies to prove that this type of drink can be damaging to your brain and also to your body," said Dr Steele, reports &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.irishmirror.ie/news/world-news/neurologist-issues-warning-over-popular-36395889" target="_self" aria-label="" rel="follow" tabindex="0"&gt;the Irish Mirror&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span data-testid="readmore" class="ReadMore_readmore-prefix__xS44r __className_12bb3e"&gt;READ MORE: &lt;span class="ReadMore_readmore-link__eF9pN"&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.themirror.com/news/health/follow-neurologists-brain-boosting-list-1150601" data-tmdatatrack="read-more" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="1150601" data-tmdatatrack-source="editorial" tabindex="0"&gt;Follow neurologist's brain boosting list to reduce your risk of dementia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="readmore" class="ReadMore_readmore-prefix__xS44r __className_12bb3e"&gt;READ MORE: &lt;span class="ReadMore_readmore-link__eF9pN"&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.themirror.com/news/health/neurologist-shares-five-signs-dementia-1386723" data-tmdatatrack="read-more" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="1386723" data-tmdatatrack-source="editorial" tabindex="0"&gt;Neurologist shares five signs of dementia 'that aren't memory loss'&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"Specifically, your cardiovascular system. But this specific study was very interesting because what they did was that they tracked people's eating and drinking habits over the course of seven years."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image-group"&gt;&lt;button class="SlideViewerButton_slide-viewer-button__BDJoG" aria-label="Open image viewer" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-controls="image-lightbox"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX false" data-testid="imageembed-1560814" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="1560814" data-tmdatatrack-type="image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Costco has confirmed that it will be switching out Pepsi products for Coca Cola products&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: Getty)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;He added: "And then what they did was they tracked them 10 years after that - to see who developed stroke and dementia symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BoxStyles_box-container__Qk3WH BoxStyles_non-commercial__aiWwo undefined" data-testid="non-commercial-1" data-position="6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"They found the people who drink diet soda on a daily basis, at least one a day, had an increased risk of stroke by 300%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"And an increased risk of dementia by 290%. These are chemicals that are damaging your body and brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"Instead, replace it with good stuff like water and tea. You don't need these sugary drinks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"Soda is just as damaging, but what we're seeing in the research is that diet soda and these chemicals that are used for sweeteners are more damaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"Even if you drink it multiple times per week, it's still damaging. Give it up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Dr Steele has spent over three decades focusing on brain health and preventing dementia, a passion born from devastating family tragedy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;He shared: "My grandmother passed from dementia, and it is one of the saddest things I've ever seen, her not knowing me or even my mum, her daughter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image-group"&gt;&lt;button class="SlideViewerButton_slide-viewer-button__BDJoG" aria-label="Open image viewer" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-controls="image-lightbox"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX false" data-testid="imageembed-1560813" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="1560813" data-tmdatatrack-type="image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Dr Clint Steele says even one a day will damage your health and you should swap it for something else - stock photo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"She was in a care facility, and they would show her flash cards of various fruits and animals - she would have no idea what they were.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"Even though she did not know who I was, she would whisper in my ear, 'Please, help get me out of here. I just want to go fishing'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;"It broke my heart, and I knew I needed to do something so others did not have to go through this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;The health professional delivered his alarming message in a video captioned: "Drinking this regularly increases your risk of stroke by 300% and dementia by 290%."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BoxStyles_box-container__Qk3WH BoxStyles_commercial__Wo6Z4 undefined" data-testid="commercial-8" data-position="10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;The bombshell disclosure shocked countless viewers. Billy admitted in the comments: "I'm on way out then as I drink a minimum of 10 cans of Diet Coke per day everyday."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Another commenter, Caz, wrote: "No diet drinks and artificial sweeteners in my house ever, real butter and real milk nothing artificial it's bad for you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Missy shared: "Husband has had diet sodas daily for many years. He was just diagnosed with dementia."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Jenny added her two cents: "At least it wasn't coffee! I'm good I hate diet soda."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Pam voiced her preference: "I'm the weirdo that only likes water and sparkling water, can't stand syrupy flavored soda and diet soda in particular."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;However, not everyone was on board with the doctor's claims. Ette rebutted: "My mother had dementia and barely ever drink pop at all, so there's that so."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Brix chimed in: "My dad has dementia and never drank a diet drink in his life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Another respondent argued: "My grandmother lived to be 94. Drank Diet Coke everyday and never had any health problems."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;One user questioned: "So why is my 92 year old mother in law still kicking it? All I have ever seen her drink for the last 40 years is Diet soda!".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Mirror US</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxNNTV6SVZEaUgwa3c5UmFMMFI2ZEo1OFlST0NGcENnaFBfYnpFZlVoaWxFdWlUeDZXMkoySTZHY3cyZk5EMU4zMmN4cFY3Qi1HdHQ2QV9jSnJCWDF2RlpzUWN3NnpCaEdRaGtXU2tyNXEtX1RBRWRyRG04dzAxMF8xdFBaeGZWNUdONEdTYnlRWWXSAZYBQVVfeXFMTUpMclhYbktsVW5kcF9OaXpuMlJGZjNkbWVIakRHYnh2eXBDOUpqYVQtdFlxX3hrM1BzWDZzLUxpSEhLdVpkRFVEUkFkWWREOENDQWZfUTk1OG8tLS1LdzdCVU1hVWRXd2Q4OFR3TGE2bnlwZHhWQVBkWGZEX2lIWHlBRENRZVBPdjNPMVVkUjRESTZVTUdR</guid></item><item><title>“年轻人越来越多地患上癌症。我们必须制造更友善的药物。” - CTech</title><link>https://www.calcalistech.com/ctechnews/article/h1t18113fbl</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-contents="true"&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="f3uk8-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="f3uk8-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="f3uk8-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“Younger people are getting cancer more and more,” said Sai Jasti, senior vice president and head of data science and AI at Bayer. “And what that means is people may have to stay on therapies for longer than what we traditionally have been used to.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="pcha-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="pcha-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="pcha-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;That demographic shift is one of several forces shaping how artificial intelligence is being applied in oncology as 2025 draws to a close. While generative AI has captured public attention, executives and clinicians working in cancer research say the more consequential changes are happening in less visible ways, driven by machine learning, deep learning, and large-scale data integration aimed at making cancer treatment more precise and, in some cases, less harmful.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="2vqm-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2vqm-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2vqm-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;At Bayer, Jasti oversees the use of AI across pharma R&amp;amp;D, from early discovery through clinical development. His core argument is that rising cancer incidence among younger patients raises the bar for drug design. If patients are expected to remain on treatment for years rather than months, toxicity and long-term side effects become central considerations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="flcpv-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta text_wide firstImageInArticle firstImageInArticleBody"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.rkelBt112MWx" id="image_ArticleImageData.rkelBt112MWx"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;2&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="calcalistExpand no-print" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.rkelBt112MWx" src="https://pic1.calcalist.co.il/picserver3/crop_images/2025/12/14/rJCeYWhM11e/rJCeYWhM11e_0_122_426_320_0_x-large.jpg" alt="Sai Jasti, senior VP and head of data science and AI at Bayer" title="Sai Jasti, senior VP and head of data science and AI at Bayer.  (Photo: Bayer) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.rkelBt112MWx" src="https://pic1.calcalist.co.il/picserver3/crop_images/2025/12/14/rJCeYWhM11e/rJCeYWhM11e_0_122_426_320_0_x-large.jpg" alt="Sai Jasti, senior VP and head of data science and AI at Bayer" title="Sai Jasti, senior VP and head of data science and AI at Bayer.  (Photo: Bayer) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Sai Jasti, senior VP and head of data science and AI at Bayer. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Bayer&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="chla9-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="chla9-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="chla9-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“That translates to the fact that we also have to make kinder medicines,” Jasti said. “So that is one of the hypotheses behind our oncology strategy, to go towards precision drug development.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="1irjp-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1irjp-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1irjp-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Precision, in this context, does not mean a sudden leap to bespoke drugs for every patient. Instead, it reflects a gradual shift toward understanding disease biology in finer detail, using large, multimodal datasets that include molecular, cellular, clinical, and real-world evidence. AI systems are then used to detect patterns across those datasets that would be difficult for humans to identify unaided.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="1dds3-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1dds3-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1dds3-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;That incremental pace is not accidental. For clinicians and AI developers alike, one of the defining realities of oncology is how slowly new technologies move from promise to practice. Ofer Sharon, MD, a physician and CEO of precision oncology company OncoHost, said the adoption curve in medicine remains fundamentally different from what the public associates with consumer AI.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="cg9nc-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta text_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.HklLULW2MZe" id="image_ArticleImageData.HklLULW2MZe"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;2&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="calcalistExpand no-print" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.HklLULW2MZe" src="https://pic1.calcalist.co.il/picserver3/crop_images/2025/12/14/r1yDIbhGWg/r1yDIbhGWg_0_33_863_648_0_x-large.jpg" alt="Dr. Ofer Sharon MD, CEO of OncoHost" title="Dr. Ofer Sharon MD, CEO of OncoHost.  (Photo: PR) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.HklLULW2MZe" src="https://pic1.calcalist.co.il/picserver3/crop_images/2025/12/14/r1yDIbhGWg/r1yDIbhGWg_0_33_863_648_0_x-large.jpg" alt="Dr. Ofer Sharon MD, CEO of OncoHost" title="Dr. Ofer Sharon MD, CEO of OncoHost.  (Photo: PR) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Dr. Ofer Sharon MD, CEO of OncoHost. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: PR&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="5ucjs-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5ucjs-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5ucjs-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“With medicine, we are still behind,” Sharon said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="qupd-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="qupd-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="qupd-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Unlike generative AI tools that can be deployed and iterated quickly, clinical AI systems must be validated through long, expensive trials to ensure they do not cause harm. Regulatory pathways were built for static products, not models that evolve as new data is incorporated. As a result, progress in oncology has been shaped less by headline-grabbing applications and more by careful integration of AI into existing clinical frameworks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="7vpvv-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7vpvv-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7vpvv-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The most tangible advances to date, Sharon said, have come from machine learning systems designed to integrate complex biological data, including genomics, proteomics, imaging, and clinical records, to identify patterns that are difficult or impossible for clinicians to detect on their own.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="e0d85-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="e0d85-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="e0d85-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“The data is there,” Sharon said. “AI holds a huge promise in being able to identify patterns that are not visible to the human eye.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="8gv8e-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="8gv8e-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="8gv8e-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Those capabilities are gradually pushing oncology toward more personalized care, but within tight constraints. Most cancer patients are still treated according to high-level clinical guidelines derived from large cohort trials, a structure that prioritizes consistency over individual variation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="40si8-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="40si8-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="40si8-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“I'm very, very positive about the progress that we are making, but I think that in most cases, if you look at the way patients are being treated, it's still done the old way,” Sharon said. “Namely, we treat patients as groups, as cohorts, not as individuals.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="5rmpt-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5rmpt-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5rmpt-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Rather than overturning that system, Sharon said the near-term trend is toward increasing its resolution, breaking broad categories into smaller subgroups defined by molecular, clinical, or protein-level characteristics. Biomarkers, he argued, are emerging as the practical bridge between AI insights and routine clinical decision-making.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="1smoq-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1smoq-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1smoq-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“If we want to see AI implemented into the clinical day-to-day,” Sharon said, “it needs to be part of the mainstream.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="96hd1-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="96hd1-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="96hd1-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Regulators are beginning to move in that direction. Sharon pointed to growing momentum at agencies such as the US Food and Drug Administration to require biomarkers alongside new drugs and to streamline approval pathways for diagnostic tools that support treatment decisions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="d6ekc-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="d6ekc-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="d6ekc-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;At large pharmaceutical companies like Bayer, those shifts are already influencing how AI is deployed across the oncology value chain, though unevenly. Jasti said the greatest gains so far have come in early-stage research, including AI-first molecule design and target validation. Clinical development remains more challenging, while patient identification using real-world data is an area of growing momentum.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="aoosf-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="aoosf-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="aoosf-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Bayer is currently developing a Microsoft-backed agentic AI framework for the Israeli market that is designed to improve access to its medicines by coordinating diagnosis, economic assessment, policy considerations, and care pathways, with the goal of bringing the system to market next year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="34kk6-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="34kk6-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="34kk6-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“All in all, it is contributing towards achieving that ambition,” Jasti said, referring to precision medicine. “But I do think in my estimation, we are at least three to five years away from realizing the full potential of it.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="4se4k-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4se4k-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4se4k-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Both executives pushed back on more futuristic visions, such as fully personalized drugs produced on demand. Human biology, Jasti emphasized, remains too complex for that level of predictability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="cn6qh-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="cn6qh-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="cn6qh-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“Biology is super, super complicated,” he said. “It’s not an internet world wherein you can just scrape through the entire wide web, train a big model, and come up with a large language model.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="euqdh-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="57eb7-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="57eb7-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="57eb7-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;For now, the trajectory of AI in oncology is defined less by spectacle than by infrastructure: better data, better models, and tighter integration between diagnostics, drug development, and clinical decision-making. As cancer increasingly affects younger populations, the pressure to make treatments not only effective but sustainable over the long term is likely to intensify.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="72i82" data-offset-key="ek5a8-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="ek5a8-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="ek5a8-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;That, more than hype cycles or chip shortages, is what executives say is driving the field forward.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CTech</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 10:50:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE5tU1RJdHZQXzg3X3FJSXdWelpDUmRseFo3MDdiV0FkVkFNbHJEMWhuOVlFSDlUV1hSYU5hSkwyMm5hbnhxdDVaZlQtSUY0WlV1UlZER3pBNnZSaDh6VmNpcHV2Z25tNG1Fc3c</guid></item><item><title>关于“处方”的喜剧：为什么进行单人表演对您的健康有益- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20251212-comedy-on-prescription-why-stand-up-is-good-for-your-health</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 kfxpiP"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Moore says the group has also helped him shift his perspective on himself. "There's this victimhood mentality where you carry [your pain] around on your shoulders and it weighs you down every single day," he says. "But here, we can get that feeling off our chest and have a laugh at the things that have happened to us."  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.angiescomedycourses.com/documents/co-produced-comedy-course-for-men.pdf" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;a report&lt;/a&gt; analysing Belcher's &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.angiescomedycourses.com/documents/co-produced-comedy-course-for-men.pdf" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;comedy-on-referral&lt;/a&gt; programme for men, co-author Lisa Sheldon, a consultant, clinical psychologist and a leader within the West London NHS Trust, also recognised this group dynamic. Among other benefits, she says, it involves "talking publicly about what it means to be human and being open about what goes on inside of us, whilst at the same time dispelling myths and establishing shared truths and connection".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The report also says using humour as a therapeutic tool, rather than framing the course as therapy, helped to "facilitate a lighter perspective on past traumas, thus lessening the burden of anxiety and fear".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Belcher agrees that the lighter framework was key. "If I'd asked these men, 'Do you want to come to a therapeutic men's school?' they wouldn't do that, but when we said, 'Come and learn stand-up comedy,' that worked," Belcher says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;&lt;span id="the-rise-of-comedy-on-'prescription'" class="sc-d16436d-0 gCPVhV"&gt;&lt;b id="the-rise-of-comedy-on-'prescription'" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;The rise of comedy on 'prescription'&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The need for therapeutic tools has grown more urgent in England, where rates of mental illness have continued to rise. The most recent data finds&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://commonslibrary.parliament.uk/research-briefings/sn06988/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt; one in six people over 16 in England &lt;/a&gt;experienced symptoms of a mental health problem in the past week. The Office of National Statistics found the rate of suicide rose to &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ons.gov.uk/peoplepopulationandcommunity/birthsdeathsandmarriages/deaths/bulletins/suicidesintheunitedkingdom/2023" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;more than 6,000 deaths in 2023&lt;/a&gt; in England and Wales – the highest since 1999, with &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ons.gov.uk/peoplepopulationandcommunity/birthsdeathsandmarriages/deaths/bulletins/suicidesintheunitedkingdom/2021registrations" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;rates among men&lt;/a&gt; particularly high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxQcDFYZTd6OXFSQmFwY1RYazB4Mndla3dfTVVPRmFFSjhueDI5aURJQnM1R3ZiWWZfTmVmNXNlb1dRUUc0RFdoZUdJa2ZPcmJkY0N2cTBYc1NhdGZZZkNmWVdLVFpKTjZnSzVWRHRKLU4xaHg3Y1NRWENtX3Z5WFllQ20tU0E1UDZ3ZEJJN0FtQ3J3VG91MVBsMk1ZWW8wbGdFMXVXSFRn</guid></item><item><title>冬天应该喝多少水？医生警告脱水的隐藏风险，分享保持水分的技巧|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/how-much-water-should-you-drink-in-winter-doctors-warn-about-hidden-risks-of-dehydration-share-tips-to-stay-hydrated-101765700483592.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/how-much-water-should-you-drink-in-winter-doctors-warn-about-hidden-risks-of-dehydration-share-tips-to-stay-hydrated-101765700483592.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;As temperatures fall, a silent health risk looms: winter&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/dr-nene-reveals-6-signs-you-are-dehydrated-how-many-do-you-check-101726984094393.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="dehydration"&gt; dehydration&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Contrary to the common assumption that dehydration is primarily a problem associated with hot weather, doctors warn that the colder months can lead to even greater fluid loss, significantly impacting the body's major systems.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Also read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/wellness-coach-shares-5-winter-friendly-foods-she-eats-regularly-to-lower-cortisol-and-manage-stress-101765184075410.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Wellness coach shares 5 winter-friendly foods she eats regularly to lower cortisol and manage stress"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wellness coach shares 5 winter-friendly foods she eats regularly to lower cortisol and manage stress&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/14/550x309/2533_1765700558863_1765700570193.jpg" alt="For people who struggle to drink enough water because they don't feel thirsty, doctors advocate for incorporating water-rich foods and beverages. (Freepik)" title="For people who struggle to drink enough water because they don't feel thirsty, doctors advocate for incorporating water-rich foods and beverages. (Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/14/550x309/2533_1765700558863_1765700570193.jpg" alt="For people who struggle to drink enough water because they don't feel thirsty, doctors advocate for incorporating water-rich foods and beverages. (Freepik)" title="For people who struggle to drink enough water because they don't feel thirsty, doctors advocate for incorporating water-rich foods and beverages. (Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;For people who struggle to drink enough water because they don't feel thirsty, doctors advocate for incorporating water-rich foods and beverages. (Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In an interview with HT Lifestyle, Dr Rahul Mathur, department of internal medicine at CK Birla Hospitals, Jaipur, highlighted the paradox. “People assume dehydration happens only in hot weather, but winters silently dehydrate us even more,” he said, adding, “Low temperatures reduce our thirst response by up to 40 percent, even when our body &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/drinking-less-than-1-5-litres-water-a-day-study-reveals-link-between-hydration-and-stress-101756185170031.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="needs water"&gt;needs water&lt;/a&gt;. Simultaneously, we lose fluids through dry indoor heating, faster breathing in cold air, and increased urination.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2024/10/14/550x309/water_trick_weight_loss_1728902400382_1728902400652.jpeg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Doctors suggest a daily water intake of around 13 cups for men and 9 cups for women, and around 3 to 4 cups per day for children. (Pexels)" title="Doctors suggest a daily water intake of around 13 cups for men and 9 cups for women, and around 3 to 4 cups per day for children. (Pexels)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Doctors suggest a daily water intake of around 13 cups for men and 9 cups for women, and around 3 to 4 cups per day for children. (Pexels)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The body-wide impact of low fluid intake&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;He cautioned that even mild dehydration — just 1–2 percent — can have a cascading negative effect on health. The brain is highly sensitive, and dehydration can lead to fatigue, headaches, and impaired concentration. Moreover, Dr Mathur said that low fluid intake “thickens blood, increasing risks of hypertension, clotting, and cardiac strain, especially in older adults.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Concentrated urine due to dehydration can result in kidney stones and UTIs, which are common during colder months, he shared, adding that dehydration can stiffen joints and reduce workout performance.&lt;/span&gt; Dr Mathur said, “Kidneys are similarly affected since concentrated urine leads to kidney stones and UTIs, which are common during colder months. Skin and mucosa suffer as reduced hydration compromises the skin barrier, causing dryness, cracked lips, and weakening immunity in the nose and throat. Joints and muscles can also feel the strain because dehydration stiffens joints and reduces workout performance.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Hydration goals and strategies&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Sandeep Patil, chief intensivist at Fortis Hospital, Kalyan, shared with HT Lifestyle that the fundamental role of water, which makes up 60 percent of the body: “Water is essential for the daily functioning of the body.&lt;/span&gt; All body fluids contain water. Along with water, waste material is excreted through the kidneys. For the digestion and absorption of nutrients, water is essential in the gut.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He recommended a daily water requirement of around 13 cups for men and 9 cups for women, and around 3 to 4 cups per day for children. “In cold weather, people tend to wear layers of clothing, which leads to overheating and perspiration, and &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/hepatologist-says-8-glasses-of-water-a-day-is-a-myth-here-s-how-much-you-should-drink-to-stay-hydrated-101749393229706.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="fluid loss"&gt;fluid loss&lt;/a&gt;, which is not recognised,” Dr Patil explained. A simple check for dehydration, he suggested, is to look at your urine: dark colour and less quantity indicate a need for more fluids.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/08/16/original/oranges_1755348281684.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Dr Mathur recommended fruits like oranges, kiwi, apples, and pomegranates.(Shutterstock)" title="Dr Mathur recommended fruits like oranges, kiwi, apples, and pomegranates.(Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Dr Mathur recommended fruits like oranges, kiwi, apples, and pomegranates.(Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Diet focus for the non-thirsty&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those who simply don't feel thirsty, both doctors advocate for a strategy focused on incorporating water-rich foods and beverages:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Fluid target: Dr Mathur suggested adults should consume 2–2.5 litres/day, including fluids from soups and fruits. Elderly individuals or those with specific conditions (like heart or kidney disease) should seek personalised medical advice.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Warm options: Warm water, clear soups, and herbal teas (like chamomile or ginger) are excellent, comforting options that aid hydration, Dr Mathur added.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Fruit and vegetable power: Dr Mathur recommended fruits like oranges, kiwi, apples, and pomegranates, and vegetables like cucumbers, tomatoes, and bottle gourds. Dr Patil added watermelon, celery, and leafy greens to the list.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Strategic habits: Dr Mathur suggested keeping a timed water bottle or drinking a glass of water before every meal.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Patil said that to stay hydrated this winter, try these simple diet tips:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;1. Water-rich foods: Include foods like watermelon, cucumbers, oranges, and leafy greens in your diet.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;2. &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/nutritionist-shares-7-herbal-teas-that-are-just-as-beneficial-as-green-tea-for-weight-loss-cinnamon-tea-hibiscus-tea-101757936331575.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Herbal teas"&gt;Herbal teas&lt;/a&gt;: Enjoy warm herbal teas like chamomile, peppermint, or ginger tea.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;3. Smoothies: Blend hydrating fruits and veggies with coconut water or yogurt.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4. Coconut water: Replenish electrolytes with this natural drink.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;5. Warm water with honey and ginger: Boost immunity and hydration.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;6. Hydrating snacks: Munch on cucumber sticks, watermelon, or frozen berries.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;7. Add water to meals: Make oatmeal, soups, or porridge with extra liquid.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;8. Electrolyte-rich drinks: Try coconut water, diluted fruit juices, or ORS solutions.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/03/18/original/shutterstock_2510611455_1742305803306.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Dr Patil said that to stay hydrated this winter, try herbal teas like chamomile, peppermint, or ginger tea.(Shutterstock)" title="Dr Patil said that to stay hydrated this winter, try herbal teas like chamomile, peppermint, or ginger tea.(Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Dr Patil said that to stay hydrated this winter, try herbal teas like chamomile, peppermint, or ginger tea.(Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Avoid the dehydrators&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both experts strongly advise limiting drinks that can worsen dehydration. “It is best to avoid too much caffeine, alcohol, and sugary energy drinks since they worsen dehydration,” said Dr Mathur. Dr Patil also suggested limiting high-salt, processed foods, which can contribute to fluid imbalance.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He said, “Caffeine and alcohol: both are diuretics, meaning they can increase fluid loss and contribute to dehydration. If you don’t feel thirsty, it’s best to &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/more-caffeine-less-control-how-drinking-too-much-coffee-before-driving-can-slow-your-reflexes-and-cloud-judgment-101762232167996.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="limit caffeine"&gt;limit caffeine&lt;/a&gt; and alcohol intake. Excessive salt can lead to water retention and increased thirst. Processed or packaged foods often contain high levels of sodium, so try to focus on fresh, whole foods.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Mathur's final advice: “Hydration is not seasonal: our cells don’t know the weather outside; they only know what they need. Listening to your body, and not just your thirst, is the key to staying healthy this winter.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 08:37:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwJBVV95cUxOQVhhUmZsMi0zaVVIRHlBaGYxZXRMczJoQ2dndm1rcllhNEE5dmRIOHgyVzBweTJPblliR1pPT1Z6LVpHRHNKQWRwNVFiaXRWRTh5NUR5WjhHTEprazBseGhPcVlwOEZ1Xy11LTFHYkxpYzVkeFlkakJNVHNEYnBGRWUzQll6NjJxUWo5SWJTbGw1a191OEdRQ1lmU1U5TFNRZHBUUExDT2p5WDdJOUpOSy16UjYwN0NtNFpMVXllMlZRdnY4TW90WjZSZTlVRUYyal9TZklnYjBIVjNza2xMUEM4OU1iMGVDcUwyNTYyWGdSWUpTbDhiQWhadTBRUGN3VTB6b1E4LXFyS1ZkNllGNFpzWdIBmAJBVV95cUxPQUtLQUV2ZmdIdFBqSzNfbkNtcHNmNm9idGVzLW1FWFIwYXM1YW9iODlfcVVQeUo2N0dOakdzbzdJMWJENGZKc2lOY0E0TV9vUDNHQWp5NzI4M1czU1dvTkVWS0dFVmhjT2E5RGhlV0tGVHVoYUUtZzFHamlETHBkLTBOUjJyMks2c0hGUUdmc2c2UGhacEFld1psd29uZ3Q5YktZVmNVelZGRW5nRER3Tnd5SG1hODJNTGVsbGhNaXpsalJBVS16c1hwQmtLMHQzRXROeUp3M2w0RG1Ra2JBRmp0Z0VocFJrZ2ZOeUN4aFdsTDBxbUlucjdscVFFeHBHNDY1VWlJcENkcV9Kbjd0UWU0b3M4V3Yz</guid></item><item><title>拥有20年经验的加州心脏病专家警告不要使用这种流行的睡眠补充剂： “要非常小心” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/california-cardiologist-with-20-years-of-experience-warns-against-this-popular-sleep-supplement-melatonin-101765697203222.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storyMainDiv" class="fullStory tfStory current videoStory story__detail storyAf101765697203222 " data-vars-storyid="101765697203222" data-story-section="lifestyle" data-story-subsection="health" data-vars-author="Akanksha Agnihotri" data-premium-story="false" data-performance-type="not-set" data-story-title="California cardiologist with 20 years of experience warns against this popular sleep supplement: ‘Be very careful’" data-collapse-article="false"&gt; &lt;p class="htEchoTopPageBanner dHide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="stickyCard"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;h1 class="hdg1"&gt;California cardiologist with 20 years of experience warns against this popular sleep supplement: ‘Be very careful’&lt;/h1&gt;  &lt;div class="actionDiv flexElm topTime"&gt; &lt;p class="dateTime secTime storyPage"&gt;Published on: Dec 14, 2025 01:23 pm IST &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="googleFollow mHide"&gt; &lt;button class="htEchoShareBarDesk"&gt;&lt;/button&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;h2 class="sortDec"&gt;As melatonin use rises among adults and children alike, questions about its safety are growing. Cardiologist Dr Sanjay Bhojraj shares what people need to know.&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;div class="storyDetails taboola-readmore"&gt; &lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/california-cardiologist-with-20-years-of-experience-warns-against-this-popular-sleep-supplement-melatonin-101765697203222.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Late nights, racing thoughts, and broken sleep have pushed many people towards &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/doctor-warns-melatonin-overuse-can-backfire-explains-why-timing-and-dosage-are-important-high-doses-do-not-improve-101763902638285.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="melatonin"&gt;melatonin&lt;/a&gt; as an easy fix. Marketed as natural and harmless, the supplement is now a nightly ritual for millions. But is it really as safe as it seems? &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Sanjay Bhojraj, a functional medicine doctor and board-certified interventional cardiologist based in California, US, with over 20 years of experience, reveals the truth behind melatonin use.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;(Also read: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/aiimstrained-neurologist-explains-whether-eggs-can-actually-cause-cancer-shares-tips-on-how-to-consume-them-safely-101765630010419.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="AIIMS-trained neurologist explains whether 'eggs can actually cause cancer’; shares tips on how to consume them safely"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AIIMS-trained neurologist explains whether 'eggs can actually cause cancer’; shares tips on how to consume them safely &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/14/550x309/2149071935_1765697615048_1765697619073.jpg" alt="Dr Bhojraj promotes magnesium over melatonin for sleep and health benefits. (Freepik)" title="Dr Bhojraj promotes magnesium over melatonin for sleep and health benefits. (Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/14/550x309/2149071935_1765697615048_1765697619073.jpg" alt="Dr Bhojraj promotes magnesium over melatonin for sleep and health benefits. (Freepik)" title="Dr Bhojraj promotes magnesium over melatonin for sleep and health benefits. (Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Dr Bhojraj promotes magnesium over melatonin for sleep and health benefits. (Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Is melatonin really safe for regular use&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Bhojraj explains in his December 12 Instagram post, “There are some concerns that were raised recently about melatonin. If used too much, it can suppress puberty in kids. So there are a lot of things that melatonin, which is a neurotransmitter, can do that I don’t love”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He highlights that while melatonin does have certain benefits, it is not something to be consumed casually or long-term without understanding its impact. “Now, it is &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/nutritionist-shares-easy-recipe-for-morning-anti-inflammatory-drink-that-eases-your-gut-and-reduces-bloating-101765688478388.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="anti-inflammatory"&gt;anti-inflammatory&lt;/a&gt;, so there are benefits to it. I’m not saying that it’s not something that we use. We just have to be very careful,” he adds.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is magnesium a safer alternative&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, Dr Bhojraj strongly advocates &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/bengaluru-nutritionist-reveals-top-signs-when-you-may-need-magnesium-supplement-if-you-have-gut-issues-101765611632733.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="magnesium"&gt;magnesium&lt;/a&gt; as a safer and more versatile alternative, especially for sleep-related concerns. “Whereas with magnesium, I use that. I love magnesium,” he says. “You can use it for sleep. You can use it to regulate bowel health. You can use it to regulate inflammation. It can help with anxiety and depression.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to him, magnesium supports multiple bodily functions and is far more forgiving when used consistently. “For so many reasons, I love magnesium. And in particular, magnesium glycinate or magnesium threonate are probably the magnesium salts that I love the most,” Dr Bhojraj notes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="recommendedSliderContextual" id="recommendedSliderContextual-101765697203222" data-vars-story_id="101765697203222" data-vars-story_section="lifestyle" data-vars-author="Akanksha Agnihotri" data-vars-story_headline="California cardiologist with 20 years of experience warns against this popular sleep supplement: ‘Be very careful’"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" class="trendTopsSHow" id="trendTopsSHow-101765697203222"&gt; &lt;div class="trendTops"&gt;  &lt;div class="trendInlineSeo"&gt;&lt;p&gt; Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;label class="moreBtn1" for="trendTopsSHow-101765697203222"&gt;&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="followHT trendSeo__1"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="bottomSeoParaEcho1"&gt; &lt;div id="bottomSeoParaEcho"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="mb5 mt5" id="bottomBreadCrumb"&gt; &lt;div class="breadcrumbs"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Home_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/" data-vars-event-cta="News"&gt;News&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Lifestyle_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle" data-vars-event-cta="Lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Health_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle/health" data-vars-event-cta="Health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; California cardiologist with 20 years of experience warns against this popular sleep supplement: ‘Be very careful’ &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="bottomSeoParaEcho pb0"&gt; &lt;label class="moreBtn" for="trendTopsSHow-101765697203222" id="spanSeeLessEcho"&gt;See Less&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;p class="relatedStoryCricket"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="saranyuPlayer" id="saranyu-player"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="relatedStory2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="us-ad align-center mb10 mt10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="htEchoShortsEntryPoint" data-size="enlarged"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="affiliate-shop-now" id="affiliate-shop-now"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 07:53:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAJBVV95cUxNQVdYNWphVHlESG9weXhBOFhSdHRVRlJnMFlNOVlhcUJ1QTFsRklHVWc0Z2ZTcEJUVDA2dnItck83ODZkYjVEaHI4V05CZHdHSVk0VDk2Szk2dEFfcmp0MnNXRXY1YV9saHVHS0ZhX2NleE5TQXlMZlZ0S1NzNldsRkVjR0tGbGtxM3RWYlZEc3pFWllFZEw5NW8zMmw0bVV2V1FKdmMtc0ltWER6XzkzRi1QMjJfQ08yT0tDQnBlZ1NLQVV6bWt0RWVJRGlmUW52NW9CNU1pZG9YdTJLblAyVGMwREQtTzlMWnhpWDI5bWpPaHJiNVZDZUNDUkZlV0xoUEZuQtIBigJBVV95cUxNQWlfcDluSm9IaS1KTmNrX25yb18zWERleGtDX3RhRmVKVEdhYUlyV3pvZm82Y3R6OGFjbVExWG9lM0NwdkRCVkhEVEp3cy1ib2h1UlhodEViWmNVdHgzM2RIbS1kUWR2cWdEc3M5NnE3a1dHT0REZHlyd3ZxVEhVVW9BNk5FZHJlanBGaGVQb0lQX29oblktZ0JUb25QZjBiT1RJdVFhQzdPN2FLejlGU0QyRm04ajZRMTNQd01heWFtdVd1S3FVYjNaWUxpZnlBWk1qMkM2X25XcGRoVGxmT0NOVTk5UFQyX0dZUGpZT0VGYVI3UkM3OVczS3JvZmtoVGR3RjZjcXlzdw</guid></item></channel></rss>