<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Brooklyn kitten ID’d as second NYC avian flu victim after contracting virus from another cat - New York Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxQbUJMRjU2dWxlU3QtbVJrNzM3R1VuODJMM0FwQUhYLWJGa242QXA3c1BIa2RXRkVvSGFTM2JoYTdGMWcwT0NueElweWc5R1J1LWhZUHg5emhGcU50T0lwVDNySzh1ZGRpeG1RZjdWb2Ffd0VPVFRLSXZKS241MzRGUjhmbmsyNGYzTzZIRTJfWlBaT0ZwaEdOMlpXdzN4blEtUzd3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom "&gt;
							


&lt;p&gt;A Brooklyn kitten has been identified as the second confirmed feline victim of avian flu in New York City — having contracted the contagion from another infected cat.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Valentino, a 1-year-old domestic shorthair, was technically the &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/02/21/us-news/some-of-nycs-500000-stray-cats-could-already-be-infected-with-bird-flu-and-a-possible-threat-to-humans-activists/"&gt;first cat in the Big Apple to die from the H5N1 virus &lt;/a&gt;after undergoing an emergency euthanasia on Feb. 1, Dr. Natara Loose of The Neighborhood Vet in Bushwick, told The Post.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;His case was only confirmed this week after a second cat, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/03/14/us-news/two-nyc-cats-dead-from-avian-flu-including-8-month-old-kitten/"&gt;an 8-month-old Upper West Side kitten&lt;/a&gt;, succumbed to the same fate.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Valentino is the second confirmed fatality in New York City of avian flu in felines.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Legitimately, had this little kitten not died recently and had it not been confirmed this week, I would still be in the process, probably for an unknown period of time, of not knowing how Valentino got it or how he died … no one would have put it out there, so it’s good news for the public,” Loose, Valentino’s veterinarian and owner, explained.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="connatix-outstream-video"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Valentino was put to sleep just 24 hours after he recorded a jaw-dropping 106-degree fever.&lt;/p&gt;


	



&lt;p&gt;The lively little black kitten had been his active and curious self in the days earlier, but Loose became concerned when she noticed he was hiding inside the Bushwick vet office, which he called home.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Valentino — whose condition was already delicate due to diabetes — was put on antibiotics and fluids and checked for multiple infections, but he didn’t respond to anything.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Valentino’s health rapidly declined within 24 hours of recording a 106-degree fever. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;theneighborhoodvet/Instagram&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The domestic shorthair was rushed to an animal hospital on Jan. 31 and underwent a procedure, but it was too late.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I euthanized him and he was here. I’m kissing him,” Loose said in a social media video, indicating she was holding Valentino close when he was put to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Suspecting her beloved kitten’s cause of death, Loose submitted Valentino for a necropsy, where it was confirmed that every organ of his body was infected by bird flu via tainted food.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Government officials were suspicious, however, because Valentino had not consumed any raw meat — which had caused the deaths of at least 85 cats across the US since 2022.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Valentino likely contracted bird flu from another cat, who survived the infection. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;theneighborhoodvet/Instagram&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A second Big Apple feline death last month — which experts believe was caused by ingesting the raw food brand Savage Cat, prompting investigators to question whether any of Loose’s furry patients had a history with the brand.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Further investigation revealed that Valentino had contracted the virus from a third cat, “Cat C,” who had been rushed into The Neighborhood Vet days before Valentino’s death.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“That cat had a mild fever. No respiratory signs, just a little uncomfortable in his belly and went home the next day completely normal,” Loose said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I read through the history of the cat and the cat had eaten the same food.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Valentino died on Feb. 1 from an emergency euthanasia.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;theneighborhoodvet/Instagram&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;On Friday, Audrey Brady, owner of Savage Cat, told The Post that the company’s ingredients are USDA inspected and are monitored for H5/H7 viruses. The brand’s raw foods were &lt;a href="https://savagecatfood.com/avian-influenza/"&gt;recalled in February after a potential link&lt;/a&gt; to another infection, which was later proven negative.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Though Valentino lives at the vet office, he did not have any direct contact with Cat C, Loose said, leading her to believe the avian flu was transmitted through the air.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;Neither Loose nor any of her employees contracted the avian flu, despite their close contact with Valentino, especially in the heartbreaking moments of his death.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I think cats-to-human is going to be pretty rare or very, very, very low risk because we were all very direct contact with him,” said Loose.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="comments-inline-cta" data-comment-count data-prompt="What do you think?"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There have been no cases of bird flu in humans in New York City, the city health department confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There has been no official recall for Savage Cat Foods, though the health department is advising New Yorkers not to feed their pets anything from the brand, or any raw meat or milk products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wpcom-liveblog-container"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;

												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQbUJMRjU2dWxlU3QtbVJrNzM3R1VuODJMM0FwQUhYLWJGa242QXA3c1BIa2RXRkVvSGFTM2JoYTdGMWcwT0NueElweWc5R1J1LWhZUHg5emhGcU50T0lwVDNySzh1ZGRpeG1RZjdWb2Ffd0VPVFRLSXZKS241MzRGUjhmbmsyNGYzTzZIRTJfWlBaT0ZwaEdOMlpXdzN4blEtUzd3</guid></item><item><title>Chocolate could be the next probiotic powerhouse - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV95cUxQa3ZkTkNiOWQxLWE3NmZLSFVNM1d6N0Z5TnBDMkVLeFduR1I3alFUUzAxNkw1ZDlVYWZKVXFwMm9DRk9iOUpCTGpMWXV5alJDNmUwMWdONHVqUVpzYkR4Sk4xQVdVN1kxdmFLWEU4ejFBYlZubUpFSlR0X1FLVXFEN0VR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;What if eating chocolate could be more than just a guilty pleasure? What if &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/chocolate-and-cocoa-prices-have-doubled-in-the-past-year-climate-change/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;chocolate&lt;/a&gt;, infused with probiotics, had hidden health benefits beyond the usual antioxidant boost from dark varieties?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists are working on just that. By infusing chocolate with prebiotics and probiotics, they aim to transform it into a functional food. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The goal is to produce a delicious, gut-friendly treat that does more than satisfy cravings. But there’s a challenge: adding health-boosting ingredients can alter texture, moisture, and even protein levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trick is to keep the chocolate as indulgent as ever while making it better for the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-probiotics-make-chocolate-healthier"&gt;Probiotics make chocolate healthier&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probiotics are tiny, beneficial microbes found in yogurt and kimchi that play a vital role in gut health. They help balance bacteria, aid digestion, and even reduce inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But they’re delicate. Stomach acid, heat, and processing can destroy probiotics before they ever reach the intestines, where they do their best work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enter prebiotics. These compounds, often dietary fibers, act as food for probiotics, helping them to thrive. Together, they form a powerhouse combination known as synbiotics. The challenge now is to find a way to embed these prebiotics and probiotics into &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/can-chocolate-survive-dna-research-may-help-save-cacao-trees/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;chocolate&lt;/a&gt; without ruining its flavor or texture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s where researchers Smriti Gaur and Shubhi Singh from the Jaypee Institute of Information Technology (&lt;a href="https://www.jiit.ac.in" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;JIIT&lt;/a&gt;) in India stepped in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of using complex processing methods, they took a different approach – corn and honey. These natural prebiotics were easy to integrate, and eliminated the need for complicated manufacturing techniques.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-experimenting-with-flavor"&gt;Experimenting with flavor &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team didn’t stop at a single chocolate &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cocoa-production-in-africa-is-under-extreme-climate-pressure/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;recipe&lt;/a&gt;. They created five versions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One was a control – pure chocolate with standard ingredients like cocoa butter, cocoa powder, and milk powder. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The others were synbiotic chocolates, each containing different combinations of prebiotics (corn and honey), probiotics (&lt;em&gt;Lactobacillus acidophilus La-14&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Lactobacillus rhamnosus GG&lt;/em&gt;), and a flavor enhancer – either cinnamon or orange.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then came the tests. Fat content remained steady across all chocolates, keeping the mouthfeel familiar, but other properties shifted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Orange-flavored chocolate, for example, changed the game. It lowered the pH, increased moisture, and even boosted protein levels compared to the other samples. Scientists believe the citrus elements interacted with the probiotics, enhancing their stability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-probiotics-change-chocolate-s-texture"&gt;Probiotics change chocolate’s texture&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Texture matters in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/sustainable-farming-could-save-the-future-of-chocolate/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;chocolate&lt;/a&gt;. The perfect piece should break with a clean snap, not crumble or feel too soft. The synbiotic chocolates, however, lost some of that sharp break. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional ingredients disrupted the chocolate’s structure, making it slightly softer. Whether that’s good or bad depends on personal preference. Some might find it more luxurious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nutritionally, though, the changes were promising. The probiotic-enhanced chocolates had higher antioxidant levels than the control. That means they not only delivered gut-friendly microbes but also an extra dose of protection against oxidative stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Storage was another key test. Would the probiotics survive? Over time, microbial counts decreased, but not as much as expected. Even after 125 days, probiotic levels remained high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This shelf life exceeded that of many other probiotic-infused chocolates that had been tested in past studies, proving that the chosen bacteria strains and prebiotic ingredients contributed to long-term stability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-real-test-is-surviving-digestion"&gt;The real test is surviving digestion&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chocolate infused with probiotics sounds great in theory, but there’s a bigger question: do the probiotics actually make it past the stomach? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Harsh digestive conditions can destroy beneficial microbes before they reach the intestines, rendering the whole idea useless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To find out, the researchers simulated human digestion in a lab. The results were encouraging. The probiotics maintained substantial viability for over five hours, meaning they had a strong chance of surviving long enough to benefit gut health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-does-it-still-feel-like-a-treat"&gt;Does it still feel like a treat?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, none of this matters if the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/new-discovery-will-help-climate-proof-chocolate/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;chocolate&lt;/a&gt; doesn’t taste good. People aren’t likely to choose gut-friendly chocolate if it doesn’t deliver the same rich, satisfying experience. So, the researchers sampled their creations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Personally, we enjoyed the orange-flavored chocolates the most, where the vibrant citrus notes complemented the rich cocoa, and it had a slightly softer texture that made each bite feel more luxurious,” said Gaur.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s a promising sign. A probiotic chocolate that doesn’t taste like a “health food” could appeal to a much wider audience. Experimenting with more flavors could make these chocolates even more exciting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-future-of-probiotic-chocolate"&gt;The future of probiotic chocolate&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This study is just the beginning. While the results suggest that synbiotic chocolates can boost gut health and antioxidant levels, there’s still room for improvement. Future research could refine the probiotic strains, adjust texture, and enhance flavors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the future, we are excited to explore additional health benefits of these chocolates while thoroughly investigating their sensory and nutritional profiles, with the goal of creating an even more wholesome and enjoyable treat,” said Gaur.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If successful, this could mark a shift in how people see chocolate – not just as a sweet indulgence, but as a functional food. Imagine a world where treating yourself means nourishing your body, too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acsfoodscitech.4c00741" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;ACS Food Science &amp;amp; Technology&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/eric-ralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 17:39:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxQa3ZkTkNiOWQxLWE3NmZLSFVNM1d6N0Z5TnBDMkVLeFduR1I3alFUUzAxNkw1ZDlVYWZKVXFwMm9DRk9iOUpCTGpMWXV5alJDNmUwMWdONHVqUVpzYkR4Sk4xQVdVN1kxdmFLWEU4ejFBYlZubUpFSlR0X1FLVXFEN0VR</guid></item><item><title>Undiscovered cause of Parkinson’s found for first time by scientists in huge breakthrough - The Independent</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikgFBVV95cUxQczBfcTVnRjlFaFdwVU9UQnRVWWQ3bUNIaHg3Nm02dTg3WloxSTRlR1NQRExLQ0s4d3dkR05qcHJ3Q3pfSGdtMVZZRXNHUG94cGtyRXowalVFa2h6TXp4ZlNzQ1hybm8wSEZFNlVoWDNNckpuT251SGlCSjloSDlnd0J3UWVYSG9OVUp5UDNrb3pndw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 lkPksW sc-jbiisr-1 hiukpJ" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 cFynzd" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base-light"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 eFDpwi"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 jkkqcL"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 dDFcwe"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 kqOtlp"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 bjQKsM"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 hWxisF sc-hez36s-16 gBaKpR"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 ifXxYf"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 jlvSeZ"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 ghJHgZ"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 bhFQeV"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 gMxIQB"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 gMxIQB"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 gMxIQB"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 fJIQUi"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 dvfakS sc-aja53j-7 gYsKvs"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 CRIit"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 ctXiMg"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 fdygxT sc-culv3z-0 kOpooG sc-a5wy94-0 hgIqfZ"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/topic/scientists"&gt;Scientists&lt;/a&gt; have made a potentially “life-changing” discovery that could pave the way for new drugs to treat Parkinson’s disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts have known for several decades that the PINK1 protein is directly linked to Parkinson’s disease – the &lt;a href="/news/uk/home-news/academics-bmj-beijing-symptoms-east-asia-b2709819.html"&gt;fastest growing&lt;/a&gt; neurodegenerative condition in the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until now, no one has seen what human PINK1 looks like, how PINK1 attaches to the surface of damaged mitochondria inside of cells, or how it is activated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But scientists have now discovered how the mutation switches on and can start using this knowledge to find a way to switch it off and slow the progression of the condition down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers at the Walter and Eliza Hall Institute, Parkinson’s Disease Research Centre, in Australia, have solved the decades-long mystery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 kWYnHL"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Science &lt;/em&gt;reveal for the first time ever the structure of PINK1 and how it binds to mitochondria – the powerhouse of a cell – and stops it functioning properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parkinson’s disease can take years, sometimes decades to diagnose. Often associated with tremors, there are close to 40 symptoms including cognitive impairment, speech issues, body temperature regulation and vision problems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The neurological condition affects around 153,000 Britons. There is currently no cure for Parkinson’s, although medicine, physiotherapy and surgery can help manage symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-482ou5-2 lafNeh sc-482ou5-3 fdIcNP image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 lkeWpK"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="2" class="sc-482ou5-0 hVSdqv"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/02/16/19/1579c6ced0b3815b4ae9d2fc2c3ad0f1Y29udGVudHNlYXJjaGFwaSwxNzA4MTcxODkz-2.74571124.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/02/16/19/1579c6ced0b3815b4ae9d2fc2c3ad0f1Y29udGVudHNlYXJjaGFwaSwxNzA4MTcxODkz-2.74571124.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/02/16/19/1579c6ced0b3815b4ae9d2fc2c3ad0f1Y29udGVudHNlYXJjaGFwaSwxNzA4MTcxODkz-2.74571124.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Some Parkinson’s patients can take more than 20 tablets a day to manage their condition" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 bNNNXy inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-482ou5-1 cFynzd dcZiNS" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base-light"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-ohzviw-0 klhTsW inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-187185"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-ohzviw-1 bDzDal"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 fWLHSZ hfwDDP"&gt;Some Parkinson’s patients can take more than 20 tablets a day to manage their condition&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 eUTWtv"&gt; (PA)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the &lt;a href="/news/health/parkinsons-disease-bood-test-symptoms-b2564686.html"&gt;hallmarks of Parkinson’s &lt;/a&gt;is the death of brain cells. Around 50 million cells die and are replaced in the human body every minute. But, unlike other cells in the body, when brain cells die, the rate at which they are replaced is extremely low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When mitochondria are damaged, they stop making energy and release toxins into the cell. In a healthy person, the damaged cells are disposed of in a process called mitophagy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a person with Parkinson’s and a PINK1 mutation, the mitophagy process no longer functions correctly and toxins accumulate in the cell, eventually killing it. Brain cells need a lot of energy and are especially sensitive to this damage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In particular, PINK1 has been linked to young-onset Parkinson’s Disease, which affects people under the age of 50. Despite the known link, researchers have previously been unable to visualise the protein or how it works.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is a significant milestone for research into &lt;a href="/topic/parkinsons"&gt;Parkinson’s&lt;/a&gt;. It is incredible to finally see PINK1 and understand how it binds to mitochondria,” said Professor David Komander, corresponding author on the study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our structure reveals many new ways to change PINK1, essentially switching it on, which will be life-changing for people with Parkinson’s,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lead author on the study, Dr Sylvie Callegari, said PINK1 works in four distinct steps, with the first two steps not having been seen before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, PINK1 senses mitochondrial damage. Then, it attaches to damaged mitochondria. Once attached, it links to a protein called Parkin so that the damaged mitochondria can be recycled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is the first time we’ve seen human PINK1 docked to the surface of damaged mitochondria, and it has uncovered a remarkable array of proteins that act as the docking site. We also saw, for the first time, how mutations present in people with Parkinson’s disease affect human PINK1,” said Dr Callegari.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea of using PINK1 as a target for potential drug therapies has long been touted but not yet achieved because the structure of PINK1 and how it attaches to damaged mitochondria were unknown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team hope to use the knowledge to find a drug to slow or &lt;a href="/news/science/parkinsons-people-university-of-oxford-university-of-cambridge-bordeaux-b2522960.html"&gt;stop Parkinson’s&lt;/a&gt; in people with a PINK1 mutation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers in the UK also believe the discovery could lead to better drug design. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consultant neurologist Dr Richard Ellis said: “It is a crucial step towards understanding the impact of PINK1 in Parkinson’s disease. These observations may hopefully create new opportunities for developing novel strategies for slowing the progression of Parkinson’s disease.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Zhi Yao, research scientist, Life Arc, said: “A robust understanding of these aspects could present a significant opportunity for accelerating drug discovery for Parkinson's disease and potentially other neurodegenerative conditions too.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Becky Jones, research communications manager at Parkinson’s UK, said: “Changes in the PINK1 have long been linked to Parkinson’s, and a specific mutation in the gene that contains the instructions for making the protein are known to cause a rare inherited form of the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-iii" class="sc-looa6c-0 kWYnHL"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s encouraging to see this research, which will help us understand how changes in PINK1 might be causing damage to dopamine-producing brain cells in people with Parkinson’s. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This knowledge unlocks future avenues for better drug design and discovery of a treatment that could slow or even stop Parkinson’s progression. This is vital, as despite it being the fastest growing neurological condition in the world, we don’t yet have any drug treatments that can do this.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 17:12:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxQczBfcTVnRjlFaFdwVU9UQnRVWWQ3bUNIaHg3Nm02dTg3WloxSTRlR1NQRExLQ0s4d3dkR05qcHJ3Q3pfSGdtMVZZRXNHUG94cGtyRXowalVFa2h6TXp4ZlNzQ1hybm8wSEZFNlVoWDNNckpuT251SGlCSjloSDlnd0J3UWVYSG9OVUp5UDNrb3pndw</guid></item><item><title>What Happens to Your Body When You Take CoQ10 Regularly - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMibEFVX3lxTE9iRFFLaC01a3pXTUlHYXVzWlRiNm1FMEw0Y3dDMlp3VENDRDJMVnFiempVY0xOclRmMC1Db1lzTEZfcUxETjNJek9lMVR4REg5aHZfN0ltdTh1NHFvdEE3aW1xYmVrZG9TQWRBeA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-generic" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coenzyme Q10 is naturally produced by the body and found in some foods. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CoQ10 may increase energy, reduce cellular damage and possibly improve heart health. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It is safe for most people except those who are pregnant or breastfeeding. It can also interact with some medications.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Coenzyme Q10 is a substance that’s naturally present in every organ in the body. It’s also found in some foods and is available in supplement form.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;CoQ10 supplements claim to have many health benefits, including increasing energy, keeping your cells healthy, promoting heart health, improving physical performance, preventing migraines and more. Because our natural CoQ10 levels decline with age, it’s also a popular supplement for longevity.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re curious about CoQ10, here’s what you need to know about its potential health benefits, side effects and risks.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-may-increase-energy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; May Increase Energy &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; CoQ10 plays an essential role in energy production. It works by helping our bodies produce a substance called adenosine triphosphate (ATP), which our cells use for energy, explains &lt;a href="https://fullwellfertility.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Ayla Barmmer, M.S., RD, LDN&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian and founder and CEO of the supplement company FullWell. Studies have investigated the effect of CoQ10 supplementation on energy levels with promising results. For instance, one meta-analysis of 13 studies found that taking a CoQ10 supplement reduced fatigue compared to a placebo.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-may-reduce-cell-damage"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; May Reduce Cell Damage &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; CoQ10 may keep your cells healthy in several ways. The first is by acting as an &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/2051586/best-antioxidant-rich-foods/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;antioxidant&lt;/a&gt;. “Antioxidants are like peacekeepers that stabilize free radicals in several ways, including giving the frantic free radical molecules an extra electron,” says Barmmer. That’s not all. “CoQ10 acts as a free radical scavenger, helping to protect cells from damage and reducing inflammation,” says&lt;a href="https://nutritiondigested.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt; Amy Brownstein, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian and owner of Nutrition Digested. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-might-improve-heart-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Might Improve Heart Health &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Heart disease is the leading cause of death in the United States. So, it’s no surprise that supplements touting their heart-health benefits are a popular choice. “CoQ10 is especially important for heart health because the heart requires a lot of energy to pump blood effectively,” says Barmmer. “By supporting energy production and helping to manage oxidative stress, CoQ10 may help maintain healthy heart function.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As encouraging as that is in theory, the National Institutes of Health points out that there is very little research on CoQ10’s ability to prevent heart disease and that the research that does exist is not conclusive.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; In addition, a systematic review of 11 studies concludes that there is no evidence, one way or the other, to suggest that it may guard against heart failure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; On the upside, the NIH says that there is some evidence that it may protect against complications from heart surgery. Some research has also shown that it may help reduce blood pressure. However, more study is needed. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-recommended-dosage"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Recommended Dosage  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Supplements are available in a wide range of doses, typically from 30 to 600 milligrams,” says Barmmer. There’s no single established dose that’s best for everyone. However, many studies have used dosages in the 100 to 200 milligram range. But don’t wing it. “It’s best to follow your health practitioner’s recommendations for individualized advice,” says Barmmer.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-potential-side-effects-and-precautions"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Potential Side Effects and Precautions &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Side effects are possible with any medication or supplement, including CoQ10. However, older research has shown that doses of 900 milligrams per day were as well-tolerated as a placebo.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; Side effects can occur but are usually mild. “Some people may experience digestive issues, dizziness, insomnia, headaches or skin rashes when taking CoQ10,” says&lt;a href="https://inutritioncenter.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt; Vanessa Imus, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian and owner of Integrated Nutrition for Weight Loss. Insomnia has also been reported. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Despite CoQ10’s solid safety record, it may not be suitable for people who are pregnant or breastfeeding. “Since research on its safety during pregnancy is limited, it’s generally recommended to discontinue when pregnancy is confirmed,” says Barmmer. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Additionally, medication interactions are possible when taking CoQ10. “Those who are diabetic or are on blood pressure-lowering meds should use caution, as it could lower blood sugar and blood pressure,” says Imus. Other medications, like blood thinners and chemotherapy drugs, can also interact with CoQ10 supplements. Before adding CoQ10 to your routine, be sure to review all your medications and supplements with your health care provider.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-bottom-line"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Bottom Line &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As we age, our bodies naturally produce less CoQ10. So, it’s easy to assume a supplement will help you feel younger, healthier and more vibrant. However, research on CoQ10 is still evolving. The best evidence is for its ability to increase energy and reduce cellular damage. It may also lower blood pressure and protect against complications from heart surgery, but more study is needed. CoQ10 has mild side effects and is safe for most people (except for those who are pregnant or breastfeeding). However, it can interact with certain medications, especially blood thinners and chemotherapy drugs and may also be problematic for anybody taking medication to lower their blood sugar or blood pressure. As with any supplement, speak with your health care professional before adding CoQ10 to your regimen to make sure it’s safe for you.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-faq mntl-sc-block-universal-faq"&gt;&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-faqs-92e608d5-0fa5-496b-9799-2dcd7fb6d977"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__title"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content mntl-accordion js-accordion"&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="1"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_1-0-section-0"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;What are the benefits of taking CoQ10?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CoQ10 is a powerful antioxidant that reduces oxidative stress and protects against cellular damage. Research finds that taking CoQ10 supplements may increase energy, protect your cells from damage and possibly improve heart health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="2"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_2-0-section-1"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Is it OK to take CoQ10 every day?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_2-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, taking CoQ10 every day has been shown to be safe for most healthy adults. However, it’s unknown if it is safe for people who are pregnant or breastfeeding, due to a lack of research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="3"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_3-0-section-2"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;What is coenzyme Q10 used for?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_3-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CoQ10 is a supplement that may help boost energy levels and promote cellular and cardiovascular health. Since the body’s natural CoQ10 levels decline with age, it is also a popular supplement for longevity. People also take it to improve physical performance, prevent migraines and ease muscle pain from cholesterol-lowering medications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibEFVX3lxTE9iRFFLaC01a3pXTUlHYXVzWlRiNm1FMEw0Y3dDMlp3VENDRDJMVnFiempVY0xOclRmMC1Db1lzTEZfcUxETjNJek9lMVR4REg5aHZfN0ltdTh1NHFvdEE3aW1xYmVrZG9TQWRBeA</guid></item><item><title>Keeping With Kennedy’s Advice, Measles Patients Turn to Unproven Treatments - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMid0FVX3lxTE85VnRIUjQ0SWhaV3ZBWTZVSDZId2E0enQweC11S0xldE4wWUxScXJFN0NjZFA0b0tJdWJRTjBHY3VCai1SanNoU3NXQkxRR3p1RHNXUU9CVnJsZ21QRjBCZjlaLV9qSU5QSkRfWndfMkRjM1AyMjNR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Struggling to contain a raging measles epidemic in West Texas, public health officials increasingly worry that residents are relying on unproven remedies endorsed by Robert F. Kennedy Jr., the health secretary, and postponing doctor visits until the illness has worsened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Hospitals and officials &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.facebook.com/story.php?story_fbid=1193400659464206&amp;amp;id=100063828481984&amp;amp;_rd" title="" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;sounded an alarm this week&lt;/a&gt;, issuing a notice explaining which measles symptoms warranted immediate medical attention and stressing the importance of timely treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;&lt;strong class="css-8qgvsz ebyp5n10"&gt;“&lt;/strong&gt;I’m worried we have kids and parents that are taking all of these other medications and then delaying care,” said Katherine Wells, director of public health in Lubbock, Texas, where many of the sickest children in this outbreak have been hospitalized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Some seriously ill children had been given alternative remedies like cod liver oil, she added. “If they’re so, so sick and have low oxygen levels, they should have been in the hospital a day or two earlier,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-1"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The growing outbreak has spread to nearly 260&lt;strong class="css-8qgvsz ebyp5n10"&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;people in Texas. So far, 34 patients have been hospitalized, and one child has died. In neighboring New Mexico counties, the virus has sickened 35 and hospitalized two. Two cases in Oklahoma have also been &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://oklahoma.gov/health/news---events/newsroom/2025/first-cases-of-measles-in-oklahoma-reported.html" title="" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;linked to the outbreak&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Texas health officials believe the true number of cases is far higher. In all, there have been 301 measles cases in the United States this year, the highest number since 2019, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported on Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 16:09:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE85VnRIUjQ0SWhaV3ZBWTZVSDZId2E0enQweC11S0xldE4wWUxScXJFN0NjZFA0b0tJdWJRTjBHY3VCai1SanNoU3NXQkxRR3p1RHNXUU9CVnJsZ21QRjBCZjlaLV9qSU5QSkRfWndfMkRjM1AyMjNR</guid></item><item><title>Cancer Vaccines Are Suddenly Looking Extremely Promising - Futurism</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiaEFVX3lxTE1KdG1DaGV0S2sxUm1YZFhvSEYyazhpSUREaUFfaVp6VWtyN29mNl85VlZHOE9XVllkcXBpVERHc19TZ3NpaEExRXN0QVJUdUF0ZHVVVGpRN0xFTU9UT1I3c3N6eVFsY0ZD?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section id="incArticle" class="post-content z-50 w-full p-3 space-y-4 bg-white border lg:-mt-6 md:p-4 md:border-gray-900 lg:ml-3 lg:w-2/3 font-b text-3"&gt;&lt;div class="space-y-4 lg:space-y-0"&gt;&lt;p class="block text-xs text-gray-500 uppercase lg:hidden font-c"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image by Getty / Futurism&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the help of mRNA technology proven effective during the COVID pandemic, researchers are now closer than ever to creating viable cancer vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/wired-health-lennard-lee-cancer-vaccines/" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;interview with &lt;em&gt;Wired&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Lennard Lee, an oncologist with the United Kingdom's National Health Service (NHS) working on mRNA cancer vaccines, says he believes the groundbreaking research may prove to be a "silver lining" in the brutal COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before COVID, as Lee told the magazine, "cancer vaccines weren’t a proper field of research."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Pretty much every clinical trial had failed," the NHS oncologist said. "With the pandemic, however, we proved that mRNA vaccines were possible."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As with mRNA COVID vaccines, the logistics of these potential new cancer inoculations work by "giving the body instructions" to fight troublesome cells, as Lee detailed, ultimately providing the immune system with a how-to manual on fighting cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Going from mRNA Covid vaccines to mRNA cancer vaccines is straightforward," he told &lt;em&gt;Wired&lt;/em&gt;. "Same fridges, same protocol, same drug, just a different patient."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of the one-size-fits-all approach taken with the widespread usage of mRNA COVID jabs, however, these new cancer vaccines will be personalized for each individual cancer patient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In the current trials," Lee elucidated, "we do a biopsy of the patient, sequence the tissue, send it to the pharmaceutical company, and they design a personalized vaccine that’s bespoke to that patient’s cancer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That vaccine is not suitable for anyone else," he recounted to the magazine. "It’s like science fiction."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Lee, breakthrough cancer vaccine innovation came on the heels of the UK's rapid infrastructure-building during the COVID pandemic, which saw the country "open and deliver clinical trials" much faster than anyone would have expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As COVID began winding down in 2022, Lee and his colleagues set up the Cancer Vaccine Launch Pad, a post-pandemic pet project that segued mRNA research into the arena of oncology. Not long after, "the dominoes started falling very quickly" as that project and others around the world rapidly progressed towards cancer vaccines. One NHS trial seeking to stop skin cancer from coming back was completed a year early — something that's "completely unheard of," Lee said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The NHS oncologist told &lt;em&gt;Wired&lt;/em&gt; that the results from that trial should come out by the end of this year or the beginning of 2026. If it was successful, Lee told &lt;em&gt;Wired&lt;/em&gt;, he and his team "will have invented the first approved personalized mRNA vaccine — an impressive feat indeed, especially this soon after the technology was deployed at scale during the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on the cancer vax: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/first-ovarian-cancer-vaccine" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Groundbreaking Ovarian Cancer Vaccine at an "Exciting" Moment, Lead Scientist Says&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 16:00:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiaEFVX3lxTE1KdG1DaGV0S2sxUm1YZFhvSEYyazhpSUREaUFfaVp6VWtyN29mNl85VlZHOE9XVllkcXBpVERHc19TZ3NpaEExRXN0QVJUdUF0ZHVVVGpRN0xFTU9UT1I3c3N6eVFsY0ZD</guid></item><item><title>My Friend Swears She Saw My Husband Cheating On Me. But She Only Spotted One, Uh, Body Part. - Slate</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihAFBVV95cUxPanlYWm1lcnhvVGJseVZHcGpTN00zb3lodjlnZzVNTGFpckhIaXFHclNJTHpTaXBkZmxYZGxGUlhweW44b1VoRS1ITUlFZVFXeU1RTHh3MDlsZHlEUUpLdFZZYlQ3VlhacWQ5NHJDNUlzTmdnaFkxNzdYZEZ2dlhPSjdhU2c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89dbj13002cw0kr0bxt1c3j@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Jessica and Rich here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89dfddt002r3b724pt8kxpf@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="44" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89df4em002g3b729btxpe5m@published"&gt;My best friend “Megan” recently attended a sex party. Not long afterward, she called to tell me she was “pretty sure” my husband “Dave” is cheating on me. Except, the story she told me is so insane and unbelievable that I don’t know what think.&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="108" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89dfjo6002w3b72bh2uz2bx@published"&gt;When I asked her what would make her think he was cheating, she said that the invitation to the party requested all the women arrive ahead of the men for the purpose of a game called “Who’s Who.” When she got there, the hosts had the women assemble in the living room where a sheet with a hole cut in it was hung to completely cover the living room doorway. Then when the men arrived, they took turns putting their dicks through the hole in the sheet and the women tried to guess who each man was before the party began. Megan said my husband’s name came up three times!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="43" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89df4i4002h3b72mge4mup3@published"&gt;Dave and I do not have an open marriage, nor do we attend those kinds of events, so there is no other conclusion to draw other than my husband must be cheating on me. How do I go about confronting him with this revelation?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89df4lm002i3b72j0ljqmb0@published"&gt;—Game Over&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89df4os002j3b72m7vywstj@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Game Over,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="70" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89dhugh00373b725fujido4@published"&gt;I don’t know what kind of party this was, but from your question, it seems like both first and last names came up during the guessing segment. That is extremely indiscreet for a sex party, but if there’s any ambiguity at all, your first step should be checking with Megan to make sure it was indeed your husband Dave who was identified (there are a lot of people named “Dave.”)&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="87" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89mevoq000l3b72py1wlau5@published"&gt;I have to tell you that this scenario is, at minimum, unconventional. I’ve never heard of this game, I’m not sure how or why it’s played (is the gag that the partygoers have seen these dicks before, but not generally in their flaccid state, so that’s the challenge?). Could Megan have information that she’s not sharing with you? Could it be that she knows Dave is cheating on you but has changed key (or perhaps all) the details in the story to protect herself? It’s all confusing.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="72" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89mf77b000p3b72mfif0c9w@published"&gt;I’m going to recommend getting more information out of Megan. Can she describe any of the dicks attributed to Dave? Maybe there’s more to tease out of this that will help clear things up. Can Megan put you in touch with someone else who was there and may have a different perspective/better means of articulating the scenario? It’s really tough to present someone with a story this convoluted as evidence of wrongdoing.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="128" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89df4wx002l3b72q6je1dwf@published"&gt;If and when (emphasis on the if) you are &lt;em&gt;sure&lt;/em&gt; sure, I think the best and most direct way to go about doing this is to tell him what you heard. Instead of introducing it as ironclad proof that he’s cheating on you, set up the scenario much as you did in this letter: Your friend (whether you want to identify Megan or not is your call) went to a sex party, and Dave’s name was mentioned several times as a possible attendee. Ask him why and listen to his answer. It might help to, ahead of confronting him, think about how he might explain himself out of the situation or even possible scenarios in which he isn’t cheating. I can’t think of any, but maybe you can.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="186" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89df500002m3b72vpfat7dn@published"&gt;The idea is to be prepared and not accept bullshit, but also not to get so wrapped up in Megan’s story that you can’t receive Dave’s. He might have a verifiable alibi! If he doesn’t, there’s some chance he’ll confess when presented with the evidence. If the conversation gets too heated to continue but you are unconvinced of an explanation he’s trotted out, let him know that you don’t believe him and that you’ll pick this conversation up later. It’s astounding to consider that your partner would be so brazen as to cheat on you at sex parties that are close enough to your circle (in proximity and social overlap) that your best friend would also be in this scene, but some people really are that brazen. I worry that if he’s willing to do that, he’ll also lie right to your face and never come clean. You can’t make someone tell you the truth, but you can let him know that you don’t believe his lies. Now is the time to consider what this, if true, will mean for your relationship and your own future.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89dtypr003j3b72rjf8ujf2@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Rich&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cm89dudyg003x3b72wf6bfgzu@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="94" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89dbj13002fw0krcyfcc5wf@published"&gt;The other day, I was looking for my cat under my son’s bed and I found a number of really strange “things.” Not sex toys, like … unidentified objects next to a bottle of olive oil he’d apparently been using for lube. We eventually found out that he was anally masturbating with them. There’s no shame in that, but we want him to be safe, and don’t think he should be using random found objects as sex toys! &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/09/anal-masturbation-sex-education-teen-advice.html"&gt;Is there a way we can talk to him about this without making him feel ashamed?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cm89dxsl000423b727dg19dh2@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Send Us Your Questions About the Workplace!

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="37" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89dxz6h00463b727wx004j5@published"&gt;The columnists behind our new advice column, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/advice/good-job"&gt;Good Job&lt;/a&gt;, want to help you navigate your social dynamics at work. Does your colleague constantly bug you after hours? Has an ill-advised work romance gone awry? &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/DEVPsiDdnLHQVX7h7"&gt;Ask us your question here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxPanlYWm1lcnhvVGJseVZHcGpTN00zb3lodjlnZzVNTGFpckhIaXFHclNJTHpTaXBkZmxYZGxGUlhweW44b1VoRS1ITUlFZVFXeU1RTHh3MDlsZHlEUUpLdFZZYlQ3VlhacWQ5NHJDNUlzTmdnaFkxNzdYZEZ2dlhPSjdhU2c</guid></item><item><title>Man notices strange symptom while eating sandwich, now has few month to live: ‘Am I not chewing it properly’ - Hindustan Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi-AFBVV95cUxPcTQwWjExUHIxSm8yZHUxdmlYR3JOT3ItcHd5WlB1clZfM293QVFzVkgzeWFTMU1GVlJlRUdjYUJmOTFaS3hWWnBjck1OempBbG93XzZlTjE1RHV1VjdfZmZQYmxrMFh1SGtlejdmWGZ6bUdfak5KamlZel9FbWVjQm9QLTVsQ2dvUnlIZVVSODM3RlhUcllFVWllQkl1Yk1ELUdNZlBFdHBUbTFXSHJyN1NqRndfWkROQnoyR2xyZDNXeFZRUTNEZk45U0l1QU9oM0hpX1lPSFdBNHRxa0lhdXNfVVJHZGtOdVRvblpCTE5mdXpOelkzOQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/trending/man-notices-strange-symptom-while-eating-sandwich-now-has-few-month-to-live-am-i-not-chewing-it-properly-101742033433074.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;What seemed like a routine meal turned into a life-changing moment for Des Longstaff, 39. Struggling to swallow a bacon and sausage sandwich, he sought medical help—only to be diagnosed with advanced stage-four oesophageal adenocarcinoma, an aggressive cancer that has spread to his liver, reported the &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/i-noticed-weird-symptom-eating-34866366" target="_blank" class="manualbacklink"&gt;Mirror&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/03/15/550x309/akjbakcna_1742034086265_1742034091076.png" alt=" He visited a doctor, who advised him to undergo an endoscopy.(Pexel)" title=" He visited a doctor, who advised him to undergo an endoscopy.(Pexel)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/03/15/550x309/akjbakcna_1742034086265_1742034091076.png" alt=" He visited a doctor, who advised him to undergo an endoscopy.(Pexel)" title=" He visited a doctor, who advised him to undergo an endoscopy.(Pexel)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;He visited a doctor, who advised him to undergo an endoscopy.(Pexel)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The landscape contractor, determined to prolong his time with his five-year-old son, is now exploring alternative treatments to fight the disease. According to Cancer Research UK, oesophageal cancer at this stage is typically incurable, but Longstaff is seeking every possible option to extend his life.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="shortEntryContainer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Recalling the moment he first noticed something was wrong, he told &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.bristolpost.co.uk/news/health/dad-battling-silent-killer-months-10025270" target="_blank" class="manualbacklink"&gt;BristolLive&lt;/a&gt;: “I am a landscaper by trade, and I was doing a job for one of my friends when his partner made me a bacon and sausage sandwich. When I was eating it – I hadn’t put any sauce on or anything – it sort of got lodged in my oesophagus, and I had a good pint of water, but it still wouldn’t budge.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“It was to the point where you’re thinking you’re choking. I thought to myself, ‘Am I not chewing it properly?’”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Diagnosis&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following this incident, Longstaff visited a doctor, who advised him to undergo an endoscopy. However, before the procedure could take place, he began vomiting blood and later noticed blood in his stool. He was immediately sent to the hospital, where a 35cm tumour was discovered in his lower oesophagus on Christmas Eve.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Initially, he had hoped for keyhole surgery to remove the tumour, but further scans revealed that the cancer had already spread to his liver, severely limiting his treatment options.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Longstaff has since begun immunotherapy to help his body’s white blood cells fight the cancer, along with another form of chemotherapy. However, he acknowledges that these treatments are not curative. “It is palliative, and it is to keep me comfortable so I don’t die straight away,” he said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“I couldn’t have knocked it back. It is something to attack the cancer; otherwise, it is going to spread all over the place. The NHS has only given me 12 months to live.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;His mother, Tracy, has launched a GoFundMe campaign to raise money for treatment in Germany, where he hopes to receive specialised care. “Des is unable to work and will not be able to for the foreseeable future. We are exploring new treatments in Germany to give Des the best chance of a five-year-plus life expectancy,” she wrote.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The fundraiser has already collected over £31,000, with the targeted amount set at £43,000. The proposed treatment, which costs €52,000 (approximately &lt;span class="webrupee"&gt;₹&lt;/span&gt;46.5 lakh), involves a combination of therapies aimed at targeting the cancerous cells in his liver.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Longstaff remains hopeful about the medical approach in Germany, explaining, “They have a totally different outlook. They have one of the best treatment plans over there, and there is no such thing as terminal. If you are terminal, you are riddled with it, but I’m not. It has stayed localised, and at the moment, I have two small dots, and they are going to turn into tumours if I am not careful.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Detailing the treatment plan, he shared, “So the idea is to go to Germany, where they are going to target the liver. It is basically an injection going into the liver that will give me the highest dose of chemotherapy, but it will only target those two dots. They are going to cut off the main artery to the main tumour in my oesophagus and let that die for five days.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“They will then cut it out and scrape around my diaphragm and around my stomach lining, but they will build the stomach lining up by putting mesh a…&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 15:00:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-AFBVV95cUxPcTQwWjExUHIxSm8yZHUxdmlYR3JOT3ItcHd5WlB1clZfM293QVFzVkgzeWFTMU1GVlJlRUdjYUJmOTFaS3hWWnBjck1OempBbG93XzZlTjE1RHV1VjdfZmZQYmxrMFh1SGtlejdmWGZ6bUdfak5KamlZel9FbWVjQm9QLTVsQ2dvUnlIZVVSODM3RlhUcllFVWllQkl1Yk1ELUdNZlBFdHBUbTFXSHJyN1NqRndfWkROQnoyR2xyZDNXeFZRUTNEZk45U0l1QU9oM0hpX1lPSFdBNHRxa0lhdXNfVVJHZGtOdVRvblpCTE5mdXpOelkzOQ</guid></item><item><title>Opioid orphans: Grandparents struggle to raise children left behind - The Seattle Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwAFBVV95cUxOV1NPQmMzX3pHYUdZUkN4d2pyMG5XdXpjTDRHbWJmSWE0ekNBX2JtZVdNYnR4cDQwRXRPVDR0YnJ4MWdXcnQ0WTNxTlR5V3FGVXlSOHNwUXdsUlVqdWJxUkM1WmRJeWZYR2V5bUlPeU1ySEJEdFZhYlVaUXZ2LUZFNlJaYUh0UUpuTHFab2tyZ29qTzc3cHUyVm5yQXVxX2dVcUo2TXk2RUJzNUo3Nm5keGdtZVlqSXQ4UE1mOG1KTXc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwAFBVV95cUxOV1NPQmMzX3pHYUdZUkN4d2pyMG5XdXpjTDRHbWJmSWE0ekNBX2JtZVdNYnR4cDQwRXRPVDR0YnJ4MWdXcnQ0WTNxTlR5V3FGVXlSOHNwUXdsUlVqdWJxUkM1WmRJeWZYR2V5bUlPeU1ySEJEdFZhYlVaUXZ2LUZFNlJaYUh0UUpuTHFab2tyZ29qTzc3cHUyVm5yQXVxX2dVcUo2TXk2RUJzNUo3Nm5keGdtZVlqSXQ4UE1mOG1KTXc?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Opioid orphans: Grandparents struggle to raise children left behind&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxOV1NPQmMzX3pHYUdZUkN4d2pyMG5XdXpjTDRHbWJmSWE0ekNBX2JtZVdNYnR4cDQwRXRPVDR0YnJ4MWdXcnQ0WTNxTlR5V3FGVXlSOHNwUXdsUlVqdWJxUkM1WmRJeWZYR2V5bUlPeU1ySEJEdFZhYlVaUXZ2LUZFNlJaYUh0UUpuTHFab2tyZ29qTzc3cHUyVm5yQXVxX2dVcUo2TXk2RUJzNUo3Nm5keGdtZVlqSXQ4UE1mOG1KTXc</guid></item><item><title>4 foods a top nutrition expert avoids at all costs, and one sweet treat he eats regularly - Fortune</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNTHFhWkF1empTNU1OYm5aRzVnd2hzcWxrUkpGS0RnLW1HVVlfNExQbnZ6b3NYMXRuRDFIeW9vZGNaeUZoNWxQWnBNWWZJREgtdFBnbUtlbjFlOV9OalFJcm44dXFqQlI5aDRfaUlrLXZNckdhRDc4cFAtZlZBOUtWVmxBamQ1M0FqNmh3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-cy="article-image" class="sc-fac7c12f-7 ifTevn"&gt;&lt;img alt="happy african american man holding plate of chips and eating snacks from potatoes on yellow isolated background, guy in white t-shirt eats fast food" data-content-placement="primary_image" fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" class="impression-element" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=320&amp;amp;q=75 320w, https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=384&amp;amp;q=75 384w, https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=480&amp;amp;q=75 480w, https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=576&amp;amp;q=75 576w, https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=768&amp;amp;q=75 768w, https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=1024&amp;amp;q=75 1024w, https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=1280&amp;amp;q=75 1280w, https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=1440&amp;amp;q=75 1440w" src="https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=1440&amp;amp;q=75"&gt;&lt;p data-cy="caption" class="sc-13b6974d-9 dKtuAn"&gt;The mixture of fat, sugars, and salt combined with a texture that almost dissolves in your mouth can make it hard to stop eating certain foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-cy="credit" class="sc-13b6974d-10 hbPqHz"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fortune</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 13:42:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNTHFhWkF1empTNU1OYm5aRzVnd2hzcWxrUkpGS0RnLW1HVVlfNExQbnZ6b3NYMXRuRDFIeW9vZGNaeUZoNWxQWnBNWWZJREgtdFBnbUtlbjFlOV9OalFJcm44dXFqQlI5aDRfaUlrLXZNckdhRDc4cFAtZlZBOUtWVmxBamQ1M0FqNmh3</guid></item><item><title>Creatine: Overall Health Benefits, Supplements and the Right Dosage - CNET</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijwFBVV95cUxOOG9PM0paaG85WkNDTXZtRnF1dUFhWmdmWlRXYVZkQ2xpX2o3TFRJcjF3TGZtT0tpYi1FVkZ3bVFTYVVyYTVPb0ZtLWJoMWQ3QUs2ajdXVms2dHlPVGVNbi1fR2E1VnNJdzlqRUdBWldka3pXVW50YXpLRXFOSGdIbDc1eGZnMTVMR0paUk0tUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="c-ShortcodeContent c-ShortcodeContent-theme:default sm:u-col-2 md:u-col-6 lg:u-col-12"&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p1"&gt;If you look in the supplement aisle at your local pharmacy, you'll likely find different forms of creatine such as gummies, powders, capsules and even drink mixes. That's because creatine is a &lt;a href="https://www.cnet.com/health/nutrition/best-creatine-supplements/" target="_self"&gt;popular fitness supplement&lt;/a&gt; for those who want to gain muscle, strength and power while improving performance. It's also naturally made in our bodies and assists our muscles with energy production when we work out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p2"&gt;Though creatine can be found in smaller quantities in foods like salmon, chicken, beef and pork, many people take supplements for fitness benefits. However, did you know that creatine can also have other effects on both your mental and physical health? To learn more, we spoke with experts about creatine's benefits, effects on weight, results and how to choose the right supplement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Creatine benefits for your overall health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although creatine is popular in the fitness space, it has other benefits that the average person can also take advantage of. For example, creatine can help with injury recovery, improve skeletal muscle and has been shown to have a positive impact on the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-small c-shortcodeImage-pullRight"&gt;&lt;a rel href="https://www.cnet.com/health-tips/" target="_blank" class="c-shortcodeImage_imageContainer"&gt;   &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jenna Stangland, a &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jennastangland/" rel="noopener nofollow" target="_blank" title="(opens in a new window)" class="c-regularLink"&gt;registered dietitian&lt;/a&gt;, specialist in sports dietetics and Momentous adviser, says, "Most recently in research, it has been shown that a daily dose of creatine can increase brain creatine levels by 6%." Part of this can be attributed to the &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/10222117/" rel="noopener nofollow" target="_blank" title="(opens in a new window)" class="c-regularLink"&gt;increase of phosphocreatine&lt;/a&gt; in the brain when taking creatine, which can help reduce cognitive neurological diseases. Phosphocreatine is a substance created by our skeletal muscles that &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4898252/#:~:text=Phosphocreatine%20is%20known%20as%20its,as%20a%20temporal%20energy%20buffer.#link={%22role%22:%22standard%22,%22href%22:%22https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4898252/#:~:text=Phosphocreatine%20is%20known%20as%20its,as%20a%20temporal%20energy%20buffer.%22,%22target%22:%22%22,%22absolute%22:%22%22,%22linkText%22:%22created%20by%20our%20skeletal%20muscles%20that%20serves%20as%20a%20buffer%20to%20maintain%20an%20energy%20form%22}" rel="noopener nofollow" target="_blank" title="(opens in a new window)" class="c-regularLink"&gt;serves as a buffer&lt;/a&gt; to maintain an energy form created by the cells called adenosine triphosphate (ATP).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-all-top spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stangland adds that creatine may even have a &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7916590/" rel="noopener nofollow" target="_blank" title="(opens in a new window)" class="c-regularLink"&gt;positive effect on your mental health&lt;/a&gt;. "It was found that when there are smaller amounts of white matter creatine and phosphocreatine in the brain, more severe depressive episodes occur," she said. Therefore, taking creatine can increase that white matter and, as a result, improve your mental state. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Creatine has also been shown to have an effect on mood, according to Strangland, by promoting brain energy levels, particularly for women. "Females have &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7998865/#:~:text=Females%20have%20been%20reported%20to,cognition%2C%20memory%2C%20and%20emotion." rel="noopener nofollow" target="_blank" title="(opens in a new window)" class="c-regularLink"&gt;lower creatine stores within the brain&lt;/a&gt; -- about 70% to 80% -- compared to males, especially in the frontal lobe, so this is an area where females especially benefit from taking creatine daily," she said. The brain's frontal lobe is known to control mood, cognition, memory and emotion. Supplementing with creatine could positively impact this part of the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;Viktor Kolmakov/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to choose a creatine supplement&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you can imagine, the supplement market is flooded with different products, many of which are questionable in nature. This is because the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/food/information-consumers-using-dietary-supplements/questions-and-answers-dietary-supplements#:~:text=The%20Dietary%20Supplement%20Health%20and%20Education%20Act%20(DSHEA)%20amended%20the,supplements%20before%20they%20are%20marketed.#link={" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" title="(opens in a new window)" class="c-regularLink"&gt;doesn't regulate dietary supplements&lt;/a&gt; for effectiveness or safety. You'll come across three different types of creatine at your supplement shop: creatine monohydrate, creatine ethyl ester and creatine hydrochloride. Of the three, creatine monohydrate is the most popular version and has proven to help people achieve their fitness goals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although creatine is a popular and well-known supplement, it's still important to be cautious when picking one out. Chrissy Arsenault, head registered dietitian consultant at &lt;a href="https://traineracademy.org/author/chrissy-arsenault/" rel="noopener nofollow" target="_blank" title="(opens in a new window)" class="c-regularLink"&gt;Trainer Academy&lt;/a&gt;, advises, "I recommend that consumers look for a brand that is reputable and third-party tested when picking a creatine." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stangland says that the ingredients section should read only creatine monohydrate, and there should not be any mention of other preservatives, additives, binders, etc. You'll find creatine monohydrate, either in powdered or capsule form, flavored or unflavored, at your vitamin store, so you can pick based on your preference. Other forms include creatine gummy and drink mixes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to take creatine to support your fitness goals&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another thing to look out for on a container of creatine is that one serving equals 5 grams. "In the serving size, you want to see that one serving is a 5-gram scoop so you can adequately scoop the recommended dose," Stangland said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How much you should take will also depend on your own goals. For example, if your goal is to build strength or muscle gain, Arsenault recommends taking at least 3 to 5 grams of creatine monohydrate daily. She adds, "For optimal absorption, aim for 20 grams divided into four daily intakes of 5 grams in combination with carbohydrate and protein."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If weight loss is your main focus, you can follow the abovementioned guidelines. "Creatine can help preserve muscle mass during calorie restriction, but listen to your body as you know it best and adjust as needed," Arsenault said. For example, some people may experience bloating and want to decrease the dosage. On the other hand, if you don't notice a difference in your "pump," you may want to increase the dosage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;Oscar Wong/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Creatine weight gain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some cases, a common side effect is weight gain. However, the weight gain is caused by temporary water retention that eventually subsides. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In the early stages of creatine supplementation, there is a slight increase in total body water when the creatine stores in the muscle increase," Stangland said, adding, "Studies have shown that this is not a long-term side effect and even after training with creatine for five to 10 weeks, the studies showed no increase in total body water." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is this has only been shown short-term or in the first few days of a loading phase of creatine at 20 grams per day. Stangland said that after those first days, the total body water returns to its normal state and hasn't shown any overall weight gain due to creatine supplementation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be mindful to drink your recommended daily water intake when supplementing with creatine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who should avoid creatine?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though creatine is a well-studied supplement and generally safe to take if you don't have any underlying conditions, some people should exercise caution before adding it to their diet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arsenault advises that people with liver disease or edema should first speak to their doctor before taking creatine. "This is because creatine is naturally made in the kidneys and liver," she said. Additionally, if you're pregnant or breastfeeding, you should also consult your doctor before supplementing with it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;Getty Images/ Oleg Breslavtsev&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How long to take creatine before you see results&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As with any supplement, creatine is not going to work overnight. Stangland recommends taking it for a minimum of four weeks to see any actual changes. "This timeframe shows increases in creatine levels in the brain and/or increases in creatine levels in the muscle for improved strength and power," she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep in mind that you may already be getting some creatine in your diet since it's a naturally occurring substance in animal protein such as red meat, chicken and seafood. However, Stangland points out that to get enough creatine from food, one would need to eat two pounds of steak or two-and-a-half pounds of salmon every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you don't see any changes by taking creatine, you might be what is called: a non-responder. "One may be a non-responder due to their biological profile if they have high creatine levels prior to starting supplementation, lower than average fat-free mass and a lower proportion of type 2 muscle fibers," Stangland said. Other circumstances where you may be a non-responder include if you've been using creatine for too long or the creatine levels in your muscles no longer increase as much as they did in the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other circumstances in which you may be a non-responder are if your diet is already heavy in animal protein. "This means that they already get enough creatine for optimal performance and have a high baseline level," Arsenault said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, creatine is a supplement and shouldn't be the only thing you focus on when working toward your fitness goals. Instead, treat it like a tool that can help you achieve them. Ultimately, a healthy diet, a balanced lifestyle, sleeping adequately and exercising regularly will help you have long-term success, no matter your goals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNET</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 13:08:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOOG9PM0paaG85WkNDTXZtRnF1dUFhWmdmWlRXYVZkQ2xpX2o3TFRJcjF3TGZtT0tpYi1FVkZ3bVFTYVVyYTVPb0ZtLWJoMWQ3QUs2ajdXVms2dHlPVGVNbi1fR2E1VnNJdzlqRUdBWldka3pXVW50YXpLRXFOSGdIbDc1eGZnMTVMR0paUk0tUQ</guid></item><item><title>Your Vision Can Predict Dementia 12 Years Before Diagnosis, Study Discovers - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipgFBVV95cUxPQkFYTkg5ZDU5WHdXNVpaNVhrLWd3V1NkSFM0bnV5cHotRHNUeENWcDZPdmdVZzRTbkFnVHFEejNaRE0xRmJGV1VybWJGTEZzTHlpLVh6VWN1MjVjcDVBaVRtdUpQMFE0LWI3dDlSanhadjlIbFVzMXVqX2Y0ekgxUVpWcTRPSnA3U1U1bms5Q016MnhKZEhUSzJaNHJXanZDYW1NR0hR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The eyes can reveal a lot about the health of our brain. Indeed, problems with the eyes can be one of the earliest signs of cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38424122/"&gt;latest study shows&lt;/a&gt; that a loss of visual sensitivity can predict dementia 12 years before it is diagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our research was based on 8,623 healthy people in Norfolk, England, who were followed up for many years. By the end of the study, 537 participants had developed dementia, so we could see what factors might have preceded this diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the start of the study, we asked participants to take a visual sensitivity test. For the test, they had to press a button as soon as they saw a triangle forming in a field of moving dots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who would develop dementia were much slower to see this triangle on the screen than people who would remain without dementia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So why might that be?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visual issues may be an early indicator of cognitive decline as the toxic amyloid plaques associated with  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="154968" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease may first affect areas of the brain associated with vision, with parts of the brain associated with memory becoming damaged as the disease progresses. So vision tests may find deficits before memory tests do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are several &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/20182034/"&gt;other aspects&lt;/a&gt; of visual processing that are affected in Alzheimer's disease, such as the ability to see outlines of objects (contrast sensitivity) and to discern between certain colours (the ability to see the blue-green spectrum is affected early in dementia), and these can affect people's lives without them being immediately aware it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aging-us.com/article/102118/text"&gt;Another&lt;/a&gt; early sign of Alzheimer's is a deficit in the "inhibitory control" of eye movements, where distracting stimuli seem to hold attention more readily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People with Alzheimer's seem to have an issue ignoring distracting stimuli, which may show up as eye-movement-control issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If dementia makes it harder to avoid distracting stimuli, then these problems could increase the risk of &lt;a href="https://www.lboro.ac.uk/news-events/news/2023/october/dementia-driving-project-andrew-morris/"&gt;driving&lt;/a&gt; accidents – something we are currently investigating at Loughborough University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_144904" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-144904" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/EyeBehindTwoFingers642.jpg" alt="An eye with two fingers in the foreground" class="size-full wp-image-144904" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/EyeBehindTwoFingers642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/EyeBehindTwoFingers642-621x415.jpg 621w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/EyeBehindTwoFingers642-600x401.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-144904" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Alzheimer's may show up as eye-movement-control issues. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEiiDPf6j0/"&gt;laurence soulez/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Recognising faces&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have &lt;a href="https://alz-journals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1016/j.jalz.2011.05.419"&gt;some evidence&lt;/a&gt; which suggests that people with dementia tend to process new people's faces inefficiently. In other words, they don't follow the usual pattern of scanning the face of the person they are talking to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In healthy people, this would be from eyes to nose to mouth. We do this to "imprint" the face and remember it for later. People can sometimes sense when the person they are talking to does not do this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fact, some doctors working with people with dementia will recognise that someone has dementia when they meet them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People with dementia can sometimes seem lost, because they do not purposefully move their eyes to scan the environment, including that of the face of the people they have just met.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It would follow that you would then later be less able to recognise people as you have not imprinted their features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So this early issue in not recognising people you have just met could be related to ineffective eye movement for new faces, rather than being a pure memory disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_144903" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-144903" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/SeniorLadyLookingConfused642.jpg" alt="An older lady in a black jacket sitting outdoors" class="size-full wp-image-144903" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/SeniorLadyLookingConfused642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/SeniorLadyLookingConfused642-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/SeniorLadyLookingConfused642-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-144903" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;People with dementia can sometimes seem lost. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEEbnSYr4c/"&gt;ivanastar/Canva)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Can eye movement improve memory?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, as visual sensitivity is related to memory performance (even using non-visual tests), we are also testing whether getting people to do more eye movements helps to improve memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Previous research on the matter is mixed, but some &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33535921/"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; found that eye movement can improve memory. Perhaps that explains why we found that people who &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC8391311/"&gt;watch more TV and read more&lt;/a&gt; have better memory and less dementia risk than those who do not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While watching TV or reading, our eyes flick back and forth over the page and TV screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, people who read often also tend to have been in education longer. Having had good education provides brain reserve capacity so that when connections in the brain are damaged, the negative result is less.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_134632" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-134632" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/08/GroupOfPeopleWatchingTV642.jpg" alt="A group of adults on a couch watching TV" class="size-full wp-image-134632" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/08/GroupOfPeopleWatchingTV642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/08/GroupOfPeopleWatchingTV642-600x337.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-134632" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Could watching TV actually be good for your brain? (&lt;a href="https://www.pexels.com/photo/a-group-of-people-sitting-in-front-of-a-television-23495473/"&gt;Vitaly Gariev/Pexels&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6984731/#:%7E:text=Several%20recent%20studies%20have%20reported,Retrieval%20Enhancement%20(SIRE)%20effect."&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt;, eye movements from left to right and right to left done quickly (two eye movements per second) were found to improve autobiographical memory (your life story).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, some studies suggest this beneficial effect of eye movement only benefits right-handed people. We are not sure why this is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite these exciting findings, treatment for memory problems using deliberate eye movements in older people has not been done that much yet. Also, using deficits in eye movements as a diagnostic is not a regular feature, despite the possibilities in eye movement technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the bottlenecks may be access to eye-tracking technologies, which are expensive and require training to use and analyse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until cheaper and easy-to-use eye trackers are available, using eye movements as a diagnostic tool for early-stage Alzheimer's is not possible outside the laboratory.&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/226356/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/eef-hogervorst-1283596"&gt;Eef Hogervorst&lt;/a&gt;, Professor of Biological Psychology, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/loughborough-university-1336"&gt;Loughborough University&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/ahmet-begde-1521745"&gt;Ahmet Begde&lt;/a&gt;, PhD Candidate, Neurorehabilitation, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/loughborough-university-1336"&gt;Loughborough University&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/thom-wilcockson-1521746"&gt;Thom Wilcockson&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Lecturer in Psychology, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/loughborough-university-1336"&gt;Loughborough University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/how-your-vision-can-predict-dementia-12-years-before-it-is-diagnosed-new-study-226356"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in April 2024.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 13:03:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPQkFYTkg5ZDU5WHdXNVpaNVhrLWd3V1NkSFM0bnV5cHotRHNUeENWcDZPdmdVZzRTbkFnVHFEejNaRE0xRmJGV1VybWJGTEZzTHlpLVh6VWN1MjVjcDVBaVRtdUpQMFE0LWI3dDlSanhadjlIbFVzMXVqX2Y0ekgxUVpWcTRPSnA3U1U1bms5Q016MnhKZEhUSzJaNHJXanZDYW1NR0hR</guid></item><item><title>Can we reverse aging? A bold new approach could reprogram cells - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxOLWZOUk11cnZTeUliSW1OREtKNUpMOS1aWFdNU3JjcWtHQkxYTzQwYXRrSG12ZGdtRG1neFY5ZUJZMmZoOFY0WGl2UGRhS0Rpemo3NjU2c0kyV2d0SVBOVGwta25BR0Q0S3hHMXJpY24zMFVnZmNDZ0Y5eGZGVXlHajQxNlVnV1hZMVRTdS1Ld3JVTHBn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aging can feel like an unstoppable force. Some researchers believe it may one day be slowed or even paused, thanks to an emerging technique known as cellular reprogramming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Curiosity has surrounded this approach since a 2016 mouse experiment at the &lt;a href="https://www.salk.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Salk Institute&lt;/a&gt;, where progeric rodents (that age more rapidly than normal) lived longer after exposure to four genes that could rewrite &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/defying-time-three-ways-to-slow-biological-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;cellular aging&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucy Xu, a postdoctoral research fellow at &lt;a href="https://oto.hms.harvard.edu/home" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Harvard Medical School&lt;/a&gt;, has followed these findings closely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-reprogramming-changes-aging-cells"&gt;How reprogramming changes aging cells&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every mammalian cell contains &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-discover-a-protein-that-reverses-cellular-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;DNA&lt;/a&gt;. However, the DNA in your heart cells behaves differently than it does in your skin cells because of the &lt;a href="https://www.genome.gov/genetics-glossary/Epigenome" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;epigenome&lt;/a&gt;, an outer layer affected by &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/scitable/topicpage/the-role-of-methylation-in-gene-expression-1070/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;methylation&lt;/a&gt; patterns that can turn genes on or off. Over a lifetime, methylation shifts with diet, pollution, exercise, and stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/22056670/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Scientists&lt;/a&gt; discovered that activating &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/cr200759" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;four reprogramming genes&lt;/a&gt;, named after Shinya Yamanaka, can strip away large portions of these methyl marks. This can reset cells to an earlier, more flexible state, which can be good or dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-potential-and-pitfalls"&gt;Potential and pitfalls&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Animal studies have linked complete reprogramming to &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/22074-teratoma" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;teratomas&lt;/a&gt;, which are bizarre growths that sprout tissues like teeth and hair in odd places.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In one early mouse experiment by &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nature12586/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Spanish researchers&lt;/a&gt;, “many of the animals died within weeks,” which reveals just how risky total cellular regression can be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In partial reprogramming, researchers use fewer &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/cr2008309" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Yamanaka genes&lt;/a&gt; or cycle them briefly to avoid pushing cells back into a stem cell state. This less-extreme version aims to refresh &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/organ-aging-can-predict-diseases-decades-in-advance/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;cells&lt;/a&gt; while preserving their identity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-safety-is-a-concern"&gt;Why safety is a concern&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I don’t believe there can be reprogramming. You’re practically telling these cells to become cancer,” said Charles Brenner, a scientist at &lt;a href="https://www.cityofhope.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;City of Hope&lt;/a&gt; research center in Duarte, California. Creating extra stem-like cells might be a path to fierce cancers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To reduce the odds of uncontrolled cell growth, some scientists use a well-known antibiotic to control gene activity. They turn it on briefly, then shut it off. The hope is that this approach rejuvenates tissues without allowing runaway &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/daily-doctor-recommended-regimen-that-could-slow-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;cell&lt;/a&gt; division.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-reprogramming-cells-in-aging-tissues"&gt;Reprogramming cells in aging tissues&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-020-2975-4%5C" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Research&lt;/a&gt; from Harvard in 2020 showed promise by focusing on eye tissues in older mice. David Sinclair, a Harvard geneticist who worked on the study, used only three of the original four genes – removing the one most associated with tumors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A biotech company, &lt;a href="https://www.lifebiosciences.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Life Biosciences&lt;/a&gt;, has advanced this strategy by testing partial cell reprogramming on monkeys with eye damage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm plans to apply for permission to do the same in people who have suffered sudden optic nerve strokes, believing the &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-024-44740-2" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;antibiotic-switch method&lt;/a&gt; is safer than previous attempts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-a-closer-look-at-aging-itself"&gt;A closer look at aging itself&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While eye tissues seem like a controlled starting point, some labs also hope to apply partial &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-discover-the-cellular-mortality-timer-that-dictates-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;reprogramming&lt;/a&gt; more broadly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A follow-up &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s43587-022-00183-2" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;project&lt;/a&gt; at the Salk Institute used carefully timed reprogramming in mice with extra copies of reprogramming genes. Tumors were less common, and some tissues showed younger biological markers, although lifespans did not increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those results fuel speculation that certain organs, such as the brain, might benefit from partial reprogramming. Investigations at Stanford University &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s43587-024-00594-3" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;tested&lt;/a&gt; this approach in mice, aiming to improve brain aging. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The targeted reprogramming boosted newly formed neurons, though the mice had an uptick in inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-many-questions-remain"&gt;Many questions remain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The technique still prompts concerns about long-term effects and who will have access if human trials succeed. Some fear only people with deep pockets may benefit initially. Others wonder if reprogramming might lead to costly or risky treatments that never live up to the hype.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some scientists remain optimistic. They believe partial reprogramming might transform eye disease care, and later, other age-related problems. They acknowledge that verifying safety is key and that any therapy for aging must pass rigorous testing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life Biosciences expects to begin clinical trials in the near future, and will use partial &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/random-dna-mutations-shape-biological-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;reprogramming&lt;/a&gt; to help certain adults who suffer acute optic nerve issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analysts say these initial results will guide future work. If the therapy shows no tumors or unexpected complications, it could open a path for new treatments targeting age-related loss of function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I worry about the speed,” Xu said, noting that more questions need answers before the technology expands beyond small clinical studies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-future-of-reprogramming-cells"&gt;Future of reprogramming cells&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one knows whether these methods will eventually slow or alter aging in humans. Undeterred, investors hope partial reprogramming can become a novel strategy for a range of conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research continues across universities and startups. Many experts see partial reprogramming as a step forward, as long as scientists can balance rejuvenation with safety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others warn that tampering with cellular identity may unleash problems we can’t yet predict. Even so, interest in these trials keeps growing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s43587-024-00594-3" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/eric-ralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 12:59:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOLWZOUk11cnZTeUliSW1OREtKNUpMOS1aWFdNU3JjcWtHQkxYTzQwYXRrSG12ZGdtRG1neFY5ZUJZMmZoOFY0WGl2UGRhS0Rpemo3NjU2c0kyV2d0SVBOVGwta25BR0Q0S3hHMXJpY24zMFVnZmNDZ0Y5eGZGVXlHajQxNlVnV1hZMVRTdS1Ld3JVTHBn</guid></item><item><title>Researchers tie health of nine organs to diseases later in life - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxOYjVMLWQzUVZKZnRsT1dFTkE1MldHRFM4WEZ2QnlyQm92ZGsya1BvdGdzQkdLUGIyRnV2TVpOZ0xoNGQ3NGVteXpMQTNhYWhzZ0k0aWlOV1VRZUtQeE5PUVM0ME9yb1NoU1VEenNvcm9Ub3NoS2pLZ1RmTHQzU21pZTloN0lSckg2aUxV?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6ZTVOSCMBVDSHNWRH32OW5VEB4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;How old are your organs? The answer might not match your chronological age — and a new analysis finds that an organ’s biological age might predict a person’s risk of diseases such as cancer, dementia and heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JNNLFZZ65VA4TLRDY2DW5YDR3U" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landig.2025.01.006" target="_blank"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt;, published in the Lancet Digital Health, analyzed data from &lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/psychiatry/research/mental-health-older-people/whitehall-ii" target="_blank"&gt;Whitehall II&lt;/a&gt;, a long-running British study of aging that has followed over 10,000 British adults for more than 35 years. Between 1997 and 1999, the Whitehall study took blood plasma samples from participants when they were 45 to 69 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KBNZARKLAJBOHAAA4FWLM45NYQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The current study analyzed those blood samples as well as follow-up data for 6,235 Whitehall participants, who were by then ages 65 to 89. The researchers used the analysis to help measure the gap between a person’s age and the biological age of nine of their organs: heart, blood vessels, liver, immune system, pancreas, kidneys, lungs, intestines and brain. Then they looked at follow-up data that showed the kinds of diseases participants developed as they aged over the next two decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GM6ZKVU2ZZBBXEXTD4JN724TGY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The organs aged at different rates in different people and even within the body, the researchers write — and those with “fast-aging” organs had an increased risk of 30 of the 45 age-related diseases studied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="Q4WSQIPYIZBSXAYM2X4SOKK7XA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Some of the associations linked faster aging organs to diseases in that organ; for example, those with accelerated lung aging were likelier to develop respiratory diseases during the 20-year follow-up period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SPEETKC4TNDZDPP6ALIVWWEE6U" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But in other cases, the link was not as direct. Faster aging of the kidneys, in particular, was linked to diseases of the kidneys and other organs, such as the liver and pancreas, and accelerated aging of multiple organs in the body increased kidney disease risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GJK4UN5LKJGE5EHZRMGUY2MLLA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“Surprisingly,” the researchers say, dementia was not best predicted by accelerated brain aging, but rather by the immune system’s biological age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4DUEA3AE3JFQTFZVSWF5DTY4ZQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The researchers say the study shows the promise of an organ-specific blood test, which is simpler than past methods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SP5BTLH25FCTJC4ZFIBVCIPDBA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In a news &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1074868" target="_blank"&gt;release&lt;/a&gt;, lead author Mika Kivimaki, a professor at University College London’s faculty of brain sciences and the study’s lead author, says such tests could one day “advise whether a person needs to take better care of a particular organ, and potentially provide an early-warning signal that they may be at risk of a particular disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h5 class="wpds-c-vXjlY wpds-c-vXjlY-bALvEi-isCenteredLayout-false" data-qa="article-header" data-contentid="S275FEG7KRFNPESUI5OTDR7PUA" data-apitype="header" level="6" id="S275FEG7KRFNPESUI5OTDR7PUA"&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 12:01:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxOYjVMLWQzUVZKZnRsT1dFTkE1MldHRFM4WEZ2QnlyQm92ZGsya1BvdGdzQkdLUGIyRnV2TVpOZ0xoNGQ3NGVteXpMQTNhYWhzZ0k0aWlOV1VRZUtQeE5PUVM0ME9yb1NoU1VEenNvcm9Ub3NoS2pLZ1RmTHQzU21pZTloN0lSckg2aUxV</guid></item><item><title>A mom's sudden pain was a deadly heart condition. An ultrasound on an iPhone helped save her life. - CBS News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikgFBVV95cUxOeVdvcW1sN18yb1RNNnlFQjlJX0R3THpIb2prYUVaTktBT0lPN0pPNGtrU2x6LUY4SnhtQl9SRHVSeFE0eXVsYzkwRzZvWEZJVzhBdWNGMy1yN3hKMU9mSWExODV4dUFudjhMN1FmdGI3bGxISmF1MUdHdDk5aG9WaXlrMFJwMGdqN3o2eVFDOFZhQQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Sara Adair knows the symptoms of aortic dissections. The hospital analyst's father and sister each experienced the dangerous cardiac condition, when the inner lining of the body's main artery tears and causes the aorta to come apart. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aortic dissections can be deadly, and are hard to diagnose. Both Adair's father and sister survived, but after her sister's aortic dissection at the age of 49, Adair was determined to learn why it had happened. She, her father and her sister were diagnosed with Loeys-Dietz syndrome, a rare genetic disorder that affects the body's connective tissues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adair, a mother of two, learned the symptoms, saw a cardiologist and had regular scans of her aorta. There were no warning signs. On July 22, 2024, she spent the afternoon attending sports tournaments and a pool party with her kids. It was just another day in a "super busy weekend," she told CBS News, and she felt "completely normal." When they finally got home at 9 p.m., she sat down to unwind. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"All of a sudden my chest started to hurt. It felt fine all day, completely normal, then just all of a sudden this crushing, horrible, chest pain I'd never felt before," Adair said. "It was long enough for me to think 'Oh, is this really what I think it is?'"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudden chest or back pain that moves into the neck is a key symptom of aortic dissection. It was exactly what had happened to Adair's sister. It was a feeling she had been dreading. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The pain moved up to to my neck, and then I was like, 'Okay, this is it. This is serious,'" she said. "I got up to tell my husband to call 911, but I made it into the living room where he was and just collapsed on the floor." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                            
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/03/14/25b27486-c26f-4ecb-ab73-fa07aab370c6/thumbnail/620x465/f603e5b525d12723c1ad0ec8ae691559/adair-family-pic-1-002.jpg?v=e7f44f50e1cf6b32bb81cbfeaec70acf#" alt="adair-family-pic-1-002.jpg " class=" lazyload" data-srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/03/14/25b27486-c26f-4ecb-ab73-fa07aab370c6/thumbnail/620x465/f603e5b525d12723c1ad0ec8ae691559/adair-family-pic-1-002.jpg?v=e7f44f50e1cf6b32bb81cbfeaec70acf 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/03/14/25b27486-c26f-4ecb-ab73-fa07aab370c6/thumbnail/1240x930/8ddb80a38ff8f32387515a89b5944723/adair-family-pic-1-002.jpg?v=e7f44f50e1cf6b32bb81cbfeaec70acf 2x" srcset="data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg%20xmlns%3D'http%3A%2F%2Fwww.w3.org%2F2000%2Fsvg'%20viewBox%3D'0%200%20620%20465'%2F%3E"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Sara Adair and her family. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Sara Adair

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What is Loeys-Dietz syndrome? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loeys-Dietz syndrome is a rare genetic condition that affects the body's connective tissues. Aortic aneurysms and dissections are a common risk for a person diagnosed with the disorder, said Dr. Hiroo Takayama, the chief of adult cardiac surgery at NewYork-Presbyterian/Columbia University Irving Medical Center. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Managing the condition includes regular cardiology appointments and scans of the heart and aorta. Some patients may be prescribed heart medication, Takayama said, and patients can also receive a surgical treatment called aortic root replacement to prevent tears in the aorta. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost all Loeys-Dietz patients will need surgery on their aorta: It's just a question of if it will be a scheduled preventative procedure or an emergency one, Takayama said.  &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="leader-plus-inc3" data-ad="leader-plus-inc" class="ad-leader-plus-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["leader-plus-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adair had been having regular check-ups, but the tests hadn't showed anything worrisome. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'd gotten all the imaging that I was supposed to, but it just wasn't detectable until it burst," Adair told CBS News. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Making a rapid diagnosis when "time is also ticking"&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though Adair knew what was happening to her, she struggled to communicate it to first responders. Her husband insisted that she be taken to the emergency room at Robert Wood Johnson University Hospital, where she worked. Paramedics conducted a diagnostic test that indicated she was having a "huge heart attack," according to Dr. Partho P. Sengupta, the hospital chief of cardiology who oversaw Adair's care team. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite similar symptoms, the treatment for a heart attack is very different than what a person having an aortic dissection will need, and that's part of what makes aortic dissections so deadly, Sengupta explained. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Over 50% of people (with aortic dissections) never make it to the hospital. Of those who make it to the hospital, their time is also ticking, because with every one-hour you delay getting the right surgery, you have a 1 to 2% increase in mortality," Sengupta said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                            
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/03/14/78edf784-021e-4005-b288-88b7fc6d9066/thumbnail/620x390/81708e3adc3fae566a7af39fde5dd109/screenshot-2025-03-14-at-8-24-28-am.png?v=e7f44f50e1cf6b32bb81cbfeaec70acf#" alt="screenshot-2025-03-14-at-8-24-28-am.png " class=" lazyload" data-srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/03/14/78edf784-021e-4005-b288-88b7fc6d9066/thumbnail/620x390/81708e3adc3fae566a7af39fde5dd109/screenshot-2025-03-14-at-8-24-28-am.png?v=e7f44f50e1cf6b32bb81cbfeaec70acf 1x" srcset="data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg%20xmlns%3D'http%3A%2F%2Fwww.w3.org%2F2000%2Fsvg'%20viewBox%3D'0%200%20620%20390'%2F%3E"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Dr. Partho P. Sengupta indicates the aorta on a scan. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Robert Wood Johnson University Hospital

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the emergency room, a cardiology fellow was able to make the correct diagnosis. Dr. Shawn Chawla,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;who trained under Sengupta, used a point-of-care ultrasound to examine Adair. The device is a probe that plugs into an iPhone, turning the device into a portable ultrasound system. The scan showed the large tear in Adair's aorta, Sengupta said. Adair was sent for a CT scan to confirm the diagnosis, then underwent open-heart surgery performed by cardiac surgeon Dr. Hirohisa Ikegami. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I know it was the ultrasound that I had in the emergency room that saved me," Adair said. "If I had been treated for a heart attack and brought, say, to the cardiac cath lab, or if I didn't go to the CT scan and get the diagnostic tests that I needed, I could have bled out." &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="leader-plus-inc4" data-ad="leader-plus-inc" class="ad-leader-plus-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["leader-plus-inc",4]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Recovering after open-heart surgery  &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adair had collapsed on a Sunday night, and she didn't wake up until Tuesday. She said she barely remembered anything that happened after she fell down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The operation hadn't been without complications. She had had a stroke during surgery, which left her with some weakness in her left arm and slightly blurry vision. Fluid collected around her lungs and heart, creating breathing difficulties. She spent several days in the ICU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                            
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/03/14/dc816cc8-88ab-44c8-991d-595e595e94f2/thumbnail/620x827/f1bd84e20b824081c3260682bf885e2e/sara-icu.jpg?v=e7f44f50e1cf6b32bb81cbfeaec70acf#" alt="sara-icu.jpg " srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/03/14/dc816cc8-88ab-44c8-991d-595e595e94f2/thumbnail/620x827/f1bd84e20b824081c3260682bf885e2e/sara-icu.jpg?v=e7f44f50e1cf6b32bb81cbfeaec70acf 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/03/14/dc816cc8-88ab-44c8-991d-595e595e94f2/thumbnail/1240x1654/49994e160329349147d5d1f3a278890f/sara-icu.jpg?v=e7f44f50e1cf6b32bb81cbfeaec70acf 2x"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Sara Adair in the ICU.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Sara Adair

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even after being released from the hospital, all Adair could think about was the night she collapsed and the terror she felt "knowing exactly what was happening, feeling it going up my neck, and knowing I had a really, really limited amount of time to get the right treatment." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She has spent months in cardiac rehabilitation and has several blood clots that still need to resolve. Despite the setbacks, she considers herself lucky. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think the worst already happened," she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only thing she fears now is what genetic testing for her children and her nieces will show. The kids have appointments scheduled to be tested for Loeys-Dietz syndrome. If necessary, they will start seeing a cardiologist who can monitor their health.&lt;/p&gt;

      

                  
        
      
                  
    

    


    
      
    
  

          
  
        

      &lt;div class="content-author"&gt;
      &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/team/kerry-breen/" class="content-author__name" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Kerry Breen&lt;/a&gt;

      &lt;div class="content-author__bio"&gt;
                  &lt;div class="content-author__full-information"&gt;
            &lt;p class="content-author__text"&gt;Kerry Breen is a news editor at CBSNews.com. A graduate of New York University's Arthur L. Carter School of Journalism, she previously worked at NBC News' TODAY Digital. She covers current events, breaking news and issues including substance use.&lt;/p&gt;
                          
                &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/section&gt;

  
  

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxOeVdvcW1sN18yb1RNNnlFQjlJX0R3THpIb2prYUVaTktBT0lPN0pPNGtrU2x6LUY4SnhtQl9SRHVSeFE0eXVsYzkwRzZvWEZJVzhBdWNGMy1yN3hKMU9mSWExODV4dUFudjhMN1FmdGI3bGxISmF1MUdHdDk5aG9WaXlrMFJwMGdqN3o2eVFDOFZhQQ</guid></item><item><title>The Best 7-Day Walking Plan for Weight Loss, Created by Certified Trainers - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgFBVV95cUxPOXREZm9YMlZpTGdEZk5INnRZUzRoUlJHUmstQjluS2lOeUVEaGNseWxXUm1xSHBrNWRrTzloa1BKa3BQcmdzdzMzWllQZENlOFdyM1dGc3NtN0xObnAtejF3V0tMR2ZnT1lzVEVWbnM2VU5Ec3RhM0RmbzAxcXF3dmxiQ3hhZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-generic" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Walking is an outstanding exercise for weight loss that you can do almost anywhere.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This 7-day walking plan for weight loss provides beginner and intermediate routines.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Aim for 150 weekly minutes of walking at a moderate pace.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Whether you’re walking your dog, walking to work or taking an after-dinner stroll, walking is a step (literally) in the right direction for your health. Especially if weight loss is a goal. Plus, it doesn’t require any expensive equipment, and you can do it almost anywhere. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As effective as walking is for weight management, there isn’t a one-step-fits-all equation. While you might have heard that 10,000 steps per day is the magic number for health, it's not necessarily the amount everybody needs, says &lt;a href="https://www.snackinginsneakers.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Chrissy Carroll, M.P.H., RD, CPT&lt;/a&gt;, a certified personal trainer, running coach and owner of Snacking in Sneakers. “The 10,000-step goal was actually an arbitrary number that came from a marketing campaign from an early pedometer,” she says. “While research has noted that among those who have lost significant amounts of weight, most do get an average of 10,000 steps per day, other studies have shown health benefits can occur at lower step amounts.”&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When it comes to walking for weight loss, it may be more helpful to focus on the amount of time you move than on the number of steps you take. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention recommends at least 150 minutes of moderate-intensity aerobic activity per week, like brisk walking, plus two additional days of muscle-training activities, such as weight lifting or resistance band workouts.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; There’s no hard-and0fast rule for how to fit this in. So, you can break it down however you like to fit it into your lifestyle. Also, keep in mind that the CDC recommendations are for optimal health. Depending on your eating patterns and lifestyle habits, you may need more than the recommended weekly 150 minutes to meet your weight-loss goals. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To get you started, Carroll and I developed this easy-to-follow seven-day walking plan for weight loss (we’re both registered dietitians &lt;em&gt;and &lt;/em&gt;certified personal trainers). Depending on your experience level, you can choose between beginner and intermediate routines.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In addition to walking, we’ve also included strength training to build calorie-burning muscle, plus stretching and active rest sessions to help you recover.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 1 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Beginner: &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;15- to 20-minute walk at a brisk pace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Intermediate: &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;30- to 35-minute walk at a brisk pace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 2 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Beginner: &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;25- to 30-minute walk at a comfortable pace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Intermediate: &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;25- to 30-minute alternating-speed walk (Rotate between 1 minute at a comfortable pace and 1 minute at a fast pace.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 3 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Beginner &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;15-minute walk at a comfortable pace &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Active recovery, such as yoga, stretching or mobility training&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Intermediate: &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;15- to 20-minute walk at a comfortable pace&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Active recovery, such as yoga, stretching or mobility training &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;20 minutes of muscular endurance training such as weight lifting or body-weight exercises &lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 4 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Beginner: &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;15- to 20-minute walk at a brisk pace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Intermediate: &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;45- to 50-minute long walk at a comfortable pace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 5 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Beginner: &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;20- to 25-minute walk at a comfortable pace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Intermediate: &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;30- to 35-minute hill walk (Find a steep hill and walk uphill at a brisk pace. Then, walk downhill at a comfortable pace. Repeat until the workout is complete.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 6 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Beginner: &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;20- to 25-minute alternating-speed walk (Rotate between 1 minute at a comfortable pace and 1 minute at a brisk pace.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Active recovery, such as yoga, stretching or mobility training &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Intermediate: &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span class="ql-cursor"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;15-minute walk at a comfortable pace&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Active recovery, such as yoga, stretching or mobility training &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 7 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Beginner: &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;10-minute walk at a comfortable pace&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Active recovery, such as yoga, stretching or mobility training &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Intermediate: &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_63-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;30-minute walk at a comfortable pace &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;20 minutes of muscular endurance training such as weight lifting or body-weight exercises &lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_64-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-strategies-for-walking-success"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Strategies for Walking Success &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get the Pace Right. &lt;/strong&gt;The CDC defines brisk walking as walking at a 15- to 20-minute per mile pace.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Or, try Carroll’s simple talk test: “A brisk walk is where you could speak some words to a friend next to you, but you wouldn’t be able to sing.”  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Listen to Your Body. &lt;/strong&gt;It can take time to work up to a brisk pace. If you’re not quite there yet, focus on taking a few seconds off your mile pace daily or weekly, checking in with how your body feels. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Break It into Bite-Size Chunks. &lt;/strong&gt;Reaching your weekly 150 minutes can come in many forms. Feel free to break up longer walks into 10- to 15-minute intervals throughout the day. Or, maybe you’d prefer to walk 2 miles per day, 5 days a week, at a 15-minute mile pace. You can also walk more slowly, focusing on hills. Neither one is better than the other. The most important thing is to do it consistently.&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7836693/sneaky-reasons-for-hitting-a-weight-loss-plateau/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add On When You Can. &lt;/strong&gt;Ideally, the goal is to work up to and then exceed the CDC’s recommended 150 weekly minutes. Adding an additional 1 to 5 minutes to your daily walk as your fitness and schedule allow is a great start.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot-inline"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When You’re Ready, Take It to the Next Level. &lt;/strong&gt;If the intermediate plan feels too easy, spice it up by throwing in a hill interval, light jog or extended walk. Better yet, consider a pair of ankle weights to help add some weight training to your sessions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_67-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-walking-can-help-with-weight-loss--health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_68-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Walking Can Help with Weight Loss &amp;amp; Health  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_69-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Weight loss isn’t the only benefit you’ll see once you start walking. Regular exercise, like walking, can improve blood sugar, cardiovascular health, mental health and sleep.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; It may even help you live longer. For instance, one meta-analysis of 15 studies found that people over 60 who walked between 6,000 and 8,000 steps per day and adults under 60 who logged between 8,000 and 10,000 steps daily had a reduced risk of mortality. While a lower risk of death doesn’t necessarily translate into pounds lost, it is certainly a positive move for your health. “Increasing steps from your current baseline will have a major benefit on health regardless of whether you reach a higher step goal,” says Carroll. That can keep you moving and active well into your future years.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_70-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_71-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As effective as walking is for weight loss, don’t underestimate the importance of your eating habits. For optimal results, consider pairing your walking routine with one of these &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/category/4305/weight-loss-meal-plans/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;healthy meal plans for weight loss&lt;/a&gt;. If possible, working with a registered dietitian can also help you develop a weight loss–friendly eating plan tailored specifically to your lifestyle and food preferences. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_72-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-tips-to-mix-up-walking--make-it-fun"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_73-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Tips to Mix Up Walking &amp;amp; Make It Fun  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_74-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enlist Entertainment.&lt;/strong&gt; Create a fun new playlist, tune into a podcast, listen to an audiobook or some stand-up comedy. Just make sure you’re in an area where it’s safe to pop in your earbuds before tuning in.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Change Your Scenery.&lt;/strong&gt; This could mean trying new trails, exploring new areas of town, going to a track, walking stadium ramps, using the treadmill next to a friend or switching up when you work out to get a glimpse of the sunrise or sunset.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reward Yourself. &lt;/strong&gt;Track your progress and give yourself a reward every time you reach a new goal. Then treat yourself to those leggings you’ve been eyeing, a new visor or a comfy new pair of walking shoes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_75-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_77-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-bottom-line"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_78-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Bottom Line &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_79-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Walking is an excellent form of movement that you can do almost anywhere, no fancy equipment or gym membership required. For optimal health, the CDC recommends 150 minutes or more of moderate-intensity aerobic activity—like walking—per week. Those extra steps will pay dividends for your long-term health. However, for weight loss, you may also need to modify what you eat in addition to getting your steps in. And don’t forget strength training. By building more calorie-hungry muscle, you’ll burn even more energy. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_80-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_81-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As effective as walking may be for weight loss, it also feels good! That’s why Carroll encourages her clients to remind themselves of the benefits that occur outside of weight loss. “When we can develop enjoyment for exercise that is not linked to a number on the scale, we're more likely to make it a lifelong habit,” she says.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxPOXREZm9YMlZpTGdEZk5INnRZUzRoUlJHUmstQjluS2lOeUVEaGNseWxXUm1xSHBrNWRrTzloa1BKa3BQcmdzdzMzWllQZENlOFdyM1dGc3NtN0xObnAtejF3V0tMR2ZnT1lzVEVWbnM2VU5Ec3RhM0RmbzAxcXF3dmxiQ3hhZw</guid></item><item><title>Why there's always room for dessert, according to brain science - NPR</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifkFVX3lxTE16ZUoxcmNFQlROeXQxYzdSVUM3Tlg2ZUxVVThneXNtNjNwQ2R6LTBZN1BZQVpONDdxVmk0YzhybllXVVgxQzNYSHFkTVJjeU5SLTdNYTVuZ3d0V3pqWEVET2tJcXdaOVNQNjhfNTBSV09YOFpLdEt2TVgzWlFHZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-54028" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                salted caramel scoop of ice cream flinging from scooper
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Maren Caruso/Digital Vision/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Maren Caruso/Digital Vision/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;You probably know the feeling of having a hearty meal at a restaurant, and feeling full and satisfied … only to take a peek at the dessert menu and decide the cheesecake looks just irresistible.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So why is it that you just absolutely couldn't have another bite, but you somehow make an exception for a sweet treat? Or as Jerry Sienfeld might put it back in the day &lt;em&gt;"Whhaaaat's the deal with dessert?!" &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Scientists now have a better understanding of the neural origins of this urge thanks to a &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.adp1510" target="_blank"&gt;recent study&lt;/a&gt; published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Science&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Working with mice, researchers tried to set up a scenario similar to the human experience described above. They started by offering a standard chow diet to mice who hadn't eaten since the previous day. That "meal" period lasted for 90 minutes, and the mice ate until they couldn't eat any more.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Want the latest stories on the science of healthy living? Subscribe to NPR's &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/newsletter/health" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Health newsletter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Then it was time for a 30-minute "dessert" period. The first round of the experiment, researchers offered mice more chow for dessert, and the mice ate just a little bit more.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;The second time around, during the "dessert" period, they offered a high sugar feed to the mice for 30 minutes. The mice really went for the sugary feed, consuming six times more calories than when they had regular chow for dessert.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In the mice, researchers monitored the activity of neurons that are associated with feelings of  fullness, called POMC neurons. They're located in a part of the brain called the hypothalamus, which is "very important for promoting satiety," says Henning Fenselau, one of the study authors and a researcher at the Max Planck Institute for Metabolism Research in Cologne, Germany.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The scientists found that when the mice were eating the high sugar diet, the neurons released beta-endorphin, an endogenous opioid — one generated within your body. This chemical bonded to opioid receptors in the mice's brains and triggered a feeling of reward.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"When we taste something sweet, it's not just the sugar we're consuming — it's triggering a system in the brain that associates that sweet taste with pleasure, which makes us want to keep eating," says Dr. Paule Joseph, a researcher who studies metabolism at the National Institutes of Health and was not associated with the study.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;When the team then blocked this opioid pathway, the mice stayed away from the sugar.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The researchers found the same neural mechanism in humans when studying donated brain tissue and scanning the brains of volunteers, who sat in an fMRI machine and were fed a sugar solution through a tube.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;This led the scientists to conclude, says Fenselau, that in humans like in mice "the opiate action in this part of the brain drives that consumption of high-sugar containing foods."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Fenselau says the results suggest that people's brains evolved to love sugar in excess.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Other research has found a link between sugar consumption and &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/06/12/1180867083/tips-to-outsmart-dopamine-unhook-kids-from-screens-sweets" target="_blank"&gt;the dopamine system&lt;/a&gt; in our brain; some research even suggests sugar's effect on the brain in the long-run &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2014/01/15/262741403/why-sugar-makes-us-feel-so-good" target="_blank"&gt;can be similar to addictive drugs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The study at the Max Plank Institute was short-term — researchers didn't keep the diet going over time to see if the mice gained weight or experienced other metabolic changes.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Joseph says a follow-up study, "to look at how these circuits function over the long term, particularly with chronic sugar exposure," could be important to understanding the development of compulsive sugar consumption.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Fenselau says studying this neural reward pathway further could shed light on how sugar overconsumption may contribute to the development of obesity.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So could a weight loss medication that blocks opiate receptors along with suppressing appetite be effective? There is one such product on the market, &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2014/09/11/347631689/fda-approves-new-diet-pill-thats-made-of-old-medicines" target="_blank"&gt;naltrexone bupropion&lt;/a&gt;, sold in the U.S. under the brand name Cerave. It's a combination of bupropion, an antidepressant that can also suppress appetite, and the opioid-blocker naltrexone, which is often prescribed on its own to treat addiction.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;But it's not as effective as the newer weight loss drugs like Ozempic and Wegovy, says Fenselau.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story originally appeared on NPR's Short Wave. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2025/02/21/1232862552/sugar-desserts-brain-craving-science" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Listen here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE16ZUoxcmNFQlROeXQxYzdSVUM3Tlg2ZUxVVThneXNtNjNwQ2R6LTBZN1BZQVpONDdxVmk0YzhybllXVVgxQzNYSHFkTVJjeU5SLTdNYTVuZ3d0V3pqWEVET2tJcXdaOVNQNjhfNTBSV09YOFpLdEt2TVgzWlFHZw</guid></item><item><title>Bird flu mutation associated with increased disease severity found in two cats - Los Angeles Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiywFBVV95cUxOMnc4YUVKdDhVVGU2TGhWX1NST1NjUFZhZGlGdzZsUU5udjZ4X2JQUFV0dlRpVzNkTlB0TURMWTE4THJqcVNpU0NjREt1X25FTGdPSHltYkNzLVRuVGdzNUx3Z2xMdUJRTkhFWWRxNUFTaVc4YzRLSm43dGxYclBDTGZfSHQyRjdHUnBaRnlxNzM4bHdIMzBmMWp6M3h2MUg1aDBMek1JT3FxNW9VamRjN0pUbjRjdUtGMmFLYVJDVC1LMHpjOVRvOE9rTQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-element="story-body" class="ct-rich-text-children font-body font-normal text-lg leading-7.75 text-primary-text-color clearfix mb-10 md:max-w-170 md:mx-auto" data-subscriber-content&gt; &lt;p&gt;A genetic mutation of the H5N1 bird flu virus — a mutation associated with increased infectiousness and disease severity — has been found in two cats, in what scientists say is another indication of the risks posed by the virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fact that the cats have the mutation “is a continued example of how this virus is evolving in nature and should concern everyone,” said Seema Lakdawala, a microbiologist at Emory University in Atlanta.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Henry Niman, founder of vaccine research firm Recombinomics Inc., reviewed the sequence data and reported the results to The Times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gene that Niman identified in the sequence data, known as PB2 E627K, has been associated with increased mammal-to-mammal transmission and disease severity in laboratory animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a similar mutation to the one found in &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.latimes.com/environment/story/2025-03-12/study-shows-widespread-h5n1-bird-flu-infection-in-cattle"&gt;San Bernardino dairy cows earlier this week&lt;/a&gt;, but has a slightly different origin. The cows were infected with the B3.13 strain of H5N1 — which has been circulating widely in dairy cows since last March. The cats were infected with the newer D1.1 strain, which is widespread in wild birds — and has also now appeared in a few cattle herds in Nevada and Arizona.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Niman said he believed the two cats were based in New Jersey and infected last month based on the scientific nomenclature used to label the genetic sequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New Jersey Department of Public Health and Raritan Township, which reported a cluster of infected cats last month in Hunterdon County, couldn’t immediately be reached for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the beginning of 2025, the U.S. Department of Agriculture has reported 51 H5N1-infected cats. They include both household pets and feral felines, and have been found in 13 states since the beginning of the year, including California, Montana, Colorado, Oregon, Washington and New Jersey. There have been more than 100 reported since last March, when the outbreak was first reported in dairy cows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.nj.gov/health/news/2025/approved/20250228a.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey Department of Public Health&lt;/a&gt;, the infected cats all lived on the same property. &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/avian-influenza-bird-flu/new-jersey-reports-h5-avian-flu-cluster-cats" target="_blank"&gt;One was feral, another was an indoor/outdoor cat&lt;/a&gt;. The living situation of the remaining four cats is unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, the genetic sequences of H5N1 virus taken from two infected cats were added to GISAID — the Global Initiative on Sharing All Influenza Data — a publicly-accessible gene data bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Richard Webby, an infectious disease expert at St. Jude’s Hospital in Memphis, Tenn., said the discovery of the mutation wasn’t alarming in and of itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This mutation has sporadically popped up in other mammal infections over the past few years,” he said. “It’s an easy change for the H5 viruses to make and it does so relatively frequently.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’ll become concerning, he said, if it spreads more widely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have been no reports of infected humans in New Jersey, and a &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.nj.gov/health/news/2025/approved/20250228a.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; from the state said the people who interacted with the infected cats were asymptomatic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That Feb. 28 release said that the infected cats had no known reported exposures to infected poultry, livestock, or consumption of raw (unpasteurized) milk or meat, “but did roam freely outdoors, so exposure to wild birds or other animals is unknown.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the outbreak started last March, &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/bird-flu/situation-summary/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;70 people in the U.S. have been infected with H5N1; one person has died&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Los Angeles Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 10:01:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiywFBVV95cUxOMnc4YUVKdDhVVGU2TGhWX1NST1NjUFZhZGlGdzZsUU5udjZ4X2JQUFV0dlRpVzNkTlB0TURMWTE4THJqcVNpU0NjREt1X25FTGdPSHltYkNzLVRuVGdzNUx3Z2xMdUJRTkhFWWRxNUFTaVc4YzRLSm43dGxYclBDTGZfSHQyRjdHUnBaRnlxNzM4bHdIMzBmMWp6M3h2MUg1aDBMek1JT3FxNW9VamRjN0pUbjRjdUtGMmFLYVJDVC1LMHpjOVRvOE9rTQ</guid></item><item><title>Why fewer kids are getting vaccinated in Florida — and how that could affect outbreaks - Miami Herald</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMidEFVX3lxTE50SzRWUi1UOXBYc255c25ORnI5NU44aTZyUnFsLURoTFh6RjRqSnFVNFE4TUNaRlJfV2RfU1Fhd0UtM1JvWHFrYWhZb2h6WF9hODVFTGtTNmNfRTkweVpIaDZ6Y0lwWEFNSm14YTh3X2x2Z25q0gF0QVVfeXFMT2UxNElZYlBiNFlxdWhpcjFKNHFrYUdpb2dxVVVoQnNrVUpQR3Q2a1E1OE9zU1BxU2kweDQ3MFgyTktLUHI0MzFoUU5fR1V4anN4QTdJMmtPUmZuZEVXMi0yS3hTSXAzSk53QkIyaDF3UU1fN08?oc=5</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMidEFVX3lxTE50SzRWUi1UOXBYc255c25ORnI5NU44aTZyUnFsLURoTFh6RjRqSnFVNFE4TUNaRlJfV2RfU1Fhd0UtM1JvWHFrYWhZb2h6WF9hODVFTGtTNmNfRTkweVpIaDZ6Y0lwWEFNSm14YTh3X2x2Z25q0gF0QVVfeXFMT2UxNElZYlBiNFlxdWhpcjFKNHFrYUdpb2dxVVVoQnNrVUpQR3Q2a1E1OE9zU1BxU2kweDQ3MFgyTktLUHI0MzFoUU5fR1V4anN4QTdJMmtPUmZuZEVXMi0yS3hTSXAzSk53QkIyaDF3UU1fN08?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Why fewer kids are getting vaccinated in Florida — and how that could affect outbreaks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Miami Herald&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikAFBVV95cUxOSF93Q1JQRm5lNkZuSkcxUV94N0xEMkpUTnZEY1FHYkU3dnpwU0FMZE1DWnl3ZXhVNFJ5X3lMNGowNmJYZ1hRVmRJY1FKLTV0ZWdWU0pOSVd0eXFzeEphYTRjLVVIc2tCcW1ROFBPVnNVUGN3bFNWMmhpTXVPOE9jMnFXZHhzdHZyS0p4UXpfY3A?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Measles vaccine rates among Philly-area kindergartners drop below ‘community immunity’ threshold&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Philadelphia Inquirer&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitAFBVV95cUxNNkloUWJTQ0RSamlXNzJNakRrTnVuRVB2TjR5SnBnZ044TW5HYjNkd05nTzF6MXRYWmtSVzZieHB1T01oWGN3RkRRZm5Ga0I1cjdYbGlWc2VMeUp2bDBHTGxOR3BOYXZJZFhiZ2dhbml5X1ZkU0FJZXBXaWZBRDJ6U2RPRGFuSTVSVkNzUk5TMzJDa2dUVVdXcGcwOFluWkVnTlNXeWh6NDNVVG5venBDX1hzN2s?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Measles vaccination rate in Wasatch County below CDC recommendation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;KPCW&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi7gFBVV95cUxOQmxKcHNoaW5KSWQzTUlZVUZuZTFxQnVLTXpHZG1LOWZfVXNjRGJLbnVLN3czb0tnbkx4ZDZlVmt6cUVSTzl3QkMzWkdmZHdKZk1XUkRTbEo1WFVZSzBWQV9vVFAzeEtCb2p2aEpxNDlVR1pUQ0NWTTVhZmxyQ2tPNjlJckVQUjJlblJnY0xIT0JpaHVmSTRlb29zU1B2amJDd2dUMl9NLWlla3hWZXVnS3htZ3NJY2xWemlMdlpGQW43X2NfMHFqYmNPMTNqVnV3b1BoZUNveW5sZUltTlk1ZURUWmhQSURVYWJEMkNB?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Editorial: Not a measly problem: Make sure you're vaccinated&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Walla Walla Union-Bulletin&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV95cUxNOUdzT3FzYlJGMGFhdDg0NmtfUkM4NXlDdmRna00xYVlqTWt2Mk4zMG5nTjFtNmJqY2hRRnBLSXRiUjN1MHdQbjNRMzI5Q3E5UnFva2xxcWZZMUZmOFpQS3c3cUNIY05jVzA3VnR5TFlUU1NLOV9KZkZLY1M5WjYzeHR3?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;By the Numbers: Measles Vaccinations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Highlands Current&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>Miami Herald</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTE50SzRWUi1UOXBYc255c25ORnI5NU44aTZyUnFsLURoTFh6RjRqSnFVNFE4TUNaRlJfV2RfU1Fhd0UtM1JvWHFrYWhZb2h6WF9hODVFTGtTNmNfRTkweVpIaDZ6Y0lwWEFNSm14YTh3X2x2Z25q0gF0QVVfeXFMT2UxNElZYlBiNFlxdWhpcjFKNHFrYUdpb2dxVVVoQnNrVUpQR3Q2a1E1OE9zU1BxU2kweDQ3MFgyTktLUHI0MzFoUU5fR1V4anN4QTdJMmtPUmZuZEVXMi0yS3hTSXAzSk53QkIyaDF3UU1fN08</guid></item><item><title>Why is it still so hard to make nuclear weapons? - Livescience.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimwFBVV95cUxQV1dub0lyUXRjMzJWQjE0S3pZd3UyWWJLYkxORWQ0WVh1Q0JYNmNQU2FDcU9YQUxLdDRqZ0dXNUlYbkNZUklEWV9OMV9jSnYwSjJrMjNyUWU5Qnkxcmtyc2ZUS1JYVzc2WS1YUk9xWjU2azZOWGxyWmpuNEpwSmtVLTZ1SWFnMnFNVkNkMm1uYVNaQTg0aXFuMWRFOA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first nuclear weapon test, code-named "&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.energy.gov/lm/trinity-site-worlds-first-nuclear-explosion" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.energy.gov/lm/trinity-site-worlds-first-nuclear-explosion" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Trinity&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;," took place in the New Mexico desert at 5:30 a.m. on July 16, 1945. This test was a proof of concept for the secret nuclear science taking place at Los Alamos as a part of the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/manhattan-project.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/manhattan-project.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Manhattan Project&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; during World War II and would lead to the atomic bombs being dropped on &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/45509-hiroshima-nagasaki-atomic-bomb.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/45509-hiroshima-nagasaki-atomic-bomb.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Hiroshima and Nagasaki&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Japan, just a few weeks later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since those detonations, the development of nuclear weapons has accelerated. Countries around the world have built their own &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.armscontrol.org/factsheets/nuclear-weapons-who-has-what-glance" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.armscontrol.org/factsheets/nuclear-weapons-who-has-what-glance" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;nuclear stockpiles&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, including over 5,000 nuclear warheads held by the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet, even though the basic components of this technology are no longer secret, nuclear weapon development remains a scientific and engineering challenge. But why are nuclear weapons still so difficult to produce?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A big part of the difficulty comes from deriving the chemical elements used inside these weapons to create an explosion, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://fas.org/expert/hans-kristensen/" target="_blank" data-url="https://fas.org/expert/hans-kristensen/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Hans Kristensen&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, director of the Nuclear Information Project at the Federation of American Scientists, told Live Science in an email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That basic idea of a nuclear explosion is that nuclear [fissile] materials are stimulated to release their enormous energy," he said. "To produce fissile material of sufficient purity and sufficient quantity is a challenge [and] this production requires considerable industrial capacity."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/human-behavior/warfare/how-many-nuclear-bombs-have-been-used" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/human-behavior/warfare/how-many-nuclear-bombs-have-been-used"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How many nuclear bombs have been used?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The enormous release of energy is called a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.energy.gov/science/doe-explainsnuclear-fission" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.energy.gov/science/doe-explainsnuclear-fission" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;nuclear fission reaction&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. When this reaction occurs, a chain reaction starts where the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/37206-atom-definition.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/37206-atom-definition.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;atoms&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are split apart to release energy. This is the same kind of reaction that makes &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/planet-earth/energy/nuclear-energy" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/planet-earth/energy/nuclear-energy"&gt;&lt;u&gt;nuclear energy&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-2cSr3UxEqDyDzmkB5sUC8M" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-2cSr3UxEqDyDzmkB5sUC8M slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get the world’s most fascinating discoveries delivered straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id="uranium-and-plutonium-enrichment-3"&gt;Uranium and plutonium enrichment&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fissile material inside a nuclear bomb is primarily isotopes of uranium and plutonium, which are radioactive elements, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.nuce.psu.edu/department/directory-detail-g.aspx?q=MXZ206" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.nuce.psu.edu/department/directory-detail-g.aspx?q=MXZ206" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Matthew Zerphy&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of practice in nuclear engineering at Penn State, told Live Science. Uranium's most common isotope, uranium-238 (U-238), is mined and then goes through a process of enrichment to transform a portion into another isotope, uranium-235 (U-235), which can more readily be used in nuclear reactions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One way to enrich uranium is to turn it into a gas and spin it very rapidly in centrifuges," Zerphy said. "Because of the difference in mass between U-235 and U-238, the isotopes are split, and you can separate out U-235."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For weapons-grade uranium, 90% of a U-238 sample needs to be transformed into U-235, Zerphy said. The most challenging part of this process, which can take weeks to months, is the chemical transformation of the element itself, which requires intensive energy and specialized equipment. One &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.nrc.gov/materials/fuel-cycle-fac/ur-enrichment.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.nrc.gov/materials/fuel-cycle-fac/ur-enrichment.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;chemical hazard&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; during this process is the possible release of uranium hexafluoride (UF₆), a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.energy.gov/nnsa/articles/sds-uranium-hexafluoride-uf6" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.energy.gov/nnsa/articles/sds-uranium-hexafluoride-uf6" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;highly toxic substance&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that, if inhaled, can damage the kidneys, liver, lungs, brain, skin and eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The process to enrich plutonium to the same degree is even trickier, he said, because this element does not occur naturally like uranium does. Instead, plutonium is a byproduct of nuclear reactors, which means to use plutonium, scientists need to handle radioactive, spent nuclear fuel and process the material through "intense" chemical deposition. The processing of this material can also pose a safety risk if a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.osti.gov/opennet/manhattan-project-history/Science/NuclearPhysics/critical-mass.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.osti.gov/opennet/manhattan-project-history/Science/NuclearPhysics/critical-mass.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;critical mass&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is collected accidentally, Zerphy said, which is the smallest amount of fissile material needed to sustain a self-sustaining fission reaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You'd be very careful to not have that happen while you're in the process of making these components to make sure that things aren't inadvertently brought together and entering some kind of criticality," he said, which could lead to an accidental explosion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/nuclear-bomb-wwii-shadows.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/nuclear-bomb-wwii-shadows.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why did the atomic bomb dropped on Hiroshima leave shadows of people etched on sidewalks?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;The production of nuclear weapons is costly, requires specialized equipment and comes with multiple risks. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Peter Zelei Images via Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the scientific principles of bringing these components together is well understood, creating and controlling this reaction in a fraction of a second can still be difficult.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The weapons are designed such that when they are detonated a 'supercritical' mass of fissile material is created very quickly … in a very small space," Zerphy said. "This causes an exponential increase in the number of fissions spreading throughout the material almost instantaneously."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This quick spread of atomic fission is a big part of what makes a nuclear reaction so destructive, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the case of thermonuclear weapons, which were developed after World War II and use a combination of both nuclear &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/fission-vs-fusion.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/fission-vs-fusion.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;fission and fusion&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to create an even stronger explosion, a standard fission reaction then has to spark a secondary and stronger fusion reaction. This fusion reaction is the same kind of power found at the center of the sun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="nuclear-weapons-testing-3"&gt;Nuclear weapons testing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once these weapons are created, scientists and engineers need to be sure the weapons will work as needed, should they ever be used. When nuclear weapons were first developed, scientists would test the weapons themselves at test sites (&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/65949-marshall-islands-more-radioactivity-chernobyl.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/65949-marshall-islands-more-radioactivity-chernobyl.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;which devastated&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the environment of the "deserted" areas where they were tested, as well as &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.nps.gov/articles/000/trinity-test-downwinders.htm" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.nps.gov/articles/000/trinity-test-downwinders.htm" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;people and animals that lived nearby&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;). In contrast, modern weapon testing relies on computer models. This is part of the work done by the National Nuclear Security Administration (NNSA).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"NNSA … develop[s] tools for qualifying weapon components and certifying weapons, ensuring their survivability and effectiveness in various scenarios," an NNSA spokesperson told Live Science in an email. "This involves advanced simulations using supercomputing systems, materials science, and precision engineering to ensure weapons function as intended."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, the complexity and challenges of building these weapons may explain why so few nuclear superpowers exist in the world today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Livescience.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxQV1dub0lyUXRjMzJWQjE0S3pZd3UyWWJLYkxORWQ0WVh1Q0JYNmNQU2FDcU9YQUxLdDRqZ0dXNUlYbkNZUklEWV9OMV9jSnYwSjJrMjNyUWU5Qnkxcmtyc2ZUS1JYVzc2WS1YUk9xWjU2azZOWGxyWmpuNEpwSmtVLTZ1SWFnMnFNVkNkMm1uYVNaQTg0aXFuMWRFOA</guid></item><item><title>10 signs your body needs more magnesium (natural foods where it is available) - The Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqAJBVV95cUxPcDZUcmFJazBPTmtWa3dtZ3dZbFhGbjdEaWE2NHRfaUlxRkt6N0FpMTNfQ3VrMy1TdXpMZzktaHpDSW9ZTUp6TXMwc2dHTVJDUzJOTnUxNGVLQUhQLWJGb3VSQWt1eWpzajIzQVhlY2cxTTFxNFNrSldweDFmWktvbVNvTEd2SlphNWtrWVFHbi1aMzkyeVMzVmZXUExhTE9Oc1RMZ2VsaGlIajhfWHFtalgyNEJYWFhESWstdEozWWFIN0FSaktSVTQzQTdUUTBvcXNZZDlic1VXVDVWZE52OG9fZ2hBejhVQnVCMWVNYWhfQ3lwWU1NTmVOQ3ZXNU9XeDU2WF84aHFXQVl0WUFoNkJYR3k3Q20tN29mejRvd21TejZZQ0VNcNIBqAJBVV95cUxPcDZUcmFJazBPTmtWa3dtZ3dZbFhGbjdEaWE2NHRfaUlxRkt6N0FpMTNfQ3VrMy1TdXpMZzktaHpDSW9ZTUp6TXMwc2dHTVJDUzJOTnUxNGVLQUhQLWJGb3VSQWt1eWpzajIzQVhlY2cxTTFxNFNrSldweDFmWktvbVNvTEd2SlphNWtrWVFHbi1aMzkyeVMzVmZXUExhTE9Oc1RMZ2VsaGlIajhfWHFtalgyNEJYWFhESWstdEozWWFIN0FSaktSVTQzQTdUUTBvcXNZZDlic1VXVDVWZE52OG9fZ2hBejhVQnVCMWVNYWhfQ3lwWU1NTmVOQ3ZXNU9XeDU2WF84aHFXQVl0WUFoNkJYR3k3Q20tN29mejRvd21TejZZQ0VNcA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;amp-story-grid-layer class="recircular" id="rcontent" template="vertical"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt;&lt;p class="mid-heading"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;You may also like&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc3 pa"&gt;Nimbu paani benefits: 8 surprising benef...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc5 pa"&gt;​13 powerful morning exercises for brain...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 08:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAJBVV95cUxPcDZUcmFJazBPTmtWa3dtZ3dZbFhGbjdEaWE2NHRfaUlxRkt6N0FpMTNfQ3VrMy1TdXpMZzktaHpDSW9ZTUp6TXMwc2dHTVJDUzJOTnUxNGVLQUhQLWJGb3VSQWt1eWpzajIzQVhlY2cxTTFxNFNrSldweDFmWktvbVNvTEd2SlphNWtrWVFHbi1aMzkyeVMzVmZXUExhTE9Oc1RMZ2VsaGlIajhfWHFtalgyNEJYWFhESWstdEozWWFIN0FSaktSVTQzQTdUUTBvcXNZZDlic1VXVDVWZE52OG9fZ2hBejhVQnVCMWVNYWhfQ3lwWU1NTmVOQ3ZXNU9XeDU2WF84aHFXQVl0WUFoNkJYR3k3Q20tN29mejRvd21TejZZQ0VNcNIBqAJBVV95cUxPcDZUcmFJazBPTmtWa3dtZ3dZbFhGbjdEaWE2NHRfaUlxRkt6N0FpMTNfQ3VrMy1TdXpMZzktaHpDSW9ZTUp6TXMwc2dHTVJDUzJOTnUxNGVLQUhQLWJGb3VSQWt1eWpzajIzQVhlY2cxTTFxNFNrSldweDFmWktvbVNvTEd2SlphNWtrWVFHbi1aMzkyeVMzVmZXUExhTE9Oc1RMZ2VsaGlIajhfWHFtalgyNEJYWFhESWstdEozWWFIN0FSaktSVTQzQTdUUTBvcXNZZDlic1VXVDVWZE52OG9fZ2hBejhVQnVCMWVNYWhfQ3lwWU1NTmVOQ3ZXNU9XeDU2WF84aHFXQVl0WUFoNkJYR3k3Q20tN29mejRvd21TejZZQ0VNcA</guid></item><item><title>Cornwall man sent cancer diagnosis text by mistake - BBC.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBhZ3E4ZHRQcXY0MEkxLTNNVG9QTlZnUHpkcU9CSWhyNGZoclljUW5fd1VNZHRoYXdDc3pGN0VaTlNncm9Qa2U1NUpveDNNNVF4WlRxYzV6VmJUZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE9nU3VLaXRoajU3c292MFZHN3N6YV9ra2hvN2sxMG9lZ3FuQzdBU3ZIV0ppd1RvSGpncWlyMTRXSUJMa29oWUg1VlV6LUpWVUoxSWVTSHAyRXdQT0tqTHdR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-518485e5-0 itISwu"&gt;Cornwall man sent cancer diagnosis text by mistake&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-b42e7a8f-0 haItSe"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-b42e7a8f-12 fcCDwR"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-b42e7a8f-5 evAEAB"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="sc-b42e7a8f-7 kItaYD"&gt;Elliot Ball&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="sc-b42e7a8f-8 bTSIhT"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BBC News, South West&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 ejjhCR"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/386f/live/8b43f4c0-010b-11f0-9ca3-873d708a8482.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/386f/live/8b43f4c0-010b-11f0-9ca3-873d708a8482.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/386f/live/8b43f4c0-010b-11f0-9ca3-873d708a8482.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/386f/live/8b43f4c0-010b-11f0-9ca3-873d708a8482.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/386f/live/8b43f4c0-010b-11f0-9ca3-873d708a8482.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/386f/live/8b43f4c0-010b-11f0-9ca3-873d708a8482.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/386f/live/8b43f4c0-010b-11f0-9ca3-873d708a8482.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/386f/live/8b43f4c0-010b-11f0-9ca3-873d708a8482.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Gwyn Morley Gwyn Morley sat on a bench with a brown dog resting on his lap. Mr Morley has a navy blue sun hat on and sunglasses. He is wearing a blue patterned shirt, grey cardigan and navy blue shorts." class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Gwyn Morley&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Gwyn Morley said the message knocked him for six when he first read it&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;A man from Cornwall has been "knocked for six" after he received a communication from the NHS mistakenly informing him he could have cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Gwyn Morley, from Charlestown, was notified by the Urology department at the Royal Cornwall Hospital in Treliske on Friday morning that he was an "urgent cancer suspect referral". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The 72-year-old said: "It sort of knocked me for six but my wife Janet said I hadn't had any recent blood tests so she was 99.99% sure it was a mistake." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;A spokesperson for the Royal Cornwall Hospitals NHS Trust confirmed a "small number" of patients had received an incorrect text message following an error in its patient messaging system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The communication sent to Mr Morley and other patients read: "You have been referred to Urology as an urgent suspected cancer referral."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The Royal Cornwall Hospitals NHS Trust spokesperson said: "We can confirm a small number of patients have received an incorrect text message following an error in our patient messaging system. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"This is an isolated incident and action has been taken to prevent further messages being sent in error.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"We are contacting all patients personally to provide reassurance and to allay any concerns they may have. We are deeply sorry for the anxiety this has caused."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Mr Morley said he had received an apology from the hospital but he and his wife described the message as "ridiculous". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;He added: "My concern is there could be several people wondering what the hell they are to do."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 07:26:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBhZ3E4ZHRQcXY0MEkxLTNNVG9QTlZnUHpkcU9CSWhyNGZoclljUW5fd1VNZHRoYXdDc3pGN0VaTlNncm9Qa2U1NUpveDNNNVF4WlRxYzV6VmJUZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE9nU3VLaXRoajU3c292MFZHN3N6YV9ra2hvN2sxMG9lZ3FuQzdBU3ZIV0ppd1RvSGpncWlyMTRXSUJMa29oWUg1VlV6LUpWVUoxSWVTSHAyRXdQT0tqTHdR</guid></item><item><title>'Abandoned' kitten found alone on Cornwall coast path - BBC.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTFByNVZUak01UWNkTHh1TVZ2Sk11VUFzWHlUQl9zTXp1Sml6U3luX0RDUzgySWotN1kzQWV3NUNvZEpHWjlwUHpUWjBPSTNrcVFfMVFjUG1sRjk3UdIBX0FVX3lxTE55X2VsM1NQa3I4c0E3Qlp5ZGxIazFTNGdNM3VlczlwZXhGM19PRHozY21xRnExWEJpTUdFcENTM0drRll4X2ZRaHB3MVJMTFV0UHhTaDRZSUR0cnZzeXpJ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-518485e5-0 itISwu"&gt;'Abandoned' kitten rescued by hiker on coast path &lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-b42e7a8f-0 haItSe"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-b42e7a8f-12 fcCDwR"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-b42e7a8f-5 evAEAB"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="sc-b42e7a8f-7 kItaYD"&gt;Elliot Ball&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="sc-b42e7a8f-8 bTSIhT"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BBC News, South West&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 ejjhCR"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/07fe/live/445b0e50-00c9-11f0-87d0-01e7c130d18d.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/07fe/live/445b0e50-00c9-11f0-87d0-01e7c130d18d.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/07fe/live/445b0e50-00c9-11f0-87d0-01e7c130d18d.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/07fe/live/445b0e50-00c9-11f0-87d0-01e7c130d18d.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/07fe/live/445b0e50-00c9-11f0-87d0-01e7c130d18d.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/07fe/live/445b0e50-00c9-11f0-87d0-01e7c130d18d.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/07fe/live/445b0e50-00c9-11f0-87d0-01e7c130d18d.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/07fe/live/445b0e50-00c9-11f0-87d0-01e7c130d18d.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Katie Spencer Bramble on Katie Spencer's lap. Bramble is a dark tortoiseshell kitten and she is looking out the window as the photo is taken." class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Katie Spencer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;The Cats Protection Cornwall Cat Centre said Bramble could have died had she not been found&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;A kitten thought to have been abandoned has been rehomed after she approached a Royal Navy engineer in Cornwall and refused to stop climbing up his leg. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Bramble, who was no more than 10-12 weeks old, ran over to Billy Kelland and his three friends as they were hiking along the coast path at Porthcurno. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Mr Kelland carried Bramble back along the path wrapped in a wool hat inside his open rucksack before calling his mother, Katie Spencer, for help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Spencer contacted Cats Protection Cornwall Cat Centre in Carnon Downs  but eventually decided to take on the lost kitten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/e2dd/live/afb2c300-00c9-11f0-82fd-37125e2ef3fc.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/e2dd/live/afb2c300-00c9-11f0-82fd-37125e2ef3fc.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e2dd/live/afb2c300-00c9-11f0-82fd-37125e2ef3fc.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/e2dd/live/afb2c300-00c9-11f0-82fd-37125e2ef3fc.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/e2dd/live/afb2c300-00c9-11f0-82fd-37125e2ef3fc.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/e2dd/live/afb2c300-00c9-11f0-82fd-37125e2ef3fc.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/e2dd/live/afb2c300-00c9-11f0-82fd-37125e2ef3fc.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e2dd/live/afb2c300-00c9-11f0-82fd-37125e2ef3fc.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Billy Kelland Billy Kelland carrying Bramble in a woollen hat while out on a coastal path with his friends." class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Billy Kelland&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;When Bramble was found she had fleas and was suffering from cat flu&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt; Gemma Reid, from Cornwall Cat Centre, condemned those who had left the kitten on the cliffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;She said: "It's never acceptable to abandon a pet and we would urge anyone who is struggling to contact us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Reid, a rehoming and welfare assistant at the charity, said cat abandonments had increased by 71% over the past three years nationwide. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;When Bramble was found she was dirty from being outside, and there was evidence she had fleas, which can cause anaemia in kittens. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The centre said she was also sneezing, had watery red eyes, was struggling to breathe and her meow was "raspy", all signs of highly infectious cat flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"It's likely she would have died a painful death if she'd remained out in the elements with her cat flu untreated," added Ms Reid. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-518485e5-0 DkKTF"&gt;'Happy little lady'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;But Bramble is now settled in her new home with Ms Spencer and Mr Kelland makes frequent visits to his feline friend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Spencer said: "Bramble is an absolute sweetheart and loving life. Our front room currently looks like a kitten play gym, but when bedtime comes, I carry her up to her room, tuck her in, and we don't hear a peep until morning."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"She loves nothing more than snuggling right into our necks and gives the gentlest, most heart-melting cuddles and purrs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"She truly is a special and happy little lady and we love her."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Reid said: "We're thrilled that Bramble has found such a loving home after her extremely tough start in life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 07:24:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFByNVZUak01UWNkTHh1TVZ2Sk11VUFzWHlUQl9zTXp1Sml6U3luX0RDUzgySWotN1kzQWV3NUNvZEpHWjlwUHpUWjBPSTNrcVFfMVFjUG1sRjk3UdIBX0FVX3lxTE55X2VsM1NQa3I4c0E3Qlp5ZGxIazFTNGdNM3VlczlwZXhGM19PRHozY21xRnExWEJpTUdFcENTM0drRll4X2ZRaHB3MVJMTFV0UHhTaDRZSUR0cnZzeXpJ</guid></item><item><title>The 4 Biggest Early Warning Signs Before A Heart Attack - HuffPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxNclk4Y2NwYlZRaG5rVUwtWF94ZkZGV2cwWDlFSEtxODdlb3l2Sm1NVy10UDNYbEpvR09XdlpKSWt2UF92QUhwZmEtZUM1UkhmZmlZUDdmSkFOMzI3Y3czaUdjbjNtbUttcXlKV18tTWh2X2FEZ1duenM2QnE1eU9Eck9MU3h6MVVnRkhhN3JOaWNuSW5Xc1RQdEFIY3BNUdIBowFBVV95cUxQWE80bnNDOFNiOUFOZlZCcWF3MC1FWjJxRXI2T1VBMFE5c3NIRmFuV21lV0pOdV9WWVBnSXk3SktUWXRxc3VyMTZST0daUGNHRHFzRF9DZ0pkb3JxdEQ5MkVRWGxBbjdRdHVtWUZ4aDZ5ZWJfYV9MRW9QaVl0dWNJcUgtelQyUF9LbHBad2pVZ1ZSZ054dFJIZW9kMHVLaGR0ak9z?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While it’s well-known that issues like high blood pressure, diabetes, smoking and not enough exercise are &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/heart-attack/understand-your-risks-to-prevent-a-heart-attack" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="risk factors" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d340fce4b036ac32c9ed27" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/heart-attack/understand-your-risks-to-prevent-a-heart-attack" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;risk factors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; for a heart attack, many people may not know the early signs to tell if a cardiac event is on its way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experts say there are designated symptoms that happen in the days and weeks before a heart attack that can be a red flag.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Knowing these signs could be a lifesaver. Heart disease &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/heartdisease/facts.htm" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="is the No. 1 killer" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d340fce4b036ac32c9ed27" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/heartdisease/facts.htm" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;is the No. 1 killer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; of men and women in the United States. And Dr. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://profiles.stanford.edu/abha-khandelwal" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Abha Khandelwal" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d340fce4b036ac32c9ed27" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://profiles.stanford.edu/abha-khandelwal" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Abha Khandelwal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a clinical associate professor of cardiovascular medicine at Stanford Health Care, said doctors are seeing an increase in mortality from heart disease during the pandemic, which underscores the importance of being armed with knowledge about your risk and the signs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Below, experts share some of the early warning signs for a heart attack and what to do if you experience them:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Chest Pain Or Pressure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Angina, which is intermittent chest pain caused by the gradual buildup of plaque inside the arteries, can be a warning sign that a heart attack or cardiac event may occur in the ensuing days, according to Dr. &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/profiles/details/roger-blumenthal" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Roger Blumenthal" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d340fce4b036ac32c9ed27" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/profiles/details/roger-blumenthal" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Roger Blumenthal&lt;/a&gt;, the director of the Johns Hopkins Ciccarone Center for the Prevention of Cardiovascular Disease and professor of medicine at Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine. A constriction or spasm of the arteries on the outside of the heart can also lead to this symptom.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you notice any sort of chest discomfort — angina can also show up in forms other than pain — it’s important to call your doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Neck, Shoulder Or Jaw Pain&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Typically we associate heart attacks with immediate pain in the left arm. However, early pain signs may not be as obvious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Sometimes angina is synonymous with chest pain or chest pressure but sometimes, especially with older individuals, there may be other associated symptoms like ... pain that radiates through the neck or shoulder or arm,” Blumenthal said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Khandelwal said it can also feel like a numbness that goes up to the jaw.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Getting Easily Winded Or Uncomfortable After Exertion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Becoming easily out of breath can be a red flag, too, Khandelwal said. This could include feeling more winded than usual after doing a simple task, like installing a new light fixture or getting your garden ready for spring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;She added that some people notice numbness in the arm or chest discomfort after extreme exertion as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Nausea Or Other Stomach Problems&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abdominal pain, nausea and overall fatigue are potential heart attack warning signs, too, according to Dr. &lt;a href="https://www.yalemedicine.org/specialists/nikhil-sikand" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Nikhil Sikand" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d340fce4b036ac32c9ed27" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.yalemedicine.org/specialists/nikhil-sikand" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;Nikhil Sikand&lt;/a&gt;, a Yale Medicine cardiologist and assistant professor at Yale School of Medicine. But that doesn’t go for everyone. “&lt;span&gt;Some patients may have mild or no symptoms at all,” he noted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: ljubaphoto via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;ljubaphoto via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Chest pain in the month before a heart attack is common.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More Frequent Or Intense Symptoms In The Days Leading Up To A Heart Attack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The time ranges between symptoms and a cardiac event vary and can look very different from person to person. But Khandelwal said roughly two-thirds of her patients can look back over the month before a heart attack and point out a time when they experienced chest pain. Some people may notice worsening symptoms in the days leading up to a heart attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Oftentimes, that day of, [or] the week of, leading up to [a heart attack]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; can be filled with more symptoms,” she said. These symptoms can be more frequent, last longer or may even be more severe. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you notice any symptoms, it’s imperative you get help. Especially if the issues come on quickly and severely; then you should call 911 immediately, Khandelwal said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you have no history of heart disease and notice mild symptoms, you should still inform your doctor, she added. Your physician can help decide what to do and arrange testing if need be.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who get medical attention promptly — even after experiencing a heart attack — can get lifesaving treatment, Sikand noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heart Attack Prevention In Your Everyday Life&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While many risk factors are out of your control, many are in your hands. Simple behaviors like committing to a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/preventing-heart-disease-walking_l_62def5bae4b03dbb991be966" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="daily walk" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d340fce4b036ac32c9ed27" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="62def5bae4b03dbb991be966" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;daily walk&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; or &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/worst-foods-for-heart-health_l_63e51cdfe4b0255caae9f325" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="cutting out certain foods" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d340fce4b036ac32c9ed27" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="63e51cdfe4b0255caae9f325" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;&lt;span&gt;cutting out certain foods&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; can help reduce your chances of a cardiac event, along with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/diabetes/prevention--treatment-of-diabetes/know-your-health-numbers" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="knowing your numbers" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d340fce4b036ac32c9ed27" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/diabetes/prevention--treatment-of-diabetes/know-your-health-numbers" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;knowing your numbers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; (blood pressure, cholesterol and blood sugar) and being aware of the warning signs of a heart attack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Before you start getting older or before you have the disease, if you can work day to day on controlling risk factors, that is the most powerful thing a person can do,” Khandelwal said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;And even if you have heart disease, it’s important to know the risk factors and do what you can to keep yourself healthy. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Once a person has had a heart attack ... they’re much more likely to have another cardiovascular event in the ensuing year — it’s important to modify their risk factors that are lifestyle habits and get on the appropriate medical therapy,” Blumenthal said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the American Heart Association, the traditional heart attack risk factors are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Smoking&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Diabetes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;High cholesterol&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;High blood pressure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Obesity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blumenthal said &lt;a href="https://www.cardiosmart.org/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="CardioSmart" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d340fce4b036ac32c9ed27" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cardiosmart.org/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;CardioSmart&lt;/a&gt;, an American College of Cardiology resource, is a great tool for folks looking to learn how to lessen their heart attack risk. Through this tool, you can find ways to help you quit smoking, learn about the benefits exercise has on your heart, get healthy-eating tips and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond at-home mitigation strategies, you should also keep in touch with your doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In addition to a healthy diet and regular exercise, the most important thing any one person can do is follow closely with a health professional at regular intervals to identify and treat potential risk factors for heart [disease],” Sikand said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 07:00:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxNclk4Y2NwYlZRaG5rVUwtWF94ZkZGV2cwWDlFSEtxODdlb3l2Sm1NVy10UDNYbEpvR09XdlpKSWt2UF92QUhwZmEtZUM1UkhmZmlZUDdmSkFOMzI3Y3czaUdjbjNtbUttcXlKV18tTWh2X2FEZ1duenM2QnE1eU9Eck9MU3h6MVVnRkhhN3JOaWNuSW5Xc1RQdEFIY3BNUdIBowFBVV95cUxQWE80bnNDOFNiOUFOZlZCcWF3MC1FWjJxRXI2T1VBMFE5c3NIRmFuV21lV0pOdV9WWVBnSXk3SktUWXRxc3VyMTZST0daUGNHRHFzRF9DZ0pkb3JxdEQ5MkVRWGxBbjdRdHVtWUZ4aDZ5ZWJfYV9MRW9QaVl0dWNJcUgtelQyUF9LbHBad2pVZ1ZSZ054dFJIZW9kMHVLaGR0ak9z</guid></item><item><title>How the Other Half Suffers - The Dispatch</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigAFBVV95cUxNaGJ1SGl4eFk0ZDVNTmZHRE02d3lmRzZDY3p4cGl6UzFkeUtrX2pDSVU4UlFETjhqeWpEemVLd0t6TnU2VVhoV1pDWFpHb01mSzFVWTlPcjY4SWdTM1JnRHBhZHZ0UXAxVTNQbEtncU13UlJvak5RV3Zrald3T21yOQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="tight-template drop-cap"&gt;
                &lt;div class="rich-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost immediately after assuming the presidency for the second time, President Donald Trump signed an &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/01/reevaluating-and-realigning-united-states-foreign-aid/"&gt;Executive Order&lt;/a&gt; freezing all foreign aid. In the weeks since, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/11/health/tuberculosis-kenya-us-cuts.html"&gt;&lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, “The whole system of finding, diagnosing and treating tuberculosis . . . has collapsed in dozens of countries across Africa and Asia.” The consequences of this system collapse in places like Kenya are dismal:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Family members of infected people are not being put on preventive therapy. Infected adults are sharing rooms in crowded Nairobi tenements, and infected children are sleeping four to a bed with their siblings. Parents who took their sick children to get tested the day before Mr. Trump was inaugurated are still waiting to hear if their children have tuberculosis. And people who have the near-totally drug-resistant form of tuberculosis are not being treated. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the West, we often think of tuberculosis as a disease of the past, akin to the Black Death or smallpox (or, until the recent &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2025/health/measles-outbreak-map.html"&gt;outbreak&lt;/a&gt; in Texas and New Mexico, measles). We remember it as “consumption,” that pesky disease that tends to afflict characters in Dickens or Tolstoy novels and kills them, slowly but surely, after they begin coughing up blood. As a result, it’s easy to forget that TB still exists. But in his new book, &lt;em&gt;Everything Is Tuberculosis: The History and Persistence of Our Deadliest Infection&lt;/em&gt;, John Green—the YouTuber, podcaster, philanthropist, and acclaimed author of young adult fiction books including &lt;em&gt;The Fault in Our Stars&lt;/em&gt;—reminds us that tuberculosis, the bacterial infection that has claimed the lives of as many as 1 in 7 human beings who ever lived, is still very much with us today. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tuberculosis has always been a challenge to humanity, but as Green notes, what’s different now is that “tuberculosis is curable, and has been since the mid-1950s.” Indeed, because of remarkable medical advances in the 20th century, “[w]e know how to live in a world without tuberculosis. But we choose not to live in that world.” In the United States and other developed countries, we sort of &lt;em&gt;do &lt;/em&gt;live in that world: While there were &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/tb/php/dear-colleague-letters/2024-reported-tuberculosis-2023.html"&gt;nearly 10,000 cases&lt;/a&gt; of tuberculosis in the U.S. in 2023 (a distressing increase of 8.3 percent over 2019 levels), the vast majority of TB cases—Green reports that more than 2 billion people worldwide are currently infected with the bacterial disease (though in most cases the infection remains forever dormant)—occurred in low- and middle-income countries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;        


&lt;div class="rich-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of those countries is West Africa’s Sierra Leone, a former colony for emancipated American slaves who fought alongside the British in the Revolutionary War. Green became interested in TB after meeting a 17-year-old boy there named Henry, who suffered from tuberculosis. Henry had been receiving treatment for several years by the time Green met him, and his prognosis was bleak. The one-two punch of child malnourishment and tuberculosis—“&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S089990070500300X#:~:text=Conclusions,great%20risk%20of%20profound%20wasting."&gt;wasting&lt;/a&gt;” is “one of the cardinal features of the disease”—left him emaciated, to the point where Green initially thought the young man was around the same age as his 9-year-old son. Worse, Henry had “yellow clouds in the whites of his eyes” due to liver toxicity, a side effect of the drugs used to treat him, and swelling in his neck indicated that TB had invaded his lymph nodes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Henry was being treated for his disease, but unsuccessfully, and it was determined that he had developed multidrug-resistant tuberculosis. This harder-to-beat version probably afflicted Henry because his father at one point insisted that he abandon professional medical treatment in favor of a faith healer. Indeed, one reason for TB’s longevity is that many patients fail to take their full course of antibiotics. This is especially the case in poor countries, where the DOTS strategy—an acronym meaning Directly Observed Therapy (Short-course)—requires a course of standardized treatment of antibiotics under physician supervision. But in many of these countries, patients struggle to get to and from the hospital to obtain their antibiotics, and their often inadequate food intake makes them susceptible to the nausea that can occur if the medications are taken on an empty stomach, causing them to reject their pills. When TB patients fail to take all their antibiotics, the bacteria that remain replicate, passing on their antibiotic-resistant genes to their progeny. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;But rather than lay the blame for TB’s sustained advantage over the human race on patients in poor countries who lack adequate health care, Green argues that “we are in this mess first and foremost because we stopped trying to develop new treatments for tuberculosis.” Green points an accusatory finger at our market-based system of drug development, arguing that there are few economic incentives for drug companies to develop additional TB treatments for people in poor countries. When in 2012 Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson developed bedaquiline, which is effective against drug-resistant tuberculosis (and could have cured Henry within months), the pharmaceutical giant engaged in what Green calls price gouging: It charged $900 for a single course of treatment in low-income countries, far more than the $130 that it charges for the same treatment today. (My inner Kevin D. Williamson insists that this 86 percent price drop is actually proof that the market is working. My inner John Green, meanwhile, wonders whether we should really allow pharmaceutical companies to price life-saving drugs so highly for people who couldn’t possibly afford them.) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of relying solely on market incentives for TB treatment, Green argues, “We could invest more public and philanthropic money into research and development of drugs, vaccines, and treatment distribution systems.” More ambitiously, we could “reimagine the allocation of global healthcare resources to better align them with the burden of global suffering—rewarding treatments that save or improve lives rather than treatments that the rich can afford.” It’s a nice thought, but even before President Trump froze foreign aid, Green’s vision seemed unlikely to manifest anytime soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Trump’s foreign-aid cutoff still spells trouble for affected TB patients. “If left untreated,” Green explains, “most people who develop active TB will eventually die of the disease.” The symptoms vary, but for many patients, “Their lungs collapse or fill with fluid. Scarring leaves so little healthy lung tissue that breathing becomes impossible. The infection spreads to the brain or spinal column.” Others “suffer a sudden, uncontrollable hemorrhage, leading to a quick death as blood drowns the lungs.” And considering that the U.S. contributed about half of all international TB funding in 2024, it’s possible that the death toll this year will exceed even the 1.25 million that it &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/29-10-2024-tuberculosis-resurges-as-top-infectious-disease-killer"&gt;reached&lt;/a&gt; in 2023, the most recent year for which data are available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the risk of being too alarmist, lackluster treatment of TB in poor countries can have spillover effects in the first world. Tuberculosis is incredibly contagious (Green notes that the average TB patient spreads the infection to 10 to 15 others per year, compared to just 1 for flu and 1.4 to 2.4 for COVID), so as fewer patients get treatment, more of their family members, neighbors, and doctors are at risk of contracting the illness. And as the infection spreads further, it could be only a matter of time before TB reaches our shores with a virulence we haven’t yet experienced. Moreover, the more TB spreads, the more time it has to mutate and become resistant to the antibiotics we currently use to treat the disease. All of which is to say that funding TB treatment and prevention programs in countries like Sierra Leone seems like a wise investment that is, ironically, “consistent with U.S. foreign policy under the America First agenda,” as the State Department &lt;a href="https://www.state.gov/implementing-the-presidents-executive-order-on-reevaluating-and-realigning-united-states-foreign-aid/"&gt;put it&lt;/a&gt; in a press release on implementing Trump’s funding freeze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;But beyond the strategic benefit to maintaining our status as the world leader in TB treatment and prevention funding, there is also a profound moral case to be made in favor of doing so. The plight of tuberculosis sufferers like Henry may not register in the nationalistic worldview of people like President Trump, Vice President J.D. Vance, or Elon Musk, but that doesn’t mean those patients’ lives aren’t worth saving. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Henry ended up surviving his TB thanks to the tireless efforts of the doctor who begged, pleaded, and cajoled government authorities to get him a course of bedaquiline. It’s unrealistic to expect that all TB patients could be saved this way. But if we stopped treating tuberculosis as though we left it in the rearview mirror decades ago, Henry’s miraculous outcome could become much more routine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;            &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Dispatch</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 06:45:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxNaGJ1SGl4eFk0ZDVNTmZHRE02d3lmRzZDY3p4cGl6UzFkeUtrX2pDSVU4UlFETjhqeWpEemVLd0t6TnU2VVhoV1pDWFpHb01mSzFVWTlPcjY4SWdTM1JnRHBhZHZ0UXAxVTNQbEtncU13UlJvak5RV3Zrald3T21yOQ</guid></item><item><title>Message from Bay Area doctors: Get vaccinated for measles - The Mercury News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxPYnFjQWwxdnY3VU9FelVVczJaZWdtUUFwb09PYmozSDM0X2lKUVNhVzRwS2pnTzB5UGRndXo0N1dWa2Z3bkh3TkstSnN4YkozQjZsLURfaHJIUGRMWXNHLUxsS2VseWV3ekI2LWMwOFh5aXU5ZVlJS1l1c1pWa0JSNEtOclpSUFZuM09iUTdRb2ZXZG03bnVVT19NTjTSAaIBQVVfeXFMUHV5c2tROW9lZW1zWmVNc0hKQktQcHJza3VqWlJPWjRLd0ZaUUZxQXNZNGswRFpEZ0NvVXA5UTQ3UGVfRzZEcThDMzlHN3V2N19TZlozUXVVblhzVWExQS0wdl8tdmNVMGFNV1RVdHdnZTRhQ0dMQzBFQXR6QXFfMXRDOV9LZ01xTHh1SnRXclhYUVJIckh6cFRJODZjLU05c3pn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-copy"&gt;&lt;p class="wp-remixd-voice-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bay Area health officials came together Friday to urge residents in the region to get a &lt;a href="https://www.mercurynews.com/2025/03/10/measles-is-spreading-are-you-protected/"&gt;measles vaccination&lt;/a&gt; if they never received one or if they avoided the disease as a child.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a statement, the Association of Bay Area Health Officials said it was making the recommendation because measles cases are rising in the United States. Officials said measles cases in west Texas and New Mexico now number about 300 and that two people have died — the first deaths from the disease in the United State since 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;a href="https://www.mercurynews.com/2025/03/10/measles-is-spreading-are-you-protected/"&gt;Measles is spreading. Are you protected?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials said the risk of exposure to measles remains low in the Bay Area. The safest way to fight it is to get a measles, mumps and rubella (MMR) vaccination shot if you’re 12 months to 3 years old, and to get two of them if you’re older than 3.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Measles is one of the most contagious viruses in the world, but it is preventable with the MMR vaccine,” San Francisco Health Officer Dr. Susan Philip said in a statement. “If children in your family are not fully vaccinated, or if you did not have measles as a child, please get the vaccine for the best protection.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials said California has reported five measles cases and that they all developed after international travel. They said there is no evidence that those cases are connected to the ones in New Mexico or Texas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles can cause serious sickness and even death. It spreads through the air when an infected person breathes, talks, coughs or sneezes and can linger in the air for several hours. Symptoms include a fever, cough, runny nose and pink eye, followed by a rash. Health officials said children under 5 years old and adults over 20, pregnant women and people with compromised immune systems are at greatest risk&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p class="time mng-originally-published"&gt;Originally Published: &lt;time datetime="2025-03-14 13:37:24"&gt;March 14, 2025 at 1:37 PM PDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Mercury News</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 06:10:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPYnFjQWwxdnY3VU9FelVVczJaZWdtUUFwb09PYmozSDM0X2lKUVNhVzRwS2pnTzB5UGRndXo0N1dWa2Z3bkh3TkstSnN4YkozQjZsLURfaHJIUGRMWXNHLUxsS2VseWV3ekI2LWMwOFh5aXU5ZVlJS1l1c1pWa0JSNEtOclpSUFZuM09iUTdRb2ZXZG03bnVVT19NTjTSAaIBQVVfeXFMUHV5c2tROW9lZW1zWmVNc0hKQktQcHJza3VqWlJPWjRLd0ZaUUZxQXNZNGswRFpEZ0NvVXA5UTQ3UGVfRzZEcThDMzlHN3V2N19TZlozUXVVblhzVWExQS0wdl8tdmNVMGFNV1RVdHdnZTRhQ0dMQzBFQXR6QXFfMXRDOV9LZ01xTHh1SnRXclhYUVJIckh6cFRJODZjLU05c3pn</guid></item><item><title>I asked a gut health expert for her top three tips for a happier, healthier digestive system - Fit and Well</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixwFBVV95cUxNb0U1Ri1ycnZPTTlrM0E5NW1mYjhpZHVpTXNkeEw2dlpCeFFqZGNuUFFvVDAweFBfd0RNRVVEaUFIck94UGJSUGdJQ29XUHdxZWZrVTJyUS0zSDVRUXB2aGNONWVtbjdjTmZJVUtZQVE3VUowR1lBQmlCWXhJR1RocjNjZGprUGxYeDBITUs1c2YyLXh3QkhjeXZVZXFzZlJYRnJOanhfQm9fTEEzYjZlOU5ubUx4anUzTkYxY0t6R01rRzFrajhZ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bit by bit, scientists are unraveling the mysteries of gut health, and the more we learn, the more we realize how much the microorganisms living in our guts are responsible for, affecting things ranging from mood to skin health to hormone production.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two people who have experienced the science firsthand are Alana and Lisa Macfarlane, who participated in the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://twinsuk.ac.uk/" target="_blank" data-url="https://twinsuk.ac.uk/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;TwinsUK&lt;/a&gt; study and discovered that despite being twins, their &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5433529/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5433529/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;gut microbiota&lt;/a&gt; were substantially different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They went on to create &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://thegutstuff.com/" target="_blank" data-url="https://thegutstuff.com/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;The Gut Stuff &lt;/a&gt;to demystify the topic and help people improve their gut health. They’ve also authored &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://target.georiot.com/Proxy.ashx?tsid=110083&amp;amp;GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Famazon.com%2F-%2Fes%2FGut-Stuff-empowering-guide-microbes%2Fdp%2F191166347X%2Fref%3Dpd_lpo_d_sccl_2%2F145-8025832-1954035%3Ftag%3Dhawk-future-20%26ascsubtag%3Dfitandwell-gb-7283867468823168458-20" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.amazon.com/-/es/Gut-Stuff-empowering-guide-microbes/dp/191166347X/ref=pd_lpo_d_sccl_2/145-8025832-1954035?" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="hawklinks" data-placeholder-url="https://target.georiot.com/Proxy.ashx?tsid=110083&amp;amp;GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Famazon.com%2F-%2Fes%2FGut-Stuff-empowering-guide-microbes%2Fdp%2F191166347X%2Fref%3Dpd_lpo_d_sccl_2%2F145-8025832-1954035%3Ftag%3Dhawk-future-20%26ascsubtag%3Dhawk-custom-tracking-20" data-google-interstitial="false" data-merchant-name="Amazon US" data-merchant-id="1471" data-merchant-network="Amazon" data-merchant-url="amazon.com"&gt;books&lt;/a&gt;, presented tummy-churning &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.channel4.com/programmes/know-your-st-inside-our-guts" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.channel4.com/programmes/know-your-st-inside-our-guts" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;TV &lt;/a&gt;and launched a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://thegutstuff.com/the-gut-stuff-app-100-days-to-hack-your-gut-health/" target="_blank" data-url="https://thegutstuff.com/the-gut-stuff-app-100-days-to-hack-your-gut-health/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;100-day app-based program&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I spoke to Alana Macfarlane, who shared her top three tips for improving your gut health, but cautioned that you shouldn't expect things to change overnight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Unfortunately, with gut health, there is no quick fix,” says Macfarlane. “It's simple swaps and habits over a long period.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-1-get-to-know-your-poo"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Get to know your poo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using something called the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.england.nhs.uk/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bristol-stool-chart-for-carer-web-version.pdf" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.england.nhs.uk/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bristol-stool-chart-for-carer-web-version.pdf" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Bristol stool chart&lt;/a&gt;, you should be regularly checking to see what your bowel movements look like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We should all be about a three or a four,” says Macfarlane. “I think the poo taboo is real and it's time that we banished it because your poo is a brilliant indicator of your gut health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-ZnjTLSxMazm49bXi4owFZm" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-ZnjTLSxMazm49bXi4owFZm slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Kinga Krzeminska / Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowing what a normal bowel movement looks like for you can be helpful to flag when something's amiss with your digestive system. If you keep a food diary as well, you may begin to notice trends or be able to identify foods that trigger certain changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Macfarlane adds that there are red flags you should be looking out for too, like blood in your stool, which may indicate a medical issue that you should raise with a healthcare professional.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-2-eat-more-fiber"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Eat more fiber&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prebiotic_(nutrition)" target="_blank" data-url="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prebiotic_(nutrition)" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Prebiotic&lt;/a&gt; fiber is the food the community of microorganisms that make up our &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4290017/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4290017/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;gut microbiome&lt;/a&gt; eat. “If you're not feeding these bugs, they're not doing their jobs,” says Macfarlane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gut microbiome is what helps us to digest our food and extract vital nutrients, breaking them down into their fundamental parts so they can be absorbed into our bodies and used, so it’s important to keep them well-fed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6124841/#:~:text=Although%20adequate%20intake%20of%20all,consume%20recommended%20amounts%20of%20fiber." target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6124841/#:~:text=Although%20adequate%20intake%20of%20all,consume%20recommended%20amounts%20of%20fiber." referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;95% of Americans&lt;/a&gt; do not hit the recommended intake of 25-30g of fiber a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We're all having fiber, we're just not getting enough,” says Macfarlane. Thankfully, there are some simple swaps you can make to increase your fiber intake gradually. Replacing white pasta, rice and bread for wholegrain options is a great place to start. For example, white bread contains &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/174924/nutrients" target="_blank" data-url="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/174924/nutrients" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;2.7g of fiber&lt;/a&gt; per 100g, compared with &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/172688/nutrients" target="_blank" data-url="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/172688/nutrients" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;6g of fiber&lt;/a&gt; in whole wheat bread: more than double the fiber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you have an issue like IBS or IBD, you have to speak to your clinician about fiber because it can affect people in different ways. You might need to start slow and work your way up to a higher amount,” says Macfarlane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-3-drink-more-water"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Drink more water&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We all know we need to drink more water, but none of us get enough,” says Macfarlane. &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.umassmed.edu/nutrition/blog/blog-posts/2022/3/so-you-want-to-increase-your-fiber-intake/#:~:text=Fiber%20binds%20with%20water%20and,are%20increasing%20your%20fiber%20intake.&amp;amp;text=As%20you%20begin%20to%20eat,accustomed%20to%20eating%20much%20fiber." target="_blank" data-url="https://www.umassmed.edu/nutrition/blog/blog-posts/2022/3/so-you-want-to-increase-your-fiber-intake/#:~:text=Fiber%20binds%20with%20water%20and,are%20increasing%20your%20fiber%20intake.&amp;amp;text=As%20you%20begin%20to%20eat,accustomed%20to%20eating%20much%20fiber." referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Fiber binds with water&lt;/a&gt;, adding bulk to your stool, which is why it’s important to ensure you’re drinking lots of water with your fiber to avoid constipation. If you don’t, the fiber has nothing to flush it through your digestive system, which is why those hard stools are so difficult to pass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-person-ZnjTLSxMazm49bXi4owFZm-Um1GtByPQFtDByph5Z2iTOX2tTzESIwm" class="slice-container person-wrapper person-ZnjTLSxMazm49bXi4owFZm-Um1GtByPQFtDByph5Z2iTOX2tTzESIwm slice-container-person"&gt;&lt;div class="person person--separator person--strapline"&gt;&lt;span class="person__strapline"&gt;About our expert&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="person__heading"&gt;&lt;span class="person__strapline-inline"&gt;About our expert&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="person__name-socials"&gt;&lt;span class="person__name"&gt;Alana Macfarlane&lt;/span&gt;&lt;nav class="button-social-group person__social-buttons" aria-labelledby="button-social-group- person__social-buttons"&gt;&lt;p id="button-social-group- person__social-buttons"&gt;Social Links Navigation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="button-social   " href="https://www.instagram.com/themactwins/?hl=en%20" target="_blank" aria-label="INSTAGRAM"&gt;&lt;span class="button-social__icon"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon_instagram" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;circle cx="12" cy="12" fill="#de3073" r="12"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M18.958 9.116a5.121 5.121 0 00-.336-1.708 3.557 3.557 0 00-2.044-2.044 5.12 5.12 0 00-1.694-.322C14.142 5.014 13.89 5 12 5s-2.142.014-2.884.042a5.213 5.213 0 00-1.708.322 3.665 3.665 0 00-2.044 2.044 5.213 5.213 0 00-.322 1.708C5.014 9.858 5 10.1 5 12s.014 2.142.042 2.884a5.12 5.12 0 00.322 1.694 3.44 3.44 0 00.812 1.246 3.4 3.4 0 001.232.8 5.175 5.175 0 001.708.336c.742.028.98.042 2.884.042s2.142-.014 2.884-.042a5.082 5.082 0 001.694-.336 3.456 3.456 0 002.044-2.044 5.006 5.006 0 00.336-1.694C18.986 14.142 19 13.9 19 12s-.014-2.142-.042-2.884zM17.7 14.828a3.946 3.946 0 01-.252 1.3 2.189 2.189 0 01-.518.8 2.165 2.165 0 01-.8.532 4.641 4.641 0 01-1.3.238c-.742.028-.966.042-2.828.042s-2.1-.014-2.828-.042a3.837 3.837 0 01-1.3-.252A2.258 2.258 0 016.54 16.13a3.91 3.91 0 01-.238-1.3c-.028-.742-.042-.966-.042-2.828s.014-2.086.042-2.828a3.787 3.787 0 01.238-1.3A2.445 2.445 0 017.87 6.54a3.856 3.856 0 011.3-.238c.742-.028.952-.042 2.828-.042s2.086.014 2.828.042a3.787 3.787 0 011.3.238 2.445 2.445 0 011.33 1.33 4.641 4.641 0 01.238 1.3c.027.742.042.952.042 2.828s-.011 2.088-.036 2.83zM12 8.4a3.6 3.6 0 103.6 3.6A3.6 3.6 0 0012 8.4zm.181 5.929a2.338 2.338 0 01-.362-4.662 2.43 2.43 0 01.362 0 2.338 2.338 0 010 4.662zm3.557-6.909a.84.84 0 11-.84.84.84.84 0 01.84-.838z" fill="#fff"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="button-social   " href="https://thegutstuff.com/%20" target="_blank" aria-label="WEBSITE"&gt;&lt;span class="button-social__icon button-social__icon-website"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon-website" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 1000 1000"&gt;&lt;path d="M1000 500A501 501 0 0 0 503 0h-6A501 501 0 0 0 0 500c0 275 223 499 498 500h4a501 501 0 0 0 498-500zM529 936V765h133c-31 90-79 154-133 171zM337 765h134v171c-54-17-101-81-134-171zM61 539h176a899 899 0 0 0 22 167H110a439 439 0 0 1-49-166zM471 64v191H331c31-101 82-173 140-191zm199 191H529V64c58 18 109 90 140 191zm270 226H763c-1-59-7-115-18-167h155a438 438 0 0 1 40 167zm-235 0H529V314h156a857 857 0 0 1 19 167zM471 314v167H296a859 859 0 0 1 19-167h156zM237 481H60a438 438 0 0 1 41-167h154a921 921 0 0 0-18 167zm59 58h175v167H320a837 837 0 0 1-24-166zm233 167V539h175a831 831 0 0 1-24 167H529zm234-166h176a436 436 0 0 1-49 166H741a893 893 0 0 0 22-166zm104-285H731c-20-68-47-126-81-169a443 443 0 0 1 217 169zM350 86c-33 43-61 101-81 169H133A443 443 0 0 1 350 86zM148 765h127c20 59 45 110 75 150a442 442 0 0 1-202-150zm502 150c30-39 56-91 75-150h127a442 442 0 0 1-202 150z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/nav&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="person__bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alana Macfarlane is a presenter, DJ, author and co-founder of &lt;a href="https://thegutstuff.com/"&gt;The Gut Stuff &lt;/a&gt;with her twin sister, Lisa. The Gut Stuff has an expert team of scientists, nutritionists, dietitians and doctors working together to cut through some of the misinformation and pseudoscience surrounding gut health and help educate people on how to better care for their unique microbiome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit and Well</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 05:06:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixwFBVV95cUxNb0U1Ri1ycnZPTTlrM0E5NW1mYjhpZHVpTXNkeEw2dlpCeFFqZGNuUFFvVDAweFBfd0RNRVVEaUFIck94UGJSUGdJQ29XUHdxZWZrVTJyUS0zSDVRUXB2aGNONWVtbjdjTmZJVUtZQVE3VUowR1lBQmlCWXhJR1RocjNjZGprUGxYeDBITUs1c2YyLXh3QkhjeXZVZXFzZlJYRnJOanhfQm9fTEEzYjZlOU5ubUx4anUzTkYxY0t6R01rRzFrajhZ</guid></item><item><title>Dementia-link to bottled water as human brains found to contain teaspoon of plastic pieces - Surrey Live</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiigFBVV95cUxPaVVsZFV3SzVaUFI5TXFrN0RNVGk3dFF0dklXWjZFTXFpR0UwVlVyYzN2TmJPZWFnU0lieEFvNjJJcmM3TExYaUhDSjFZSVFtXzBCRjVKWkJkNXNqUHllTl9NRjFtTk9zb2tqWDFUVTRZRUJnOXNIYlplQk5KYVJpbTNnNnJMZ2kxX2fSAY8BQVVfeXFMUEVTOV9xZVZUTUJBdV96d1U4UU4wZFFuS2FZVGxLdURVcndvdTFGTTVCalJIZ190UEpoa1JPRS15N2l3VC11YkZVc1VwT2ZpT01GX3pqQW9UMi1DUzBLTlFhUVFjeEctYkxLRDFkWENDd1drSlA4V1c5SFhFUlBrSm1aRjV6STJHbndEbUZMazg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists have issued a warning after a study found the human brain contains about a spoon's worth of plastics. The levels of microplastics and nanoplastics (MNPs) were three to five times higher in brains belonging to those with dementia.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; According to an &lt;a href="https://genomicpress.kglmeridian.com/view/journals/brainmed/aop/article-10.61373-bm025c.0020/article-10.61373-bm025c.0020.xml" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;article published in Brain Medicine&lt;/a&gt; the discovery was "alarming" and warned this was "particularly in patients with dementia". And it said while it was almost impossible to avoid ingesting plastic there were ways to reduce the risk. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A number of studies over recent years have highlighted the increasing risk of consuming plastic. This has included microplastics affecting the lungs, fertility and inflammation.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Researchers published a study in Nature Medicine which found levels of microplastics in the brain are at much higher amounts than in other organs, such as the liver and kidneys. They also found that people in their study who were diagnosed with &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/142214" rel="nofollow"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt; had up to 10 times more microplastics present in their brains than those without the condition. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It found that the human brain contains approximately a spoon's worth of microplastics and nanoplastics. And those researchers warned these microplastics were of a smaller size (&amp;lt;200 nm) and most often polyethylene.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Commenting on the study Prof Tamara Galloway, Professor of Ecotoxicology, University of Exeter, said: “Microplastics are a ubiquitous consequence of modern life, present in air, water and food and it should come as no surprise to find that most people have microplastics present in their bodies. What we don’t yet know is what the implications are for human health.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Two things stand out from this study. The first is that there was no relationship between the age of the subjects and the amount of microplastics present in the brain samples. This is important because it suggests that microplastics do not accumulate continuously in brain tissues as we age. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The second thing to stand out is the increase in levels of contamination over time, with a 50% increase in levels of microplastics present in the brain samples collected over the last eight years, reflecting the increased production and use of plastics over a similar timeframe. This is significant because it suggests that if we were to reduce environmental contamination with microplastics, the levels of human exposure would also decrease, offering a strong incentive to focus on innovations that reduce exposure."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is the problem with plastic?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Plastic does not biodegrade but instead breaks down into smaller pieces - microplastics - which are eaten by animals. This means they find their way to the dinner table.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; They also find their way into our bodies through bottled water. And research shows even teabags are an offender for containing the product.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Experts writing in Brain Medicine said: "Given the widespread presence of microplastics in the environment, completely eliminating exposure is unrealistic. A more practical approach is to reduce the most significant sources of microplastic intake. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So what can we do about it? It's almost impossible to avoid but there are steps that can reduce the risk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Water&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;A study in the &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.est.9b01517" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;journal Environmental Science and Technology&lt;/a&gt; found bottled water was the second greatest source of microplastics - the first was the air we all breathe. In third place was seafood which the authors concluded made up the " large majority of microplastic intake".&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The researchers in that study believe changing from bottled water to tap water could reduce the intake of microplastics from 90,000 each year to 4,000. While the higher figure accounts for people who only drink bottled water and the lower for those exclusively tap water it means in reality most people will sit somewhere in between.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tea Bags&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;A separate study&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31552738/" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt; published in the same journal&lt;/a&gt; looked at teabag use. In the past the bags were made of paper but this has now switched to plastic for many manufacturers. The scientists steeped one teabag in 95C water and it released 14 billion microplastics into the drink.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For big tea drinkers it could be worth finding which firms still use paper for their bags. Yorkshire Tea is one which has acted on the plastic concerns saying: "The bags in all our regular UK Yorkshire Tea boxes are now plant based. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Most of the bag is made from natural fibres like wood pulp and the seal is made with PLA - an industrially compostable, plant-based plastic which is much better for the environment when it's properly disposed of."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reheating or storing food&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to the Brain Medicine team the kitchen is somewhere changes can be made. It looked at levels of BPA - a chemical compound used in the production of plastics, which is released when plastics degrade.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;They advised: "Stopping the practice of heating food in plastic could be one of the most effective ways to reduce microplastic consumption." They added: "Food storage may contribute to microplastic exposure.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"A randomised crossover trial of canned foods showed a more than 1000% rise in urinary bisphenol A (BPA) levels after five days of daily canned soup intake. This suggests that limiting canned food consumption and opting for non-plastic or BPA-free packaged alternatives can effectively reduce exposure. BPA spikes' duration and health impact remain unclear, warranting further research."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It also said avoiding plastic and opting for glass or stainless steel containers may reduce intake. It added: "Heating food in plastic containers, especially in the microwave, can release staggering amounts of microplastics and nanoplastics—up to 4.22 million and 2.11 billion particles per square centimetre in just three minutes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Even long-term storage at room temperature or in the fridge leads to significant plastic shedding. These plastics show toxic potential, with in vitro studies revealing up to 77% cell death in human kidney cells after prolonged exposure."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Processed foods&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Highly processed foods, like chicken nuggets, contained 30 times more microplastics per gram than chicken breasts, highlighting the impact of industrial processing, which often uses plastics at some point," says the Brain Medicine report.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Can you get rid of plastic from the body?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Little research has been done on how successful the body is at clearing microplastics, say the Brain Medicine experts. &lt;/span&gt;They said: "One study of 20 people measured BPA in blood, sweat, and urine. 16 of the individuals had BPA identified in their sweat, with this being the only identified source of BPA in some individuals.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"This suggests that induced sweating could facilitate the removal of BPA, though further studies are required to investigate its efficacy and long-term implications. While some evidence suggests that sweat may facilitate the excretion of certain plastic-derived compounds like BPA, no direct research currently confirms its role in reducing the microplastic burden in humans.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Further studies are needed to determine whether these strategies are effective in eliminating microplastics from the body."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The team concluded there was hope that the body could clear the microplastic accumulation as studies showed there was little evidence to show the older a person the more plastic in their body. They said this suggested that despite ongoing environmental exposures, the body has mechanisms to clear these particles over time through sweat, urine, and faeces.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;They added: "As methods for measuring microplastics in living humans improve, we can test the common-sense hypothesis that reducing intake of microplastics (e.g., drinking tap water, avoiding plastic tea bags, using metal or glass for cooking and storage, minimizing highly processed foods stored in plastic) and enhancing elimination may reduce accumulation in humans.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"In fish models, it takes approximately 70 days to clear 75% of accumulated brain microplastics, suggesting that decreased inputs and increased outputs must both be maintained for long enough durations to see measurable changes. As the knowledge increases, government-wide initiatives will help us reduce exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Surrey Live</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxPaVVsZFV3SzVaUFI5TXFrN0RNVGk3dFF0dklXWjZFTXFpR0UwVlVyYzN2TmJPZWFnU0lieEFvNjJJcmM3TExYaUhDSjFZSVFtXzBCRjVKWkJkNXNqUHllTl9NRjFtTk9zb2tqWDFUVTRZRUJnOXNIYlplQk5KYVJpbTNnNnJMZ2kxX2fSAY8BQVVfeXFMUEVTOV9xZVZUTUJBdV96d1U4UU4wZFFuS2FZVGxLdURVcndvdTFGTTVCalJIZ190UEpoa1JPRS15N2l3VC11YkZVc1VwT2ZpT01GX3pqQW9UMi1DUzBLTlFhUVFjeEctYkxLRDFkWENDd1drSlA4V1c5SFhFUlBrSm1aRjV6STJHbndEbUZMazg</guid></item><item><title>Dementia-link to bottled water as human brains found to contain teaspoon of plastic pieces - Surrey Live</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiigFBVV95cUxPaVVsZFV3SzVaUFI5TXFrN0RNVGk3dFF0dklXWjZFTXFpR0UwVlVyYzN2TmJPZWFnU0lieEFvNjJJcmM3TExYaUhDSjFZSVFtXzBCRjVKWkJkNXNqUHllTl9NRjFtTk9zb2tqWDFUVTRZRUJnOXNIYlplQk5KYVJpbTNnNnJMZ2kxX2c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists have issued a warning after a study found the human brain contains about a spoon's worth of plastics. The levels of microplastics and nanoplastics (MNPs) were three to five times higher in brains belonging to those with dementia.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; According to an &lt;a href="https://genomicpress.kglmeridian.com/view/journals/brainmed/aop/article-10.61373-bm025c.0020/article-10.61373-bm025c.0020.xml" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;article published in Brain Medicine&lt;/a&gt; the discovery was "alarming" and warned this was "particularly in patients with dementia". And it said while it was almost impossible to avoid ingesting plastic there were ways to reduce the risk. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A number of studies over recent years have highlighted the increasing risk of consuming plastic. This has included microplastics affecting the lungs, fertility and inflammation.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Researchers published a study in Nature Medicine which found levels of microplastics in the brain are at much higher amounts than in other organs, such as the liver and kidneys. They also found that people in their study who were diagnosed with &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/142214" rel="nofollow"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt; had up to 10 times more microplastics present in their brains than those without the condition. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It found that the human brain contains approximately a spoon's worth of microplastics and nanoplastics. And those researchers warned these microplastics were of a smaller size (&amp;lt;200 nm) and most often polyethylene.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Commenting on the study Prof Tamara Galloway, Professor of Ecotoxicology, University of Exeter, said: “Microplastics are a ubiquitous consequence of modern life, present in air, water and food and it should come as no surprise to find that most people have microplastics present in their bodies. What we don’t yet know is what the implications are for human health.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Two things stand out from this study. The first is that there was no relationship between the age of the subjects and the amount of microplastics present in the brain samples. This is important because it suggests that microplastics do not accumulate continuously in brain tissues as we age. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The second thing to stand out is the increase in levels of contamination over time, with a 50% increase in levels of microplastics present in the brain samples collected over the last eight years, reflecting the increased production and use of plastics over a similar timeframe. This is significant because it suggests that if we were to reduce environmental contamination with microplastics, the levels of human exposure would also decrease, offering a strong incentive to focus on innovations that reduce exposure."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is the problem with plastic?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Plastic does not biodegrade but instead breaks down into smaller pieces - microplastics - which are eaten by animals. This means they find their way to the dinner table.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; They also find their way into our bodies through bottled water. And research shows even teabags are an offender for containing the product.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Experts writing in Brain Medicine said: "Given the widespread presence of microplastics in the environment, completely eliminating exposure is unrealistic. A more practical approach is to reduce the most significant sources of microplastic intake. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So what can we do about it? It's almost impossible to avoid but there are steps that can reduce the risk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Water&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;A study in the &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.est.9b01517" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;journal Environmental Science and Technology&lt;/a&gt; found bottled water was the second greatest source of microplastics - the first was the air we all breathe. In third place was seafood which the authors concluded made up the " large majority of microplastic intake".&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The researchers in that study believe changing from bottled water to tap water could reduce the intake of microplastics from 90,000 each year to 4,000. While the higher figure accounts for people who only drink bottled water and the lower for those exclusively tap water it means in reality most people will sit somewhere in between.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tea Bags&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;A separate study&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31552738/" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt; published in the same journal&lt;/a&gt; looked at teabag use. In the past the bags were made of paper but this has now switched to plastic for many manufacturers. The scientists steeped one teabag in 95C water and it released 14 billion microplastics into the drink.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For big tea drinkers it could be worth finding which firms still use paper for their bags. Yorkshire Tea is one which has acted on the plastic concerns saying: "The bags in all our regular UK Yorkshire Tea boxes are now plant based. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Most of the bag is made from natural fibres like wood pulp and the seal is made with PLA - an industrially compostable, plant-based plastic which is much better for the environment when it's properly disposed of."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reheating or storing food&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to the Brain Medicine team the kitchen is somewhere changes can be made. It looked at levels of BPA - a chemical compound used in the production of plastics, which is released when plastics degrade.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;They advised: "Stopping the practice of heating food in plastic could be one of the most effective ways to reduce microplastic consumption." They added: "Food storage may contribute to microplastic exposure.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"A randomised crossover trial of canned foods showed a more than 1000% rise in urinary bisphenol A (BPA) levels after five days of daily canned soup intake. This suggests that limiting canned food consumption and opting for non-plastic or BPA-free packaged alternatives can effectively reduce exposure. BPA spikes' duration and health impact remain unclear, warranting further research."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It also said avoiding plastic and opting for glass or stainless steel containers may reduce intake. It added: "Heating food in plastic containers, especially in the microwave, can release staggering amounts of microplastics and nanoplastics—up to 4.22 million and 2.11 billion particles per square centimetre in just three minutes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Even long-term storage at room temperature or in the fridge leads to significant plastic shedding. These plastics show toxic potential, with in vitro studies revealing up to 77% cell death in human kidney cells after prolonged exposure."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Processed foods&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Highly processed foods, like chicken nuggets, contained 30 times more microplastics per gram than chicken breasts, highlighting the impact of industrial processing, which often uses plastics at some point," says the Brain Medicine report.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Can you get rid of plastic from the body?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Little research has been done on how successful the body is at clearing microplastics, say the Brain Medicine experts. &lt;/span&gt;They said: "One study of 20 people measured BPA in blood, sweat, and urine. 16 of the individuals had BPA identified in their sweat, with this being the only identified source of BPA in some individuals.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"This suggests that induced sweating could facilitate the removal of BPA, though further studies are required to investigate its efficacy and long-term implications. While some evidence suggests that sweat may facilitate the excretion of certain plastic-derived compounds like BPA, no direct research currently confirms its role in reducing the microplastic burden in humans.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Further studies are needed to determine whether these strategies are effective in eliminating microplastics from the body."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The team concluded there was hope that the body could clear the microplastic accumulation as studies showed there was little evidence to show the older a person the more plastic in their body. They said this suggested that despite ongoing environmental exposures, the body has mechanisms to clear these particles over time through sweat, urine, and faeces.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;They added: "As methods for measuring microplastics in living humans improve, we can test the common-sense hypothesis that reducing intake of microplastics (e.g., drinking tap water, avoiding plastic tea bags, using metal or glass for cooking and storage, minimizing highly processed foods stored in plastic) and enhancing elimination may reduce accumulation in humans.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"In fish models, it takes approximately 70 days to clear 75% of accumulated brain microplastics, suggesting that decreased inputs and increased outputs must both be maintained for long enough durations to see measurable changes. As the knowledge increases, government-wide initiatives will help us reduce exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Surrey Live</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxPaVVsZFV3SzVaUFI5TXFrN0RNVGk3dFF0dklXWjZFTXFpR0UwVlVyYzN2TmJPZWFnU0lieEFvNjJJcmM3TExYaUhDSjFZSVFtXzBCRjVKWkJkNXNqUHllTl9NRjFtTk9zb2tqWDFUVTRZRUJnOXNIYlplQk5KYVJpbTNnNnJMZ2kxX2c</guid></item><item><title>Two house cats infected with bird flu in New York City: health officials - New York Daily News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirAFBVV95cUxPdnU1VG1ZNjFNcmpnRERrUjlUNE1SZ3ZQNUFEYUtxcUI5R2hPWktkZ1ZvMjR0dUpMREZYa0VIbTNUNW1rbnM3OTAxRzlENC0tQ3FvV25BSHRzbUNObEZRSGdMcmdjNUJaVjB2bzhMbXZvYVJ3MTMzcG5sSENvSFZDODRkQ3BUdE1WbFlNT3pvWkpqdW5ZcE00R0ZvUlJTNTJib3NkcDJTeVdSalht?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-copy"&gt;&lt;p class="wp-remixd-voice-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two cats in different households in New York City were infected with bird flu, the city’s Health Department &lt;a href="https://www.nyc.gov/assets/doh/downloads/pdf/press/2025/03142025-bird-flu-cats.pdf"&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Officials did not disclose the cats’ conditions and are still investigating how they contracted the virus, but urged pet owners not to let their felines roam outdoors or feed them raw food or raw milk — common ways avian influenza can be transmitted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The current risk to New Yorkers of bird flu remains low,” Michelle Morse, acting commissioner of the New York City Health Department, said in a statement Friday. “Bird flu viruses present a wider risk to the general public only if the virus develops the ability to transmit between people — which we have not seen.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s possible for people to catch bird flu from animals, however, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/bird-flu/virus-transmission/avian-in-humans.html"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. Since the start of the current outbreak in 2022, 70 people have been infected with bird flu, one of whom died, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="s2nPlayer k-Gqp3X1BH" data-type="float" data-s2n-api="dfm_stn_player_script_id_Gqp3X1BH"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Feb. 7, after detection of avian flu at seven live poultry markets in Brooklyn, the Bronx and Queens, Gov. Hochul ordered all live bird markets in New York City, plus Westchester, Suffolk and Nassau counties, 82 fowl markets in all, &lt;a href="https://agriculture.ny.gov/news/governor-hochul-announces-additional-measures-prevent-spread-highly-pathogenic-avian-influenza"&gt;to close for a week, and to be cleaned and disinfected&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p class="time mng-originally-published"&gt;Originally Published: &lt;time datetime="2025-03-14 23:55:33"&gt;March 14, 2025 at 11:55 PM EDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Daily News</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:55:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxPdnU1VG1ZNjFNcmpnRERrUjlUNE1SZ3ZQNUFEYUtxcUI5R2hPWktkZ1ZvMjR0dUpMREZYa0VIbTNUNW1rbnM3OTAxRzlENC0tQ3FvV25BSHRzbUNObEZRSGdMcmdjNUJaVjB2bzhMbXZvYVJ3MTMzcG5sSENvSFZDODRkQ3BUdE1WbFlNT3pvWkpqdW5ZcE00R0ZvUlJTNTJib3NkcDJTeVdSalht</guid></item><item><title>OSDH reports 2 probable measles cases, potential public exposures - News On 6</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwFBVV95cUxNdWpRbjc0cnJmY0k1Z0lFcVV6NFhzU3pQcXpBTjZibjh6ZEE3YzhuZnRrMm1HYkhBZXp4Zmd4R29ubEpJQ3k5RDN5RW5obDZkUXVhZHN5UENhdEpTXzExdkRIMDdLWlh2dGFNQjVKQnpZQ2ZVQ0RUZUhMVHNuNnRKYWFlTHpLRmRvN0MzSnVxTXI0SGtJQTRJRjdha2puYl9adFBGekszV0hiWWR1N1N0N2VOQnhOOU41dEx3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="viking-story-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Oklahoma State Department of Health (OSDH) has identified two additional probable measles cases, officials announced Friday. The cases were reported on March 14, and an investigation is underway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials said the individuals were in public settings while contagious, potentially exposing others to the virus. The following locations have been identified as possible exposure sites:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;February 27, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li data-list="bullet"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kohl's&lt;/strong&gt; (12405 E 96th St N, Owasso) | 1:30 - 5:30 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-list="bullet"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aldi&lt;/strong&gt; (9259 N Owasso Expressway, Owasso) | 4:20 - 7:00 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-list="bullet"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walmart Supercenter&lt;/strong&gt; (12101 E 96th St N, Owasso) | 5:15 - 8:00 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-list="bullet"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sam’s Club&lt;/strong&gt; (12905 E 96th St N, Owasso) | 7:00 - 9:21 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-list="bullet"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sprouts Farmers Market&lt;/strong&gt; (9601 N 133rd E Ave, Owasso) | 7:30 - 10:02 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March 2, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li data-list="bullet"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lowe’s Home Improvement&lt;/strong&gt; (1746 S Lynn Riggs Blvd, Claremore) | 7:00 - 9:27 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials urge anyone who visited these locations during the listed times and is unvaccinated, unsure of their vaccine status, or concerned about exposure to &lt;a href="https://redcap.health.ok.gov/surveys/?s=474CYE3F9F"&gt;complete this form&lt;/a&gt;. Health officials will provide further guidance between 8 a.m. and 8 p.m., seven days a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those exposed who are not immune should avoid public settings for 21 days from their exposure date. Individuals experiencing flu-like symptoms, fever, or a new rash and who visited these locations should self-isolate and contact their healthcare provider before seeking medical care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The OSDH Epidemiologist-on-Call can be reached at 405-426-8710 from 8 a.m. to 8 p.m. daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials confirmed these cases are linked to the Texas and New Mexico outbreak and not the two cases announced on March 11. All four probable cases in Oklahoma involved unvaccinated individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Per state law, measles is an immediately notifiable disease. Health care providers, laboratories, and hospitals must report suspected or confirmed cases to the OSDH immediately at 405-426-8710, available 24/7.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The OSDH is working with the Tulsa Health Department on this investigation and will provide updates at &lt;a href="https://Oklahoma.gov/health/measles"&gt;Oklahoma.gov/health/measles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>News On 6</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 02:37:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxNdWpRbjc0cnJmY0k1Z0lFcVV6NFhzU3pQcXpBTjZibjh6ZEE3YzhuZnRrMm1HYkhBZXp4Zmd4R29ubEpJQ3k5RDN5RW5obDZkUXVhZHN5UENhdEpTXzExdkRIMDdLWlh2dGFNQjVKQnpZQ2ZVQ0RUZUhMVHNuNnRKYWFlTHpLRmRvN0MzSnVxTXI0SGtJQTRJRjdha2puYl9adFBGekszV0hiWWR1N1N0N2VOQnhOOU41dEx3</guid></item><item><title>A New York City Pediatric Infectious-Diseases Doctor's Dire Warning - Air Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiZ0FVX3lxTE5LNFNBMXc2ckxTQmJNejBuVlFvRGNaYmFfWkpHT2lEb2dmUDljdlBEVS1LclRSOXVCREhPMXpQN1hNMHV1Zmg2bmlCbnpDanVycEQxV21BdDBKWmNSMTZ0ZTBBb1VFUWM?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-template-default" data-article-target="body"&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="drop-cap"&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;’ve spent a lot of time in children’s hospitals. I trained as a pediatric resident in New York City at the turn of the millennium and was a pediatric infectious-diseases fellow in Philadelphia after that. Twenty-five years later, I still love the challenge of a difficult diagnosis, the chance to help a family through a hard time, a moment of connection with a frightened kid. Children’s hospitals are places that no family wants to end up, but they’re also places of immense hope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was a tiny part of a long, steady progression in the profession of pediatrics. Thanks to an upward curve of knowledge and skill, we could do more to help sick children than the generation of pediatricians before us, and my colleagues and I would inevitably be surpassed by the generation that followed.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p class="prewall-fade"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="paywall-card m-b-lg print:hidden" aria-role="region" tabindex="0" aria-label="Air Mail Pay wall, please enter your e-mail address to read the full article"&gt;
  &lt;aside class="paywall-signup is-hidden" data-controller="paywall paywall-capture" data-paywall-type-value="capture" data-paywall-capture-article-value="q4hoP1" aria-hidden="true" data-purpose="paywall-capture"&gt;

  

  &lt;div class="text-content is-centered"&gt;
  &lt;h2 class="article-card-title" data-paywall-capture-target="headline"&gt;
    
      Enter your e-mail to read the full story for free&lt;br&gt;and to receive our weekly e-mail newsletter
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;

  
    
  

  

  &lt;p class="mt-5 text-center text-md" data-paywall-capture-target="intro"&gt;
    Or &lt;a href="/AMSTPATTY5025?from=q4hoP1" data-turbo="false"&gt;subscribe to AIR MAIL&lt;/a&gt; for full access. Start your &lt;em&gt;free trial&lt;/em&gt; today.
  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;p class="mt-5 mb-0 article-card-text text-center" data-paywall-capture-target="existing"&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;Already a subscriber? &lt;a href="/subscription/sign-in?from=q4hoP1"&gt;Sign in here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/aside&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Air Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 02:07:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZ0FVX3lxTE5LNFNBMXc2ckxTQmJNejBuVlFvRGNaYmFfWkpHT2lEb2dmUDljdlBEVS1LclRSOXVCREhPMXpQN1hNMHV1Zmg2bmlCbnpDanVycEQxV21BdDBKWmNSMTZ0ZTBBb1VFUWM</guid></item><item><title>Officials confirm Michigan’s first measles case of 2025 - WOODTV.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxQYlhrdHFMUW9sSkgwSUZCY2xjNEs5cU5uVWo4aW9KN3oxbmZ6WmFjc1NSclROYkJnUzFGT29XN1J5Q2FTZ2hhNXFEejBfRDVwRnZmOFJCSTkzaTB2SU9FNi1RbS1DUkxra3JLVTJwcmdmaWswQjJDTEI5VW5ObHo1ZVNxX19CdVhsSDlKV3E1VEc1bVZzaWMw0gGcAUFVX3lxTE9vMWlTckhpNUdTaGRGeEFDanNObVZmU3c4dzBWaVJhVEt0Zm1ZSjBVRkxUT3dvV2txeUs5aHZmd2dveUpSZjM3WjhJQmk0bVlmVGI4eUg2bGZFVFM0cGUwdnpsOUVRbWxYY21rQXo0U3pOWTRrTWtvOTh5ZkpocVljSzVvcGN2X1ROd3c4Y2NWOVVBT2RoY2hWUlBZQg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>WOODTV.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 00:21:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQYlhrdHFMUW9sSkgwSUZCY2xjNEs5cU5uVWo4aW9KN3oxbmZ6WmFjc1NSclROYkJnUzFGT29XN1J5Q2FTZ2hhNXFEejBfRDVwRnZmOFJCSTkzaTB2SU9FNi1RbS1DUkxra3JLVTJwcmdmaWswQjJDTEI5VW5ObHo1ZVNxX19CdVhsSDlKV3E1VEc1bVZzaWMw0gGcAUFVX3lxTE9vMWlTckhpNUdTaGRGeEFDanNObVZmU3c4dzBWaVJhVEt0Zm1ZSjBVRkxUT3dvV2txeUs5aHZmd2dveUpSZjM3WjhJQmk0bVlmVGI4eUg2bGZFVFM0cGUwdnpsOUVRbWxYY21rQXo0U3pOWTRrTWtvOTh5ZkpocVljSzVvcGN2X1ROd3c4Y2NWOVVBT2RoY2hWUlBZQg</guid></item></channel></rss>