<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>肯尼迪可能会彻底改革儿童疫苗接种计划，建议美国儿童少接种疫苗- WRAL</title><link>https://www.wral.com/news/local/health-kennedy-childhood-vaccine-schedule-denmark/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;
					&lt;p id="font-resize" class="font-resize-container"&gt;
						&lt;button id="small-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa small-buttom-font-svg" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;button id="medium-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;button id="large-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;

					
						&lt;p&gt;Over the last year, Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. and his appointees have taken tentative steps toward his goal of remaking the childhood vaccination schedule.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;But emboldened by a directive from President Donald Trump, Kennedy is now poised to make a seismic shift. He is expected to announce in the new year that American children should be immunized according to a different schedule with fewer vaccines, used by the much smaller, largely homogenous country of Denmark.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
								
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;A wholesale revision of the schedule would bypass the evidence-based, committee-led process that has underpinned vaccine recommendations in the country for decades, and could affect whether private insurance and government assistance programs will cover the shots.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;And many medical experts worry that losing strong endorsements of some vaccines will create financial and logistical hurdles to obtaining them, further erode Americans’ confidence in immunizations and increase the chances of disease outbreaks. Measles and whooping cough are already resurgent in multiple states because of dropping vaccination rates.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;It is unclear whether any changes will still protect vaccine manufacturers from being sued for claims of harm. Without that guarantee, companies might face “frivolous” lawsuits and flee the American market as they did before such protections were instituted in the 1980s, some vaccine experts warned.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Trump directed Kennedy to align recommendations for childhood vaccines with “best practices from peer, developed countries,” calling the United States “a high outlier in the number of vaccinations recommended for all children.” He pointed to Denmark, Germany and Japan as examples of nations that immunize against fewer diseases.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;The directive said that health officials should make the changes “while preserving access to vaccines currently available to Americans,” suggesting to some public health experts that those who wish to get them may still be able to do so in consultation with a health care provider.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
								&lt;p class="opscoad-Mobile_In_Content" data-unit="wral-v4/news/local/health-kennedy-childhood-vaccine-schedule-denmark"&gt;
								&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;p class="opscoad-article_in_read" data-unit="wral-v4/news/local/health-kennedy-childhood-vaccine-schedule-denmark/"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Still, even if only some Americans follow a reshaped schedule that includes fewer immunizations, medical experts said, it is almost certain to lead to more cases of infectious disease.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;“They’re going to bring back suffering and death,” said Dr. Sean O’Leary, chair of the infectious disease committee for the American Academy of Pediatrics. “I don’t say that with any hyperbole. That’s exactly what’s going to happen.”&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;The Department of Health and Human Services did not immediately respond to a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;This article originally appeared in &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/19/health/kennedy-childhood-vaccine-schedule-denmark.html"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
					
				&lt;/div&gt;


				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WRAL</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:55:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNMWRmWXVZMzJnQmt1VGFfY1E5ZUhhclVjbVByelFhVDdWT1pNME1vMExRN1JHYnh2c0JKWjJqNC1FZm1aQ2xyS085c2Jjcl81OVJCT1V3WkRuLTdXS0c3cnUzLUJPR2d3VDdpR2lJVTBDM3pMY1FzYTktcU1mR0x4ZXV0V2dLVUZVNlE</guid></item><item><title>“永远的化学物质”与另一种毁灭性的终身疾病有关：研究-纽约邮报</title><link>https://nypost.com/2025/12/20/health/forever-chemicals-linked-to-devastating-lifelong-condition/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom"&gt;
							


&lt;p&gt;The news just keeps getting worse for “forever chemicals.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;These man-made substances — designed to repel oil, water and stains — can be found in &lt;a href="https://www.niehs.nih.gov/health/topics/agents/pfc" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;thousands of everyday items&lt;/a&gt;, from nonstick pans and fast-food wrappers to waterproof jackets. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Scientists have already linked them to a laundry list of health problems, including &lt;a href="https://keck.usc.edu/news/usc-study-shows-how-pfas-disrupt-healthy-function-in-human-liver-cells/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;liver damage&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://hsph.harvard.edu/news/exposure-to-pfas-associated-with-increased-blood-lipids-possible-cvd-risk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;high cholesterol&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2023/03/21/inescapable-forever-chemicals-hurt-pregnancy-odds-warning-to-women/"&gt;fertility troubles&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/12/09/health/forever-chemicals-may-triple-risk-of-infant-death-new-study/"&gt;birth defects&lt;/a&gt; and several types of &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2022/08/09/forever-chemicals-linked-to-liver-cancer-in-first-human-study/"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Forever chemicals don’t break down easily, accumulating in the environment and the human body over time.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;luchschenF – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Now, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0160412025007445?via%3Dihub" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;new research&lt;/a&gt; suggests that people exposed to two major environmental toxins — perfluorooctane sulfonic acid (PFOS) and polychlorinated biphenyls (PCBs) — are more likely to be diagnosed with multiple sclerosis, or MS. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="connatix-outstream-video"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chronic autoimmune disease attacks the central nervous system, disrupting communication between the brain and the rest of the body. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It can lead to a wide range of symptoms, including numbness, muscle weakness, trouble walking, vision problems, extreme fatigue, pain and cognitive difficulties.&lt;/p&gt;


	



&lt;p&gt;“People with the highest concentrations of PFOS and PCBs had approximately twice as high odds of being diagnosed with MS, compared with those with the lowest concentrations,” Kim Kultima, who led the study, said in a &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-exposure-pfas-pcbs-linked-higher.html#goog_rewarded" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Previous research has shown that forever chemicals can &lt;a href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.2105018118" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;interfere with the immune system&lt;/a&gt;, either weakening it or sending it into overdrive. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That immune disruption has been tied to autoimmune diseases beyond MS, including &lt;a href="https://www.jrheum.org/content/52/Suppl_1/123" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;lupus&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12170615/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;rheumatoid arthritis&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11209830/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;inflammatory bowel disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Difficulty walking is one of the most common and debilitating symptoms of multiple sclerosis. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Halfpoint – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In the new study, Kultima and her team analyzed blood samples from 900 people in Sweden recently diagnosed with MS and compared them with samples from people without the disease.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The researchers measured toxin levels in each group, then used statistical models to see how strongly chemical exposure lined up with the odds of developing MS. &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Because people are typically exposed to multiple chemicals at once, the team also looked at how combined exposure affected their risk.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“We could then see that an increase in total exposure was linked to higher odds of MS, even after adjusting for previously known lifestyle and genetic risk factors,” said Aina Vaivade, the study’s first author. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The team also dug into genetics, looking at how inherited traits might interact with chemical exposure.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In earlier studies, people carrying a certain gene variant were thought to have a lower risk of developing MS. However, the new research found that those same people had higher odds of MS if they were also exposed to elevated levels of PFOS. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“This indicates that there is a complex interaction between inheritance and environmental exposure linked to the odds of MS,” Kultima said. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“We therefore think it is important to understand how environmental contaminants interact with hereditary factors, as this can provide new knowledge about the genesis of MS and could also be relevant for other diseases,” she added. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Multiple sclerosis affects the brain and spinal chord, disrupting communication with the rest of the body.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Valerii Apetroaiei – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While the study focused on people with MS, it adds to mounting evidence that these chemicals pose serious long-term health risks.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;They seep into the soil, water and air — and studies show nearly all Americans have &lt;a href="https://www.nationalmssociety.org/understanding-ms/what-is-ms/who-gets-ms/how-many-people" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;measurable levels in their blood&lt;/a&gt;, including newborns.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;Even more troubling, the toxins don’t break down easily, allowing them to linger in the environment, and inside the human body, for an unknown amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That’s why PCBs, despite being &lt;a href="https://ecology.wa.gov/blog/january-2024/polychlorinated-biphenyls-pcbs-were-banned-45-years-ago-why-are-they-still-a-problem" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;banned in the US since 1979&lt;/a&gt;, are still found in the environment and older products. PFAS, meanwhile, remain widely used today.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="comments-inline-cta" data-comment-count data-prompt="What do you think?"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Experts say there are steps you can take to reduce your exposure, such as &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/07/26/health/new-tool-can-remove-99-of-a-forever-chemical-from-water/"&gt;filtering drinking water&lt;/a&gt; and steering clear of nonstick cookware and grease-resistant food packaging.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Looking for “PFAS-free” labels and choosing fresh, unpackaged foods can further help cut down contact with these chemicals both at home and in your everyday diet.&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;

												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 15:05:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxNOE9nb0dqV0RXVERHdUhCSHhjdUQ4Z3E5b04xQlNwbktDN3V3MGstZzNXaFUwUDdlbjMwbUhRc1hER0xleWw3QUFlUl9VWXZLVmdybjBuY24xaFNyazkxeVFyZkdxS0MtRm5JZk9VTkgtallob0RPWWhUd2VrLW5iLVBtcUJsX2d5T05mYWJOTFl1cTluUHNjSWhvazE</guid></item><item><title>即将崩溃的女性通常会开始为自己购买这11样东西- YourTango</title><link>https://www.yourtango.com/self/women-verge-breaking-down-usually-start-buying-these-things-for-themselves</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every day, many people struggle to keep it together. No matter what life throws their way, they do their best to push those ugly feelings aside and push forward. Unfortunately, stress and overwhelm eventually catch up, which can create a desire to purchase certain items to bring calm and relaxation. And whether it's candles or loads of takeout, women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot of women, in particular, feel pressure to juggle everything and maintain their composure. From landing their dream career to being the perfect mother, womanhood is exhausting, to say the least. When a woman begins buying certain things, it could be a strong indicator that she's spiraling mentally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these 11 things for themselves&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Comfy weighted blankets&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-comfy-blankets.png" alt="woman enjoying tea wrapped in a weighted blanket" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves comfy weighted blankets" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;dekazigzag | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a woman finds it comfortable and they're going through it, expect them to add a weighted blanket to their online cart immediately. Sure, she may have a few blankets in her bed already, but another one never hurts. And for many, something is grounding about sleeping with a weighted blanket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a &lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/279846113_Positive_effects_of_a_weighted_blanket_on_insomnia" rel="nofollow"&gt;study published in the Journal of Sleep Medicine and Disorders&lt;/a&gt;, weighted blankets actually have a positive effect on sleep. People report feeling more comfortable and safe while sleeping with a weighted blanket. So, if a woman is close to experiencing a mental break of sorts, having weight on top of her might be just what she needs to feel good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/small-signs-woman-who-deeply-unhappy-with-her-life"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Small Signs Of A Woman Who Is Deeply Unhappy With Her Life&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. Self-improvement journals&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-self-improvement-journals.png" alt="woman on the verge of breaking down writing in a journal" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves self improvement journals" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;PeopleImages | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone wants to &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/ways-become-better-version-yourself"&gt;be the best version of themselves&lt;/a&gt;, growing and learning throughout life. But as things become harder and pressure builds, we abandon these goals entirely. And sometimes, it takes something drastic to make a woman snap out of it and focus on herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying self-improvement journals for themselves as a way to feel grounded with nowhere else to turn to. They invest in journaling and engage in it religiously. While they might not be able to afford a therapist, they know that healthy venting of their emotions is crucial to keeping them from breaking down completely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/signs-youre-not-lazy-youre-just-emotionally-done"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Signs You're Not Lazy — You're Just Emotionally Done&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. Skincare products&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-skincare-products.png" alt="woman with towel wrapped around hair applying skincare products" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves skincare products" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Gorgev | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For women who are running themselves dry, it's probably been a while since they prioritized their skincare. So busy with everything and everyone else around them, they barely have enough time to properly take care of themselves, let alone their body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sure, she might have a lot of products, from the newest Korean skincare mask all the way to an overpriced lip balm. However, it never hurts to buy one more thing if it's going to help with self-care. And as &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/a-deeper-wellness/202302/understanding-the-mental-health-and-self-care-connection"&gt;clinical psychologist Monica Vermani&lt;/a&gt; pointed out, "Quality &lt;a href="https://www.nimh.nih.gov/health/topics/caring-for-your-mental-health" rel="nofollow"&gt;self-care is linked to improved mental health&lt;/a&gt;, with benefits like enhanced self-esteem and self-worth, increased optimism, a positive outlook on life, and lower levels of anxiety and depression."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/love/wives-stay-quiet-during-arguments-usually-feel-these-things-theyll-never-admit"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wives Who Stay Quiet During Arguments Usually Feel These 11 Things They'll Never Admit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4. Assortments of tea&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-tea.png" alt="smiling woman in cardigan drinking tea " title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves tea" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Drazen Zigic | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coffee is amazing, especially on tough days when people don't feel like getting up for work. But coffee isn't as calming as tea and can make a woman's mental breakdown worse. For a woman like this, she may end up buying lots of different teas to try, often drinking it for comfort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/live-long-and-prosper/202207/taking-time-for-tea-comforting-rituals-in-stressful-times"&gt;well-being researcher Jasmin Tahmaseb-McConatha&lt;/a&gt; said, rituals like drinking tea can "soothe difficult times, relieve anxiety and stress, and connect us to others." So, the next time a woman feels anxious, a nice &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health/affordable-ways-to-calm-your-nerves"&gt;hot cup of tea will calm her nerves&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/subtle-signs-woman-who-has-been-through-lot-life-according-research"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Subtle Signs Of A Woman Who Has Been Through A Lot In Life, According To Research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;5. Comfort clothes&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-comfort-clothes.png" alt="woman in comfort clothes standing outside with tea" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves comfort clothes" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Aleksandra Suzi | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nobody likes wearing overly tight clothes. Whether it's at work or with the in-laws, these restrictive clothes can make a woman's mental state worse. Filled with anxiety, she might feel more trapped than ever before. And while she may be at her wits' end right now, slipping into comfortable clothing can do wonders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From wearing sweatpants to baggy shirts, women who are having a breakdown make sure they're comfortable. While they can't control what's happening around them, they can change small things to make themselves feel just a little less anxious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/subtle-signs-not-just-stressed-completely-exhausted-emotionally"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;15 Subtle Signs You're Not Just Stressed, You're Completely Exhausted Emotionally&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;6. Candles&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-candles.png" alt="woman smelling candles at the store" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves candles" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Vladeep | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying candles for themselves. And while it might not make much sense, candles have a bigger impact on people than most realize. Besides the warmth it provides, candles can play a part in improving mental health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://www.kacadas.com/blogs/default-blog/can-candles-have-an-effect-on-your-mental-health" rel="nofollow"&gt;psychotherapist and cognitive behavioral therapist Chryssa Chalkia&lt;/a&gt;, "It is scientifically proven that scented candles can play an essential role in the physiological effects of mood, stress, working capacity, and overall mental health... The smell of scented candles stimulates our limbic system, the part of the brain that is home to our memory and emotions. Hormones like serotonin and dopamine can be produced to help regulate mood."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/little-things-deeply-unhappy-people-have-homes-anyone-else-never-buy"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Little Things Deeply Unhappy People Have In Their Homes That No One Else Would Ever Buy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;7. Takeout&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-takeout.png" alt="woman in suit eating takeout" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves takeout" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;PeopleImages | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life can get exhausting, whether it's juggling work, family, or other responsibilities. For women experiencing burnout and exhaustion, cooking is the last thing they're worried about, so they'll often order takeout. It might not be the healthiest option, but takeout in moderation isn't necessarily a bad thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not only is it convenient, but it can bring a ton of comfort too. In fact, &lt;a href="https://www.upi.com/Health_News/2011/03/27/Meatloaf-mashed-potatoes-fight-loneliness/UPI-79641301252021/" rel="nofollow"&gt;one study published in Psychological Science&lt;/a&gt; found that comfort foods can improve our mood. So, women shouldn't be afraid to eat takeout, as there's a small sense of joy in enjoying a comforting meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/things-emotionally-exhausted-people-start-avoiding-completely"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Things Emotionally Exhausted People Start Avoiding Completely&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;8. Supplements and wellness products&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-supplement-and-wellness-products.png" alt="woman taking daily supplements with water" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves supplement and wellness products" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;insta_photos | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life can get busy, especially for women who are mothers and working full-time. They don't always have the time to care about their health. But whether it's supplements to improve their fiber intake or strengthen their gut, ​​women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many women who are worn down find themselves worrying about every little thing. Especially with so many health scares, to keep their sanity in check, they'll purchase wellness products for peace of mind and sanity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/money/grew-up-broke-made-it-still-probably-cant-bring-yourself-buy-simple-things"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If You Grew Up Broke But Made It, You Still Probably Can't Bring Yourself To Buy These 11 Simple Things&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;9. New hobbies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-new-hobbies.png" alt="woman painting enjoying new hobby" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves new hobbies" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;GBJSTOCK | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a woman is stressed and looking for an escape, there are a ton of things she can do. She may not be great at painting or fishing, but because she's been feeling overwhelmed, with no other option, she's finding a great way to escape from reality by buying new hobbies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Engaging in new hobbies is actually a good thing. According to &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/social-instincts/202502/3-kinds-of-hobbies-that-can-help-us-thrive"&gt;psychologist Mark Travers&lt;/a&gt;, "While physical and creative hobbies nurture your body and soul, &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/special-interests-women-who-are-more-intelligent-than-everyone-else"&gt;intellectual hobbies keep your mind sharp&lt;/a&gt;, curious, and engaged with the world around you... In this way, finding a hobby that challenges your intellect can feel like rediscovering a part of yourself you didn't realize was missing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/signs-woman-emotionally-drained-but-keeps-pushing-through"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Signs A Woman Is Emotionally Drained But Keeps Pushing Through&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;10. Organizing items&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-organization-items.png" alt="woman doing laundry " title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves organization items" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Evgeny Atamanenko | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once a woman is going through it, her environment will show it. From clothes on the floor to dishes on the countertop, her surroundings look disastrous. But by purchasing items intended for organizing her home, she's on a mission to improve herself from the outside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because &lt;a href="https://www.webmd.com/balance/ss/slideshow-clutter-affects-health"&gt;clutter can negatively affect a person's mental health&lt;/a&gt;, she's prepared to spend hours &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/quick-organizing-tips-declutter-your-home"&gt;dusting, organizing, and cleaning her home&lt;/a&gt; until it's spotless. Not only does it feel good, but it keeps her distracted from the negative thoughts she has swirling around in her head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/subtle-signs-woman-been-misunderstood-her-whole-life-according-research"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Subtle Signs Of A Woman Who Has Been Misunderstood Her Whole Life, According To Research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;11. Plants&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-plants.png" alt="woman smiling holding plants" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves plants" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;ShotPrime Studio | Shutterstock &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plants are a huge upkeep, and it's not always fun to keep them alive. But there's no denying that they improve a woman's environment and make her more excited. Whether it's learning new tips and tricks or spending hours digging in the backyard, there's &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/art-green-living-hidden-perks-filling-home-with-plants"&gt;something calming about plants&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1186/s40101-015-0060-8" rel="nofollow"&gt;study published in the Journal of Physiological Anthropology&lt;/a&gt; found, "active interaction with indoor plants can reduce physiological and psychological stress compared with mental work." For women on the verge of breaking down, plants are a great tool to keep her calm and engaged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/small-ways-take-better-care-yourself-nothing-do-diet-exercise"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Small Ways To Take Better Care Of Yourself That Have Nothing To Do With Diet And Exercise&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Marielisa Reyes is a writer with a bachelor's degree in psychology who covers self-help, relationships, career, family, and astrology topics.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="midcat-most-popular"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Related Stories From YourTango:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="rc-widget-c743d1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>YourTango</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:31:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxNSF9MRUx5d0ttWHJwV0czOUVBM3p4TFBqcVhHZU5tVlVhNEJ3a0M4aEthN1F2N3VMNFBwTi1vUExNSFVkNm5EdkRETUVFVkQ3amJOZWRlb1FrM25Fc0tZU21aQVFDcDhoTUFlZGxIWWZ1RXlBZTJJc0IzaHRDRkcyVDhfSFdCdG8ydndQUEhrOVlidjNkTEVFbmx3OU9kMmxPODdxTC1tUGs</guid></item><item><title>科学家警告流行的止痛药可能弊大于利- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/scientists-warn-popular-painkiller-may-do-more-harm-than-good/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:15:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxONU1DbTRud0NUUVM3am1hNTRMV0VpaXQ4OW80Ml81SUtpQWRENDhVN090aVlPNzctak82ckF2dnV6NVVKR1cyWmMwU08wQ0o4SnREZ1EyR05ZSEFQREZfaTJORzFKZjdYaEdXLWdCS2RQMXYzLXh6UHJlTG9Ed0dCOUpJNnl0bXhkcDZIemt6dGU</guid></item><item><title>18名在家庭中处理过阿尔茨海默氏症的人分享了他们注意到的早期迹象- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/scarymouse/what-its-like-alzheimers-family-signs-wish-knew-earlier</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-20
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139743837" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title  "&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;So, what do you think? If you've dealt with something similar, I'd love to hear about your experience in the comments below. You never know — your story might be helpful to others going through something similar! If you want to write in but prefer to stay anonymous, you can utilize this anonymous form. Your story could be included in a future BuzzFeed article!&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Please note: some comments have been edited for length and/or clarity.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:16:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPbUlpVTBlNDJCZVYxSXBtei1WdEpkREVPX1E2WTNWY2JPMEpsYjVVaUFxMm11ZTJudkFVd2otOFk2YlhOUDdVM3UwdWp4aWxzQzVCbmo1aU1KRTJMNVVEMWRuZmlPTldVMXg2NkVyODhkSEhOSUpGRVF5OElHal9hSjA2dzNoZkxVTGVCR1JwWnhINUk2cnc</guid></item><item><title>你终于去看医生了。以下是如何充分利用它-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/doctor-visits-checkup-questions-primary-care-3fcde5b5c927734429818bd0ed1c6680</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It’s not unusual for a 20-something to text Mom in a panic from the doctor’s office, seeking help answering a question. And patients of any age can struggle to recall all their medicines — or forget to mention a concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting the most out of a doctor’s visit requires some advance preparation. Even the professionals plan ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is really hard — even for me as a doctor going to see my own family doctor — to remember the things that I wanted to bring up,” said Dr. Sarah Nosal, president of the American Academy of Family Physicians. “The worst is when you’ve had that moment with your doctor” only to recall another problem after walking out, she said. “You’ve lost that time.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her top tip: Bring a list of symptoms and questions to show at the start of the visit. The first item should be your top concern, but seeing the full list helps your doctor prioritize what’s most medically urgent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’m actually going to be able to see, is there a red flag?” explained Nosal, who has some advice about prepping for a typical primary care visit.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2&gt;Your primary care doctor monitors your overall health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some illnesses require specialists like a cardiologist or rheumatologist. But regardless of your age or how healthy you are, research has long shown that a relationship with a primary care provider is important for overall health. It might be a family physician like Nosal, who cares for all ages, or an internist. Some patients choose gynecologists, geriatricians, or have a primary care team that includes nurse practitioners or physician assistants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Primary care is more than preventive checkups to help avoid illness, such as vaccinations, cancer screenings or health advice. It also includes detecting and treating common problems like high blood pressure, and helping to find and coordinate specialty care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“That ongoing relationship also helps me know your ‘normal,’” Nosal explained. “If something’s different or changes or you feel off, when you tell me that information and I also have known you over time, we can really figure out together what’s going on.”&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Quiz your family before the appointment&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Young adults navigating health care on their own for the first time may need help filling out forms with their personal medical history. Have you ever had general anesthesia? Is your tetanus shot up to date?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you still have access to the patient portal at your former pediatrician’s office, you can see records of vaccinations and prior illnesses, or you may have to request them or quiz parents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all ages, family medical history is critical — and needs regular updating. Ask what diseases your close relatives have had and how they fared. For example, if Type 2 diabetes runs in the family, or Grandma had a stroke, or someone had cancer at a young age, that information could help tailor your preventive care, Nosal said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Fill out your paperwork ahead of the visit&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Filling out paperwork from home makes it easier to check medicine bottles for the name and dose. Include both prescription and over-the-counter medicines, pills or creams — and don’t forget vitamins and supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why are the latter important? Some can interact with prescription medicines. Nosal cited some patients whose longtime treatments quit working after they started taking turmeric, a spice also sold as a supplement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also before your visit, check if the doctor received records of recent lab tests, hospitalizations or visits to other health providers, since electronic medical records aren’t always automatically shared.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Keep a running list of questions before a doctor visit&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some symptoms are bad enough to prompt an urgent visit. But if you’ve got a checkup coming, whether it’s routine or to follow up on health problems, start a list of questions in advance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice a pain when you move a certain way? Or chatting with a friend who just got a colonoscopy and wonder if you’re due? Pop those on your list right away, before you forget — and be specific in describing symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nosal keeps a running list on her phone and, ahead of visits with her own doctor, sends it as a heads-up through her patient portal. Patients also can include their list on visit check-in forms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea is to address the most urgent questions first, rather than patients running out of time before raising a key concern. Nosal said questions about mental or sexual health and wellness especially tend to come up at the last minute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever the medium, “please bring that list,” she said. “That’s the most critical of all pieces.”&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;It’s OK to ask again&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;People may know to ask questions about treatments, such as how well they work and what side effects to expect. But it’s also important to understand why a doctor makes a particular diagnosis or, conversely, isn’t as worried about a symptom as you might be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t hesitate to say, “Explain to me what else could be going on,” Nosal advised. “What would be the next step? How would you evaluate that for me, to know if it’s this or that?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most health advocacy groups also advise bringing along a friend or relative, especially if you have serious or multiple health problems. They can help ask questions and take notes.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;“Whether you are 20 or you are 85, you will not remember everything from your medical visit,” Nosal said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:05:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxOc0xFRDltbnNnU05Lb2ZJSDFSZ2EwOS12bElONk1PNi00OGNhem81cEF0LUpodkxGbkc4bV9fMExsa2d3SWFSUlBqOUxqUXdTTDlCdktjMUNPcDlXYXZxNVU4WWdyS0RHRE9hbUdyQ0RJRzFBNHhVaUgtaDFObWdzWHFBWHYwYnE4R1RuLWdMZk1BNDFTWkpkckdyRE5TMWZDSmltX1JBZw</guid></item><item><title>我们需要停止在假期周围说话的有毒短语- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/toxic-phrase-holidays-goog_l_6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Just 12 hours after the last Halloween trick-or-treater left and my sugared-up kids were tucked into bed, I started my typical Monday morning fitness class. But mid-plank, the instructor’s comment caught me off guard, and didn’t sit well with me the rest of the day. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Let’s work off all that Halloween candy!” she shouted into her mic. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The nonchalant phrase of “let’s work off ___,” while surely intended as a lighthearted joke, is seriously problematic, according to experts. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The idea that you need to out-exercise food or earn any treats isn’t just prevalent during Halloween ― it’s also extremely common to hear during the holiday season. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here’s why this mentality needs to stop, and how you can feel good in your body instead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: SCIENCE PHOTO LIBRARY via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;SCIENCE PHOTO LIBRARY via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Experts explain why it's important to overcome the damaging notion that you have to work out in order to eat holiday meals or treats.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It discredits the more important benefits of exercise&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I definitely wasn’t at the gym that morning to burn off Sugar Daddys and Dots. I was there to strengthen my postpartum abs, to visit my friends and to move my body so it felt limber and strong.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://healthyemmie.org/pages/about-me" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Emmie Keefe" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://healthyemmie.org/pages/about-me" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;Emmie Keefe&lt;/a&gt;, a Boston-based nutritionist, said whenever instructors focus on this calorie-based “motivation,” it backfires. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“We should never exercise for the sake of burning calories. ... We should exercise for cardiovascular health, for mental health, for emotional health. It gives structure to your day. You can create social relationships through classes together,” she explained. “There are &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;so many reasons to exercise. B&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;urning calories shouldn’t be one of them.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent research shows that &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/weight-loss-may-not-make-you-healthier_l_61638056e4b0cc44c50dcbfe" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="focusing on regular exercise improves your longevity" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="61638056e4b0cc44c50dcbfe" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;focusing on regular exercise improves your longevity&lt;/a&gt; ― even more than focusing on weight loss. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/reasons-exercise-nothing-to-do-losing-weight_l_5f0873bdc5b63a72c340c2e5" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="Exercise also" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="5f0873bdc5b63a72c340c2e5" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;Exercise also&lt;/a&gt; alleviates symptoms of anxiety and depression, enhances creativity, and helps you sleep better. Meanwhile, &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/phrase-think-about-exercise_l_60e59fe3e4b08ebff5e4b9db" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="looking at exercise as punishment rather than a beneficial activity" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="60e59fe3e4b08ebff5e4b9db" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;looking at exercise as punishment rather than a beneficial activity&lt;/a&gt; makes you less likely to engage in the healthy behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Keefe added that the “mental gymnastics” of trying to count calories in and out with food and exercise isn’t always realistic or helpful. Instead, regular exercise can help you feel more motivated in other areas of your life and that you’ve started the day off in a productive way. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;What that walk and that workout class is not going to do is burn off what you ate right before,” she said. “That way of thinking is big, big trouble.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="cli cli-pullquote"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-pullquote__content"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__quote accent-cli"&gt;“There are so many reasons to exercise. Burning calories shouldn’t be one of them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__attribution caption-cli"&gt;- Emmie Keefe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It promotes harmful eating mindsets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;How do you feel when you are about to dig into a pumpkin pie you only encounter once or twice per year? Hopefully simply excited, and not anything else. According to Alyssa Royse, owner of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rocketcommunityfitness.com/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Rocket Community Fitness" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.rocketcommunityfitness.com/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rocket Community Fitness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in Seattle, the mindset that you have to deserve that pie or undo the damage is “really dangerous.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“It links us to this idea that we have to earn the right to eat and have to earn the right to have pleasure. Both of those things are innate in simply having a body ... by virtue of being alive, you are allowed [both],” she said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“When we moralize food, we trigger all sorts of dangerous thoughts and behavior patterns in people,” she continued. &lt;/span&gt;This includes eating disorders, which can lead to &lt;a href="https://www.nimh.nih.gov/health/publications/eating-disorders" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="major long-term health complications" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.nimh.nih.gov/health/publications/eating-disorders" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;major long-term health complications&lt;/a&gt; like heart damage, hair growth issues, brain damage, lethargy and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Instead of creating these negative connections, trainers in her gym don’t mention food. If the holidays do come up, they try to focus on positive aspects like, “go have fun and enjoy the bounty, go feel the joy ... that’s the primary purpose of your body ― to experience joy,” Royse said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Royse added that people already have these damaging thoughts on their own around the holidays, as a result of years of toxic messaging in media where people are pushed to be thinner. She encourages her clients to challenge these connections they and others have made, and move instead toward body and food neutrality. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Food doesn’t need to be an emotional or moral experience. You are allowed to just have it,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Keefe also noted that shaming yourself for what you ate can have an additional physical consequences. As a result of the stress hormones you release through that thought pattern, you can experience &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/11874-stress" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="stomach pains and digestive problems" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/11874-stress" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;stomach pains and digestive problems&lt;/a&gt; (along with so many other issues like headaches, heart palpitations and more).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; “You’re really making yourself suffer twice,” she said. Instead, she emphasizes enjoying it and moving on.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="cli cli-pullquote"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-pullquote__content"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__quote accent-cli"&gt;“Food doesn’t need to be an emotional or moral experience. You are allowed to just have it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__attribution caption-cli"&gt;- Alyssa Royse&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Listen to your body instead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Both experts believe it’s necessary to tune in to your body instead of letting outside forces influence how you feel, especially when it comes to the holidays. This process, also known as mindful eating, is where you pay close attention to your food ― mentally noticing how it tastes and how enjoyable it feels to eat it. It also has you listen to your natural hunger and fullness cues. Food is not something you’ve “earned” and there is absolutely no expectation that you need to “work it off.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Royse said she specifically tries to drink more water (one glass per &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/holiday-drink-recipes_n_5a2818d8e4b02d3bfc3774ae" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="holiday cocktail" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="5a2818d8e4b02d3bfc3774ae" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;holiday cocktail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;) and take more walks, not as a penalty but as a way to counteract any physical discomfort she might be feeling.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Keefe enjoys whatever holiday foods she wants, while also prioritizing nutrition. She chooses fruits and vegetables when she can, noting that the holidays don’t necessarily mean you have to only eat rich foods or only stick to the veggie tray. She has also seen clients make themselves sick trying to preemptively offset the holidays’ physical impact.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“They exhaust themselves with exercise in anticipation or in reaction to how they’ve eaten during the holidays. Their overall health declines ... their bodies are under enormous stress,” she said. “Treat your body kindly.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you’re struggling with an eating disorder, call the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nationaleatingdisorders.org/find-help-support" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="National Eating Disorder Association hotline" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="http://www.nationaleatingdisorders.org/find-help-support" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;&lt;em&gt;National Eating Disorder Association hotline&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; at 1-800-931-2237.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxOeEhWeHNsUVZRY1FnX3BaRm9oZ0M0emJlQmFtbThNVnB0UGpMNUpyMWZrUjk0NmlPNGpoMW1GVzR4YTN2MWJVaktLT1pQcnliVkFXV3JwZy1zVFo4TTlBZF9USzlfdmpmcnk5MnRHT1Y5NVB2ZVNMMTZIOXB0VVNfcFhiSFk4NkJTY0l3MdIBkgFBVV95cUxPTmN5QTh4RHJjTHk2cWRFcmlRVE42ZXUwUlA2RnN1eWtzM3NuSVBBMUVXcTc5b1MwczRRWjVHTGJkS2c0M1pCT19zcjUwRmowYXBQVHBzX25jcXhVVzIzUVpQQVRMbWhJOWdxYUZSRG1RakQ2SFczTWhLSW9qcHVsRE4wdUpLMG1UQUFPQU1taFZyUQ</guid></item><item><title>“即将离职”的9岁儿童将“一夜之间”变成了父母不认识的愤怒的人。然后得到令人震惊的诊断（独家） - AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/outgoing-9-old-changes-overnight-103000223.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Loos&lt;/p&gt; Crystal Loos' daughter&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2023, Crystal Loos noticed that her daughter was acting differently — the once bubbly child became reserved and angry, pulling back from friends, school and the world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It was utter terror, like she wasn't herself," the mother tells PEOPLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;After searching for answers, Loos' daughter finally got a diagnosis that changed everything&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the spring of 2023, Crystal Loos began noticing that her daughter wasn’t acting like her normal self. Her once bubbly elementary schooler seemed distracted and pulled away from school, her friends and the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Illinois mother of three tells PEOPLE that her daughter, Lacy Mae, stopped eating foods that she used to enjoy, and, at the time, Loos thought it was depression and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Before this, she was the happiest, funniest, most outgoing child ever. She never had any issues," Loos, 30, shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, in July 2024, there was a "complete overnight change," and the then-9-year-old was no longer “herself."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Lacy Mae was diagnosed with anxiety and depression, Loos knew deep down it was something else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They tried to put her on SSRIs, they tried to get her into a psychiatrist, psychologist, everything," she says. "But I just felt that there was something deeper going on."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Loos&lt;/p&gt; Crystal Loos' daughter&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The night in July came, and it was like she had a psychotic break that night, and she was banging on my door. She was begging to go to the hospital," Loos continues. "She knew something was wrong, but she didn't know what, because she couldn't even explain to me what was going on. It was just like she didn't have control over her brain.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos describes a period of time where her young daughter wouldn't sleep, felt paranoid and constantly begged to be taken to the hospital to figure out what was wrong with her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It was utter terror, like she wasn't herself. She had dilated pupils. You looked at her, and she just wasn't the same kid, like, it was like something took over her," Loos says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although they "had gone to multiple hospitals," nearly everyone agreed that it was just depression and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At that point, Loos’ daughter begged to be admitted to a psych ward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“She's 10 years old, so that's crazy, obviously, but she just wanted her health to get fixed," Loos says. "She begged, begged, begged to be admitted. She was, at this point, suicidal."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We had to sometimes hold her down because she was trying to hurt herself or us. Sometimes we would have to lock her and us in a room together so that she wouldn't. She was more of a danger to herself than us," she shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos, who was recently postpartum when Lacy Mae's health took a turn, says her parents then stepped in to help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Loos&lt;/p&gt; Crystal Loos' daughter&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Eventually, she did have to move in with my parents because I had a newborn baby, and then I also have a 5-year-old, and my 5-year-old was just terrified of her," she says. "He was just absolutely terrified because she was screaming. Rage is what I could describe her. She had so much rage in her.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos’ daughter refused to eat, refused to go to school, and ended up missing most of fourth grade. While many people believed the new baby could have caused Lacy Mae's personality change, Loos noted that it was much deeper than that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I'm like, ‘You guys don't get it. She was running away from home. She was trying to jump out of moving cars, like just complete psychosis.’ It was nothing like I've ever seen before. Especially as a child and in my childhood, I never had any issues before this," she shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eventually, Lacy Mae was admitted to a behavioral health unit. During that time, Loos turned to various Facebook mom groups for support, asking if anyone else had ever experienced something similar. A few people mentioned that it could be PANS/PANDAS, so Loos got to work researching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I went to the psychiatrist at the children's hospital, and I literally begged. I was bawling at him. I said, 'She has something wrong with her. I think this is what it is: PANS /PANDAS. Can we do any further workup?' They refused to do that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/pans.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Stanford University School of Medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Stanford University School of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, Pediatric Acute-onset Neuropsychiatric Syndrome (PANS) is a clinical diagnosis for children who "have a dramatic – sometimes overnight – onset of neuropsychiatric symptoms" characterized by the sudden onset of obsessive-compulsive symptoms (OCD) or eating restrictions. They may also have symptoms of depression, behavioral regression, irritability, anxiety, sleep issues, and difficulty with schoolwork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Pediatric Autoimmune Neuropsychiatric Disorders Associated with Streptococcal Infections (PANDAS) is a subset of PANS, and has five distinct criteria for diagnosis, including "abrupt 'overnight' OCD or dramatic, disabling tics; a relapsing-remitting, episodic symptom course; young age at onset (average of 6–7 years); presence of neurologic abnormalities;" and a recent streptococcal infection, such as strep throat, peri-anal strep or scarlet fever, per the &lt;a href="https://www.pandasppn.org/what-are-pans-pandas/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PANDAS Physicains Network.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;PANDAS Physicains Network. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There isn’t an official test to diagnose PANS/PANDAS, making it hard for medical professionals to determine it as the root cause of symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, Loos took her daughter out of the psych ward and searched for a doctor who specialized in PANS/PANDAS. They eventually contacted Indiana-based specialist Dr. Antoine, and in September 2024, after in-depth blood work, Lacy Mae was officially diagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was put on antibiotics and received IVIG (Intravenous Immunoglobulin) to help her immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Loos&lt;/p&gt; Crystal Loos and her daughter&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“She had different infections in her body that were mistakenly attacking her brain. She had several different infections," Loos shares. "She had a tick-borne illness. She had mycoplasma, plasma pneumonia, and these are all things that Dr. Antoine checked for. That's how we figured out what was going on."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He put her on antibiotics to kill these infections, and then he put her on antibiotics to regulate her immune system, and then the IVIG, that's also to regulate the immune system, and then different supplements just to get her immune system back to normal so that it attacks the infection rather than attacking her brain,” Loos adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slowly, treatment began to work, and by December of 2024, Loos says they started to “see her again.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Loos admits the tween "still had a lot of episodes after that,” the severity of those episodes decreased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I was having just so much anxiety through all this because I was like, I don't know what to do," she shares. "I can't even describe how bad it was. It was literally like a living hell.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lacy Mae was also put on an anti-psychotic to help calm her down, and now, just over one year after her diagnosis, Loos says the 10-year-old is "99%" herself again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“She does have some setbacks and a little bit of anxiety here and there, but for the most part, ever since we found Dr. Antoine and got on the right medication, she has been thriving, and life is pretty much back to normal for the most part," Loos says. "She goes to school. She plays sports. She plays with her friends, which she hasn't done for a while. Now she's completely back to living life and enjoying life again.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos recently shared a &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@crysrenae/video/7580132165707451662" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:TikTok video;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;TikTok video&lt;/a&gt; showing the difference in her daughter to raise awareness of PANS/PANDAS. The video went viral, amassing over 45 million views.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She says that parents have since reached out to share their own stories about how their children changed seemingly without cause. She’s been able to connect them with resources and talk them through what they’re feeling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I want parents to get answers. I want them to know that this is a thing and something to look into if your child has similar symptoms. I wish I would have found it sooner, before our life got really hard with it," she tells PEOPLE. "It's really amazing, because I've gotten so many messages and people, saying the kindest things and that they've been through it, and they know how it feels, and they're so grateful that I'm spreading awareness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When we were going through this, I was really struggling because I didn't feel like I could find other parents that were dealing with this," she continues. "It’s very, very lonely, and you want to find any information you can, and there's just not a lot out there."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos wants to educate people on PANS/PANDAS since it's a diagnosis that "is not widely known."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although I think it's honestly not a rare diagnosis. It’s more common than we think," she adds. "I think it's just often misdiagnosed as other things. I just want people to be aware of what everyone's going through when they have PANS/PANDAs.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you or someone you know is struggling with mental health challenges, emotional distress, substance use problems, or just needs to talk, call or text 988, or chat at &lt;a href="http://988lifeline.org/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:988lifeline.org;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;988lifeline.org&lt;/a&gt; 24/7.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/girl-diagnosed-with-pandas-after-extreme-behavior-changes-exclusive-11871633" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 10:47:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxOM1NJZ2JVRm5YX3RlWWQ4ZC1oOVFPaWVuNmVlOVQxaDRtLTJ0clRpZS1rblpXckdiUVhpTVp0dFIwNWVnQlg4WFg5N0tZQUNZRGVQNUkwcVk0aWRqTlY3MWp3eENiaWVZLXJKSzJBbS1KS1hkdThreHV2bkNnZUtRNzNB</guid></item><item><title>美国疫情激增导致德克萨斯州冬季病毒高传染性飙升- MySA</title><link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/local/article/outbreaks-contagious-winter-virus-texas-21234786.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>MySA</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 10:18:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxNVVAzOEFGakVzcnhLcEV5N3Y0a3ctcDBjaG9hVC1BY1Q3X01Qdy1ScGhWeVo3UTIyR3E3UVE2dHE0QUluVVQ4N2c3SURXa1M0cXN1SmdkVHJaajM3WEpxQkROd2JSajV1NThSSzRremRuS3hDZXBSUmlHUWJ1LVZ1MWwzNjdIQ1hzTlJtSXNTc1JtalBzLUJsVHZNSC0zZzZyU3c</guid></item><item><title>改善云室- Hackaday</title><link>https://hackaday.com/2025/12/19/improving-the-cloud-chamber/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/Article" id="post-885801" class="post-885801 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-classic-hacks category-science tag-cloud-chamber tag-peltier tag-wilson-cloud-chamber"&gt;
    

    &lt;div class="entry-content" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Want to visualize radioactive particles? You don’t need a boatload of lab equipment. Just a cloud chamber. And [Curious Scientist] is showing off an &lt;a href="https://curiousscientist.tech/blog/diy-cloud-chamber-with-hv-grid" target="_blank"&gt;improved miniature cloud chamber&lt;/a&gt; that is easy to replicate using a 3D printer and common components.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The build uses a Peltier module, a CPU cooler, an aluminum plate, thermal paste, and headlight film. The high voltage comes from a sacrificed mosquito swatter. The power input for the whole system is any 12V supply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cloud chamber was high tech back in 1911 when physicist Charles T. R. Wilson made ionizing radiation visible by creating trails of tiny liquid droplets in a supersaturated vapor of alcohol or water. Charged particles pass through, leaving visible condensation trails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span id="more-885801"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the post, the cost of everything is under $100. He hasn’t made the 3D printed parts freely available, but there are enough pictures that you can probably work it out yourself. Besides, you’d almost certainly have to rework it for your particular jar, anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After all, a cloud chamber’s construction isn’t a state secret. We’ve seen some fancy &lt;a href="https://hackaday.com/2025/08/09/desk-top-peltier-powered-cloud-chamber-uses-desktop-parts/"&gt;Peltier-based designs&lt;/a&gt;. If you manage your expectations, you can build one for even less using a &lt;a href="https://hackaday.com/2022/02/11/maybe-the-simplest-cloud-chamber/"&gt;plastic bottle and ingenuity.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	            &lt;/div&gt;
    
    
&lt;/article&gt;

            	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hackaday</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibEFVX3lxTFBmV05TeTZoQTlYcUQ5bW5wOFpzYWtFV0tSVlZnMy1kTkQ4ZE1DVGh4UzNENnNqZ3RUX2hWSGVwN3FCdXB6eGluUWFUaTVYVzJjd2t3bzFuVUotNHFReE02OWg0ekU1aEQyaHRmWg</guid></item><item><title>美国计划停止推荐大多数儿童疫苗，服从医生--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/19/childhood-vaccine-schedule-denmark-revisions/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GH9WQ4N8Y11Y98BXM8HN2GZR30" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The Trump administration plans to shift the federal government away from directly recommending most vaccines for children and suggest they receive fewer shots to more closely align with Denmark’s immunization model, according to two people familiar with the matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 01:37:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxQVTB6dXFKVHZVUjVfZWE1cjRBVTg4cDBsenNFQUZjNGd0aHA1aWZjNDFDdzlfX05EVUdQU2ZkVnpkdlJ5TEVmTGlMQWpVVjFWVVU1SGlOaktWVFJmQm92MXFXN0F0RjVYVW5obi11c0o1akRmXzBqWUtsZlEzVmpJa3NGblktQ1Y3X3otYl93SEc3am5YMWRQd2RB</guid></item><item><title>当你吃黄油时，你的心脏健康会发生什么- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/is-butter-bad-for-your-heart-health-11873630</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Butter may impact your risk of heart disease and type 2 diabetes in ways you might not expect. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Butter contains saturated fats, and also has vitamins A, D and vitamin K2.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Enjoy butter in moderation and pair it with nutrient-dense foods like vegetables.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Butter makes almost everything taste better. A pat melting over a warm piece of toast, a spoonful swirled into a sauce or a dab on a stack of pancakes; it adds a rich, satisfying flavor that is hard to replicate. But for years, butter has been at the center of a debate about its impact on our health, particularly our hearts. Is it a dietary villain to be avoided at all costs, or can it be part of a healthy lifestyle?
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Experts say the truth about butter is more nuanced than a simple "good" or "bad" label. The story involves saturated fat, cholesterol and the context of your entire diet. Let’s break down what really happens to your heart health when you eat butter.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; First, it helps to know what’s actually in that golden stick. Butter is a dairy product made by churning cream until the fat separates from the liquid (buttermilk). It's primarily composed of fat (about 80%) with the rest being water and milk solids.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This fat content is what gives butter its creamy texture and rich flavor. It also contains some fat-soluble vitamins, including vitamin A, vitamin E and vitamin K2.&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; However, the main point of discussion is its high concentration of saturated fat. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-butter-affects-heart-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Butter Affects Heart Health &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The way butter interacts with your body is complex. It influences several key markers of heart health, from cholesterol levels to insulin resistance.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Saturated Fat and LDL Cholesterol &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; There’s no debating that butter is high in saturated fat. As &lt;a href="https://drlisayoung.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Lisa Young, Ph.D., RD&lt;/a&gt;, notes, “A diet high in saturated fat can prompt the liver to produce more LDL cholesterol.”&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; LDL cholesterol is often called the "bad" cholesterol because, over time, elevated levels can contribute to plaque buildup in the arteries, making them narrower and stiffer. This process, known as atherosclerosis, can increase the risk of heart attack and stroke. For this reason, dietary guidelines have traditionally recommended limiting saturated fat intake. One study showed that eating two tablespoons of butter per day was linked to elevated total cholesterol and LDL cholesterol, reinforcing this concern.&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; However, new research indicates that consuming dairy products, even those higher in saturated fat, might be linked to a lower risk of heart disease. This has led to the idea of the "dairy food matrix," which looks at how the unique structure of dairy impacts health. When examining different types of dairy, the findings suggest that saturated fats from dairy and dairy-based fats are either neutral or potentially beneficial for heart and metabolic health.&lt;span data-cite="5" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Impact on HDL Cholesterol &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While the focus is often on LDL, butter may also influence HDL cholesterol, the "good" kind. HDL helps remove cholesterol from your arteries, transporting it back to the liver where it can be processed and removed from the body. Some research suggests that certain fats in butter, while raising LDL, might also give a slight boost to HDL levels. This dual effect adds a layer of complexity to understanding butter's overall impact.&lt;span data-cite="6" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Triglycerides and Insulin Resistance &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Emerging research is exploring how different foods affect other heart health markers like triglycerides (a type of fat in your blood) and insulin resistance. High triglycerides are a known risk factor for heart disease.&lt;span data-cite="7" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Interestingly, some recent findings suggest that butter's effect might not be as straightforward as once believed. For example, one study looked at how butter, margarine and non-hydrogenated oils affect heart and metabolic health over time.  “Results found about 1 teaspoon of butter daily was linked to lower risk of heart disease and type 2 diabetes. Findings included less insulin resistance, higher blood HDL-cholesterol (HDL-C or “good” cholesterol) and lower triglyceride (TG) levels,” per &lt;a href="https://www.usdairy.com/news-articles/contributors/christopher-cifelli" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Chris Cifelli, Ph.D., FASN&lt;/a&gt;. On the other hand, eating more margarine was tied to a higher risk of both heart disease (29% increase) and type 2 diabetes (41% increase). In summary, butter, when consumed in moderation, may be a healthier fat choice compared to margarine, especially for heart and metabolic health.&lt;span data-cite="8" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; How Butter Stacks Up Against Other Fats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When choosing a spread or cooking fat, the options can be overwhelming. Here’s a quick look at how butter compares to other common fats.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Olive Oil:&lt;/strong&gt; Extra virgin olive oil is rich in monounsaturated fats and antioxidants, which are widely recognized for their heart-protective benefits. It's associated with lower LDL cholesterol and reduced inflammation, making it a staple of heart-healthy diets like the Mediterranean diet.&lt;span data-cite="9" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; For cooking and dressings, it's generally considered a healthier choice than butter.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Margarine:&lt;/strong&gt; For decades, margarine was promoted as a heart-healthy alternative to butter. However, early versions were high in trans fats, which are now known to be far more harmful to heart health than saturated fats. While most modern margarines are free of trans fats, their healthfulness depends on the oils from which they are made. Spreads made from olive or avocado oil may be better choices.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coconut Oil:&lt;/strong&gt; Like butter, coconut oil is high in saturated fat. However, the type of saturated fat is different. Coconut oil contains more medium-chain triglycerides (MCTs), which are metabolized differently than the long-chain fatty acids in butter. &lt;span data-cite="10" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; While some claim MCTs offer health benefits, research shows that coconut oil may be linked to elevated LDL cholesterol more than unsaturated plant oils, so it should also be consumed in moderation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-to-enjoy-butter-wisely"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How to Enjoy Butter Wisely &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The consensus among experts is that you shouldn’t eat butter by the stickful, but generally healthy people don’t necessarily need to banish butter from their kitchen. It’s all about balance, portion size and what you’re eating it with.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “When it comes to diet, small amounts of butter can add flavor and can be part of a balanced diet when paired with heart-healthy foods like vegetables and whole grains,” explains &lt;a href="https://whitnessnutrition.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Whitney Stuart, M.S., RD&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Here are some practical tips for enjoying butter wisely:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Practice Moderation:&lt;/strong&gt; A little goes a long way. Instead of slathering a thick layer on your toast, use just a thin pat. Measure it out to keep portion sizes in check.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pair it with Nutrient-Dense Foods:&lt;/strong&gt; Using a small amount of butter to sauté vegetables or spread on a slice of whole-grain bread is much different from adding it to highly processed foods. The overall nutritional quality of your meal matters most.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose Your Moments:&lt;/strong&gt; Save butter for when its flavor can really shine. For everyday cooking, consider using healthier fats like olive oil. For that perfect flaky pie crust or a special sauce, butter might be the right choice.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch Overall Calorie Intake:&lt;/strong&gt; "High butter intake can contribute to excess calorie consumption and weight gain, which further impacts heart health," Stuart advises. Be mindful of your total daily intake of fats and calories.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Butter can absolutely have a place in a balanced, nutrient-rich diet, especially when used thoughtfully. Context matters – no expert is suggesting eating a stick of butter every day, but incorporating small amounts to enhance the flavor of nutrient-dense foods, like vegetables or whole grains, can make healthy eating more enjoyable and sustainable. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As Cifali notes, "Butter can likely fit into an overall nutrient-rich, balanced diet that includes the recommended nutrient-dense food groups like vegetables, whole grains, dairy foods (i.e., milk, cheese, yogurt), fruits and lean proteins—as long as daily calories and saturated fat are kept in check." This approach emphasizes moderation and the importance of the overall dietary pattern rather than focusing on individual foods in isolation.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Emerging research also suggests that butter, when consumed in moderation, may have a more neutral or even beneficial impact on heart and metabolic health than previously thought. For example, using a small pat of butter to sauté vegetables might not only improve their taste but also help you meet your daily vegetable intake—a win for both flavor and nutrition. The key is to enjoy butter as part of a diet rich in whole, nutrient-dense foods while being mindful of portion sizes and overall calorie intake. By doing so, you can strike a balance that supports both your health and your palate.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE5xMXRkQWpQQ25KVmZVYUJrZVctWWRmZm1xeGk1V0ZxUGt0TEZfNUVzcXdnT0w1ZDdMQ21nRGwzaTJiOVBfOWllalVRLU9pYXhTSzNnSWYzSkNZcXdiVkV6cU5kZmJ5Uml4dFluVkYwT1VleW95ajhGeTY0SQ</guid></item><item><title>Golden Retriever对被排除在家庭照片之外的反应让每个人都感到不安- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/golden-retriever-reaction-being-left-001500836.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Image via Shutterstock&amp;amp;sol;Barnabas Davoti&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boone is one of the bestest boys on the planet. He loves his humans and life in general, and as far as Golden Retrievers go, he’s as loyal as they come. Anyone who meets Boone can tell instantly that he takes his role as a family member very seriously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine his surprise when his family betrayed that loyalty by having a backyard photo shoot without him. There they were, dressed nicely and standing arm in arm in front of the &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/articles/golden-retriever-loses-ball-bushes-120000740.html" data-ylk="slk:bushes;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link rapid-noclick-resp yahoo-link"&gt;bushes&lt;/a&gt;—and where was 5-year-old Boone?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the house, dramatically making a scene in the window for all to see! Boone made sure his humans could not miss how he was feeling about the obvious oversight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fluffy Golden Retriever spotted his humans out in the yard and clearly felt like he belonged out there, too. He propped himself up at the &lt;a href="https://pawnation.com/news/goldendoodle-conducts-neighborhood-trash-truck-watch" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:window;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;window &lt;/a&gt;and performed his best air bicycle routine against the glass, desperately trying to get their attention. He wanted his paw parents to know he was unfairly excluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/dog-face" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🐶;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;🐶&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/newsletters/parade-pets" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SIGN UP to get “pawsitivity” delivered right to your inbox with inspiring &amp;amp; entertaining stories about our furry &amp;amp; feathered friends;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIGN UP to get “pawsitivity” delivered right to your inbox with inspiring &amp;amp; entertaining stories about our furry &amp;amp; feathered friends&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/paw-prints" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🐾🐾;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;🐾🐾&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/articles/grandma-throws-golden-retriever-surprise-013000897.html" data-ylk="slk:Related: Grandma Throws Golden Retriever a Surprise Birthday Party and His Reaction Is Priceless;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link rapid-noclick-resp yahoo-link"&gt;Related: Grandma Throws Golden Retriever a Surprise Birthday Party and His Reaction Is Priceless&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Honestly, it was like he was saying, “Hey! You forgot me!” or “How dare you leave me out of the photo—I make everything better!” And he’s not wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Let's Check in With the Comment Section&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The TikTok video, recently shared by @golden_boy_boone, quickly captured viewers’ attention. Many of the Golden Retriever’s fans were flabbergasted that he’d intentionally been left out of the portrait. @blah asked, “Now, why would you leave him out?” while @feegs23 summed it up perfectly with a simple, “How rude!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several of Boone’s fellow four-legged TikTok stars also took his side. @RebaandDolly declared, “Rude! Your family photo is missing the main character!” while @Mygoldennuggettito exclaimed, “What!!! Get him out there now!!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite not being in the actual photo, Boone let everyone know that he was the star of the show, nonetheless!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally published by &lt;a href="https://pawnation.com/news/golden-retriever-left-out-of-family-photo-everyone-upset" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PawNation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;PawNation&lt;/a&gt; on Dec 20, 2025, where it first appeared in the &lt;a href="https://pawnation.com/news" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:News;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;News&lt;/a&gt; section. Add PawNation as a &lt;a href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=pawnation.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Preferred Source by clicking here.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Preferred Source by clicking here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 00:25:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNTk1QV1NVbTh1aVRGekNoWTBGNkI3eVBwQkRaY29tNGJVR295UjlLU1JQUWpnQ0pDb0lEOTV2VEZla0w2NmpySEViV3kwSW1XV1BhcFZ2b3NYTlhCcG9NUGdKNFUxYS1zbEhwNW5wRUJYRngtSUQ0dVp0UDVreU1nblJqakFXOGM</guid></item><item><title>今年冬天流感到底是怎么回事？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cr7lpmkl9r1o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;What's really going on with flu this winter?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 gXJgDY"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 gqeTMs"&gt;James Gallagher&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 bIfajQ"&gt;Health and science correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/120f/live/35f91230-dcf1-11f0-bc51-61713ec32de7.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/120f/live/35f91230-dcf1-11f0-bc51-61713ec32de7.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/120f/live/35f91230-dcf1-11f0-bc51-61713ec32de7.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/120f/live/35f91230-dcf1-11f0-bc51-61713ec32de7.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/120f/live/35f91230-dcf1-11f0-bc51-61713ec32de7.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/120f/live/35f91230-dcf1-11f0-bc51-61713ec32de7.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/120f/live/35f91230-dcf1-11f0-bc51-61713ec32de7.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/120f/live/35f91230-dcf1-11f0-bc51-61713ec32de7.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Sick looking man wrapped up in a cream coloured blanket and holding a tissue to his nose. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Flu should always be taken seriously. It is a virus that kills thousands of people every winter and puts intense strain on hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, I can't remember a flu season that has played out quite like this. There have been claims it is both a "superflu" and "unprecedented" across the media and even from NHS England - while experts say this year's flu is not out of the ordinary with accusations of "crying wolf".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So what's really going on and is anything truly different this year?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/c2dr8gzdz1wo" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;As I reported in early November&lt;/a&gt;, there were concerns the flu season had the potential to be the worst for a decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Scientists who track the multitude of flu viruses around the world noticed seven fresh mutations appear in a strain of influenza – a type called H3N2 – in June.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This newly mutated virus rapidly became the dominant form of H3N2 and was named subclade-K.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The flu season took off a month early in the UK hinting the virus may have the potential to spread more widely than normal and it was too late to adjust this year's flu vaccine to match the new mutations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;That was the concern, but the reality has been more in line with a normal flu than a super flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images 3D illustration showing spherical object representing the virus. It is covered in green and orange spikes which represent the two key proteins on the surface of a flu virus. There is one flu virus in focus in the bottom right and more in varying degrees of blur in the background. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;H3N2 strain of influenza &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The K-flu virus has not gained a dramatic ability to rip through the population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It was basically spreading at a very similar speed to previous years, it was towards the upper end, but it wasn't an outlier," says Prof Christophe Fraser, who is analysing the spread of the virus at the Pandemic Sciences Institute at the University of Oxford.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;His team's latest analyses, still to be published, suggest the mutations did give the virus a slight edge at slipping past our immunity – in the region of 5-10% more than usual. It is not clear if that applies to everyone or is concentrated just in children and young adults who have caught less flu in the past and who have been most affected so far. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;H3N2 viruses always tend to be more severe for the elderly and there is no clear evidence the virus is worse than expected this year. A rapid analysis of the seasonal flu vaccine also suggested it was performing &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.eurosurveillance.org/content/10.2807/1560-7917.ES.2025.30.46.2500854#html_fulltext" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;in line with previous years&lt;/a&gt; despite fears of a mismatch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Jamie Lopez Bernal, a consultant epidemiologist at the UKHSA, said: "The things that we saw that were unusual this season are the early start to the season, we also saw this change to the virus, with more evolution than we typically see.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"But overall, in terms of the impact on the NHS and the impact on people's health, we're seeing a broadly typical flu season."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There are suggestions that flu may already be peaking, although this comes with significant uncertainty. There are questions about what happens over Christmas when everyone meets up and it's easier for the virus to infect older people who are more at risk. There are also signs a different strain of flu - H1N1 - is picking up in Europe and may lead to an increase in cases here too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But a "broadly typical flu season" is probably not the sense you'd get from watching or reading the news.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Statistical artistry was used to compare an early flu season to one that started much later allowing claims of flu cases being &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.england.nhs.uk/2025/12/nhs-ready-double-whammy-winter-fludemic-strikes/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;"an incredible 10 times higher"&lt;/a&gt; than in 2023. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It was technically true, but is like saying your train to Glasgow got you there in record time… but the journey time was identical, you just booked an earlier train. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;NHS England was not the first organisation to start calling it superflu, but Prof Meghana Pandit, national medical director at NHS England, did label it an "&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/c8r30787e76o" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;unprecedented wave of super flu&lt;/a&gt;". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It has been suggested by the British Medical Association that flu has been used to scaremonger while resident doctors were deciding whether to continue their strike action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Superflu isn't a scientific description and the BBC Health Team has not found any expert who thinks it is an accurate one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I don't think it's a helpful term, there isn't a particularly unusual set of symptoms, there's no indication of it being associated with exceptional severity, exceptionally rapid spread or exceptional health impact," says Prof Fraser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;One of the UK's top flu scientists, Prof Nicola Lewis, the director of the World Influenza Centre at the Francis Crick Institute, said the virus was "not particularly unusual" and that she saw "no evidence" the virus was "particularly different" and superflu "wouldn't be my description".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The former deputy chief medical officer for England through the pandemic, Prof Jonathan Van-Tam, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:7405275742994919424/?commentUrn=urn%3Ali%3Acomment%3A%28activity%3A7405275742994919424%2C7405516492009676800%29&amp;amp;replyUrn=urn%3Ali%3Acomment%3A%28activity%3A7405275742994919424%2C7406388088220065792%29&amp;amp;dashCommentUrn=urn%3Ali%3Afsd_comment%3A%287405516492009676800%2Curn%3Ali%3Aactivity%3A7405275742994919424%29&amp;amp;dashReplyUrn=urn%3Ali%3Afsd_comment%3A%287406388088220065792%2Curn%3Ali%3Aactivity%3A7405275742994919424%29" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;posted&lt;/a&gt;: "I'm very unclear what is meant by the rather silly term of 'superflu'."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Crying wolf?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Persuading people to get the flu vaccine saves lives and last winter the jabs were estimated to have kept around 100,000 people &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/flu-vaccine-prevented-around-100000-hospital-admissions" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;out of hospital&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, experts have started to question whether the escalation in language used since the Covid pandemic could harm trust in official health advice. Previous winters came with warnings of a tripledemic of flu, Covid and RSV; then it was upgraded to a quademic adding in norovirus; this year it's superflu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Simon Williams, who researches psychology and public health at Swansea University, says there are issues with the "current language around every winter being 'the worst' in some way or another" and risks a "cry wolf" effect that damages trust and means people become "numb" to the advice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He said there was a danger of "over-using the narrative that viruses will overwhelm the NHS" when "ultimately the NHS hasn't got overwhelmed to the point of not being able to carry out emergency and basic functions".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Instead he argues a "fine balance" is needed between raising awareness and "not falling into the trap of fear-messaging or being overly alarmist, which can backfire".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Prof Jonathan Ball, a virologist at Nottingham University, agrees saying: "I think it is a concern to use words like super flu, when we may one day experience a real super flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We have to be very, very careful about how we communicate these things to the public, because there is a risk that we can cry wolf."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 00:06:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5tSUo1a2tSTFFDTzVSLTZSSDJlUWxzVTNnZU9ZczdvbEZOZHRtZXN6MlY2UUs2TkVmWTRtc3JvTm1ZeFJibnZwRWJZTXV2OVRTd1dvd3FiOGliZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE9ncGlJaU55Rm9xR3dHS1JIZmpVTkJUN0lCNmd6UFllOWJZM19nSFo3cVdCYXZtSGl0UlQ0RUJZNy1VNUFSTG5NdmlRUXFyc1RyTEtQeEdBSGplWE1lUUR3</guid></item><item><title>每500名阿拉斯加人中就有1人死于新冠肺炎疫情，州报告-安克雷奇每日新闻</title><link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2025/12/19/1-in-500-alaskan-deaths-during-pandemic-was-from-covid-19-state-reports/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="adn-article-body default  teads_enabled"&gt;&lt;figure class="c-media-item"&gt;&lt;img data-chromatic="ignore" alt="" class="c-image" loading="lazy" src="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/CWCSO5CFIJHQTPEKFXP3XC7QPA.JPG?auth=27fd90c0d4c7258f0b6d8eecbc6c6984bb4e95556eb290bba6662cf13a36d39b&amp;amp;width=800&amp;amp;height=587" srcset="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/CWCSO5CFIJHQTPEKFXP3XC7QPA.JPG?auth=27fd90c0d4c7258f0b6d8eecbc6c6984bb4e95556eb290bba6662cf13a36d39b&amp;amp;width=274&amp;amp;height=201 274w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/CWCSO5CFIJHQTPEKFXP3XC7QPA.JPG?auth=27fd90c0d4c7258f0b6d8eecbc6c6984bb4e95556eb290bba6662cf13a36d39b&amp;amp;width=400&amp;amp;height=293 400w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/CWCSO5CFIJHQTPEKFXP3XC7QPA.JPG?auth=27fd90c0d4c7258f0b6d8eecbc6c6984bb4e95556eb290bba6662cf13a36d39b&amp;amp;width=768&amp;amp;height=563 768w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/CWCSO5CFIJHQTPEKFXP3XC7QPA.JPG?auth=27fd90c0d4c7258f0b6d8eecbc6c6984bb4e95556eb290bba6662cf13a36d39b&amp;amp;width=1024&amp;amp;height=751 1024w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/CWCSO5CFIJHQTPEKFXP3XC7QPA.JPG?auth=27fd90c0d4c7258f0b6d8eecbc6c6984bb4e95556eb290bba6662cf13a36d39b&amp;amp;width=1440&amp;amp;height=1056 1440w"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="c-media-item__fig-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="c-media-item__caption"&gt;Signs outside the Alaska Airlines Center in Anchorage, photographed on Saturday, Jan. 9, 2021. (Emily Mesner / ADN)  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Over a roughly three-year period beginning in March 2020, 1,564 Alaskans died from COVID-19.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;That’s according to a new report from the Alaska Department of Health, which provides a detailed review of data on how the state fared dealing with the coronavirus between March 2020 and the end of the the federal public health emergency in May 2023. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;“This report ... represents the first comprehensive, retrospective analysis that brings together epidemiological data across the full course of the COVID-19 pandemic in Alaska,” Department of Health spokesperson Shirley Sakaye wrote in an emailed response to questions. “While the pandemic’s impacts extended far beyond what can be captured in an epidemiological summary, this report provides a consolidated, data-driven account of Alaska’s COVID-19 experience.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Epidemiologists looked at death records, hospitalizations, demographics, infections, vaccination rates and public health responses, producing an analysis that evaluates the different phases that played out as Alaska weathered the pandemic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;The 1,564 COVID deaths equates to 1 in every 500 Alaska residents during the period of review, they concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;“Seventy-four percent of those who died and were eligible for COVID-19 vaccine had opted not to receive it‚" states the &lt;a href="https://epi.alaska.gov/bulletins/docs/rr2025_01.pdf" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://epi.alaska.gov/bulletins/docs/rr2025_01.pdf"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt;, published earlier in December by the state’s Section of Epidemiology. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;The report provides a chronological review of how the virus impacted Alaska, broken down into seven distinct phases determined by developments in the public health response and viral mutations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;“Over time, it became clear that simply aggregating numbers across multiple years did not adequately reflect the reality of the pandemic, because the context was continually changing,” Sakaye wrote of the impetus for the analysis. “To better capture that complexity, the report organizes Alaska’s experience into distinct pandemic ‘eras.’ This approach more accurately reflects how conditions, risks and public health responses shifted over time. One of the key takeaways is that a pandemic is not a single event, but an extended and evolving experience.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-media-item"&gt;&lt;img data-chromatic="ignore" alt="" class="c-image" loading="lazy" src="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/5JXCHUDALFCUHG7YEEKUQRGDQA.JPG?auth=c7b441b4e7af06abc7c6aa84512ad058eba54ec36bb85d1cdecf593ef0e2de49&amp;amp;width=800&amp;amp;height=550" srcset="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/5JXCHUDALFCUHG7YEEKUQRGDQA.JPG?auth=c7b441b4e7af06abc7c6aa84512ad058eba54ec36bb85d1cdecf593ef0e2de49&amp;amp;width=274&amp;amp;height=188 274w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/5JXCHUDALFCUHG7YEEKUQRGDQA.JPG?auth=c7b441b4e7af06abc7c6aa84512ad058eba54ec36bb85d1cdecf593ef0e2de49&amp;amp;width=400&amp;amp;height=275 400w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/5JXCHUDALFCUHG7YEEKUQRGDQA.JPG?auth=c7b441b4e7af06abc7c6aa84512ad058eba54ec36bb85d1cdecf593ef0e2de49&amp;amp;width=768&amp;amp;height=528 768w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/5JXCHUDALFCUHG7YEEKUQRGDQA.JPG?auth=c7b441b4e7af06abc7c6aa84512ad058eba54ec36bb85d1cdecf593ef0e2de49&amp;amp;width=1024&amp;amp;height=704 1024w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/5JXCHUDALFCUHG7YEEKUQRGDQA.JPG?auth=c7b441b4e7af06abc7c6aa84512ad058eba54ec36bb85d1cdecf593ef0e2de49&amp;amp;width=1440&amp;amp;height=990 1440w"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="c-media-item__fig-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="c-media-item__caption"&gt;A sign taped to the front door of The Kobuk on W. Fifth Avenue in downtown Anchorage asks patrons to wear a face mask while in their store on Monday, Aug. 23, 2021. (Emily Mesner / ADN) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Alaska’s former chief medical officer, Dr. Anne Zink, who helmed the state’s response to the coronavirus, said the report is valuable for public health officials and policymakers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;“I think it’s really for the future,” said Zink, who no longer works for the state. During the pandemic, she said, she regularly consulted old epidemiological reports on Alaska’s response to previous epidemics like influenza, which informed public health measures to COVID-19.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Zink did not author the new coronavirus report but did review it and provide feedback. She said she&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;found the delineation between phases to be particularly useful. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;The first era, for example, was the “pandemic onset,” from March until May 2020, a time when the state saw a low number of cases and people were still largely obeying government public health orders such as business closures, physical distancing and limited travel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;“Alaska’s geographic location and the implementation of (non-pharmaceutical interventions) prior to the first detected case prevented widespread community transmission. This resulted in a smaller initial COVID-19 wave and lower rates of morbidity and mortality compared to many areas in the contiguous U.S. for the same period,” wrote report author Katherine Newell with the Alaska Section of Epidemiology, who no longer works for the state. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Alaska started seeing more infections in the summer of 2020, as prevention measures started to be relaxed in some jurisdictions. The state and its health care partners were aggressive about virus testing for critical infrastructure employees, travelers and the public. By August of that year, Alaska was “the most tested state (per capita) in the nation,” according to the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-media-item"&gt;&lt;img data-chromatic="ignore" alt="" class="c-image" loading="lazy" src="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/QQKJFM5KP5FT5NPQYKLOAYLVI4.JPG?auth=908993083eb641378f9ecdec67f2547790e68019e4608ac0660b731b980018ef&amp;amp;width=800&amp;amp;height=552" srcset="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/QQKJFM5KP5FT5NPQYKLOAYLVI4.JPG?auth=908993083eb641378f9ecdec67f2547790e68019e4608ac0660b731b980018ef&amp;amp;width=274&amp;amp;height=189 274w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/QQKJFM5KP5FT5NPQYKLOAYLVI4.JPG?auth=908993083eb641378f9ecdec67f2547790e68019e4608ac0660b731b980018ef&amp;amp;width=400&amp;amp;height=276 400w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/QQKJFM5KP5FT5NPQYKLOAYLVI4.JPG?auth=908993083eb641378f9ecdec67f2547790e68019e4608ac0660b731b980018ef&amp;amp;width=768&amp;amp;height=529 768w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/QQKJFM5KP5FT5NPQYKLOAYLVI4.JPG?auth=908993083eb641378f9ecdec67f2547790e68019e4608ac0660b731b980018ef&amp;amp;width=1024&amp;amp;height=706 1024w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/QQKJFM5KP5FT5NPQYKLOAYLVI4.JPG?auth=908993083eb641378f9ecdec67f2547790e68019e4608ac0660b731b980018ef&amp;amp;width=1440&amp;amp;height=993 1440w"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="c-media-item__fig-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="c-media-item__caption"&gt;Avii Mafuao receives a COVID-19 test at a drive-through testing site at 4810 C Street in Anchorage on Jan. 8, 2022.  (Emily Mesner / ADN) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Later eras are defined by rising levels of viral transmission and hospitalization, the arrival of effective vaccines and subsequent waves of coronavirus variants that pushed Alaska’s health care system close to collapse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Two points of interest highlighted in the report are the disproportionately high toll the disease inflicted on particular groups of Alaskans, and the severity of the delta variant, which caused almost half of the state’s total COVID-19 deaths within a six-month period between July and December 2021. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;“Despite these increases in statewide testing and contact tracing capacity, COVID-19 community transmission continued to increase during this era, resulting in Alaska’s first notable surge in cases, hospitalizations, and deaths,” the report continues. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Many of of those outbreaks spread through congregate settings like “seafood processing plants, correctional facilities, long-term care and assisted living facilities, and healthcare institutions.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;As the virus spread, it hospitalized and killed two groups at a particularly high rate: “American Indian/Alaska Native persons, and Asian/Pacific Islander persons,”&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;according to the report’s review of state demographic data in death and hospitalization records. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Prior to the arrival of widespread vaccination in January 2021, the disparities in health outcomes grew large. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;“Mortality rates among AI/AN and Asian/PI persons were 5.5 and 3.6 times as high as the rate among White persons,” the report states. “These racial disparities in both COVID-19 mortality and hospitalizations continued for the entirety of the pandemic in Alaska.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-media-item"&gt;&lt;img data-chromatic="ignore" alt="" class="c-image" loading="lazy" src="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/5ZRCOQ7KOFFODIBRNYN32L6ZZY.JPG?auth=2ba701a8598a65b1ffc970796d07d1eb8070131cada4ea4959e329e8937506ae&amp;amp;width=800&amp;amp;height=544" srcset="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/5ZRCOQ7KOFFODIBRNYN32L6ZZY.JPG?auth=2ba701a8598a65b1ffc970796d07d1eb8070131cada4ea4959e329e8937506ae&amp;amp;width=274&amp;amp;height=186 274w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/5ZRCOQ7KOFFODIBRNYN32L6ZZY.JPG?auth=2ba701a8598a65b1ffc970796d07d1eb8070131cada4ea4959e329e8937506ae&amp;amp;width=400&amp;amp;height=272 400w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/5ZRCOQ7KOFFODIBRNYN32L6ZZY.JPG?auth=2ba701a8598a65b1ffc970796d07d1eb8070131cada4ea4959e329e8937506ae&amp;amp;width=768&amp;amp;height=522 768w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/5ZRCOQ7KOFFODIBRNYN32L6ZZY.JPG?auth=2ba701a8598a65b1ffc970796d07d1eb8070131cada4ea4959e329e8937506ae&amp;amp;width=1024&amp;amp;height=696 1024w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/5ZRCOQ7KOFFODIBRNYN32L6ZZY.JPG?auth=2ba701a8598a65b1ffc970796d07d1eb8070131cada4ea4959e329e8937506ae&amp;amp;width=1440&amp;amp;height=979 1440w"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="c-media-item__fig-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="c-media-item__caption"&gt;Angel Libby prepares to administer a COVID-19 test at the drive-through testing site at 4810 C Street in Anchorage on Saturday, Jan. 8, 2022. (Emily Mesner / ADN) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Zink said she wished there had been more demographic nuance in reporting the results. Even though Asians and Pacific Islanders are assessed as part of the same group, the Pacific Islander community in Alaska fared far worse, she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;The report does not explain the reasons for the disparities. Zink said many of the patterns that played out from the coronavirus mirror trends from other diseases that have spread through Alaska.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;“Alaska Natives have worse health outcomes,” Zink said, offering several socioeconomic factors that likely play a role, including household overcrowding, lack of water and sewer infrastructure in many communities, and inconsistent access to emergency medical care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;But, she added, much about the coronavirus’s transmissibility and pathology is still being studied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;“I don’t want to pretend we know what we don’t know,” Zink said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="adn-article-body__h3"&gt;Delta devastation&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Once vaccines arrived, Alaska vaccinated early and rapidly. At least at first. In a five-month period, 289,287 Alaskans got their primary vaccine dose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;“This marked the largest state vaccination campaign ever undertaken,” the report states. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;By July of 2021, though, the delta variant had become the dominant coronavirus strain in Alaska, and it &lt;a href="https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2021/12/05/alaska-saw-a-major-increase-in-overall-deaths-across-the-state-after-introduction-of-delta-variant/#:~:text=The%20latest%20count%20of%20vaccine,getting%20booster%20shots%20when%20eligible." target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2021/12/05/alaska-saw-a-major-increase-in-overall-deaths-across-the-state-after-introduction-of-delta-variant/#:~:text=The%20latest%20count%20of%20vaccine,getting%20booster%20shots%20when%20eligible."&gt;devastated many communities&lt;/a&gt;. By the end of the year, 719 people died of COVID-19, 46% of the total killed during all three years of the pandemic in Alaska. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-media-item"&gt;&lt;img data-chromatic="ignore" alt="" class="c-image" loading="lazy" src="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/3LJROBTBBFBGPPNAOIFP6GE37Q.JPG?auth=dceba2f209e80a6585b8b68a98ddaa0ee085827639b2b75e210510cc519f37b5&amp;amp;width=800&amp;amp;height=540" srcset="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/3LJROBTBBFBGPPNAOIFP6GE37Q.JPG?auth=dceba2f209e80a6585b8b68a98ddaa0ee085827639b2b75e210510cc519f37b5&amp;amp;width=274&amp;amp;height=184 274w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/3LJROBTBBFBGPPNAOIFP6GE37Q.JPG?auth=dceba2f209e80a6585b8b68a98ddaa0ee085827639b2b75e210510cc519f37b5&amp;amp;width=400&amp;amp;height=270 400w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/3LJROBTBBFBGPPNAOIFP6GE37Q.JPG?auth=dceba2f209e80a6585b8b68a98ddaa0ee085827639b2b75e210510cc519f37b5&amp;amp;width=768&amp;amp;height=518 768w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/3LJROBTBBFBGPPNAOIFP6GE37Q.JPG?auth=dceba2f209e80a6585b8b68a98ddaa0ee085827639b2b75e210510cc519f37b5&amp;amp;width=1024&amp;amp;height=691 1024w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/3LJROBTBBFBGPPNAOIFP6GE37Q.JPG?auth=dceba2f209e80a6585b8b68a98ddaa0ee085827639b2b75e210510cc519f37b5&amp;amp;width=1440&amp;amp;height=972 1440w"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="c-media-item__fig-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="c-media-item__caption"&gt;Nurse Bethany Zimpelman prepares to administer doses of the Pfizer-BioNTech COVID-19 vaccine to children during a vaccine clinic at Tikahtnu Commons in Anchorage on Nov. 3, 2021. (Emily Mesner / ADN) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;The virus was the “leading cause of death in Alaska during this era,” more lethal than cancer, heart disease or other common killers. Those who died were overwhelmingly older: The median age of death during the delta era was 75. They were also overwhelmingly unvaccinated: 80% of those who died, 575 people, “were unvaccinated against COVID-19 at the time of their death,” according to the report. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;In that same six-month period, 2,021 Alaskans were hospitalized because of COVID-19, putting “unprecedented strain on staff and bed capacity” at hospitals around the state, and prompting officials to coordinate bringing more than 400 health care workers up from outside to assist. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;When the omicron variant replaced delta as the dominant strain, it proved far more transmissible, but less potent. The number of confirmed COVID-19 cases increased, but hospitalizations and death rates declined. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-media-item"&gt;&lt;img data-chromatic="ignore" alt="" class="c-image" loading="lazy" src="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/Q4ANV25URNDX3JGOC2OC7BNP5Y.jpg?auth=fe9b73312776a1aac530031445bbbbdad28ba13c126143bae4e3c339fecd2f7b&amp;amp;width=800&amp;amp;height=533" srcset="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/Q4ANV25URNDX3JGOC2OC7BNP5Y.jpg?auth=fe9b73312776a1aac530031445bbbbdad28ba13c126143bae4e3c339fecd2f7b&amp;amp;width=274&amp;amp;height=182 274w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/Q4ANV25URNDX3JGOC2OC7BNP5Y.jpg?auth=fe9b73312776a1aac530031445bbbbdad28ba13c126143bae4e3c339fecd2f7b&amp;amp;width=400&amp;amp;height=266 400w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/Q4ANV25URNDX3JGOC2OC7BNP5Y.jpg?auth=fe9b73312776a1aac530031445bbbbdad28ba13c126143bae4e3c339fecd2f7b&amp;amp;width=768&amp;amp;height=511 768w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/Q4ANV25URNDX3JGOC2OC7BNP5Y.jpg?auth=fe9b73312776a1aac530031445bbbbdad28ba13c126143bae4e3c339fecd2f7b&amp;amp;width=1024&amp;amp;height=682 1024w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/Q4ANV25URNDX3JGOC2OC7BNP5Y.jpg?auth=fe9b73312776a1aac530031445bbbbdad28ba13c126143bae4e3c339fecd2f7b&amp;amp;width=1440&amp;amp;height=959 1440w"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="c-media-item__fig-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="c-media-item__caption"&gt;Nurses Crista Johnson, left, and Jeremiah Hassemer prepared monoclonal antibody treatments before the clinic opened at Tikahtnu Commons in East Anchorage on Sept. 24, 2021. (Marc Lester / ADN) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;The data included in the report’s analysis has limits, particularly when it comes to the efficacy of certain public health measures, and the disease’s relationship with other lethal health factors. The author steers away from attributing COVID-19 deaths that might have technically been caused by factors like heart disease, underlying conditions or drug overdoses, but were exacerbated by pandemic conditions like social isolation or restricted health care access. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;“These excess deaths reflect the broader consequences of the pandemic on the public’s health. Further research is necessary to fully understand the factors driving excess mortality and the broader public health impact of the pandemic in Alaska,” the report states. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Fully vaccinated Alaskans still got sick with COVID-19 and some, particularly those who were older or in poor health, still succumbed to the disease. But one of the repeated conclusions in the analysis is that the state’s early vaccine uptake helped protect residents during the later waves of highly transmissible variants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;“Based on the significant difference in age-adjusted mortality rates between vaccinated and unvaccinated persons, high vaccine uptake during this era likely saved numerous lives in Alaska,” the report notes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;&lt;i&gt;[&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Correction:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt; This story and headline have been updated to clarify that 1 in 500 Alaskans died from COVID-19 during pandemic, not that 1 in 500 Alaskan deaths during pandemic was from COVID-19.]&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:article-html-block-XZPCKSSMAFCDHH26Q55VTZQV4I" data-fusion-component="article-html-block-XZPCKSSMAFCDHH26Q55VTZQV4I"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="adn-article-body__html"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:article-html-block-XZPCKSSMAFCDHH26Q55VTZQV4I" data-fusion-component="article-html-block-XZPCKSSMAFCDHH26Q55VTZQV4I"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Anchorage Daily News</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:15:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxPSjFaSm45Zzl1X25HRE1xZC10T1RNQW42MUpYWWx2SzBJQW8tZVFGWkRLejlYYjhzTUQ1MUg3NUw3cEVkS2RoczJYOGwtamVLei1FdWdVX29HX25ZWHN1NV9OZGNMTnBya0c3OW1XTjNfMFRScVg2Mk9nMlNUQ1FkbkNIbGhMSi1JN2VBMFdDWDhudlV1ZXhXdkJINHZvZHhmS2VsaS1UdUdVNm9yeVNtNC10R3UyUQ</guid></item><item><title>新研究表明，随着年龄的增长，这种早晨的习惯可以支持您的骨骼健康- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/tea-bone-health-study-11873585</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new study suggests morning tea drinkers may have stronger bones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tea is linked to improved bone mineral density in postmenopausal women.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The study excluded decaffeinated or herbal tea, but included all other varieties.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Osteoporosis seems to be one of those often overlooked conditions that takes a back seat to more urgent ones, like heart disease and cancer. But in the bigger health picture, osteoporosis can also impact quality of life.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Osteoporosis is a disease that develops when your bone mineral density (BMD) and bone mass decrease.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; It’s often referred to as a "silent" disease because it typically has no symptoms—until you break a bone.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The risk of osteoporosis increases with age, especially after menopause. Based on the latest data, about 13% of U.S. adults over 50 were diagnosed with osteoporosis; this number jumps to almost 18% for those 65 and over.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; If we consider just women, 13% of those in the 50 to 64 age bracket had osteoporosis, and 27% of those aged 65 and over had the disease.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Many factors influence one’s risk for osteoporosis, many of them lifestyle-related. For example, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/exercises-women-over-50-for-strong-bones-11833636" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;weight-bearing exercise&lt;/a&gt;, like &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/benefits-of-gaining-muscle-mass-11750809" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;strength training&lt;/a&gt; and walking, may help prevent osteoporosis. Smoking and heavy alcohol use increase your risk.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; And of course, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-for-bone-health-11745664" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;what you eat also plays a role in bone health&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While we know that foods, like dairy, are rich in bone-supporting nutrients, including calcium, magnesium, phosphorus and vitamin D, some beverages have not yet locked in their bone-health status. Take coffee and tea, for example. Studies have been inconsistent in their results regarding coffee and tea consumption and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/things-to-do-every-week-for-stronger-bones-11853649" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;bone mineral density&lt;/a&gt; in postmenopausal women. That’s why researchers in Australia took a closer look at this topic, trying to clear up some of the confusion. They published their findings in &lt;i&gt;Nutrients&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Let’s break down what they found.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-was-this-study-conducted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Was This Study Conducted? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Researchers drew about 10 years of data from a 20-year study called the Study of Osteoporotic Fractures (SOF), which included more than 9,700 women aged 65 and older. At clinical visits during years two, four, five and six of the study, the participants had their femoral neck and total hip bone mineral densities measured, which are common BMD measurement sites.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; At the same clinical visits, participants also completed self-administered questionnaires regarding coffee and tea consumption. Specifically, for coffee, they were asked, "Do you currently drink regular coffee? If yes, on average, how many cups of regular coffee do you usually consume per day?" For tea consumption, participants were asked "Do you currently drink tea or iced tea (excluding herbal or decaffeinated varieties)? If yes, on average, how many cups of tea do you usually consume per day?"
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Demographics, which would be adjusted for during statistical analyses, were also collected, including age, BMI, cigarette smoking status, age at menopause, lifetime alcohol intake, lifetime physical activity and oral estrogen and steroid use. Medical histories were also taken, and weekly calcium and protein intake were calculated based on a 20-item dietary scale that participants completed at baseline.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-did-this-study-find"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What Did This Study Find? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Researchers found no positive benefits of drinking coffee on bone mineral density. However, they did find potential negative effects on bone mineral density for those who drank more than five cups of coffee a day.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Tea drinkers, however, may have an advantage over coffee drinkers, as researchers found an association between tea consumption and higher total hip bone mineral density in older postmenopausal women.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Researchers note a few limitations to their study, starting with participants' self-reporting of coffee and tea consumption. Related to this, participants were not asked more detailed questions, like the size of their beverage cups and beverage strength. In addition, due to the length of follow-up (10 years) and the ages of the women, some died before the study’s end, and others were unable to finish due to health reasons. The dwindling participant pool may have weakened the study results.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-does-this-apply-to-real-life"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Does This Apply to Real Life? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Coffee and tea are some of the most widely consumed beverages globally. Because they’re &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7775696/plant-based-diet-for-beginners-your-guide-to-getting-started/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;plant-based&lt;/a&gt;, they contain antioxidants and the potential to lower inflammation and disease risk.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; For example, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8069479/is-coffee-good-for-you/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;coffee has been linked with&lt;/a&gt; a healthier heart and brain, among other benefits. It might also boost your mood and give you more energy.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re a regular tea sipper, you might even live longer and have a stronger immune system.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The great thing about tea is that there’s a flavor for everyone. From green, black and white to jasmine, rooibos and mint, teas span the flavor spectrum—and they're all loaded with powerful plant compounds. If you want to go beyond traditional hot or iced tea, brew up some of our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/8050463/how-to-make-thai-iced-tea/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Thai Iced Tea&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/266309/warm-honey-green-tea/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Warm Honey Green Tea&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/berry-green-tea-smoothie-8746131" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;Berry Green Tea Smoothie&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When it comes to bone health, other foods also have an influence. For example, you’re aware that dairy is good for your bones, but &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-protein-for-bone-health-11719674" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;canned salmon&lt;/a&gt; is also a great bone builder. There’s also evidence that the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/bone-health-mediterranean-diet-11711574" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt;, especially when combined with exercise, may help prevent osteoporosis.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/30-day-mediterranean-diet-meal-plan-for-healthy-aging-created-by-a-dietitian-11739365" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;Check out our 30-Day Mediterranean Diet Meal Plan for Healthy Aging&lt;/a&gt;. It’s chock-full of bone-, heart- and brain-healthy foods that will protect your overall health.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This study suggests that more than five cups of coffee a day may have detrimental effects on bone mineral density. Tea, however, appears to have a positive effect. Check out all of our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipes/18065/drinks/tea/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;healthy tea recipes&lt;/a&gt; for delicious, nutritious inspiration. In addition, incorporate &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-exercises-for-women-over-50-8966927" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;weight-bearing exercises&lt;/a&gt; into your day, and include &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/the-7-best-foods-for-osteoporosis-8706086vegetables-that-are-healthier-raw-than-cooked-11786573" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;bone-building foods&lt;/a&gt;, like dairy, canned fish, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/vegetables-that-are-healthier-raw-than-cooked-11786573" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;cruciferous veggies&lt;/a&gt; and beans. There’s even evidence that &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/do-vibration-plates-work-11856562" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="5"&gt;whole body vibration training&lt;/a&gt; may improve BMD.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:12:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiaEFVX3lxTE9NUElSemhZVXUtWUFxN1g4SUNlcDZ3d1NSTi1kOTZoQWJlRzhPSVFCdmM1TEFUejNVbWpEUTFndkpzUUo3QXNtTEZSU29qQ0phNWNVZmVrRTZKQXB5VkVMSEx5WmJlX2c3</guid></item><item><title>您所在州的流感有多严重？新变种传播的注意事项- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/flu-season-states-severity-new-variant-k-vaccines-kids-rcna250056</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b9a58c" class="body-graf"&gt;Flu season has taken off nationwide, with cases rising rapidly in some parts of the country over the past few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d7cbf6" class="body-graf"&gt;“We’ve seen sustained, elevated activity across multiple key indicators in many areas of the country,” said Alicia Budd, head of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention’s domestic influenza surveillance team. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-528028" class="body-graf"&gt;The CDC released its &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-50.html" target="_blank"&gt;latest report on flu Friday&lt;/a&gt;, estimating that so far this season, there have been at least 4.6 million illnesses, causing more than 49,000 hospitalizations and 1,900 deaths. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3d439c" class="body-graf"&gt;Young children, infants through age 4, have been hit hardest so far. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-ab730b" class="body-graf"&gt;There’s plenty of other evidence of an early and aggressive flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-63b58b" class="body-graf"&gt;From November to December, wastewater concentrations of influenza type A rose 390% nationwide, according to data from &lt;a href="https://data.wastewaterscan.org/?charts=CjcQACABSABaC0luZmx1ZW56YSBBcgoyMDI1LTExLTA3cgoyMDI1LTEyLTE5igEGNWRiYjM2wAEB&amp;amp;selectedChartId=5dbb36" target="_blank"&gt;WastewaterSCAN&lt;/a&gt;, an academic program through Stanford University in partnership with Emory University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1a47d5" class="body-graf"&gt;The upward trend is increasing “very consistently,” said Marlene Wolfe, program director for WastewaterSCAN and an assistant professor of environmental health at Emory. “We’re not yet seeing any sign of plateauing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b020d5" class="body-graf"&gt;Dr. Chase Shutak, medical director of Children’s Minnesota, said positive flu cases at the facility doubled within the past week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4cfd70" class="body-graf"&gt;Symptoms have varied. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-2cc674" class="body-graf"&gt;“In some years, every kid who presents with the flu just has that classic influenza appearance. They look kind of dazed. They’re miserable. There’s a glassy look to their eyes,” he said. In addition this year, he said, there’s a fair number of kids who have milder symptoms but “annoying enough that they’re still coming in.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-dd3020" class="body-graf"&gt;Influenza A, specifically H3N2, is the dominant strain right now. While anyone of any age can be affected, H3N2 tends to cause more hospitalizations and deaths in older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b6c3fd" class="body-graf"&gt;There is concern that kids who are sick now with flu will spread it to grandparents and other older adults over the holidays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b03c5c" class="body-graf"&gt;“With schools going on break for a couple of weeks and family gatherings happening, it’s quite possible that some of the existing mixing of viruses amongst the school groups are going to change to a different population,” Budd said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-a77fdf" class="body-heading"&gt;Where is flu spreading? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="styles_inlineImage__FvnTh styles_medium__MEKii" id="anchor-96f626"&gt;&lt;picture class="styles_image__i32F7" data-testid="picture" data-flavor="fit" data-original-height="1238" data-original-width="2500"&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 1000px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-12/251219-cdc-influenza-map-bf-1330-1de503.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251219-cdc-influenza-map-bf-1330-1de503.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 320px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-12/251219-cdc-influenza-map-bf-1330-1de503.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251219-cdc-influenza-map-bf-1330-1de503.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251219-cdc-influenza-map-bf-1330-1de503.jpg" alt="U.S. map showing flu spread, ending Dec. 13."&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption styles_caption__TCewG" data-testid="caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption__container" data-testid="caption__container"&gt;U.S. map showing flu spread, ending Dec. 13.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="caption__source" data-testid="caption__source"&gt;CDC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-512050" class="body-graf"&gt;Flu activity is high or very high in 14 states — including Colorado, Idaho, Louisiana, Michigan, New Jersey and South Carolina — as well as New York City; Washington, D.C.; and Puerto Rico, according to the CDC report. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-ecda59" class="body-graf"&gt;Flu doesn’t need to be widespread, however, to be deadly. While the CDC’s latest report shows “minimal” flu activity in Wisconsin, for example, &lt;a href="https://www.dhs.wisconsin.gov/news/releases/121825.htm" target="_blank"&gt;state health officials reported&lt;/a&gt; Thursday that a child in the state died of flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7c3493" class="body-graf"&gt;On Wednesday, the &lt;a href="https://www.ncdhhs.gov/news/press-releases/2025/12/17/ncdhhs-announces-first-pediatric-flu-death-2025-26-season-urges-vaccination-children-6-months-and" target="_blank"&gt;North Carolina Department of Health and Human Services&lt;/a&gt; reported its first pediatric flu death of the season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bac42a" class="body-graf"&gt;Those cases are likely not counted among the CDC’s latest report, which shows three pediatric flu deaths so far this year, as the data is current through Dec. 13. The CDC’s next flu update will release on Dec. 30.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4c71f8" class="body-graf"&gt;The 2024-2025 flu season was particularly deadly, especially for children. According to the latest data, 288 children died of flu — tying a record set during the 2009-2010 H1N1 pandemic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8b0029" class="body-graf"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7436a2.htm" target="_blank"&gt;CDC report published in September&lt;/a&gt; found that half of the children who died of flu last year were otherwise healthy. About 89% hadn’t received the flu vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-6d434f" class="body-heading"&gt;Will the flu shot work this year?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e1aecc" class="body-graf"&gt;The annual flu shot is notoriously imperfect when it comes to matching the exact strains of flu that circulate. This year, a strain called H3N2 subclade K emerged, making changes on the surface protein of the virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-896c6d" class="body-graf"&gt;The surface protein is important because that’s what the body looks for to recognize whether it’s seen the virus before. If the protein looks even slightly different, the body may not be able to fight it off as well. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-571039" class="body-graf"&gt;Budd said it’s hard to predict how well this vaccine will ultimately work. Even though the strain has “drifted” a bit, the vaccines do contain protection against H3N2 virus in general.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9904a1" class="body-graf"&gt;“We’ve had past seasons where there have been what we call drifted viruses, which is how we would categorize this subclade K,” she said. “In some of those instances, there have been impacts on vaccine effectiveness, but there have also been seasons with drifted strains where we’ve seen the vaccine continue to provide protection.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b9de3e" class="body-graf"&gt;Budd said it’s important for everyone, including children, to get the flu shot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7605af" class="body-graf"&gt;“It is still the primary preventive measure against flu, severe illness, and we absolutely continue to recommend it this year, even in light of the drifted strain,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-527bf3" class="body-graf"&gt;Demand for Tamiflu, an antiviral used to help treat the flu, is slightly higher than it was this time last year, &lt;a href="https://www.goodrx.com/healthcare-access/research/flu-season-tracking-tamiflu-fills" target="_blank"&gt;according to GoodRx.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-31e609" class="body-graf"&gt;People generally only get prescription antivirals when they’re sick enough to go to the doctor, not just because they tested positive for the flu, said Tori Marsh, senior director of research for GoodRx. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e97017" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“What stands out this season is how early Tamiflu use is climbing,” she said. “When we see prescription antiviral use rise sooner than average, it often points to flu activity building earlier and potentially lasting longer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:42:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxORnhRcmJjVjJpVVlaM0N1S1hYeUxCazA0OFlfNnhQUVUzeXZlMTZmYjFPMl9wc0ZhMjRkdFNmbWFCWl9KVW9JbENONUlnRE5GYXhhRTMyZ05Ib28wSjlndG9xZ2VxUElWSVItMjV2Z3VHYlNIdjU2UHhvOUZjZHp1WWNWbEE3em1aVHlqSlVoSC1vRFhmVXhGR0tDTkdObXJORGZGQnhadU5lRm5O0gFWQVVfeXFMT3FFR0pETzRtRWdmV3N4cjVOLTJpU2UtTGNJNmVxWEhaWFh1U29BbnpwME1FQWVQS3dIckFiUXJfWlZoTi1od2h3UkphbVpxMzVEekIxQ0E</guid></item><item><title>随着流感开始蔓延，湾区学区近三分之一的孩子生病--《旧金山纪事报》</title><link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/health/article/marin-flu-outbreak-schools-21252876.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>San Francisco Chronicle</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:19:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxPemszLXJrZWpPRnZzbGV2T1lscXFfdXpIVTA4ZHVwcXJSTlhiN29Jd0lPUDVGRkRuM29jYUxYLVBCaU5NcHB5cDRJN3hQR3J5TnRsVDdtUENkdTZ1ZngyZDl4YmFlbzZFMmExYnAyOGlaaE95b1hfMFNaRzBlUlRmbVhMOG9vVThuMGc</guid></item><item><title>美国授予研究非洲婴儿乙型肝炎疫苗的丹麦科学家无竞标合同-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/hepatitis-b-vaccine-contract-guineabissau-1fbca4928e01f364e20ae5ae57b2330e</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Trump administration has awarded a $1.6 million, no-bid contract to a Danish university to study hepatitis B vaccinations on newborns in Africa that is raising ethical concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The unusual contract was awarded to scientists who have been cited by anti-vaccine activists and whose work has been questioned by leading public health experts. Some experts have suggested the research plan is unethical, because it will withhold vaccines that work from newborns at significant risk of infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The contract did not undergo a customary ethics review, The Associated Press has learned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention awarded the grant to a research team at the University of Southern Denmark that has been lauded by U.S. Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., according to a &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.govinfo.gov/content/pkg/FR-2025-12-18/pdf/2025-23245.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;federal notice posted this week.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the team’s leaders is Christine Stabell Benn, a consultant for a Kennedy-appointed committee that recently voted to &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/vaccines-babies-hepatitis-b-10f8db54beb38c5cd39a94f8a3657752"&gt;stop recommending&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; a dose of hepatitis B vaccine for all U.S. newborns.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;The study is to begin early next year in Guinea-Bissau, an impoverished West African nation where hepatitis B infection &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31746078/#:~:text=Results:%20A%20total%20of%202715,enqu%C3%AAtes%20dans%20la%20population%20g%C3%A9n%C3%A9rale." target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;is common&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The researchers are funded for five years to study 14,000 newborns.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It’s to be a randomized controlled trial, with some infants given the hepatitis B vaccine at birth and some not. Children will be tracked for death, illness and long-term developmental outcomes. &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;Most of the children will be followed for less than two years to look for side effects, but the first 500 enrolled will be followed for five years to look for behavior and brain development problems. There is no placebo involved, according to a copy of the study protocol prepared earlier this year that was obtained by the AP. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hepatitis B can be passed from an infected mother to a baby. It also can be spread by other infected people a baby comes in contact with.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Research and widespread medical consensus holds that the hepatitis B vaccine protects newborns, so withholding it from some babies — in this case, Black babies — has raised ethical alarms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical evidence is clear that the vaccine protects infants from developing liver disease and an early death. The well-documented infection risk far outweighs hypothetical concerns about side effects, said Dr. Boghuma K. Titanji, an Emory University infectious diseases doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She called the study “unconscionable,” and said it likely will exacerbate existing vaccine hesitancy in Africa and elsewhere. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There’s so much potential for this to be a harmful study,” said Titanji, who is from Cameroon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Benn did not respond to an email seeking comment about the proposal. An automatic response said she is out of the office until early January. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But, in &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.bandim.org/hepatitis-b-vaccine-at-birth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;a statement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, the research team said the study “will be the first and likely the only one of its kind.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They said it takes advantage of an unusual window of opportunity: Guinea-Bissau doesn’t currently recommended a birth dose of the hep B vaccine, but the nation will be implementing universal vaccination of newborns in 2027.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Vaccine skeptics and opponents have suggested that all the vaccine’s possible side effects were inadequately studied before the CDC began recommending it for newborns in 1991. Public health experts counter that over more than three decades no serious side effect has been documented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The award is highly unusual. The CDC did not announce a research funding opportunity and invite proposals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The proposal was unsolicited and the award did not go through customary review, said a CDC official with knowledge of the decision. Department of Health and Human Services officials told CDC officials to approve it and said HHS would provide special funding for it, the CDC official said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In private communications channels, CDC staffers were expressing outrage about the award, said the official, who is not authorized to talk about it and spoke on condition of anonymity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of those CDC scientists have compared the work to the infamous &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/30ba57133d6b47618eff042285b54d0e"&gt;Tuskegee Study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, which the agency oversaw in its later stages. In that decades-long study, health workers withheld treatment from unsuspecting Black men infected with syphilis so doctors could track the horrible ravages of the disease. &lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Like Tuskegee, this study involves the prospect of researchers watching people grow ill when a medical intervention could have kept them healthy, Titanji echoed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is an apt comparison,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study’s researchers say the trial was approved by a national ethics committee in Guinea-Bissau. But it did not undergo a customary ethics review within the CDC, the agency official told the AP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a statement, HHS spokesman Andrew Nixon said “we will ensure the highest scientific and ethical standards are met.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public health scientists noted questions have been raised in the past about research led by Benn and her husband, Peter Aaby, in their &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.bandim.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Bandim Health Project&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Other &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0264410X25012344" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Danish researchers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; who reviewed Aaby and Benn’s work have described questionable research practices. Earlier this year, former CDC Director Dr. Tom Frieden wrote &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/07/02/rfk-jr-vaccines-former-cdc-director-tom-frieden-says-kennedy-mangled-science-in-gavi-decision/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;an editorial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; calling a 2017 study co-authored by Aaby and Benn “fundamentally flawed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several researchers had harsh words about the latest award.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Aaby and Benn are doing the Guinea-Bissau HBV vaccine depravation trial,” Carl Bergstrom, a University of Washington evolutionary biologist, wrote in &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://bsky.app/profile/carlbergstrom.com/post/3mac5tfh4722v" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;a post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; on Bluesky. “Did RFK Jr. just call up the first name in the antivax yellow pages?” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Angela Rasmussen, a virus expert at the University of Saskatchewan, &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://bsky.app/profile/angierasmussen.bsky.social/post/3mablyin5is2e" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;said Kennedy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; was giving taxpayers’ money to his “cronies” for a “grossly unethical study that will expose African babies to hep B for no reason.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Science and Educational Media Group and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:54:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxOQTd0bi1pX25HOVRSa0ZCNlZNSkN4ZUdmVlE1REFxdWFZMFV4WHZkWFJtWk1YNlNxc0JfVmxDX2tDdlNDWDVLUmlrUnNjeDY0dXEwb0RFZWNwMG9rVnZLczdBXzd1bE13YlJWWVp3cUJiam1rdDJjUDRKYTlIeWMzNEVKVmFCRXUtZFpnM01Pby1pRlkxQTZsMldlbDdKTVBVaG5F</guid></item><item><title>湾区的“超级流感”风险在假期前增加- SFGATE</title><link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/super-flu-risk-in-bay-area-holidays-21252466.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>SFGATE</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:25:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxPdVBuSF9jTjNwRHFub0s3T1VYZ3dMbWxNVTMwdHZmRHNiUGYyNmRxdjBBTWYyeWdIRGpkMGV4X1UwYWFJMXBMeV83OUhyUFlwNzFTdEt0UUctNXNWNjRqdEM3Y0dqc2hyZ0NCM2Z5V2Jtd1NpZC1nYndlcDNKRjN4cVZ1eXpkd2hRTHBhdGd2ZVk</guid></item><item><title>情绪压力触发深度睡眠的即时唤醒-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://neurosciencenews.com/emotional-stress-sleep-30064/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;A new study uncovers a precise brain pathway that rapidly converts emotional stress into sudden wakefulness during NREM sleep. Researchers found that GABAergic neurons in the BNST activate glutamatergic neurons in the DpMe, causing immediate arousal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the DpMe neurons were removed, the arousal response weakened dramatically, proving they are essential for this stress-to-wake circuitry. These findings reveal how fear and anxiety can instantly disrupt sleep and point to new therapeutic targets for stress-related insomnia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stress Pathway:&lt;/strong&gt; BNST GABAergic neurons trigger fast arousal via DpMe glutamatergic neurons.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential Role:&lt;/strong&gt; Removing DpMe glutamatergic cells sharply reduced stress-induced wakefulness.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clinical Potential:&lt;/strong&gt; Targeting this circuit may help treat stress-related insomnia and mood disorders.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;University of Tsukuba&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Emotional states and stress strongly influence sleep-wake regulation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The amygdala and its related structures have long been implicated in regulating arousal. However, the underlying neural mechanisms remain unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this study, the researchers examined how GABAergic neurons in the BNST interact with glutamatergic neurons in the DpMe to induce rapid arousal from non-rapid eye movement (NREM) sleep in mice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Optogenetic stimulation of BNST GABAergic neurons during NREM sleep resulted in immediate arousal, accompanied by a robust increase in DpMe neuronal activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversely, selective ablation of glutamatergic neurons in the DpMe significantly reduced this response, demonstrating their essential role in the process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This study was the first to thoroughly describe a BNST-DpMe neural pathway mediating emotional signals to arousal centers. In addition, the findings offer novel insights into how mental stressors such as fear and anxiety can disrupt sleep and highlights potential therapeutic targets for stress-related insomnia and mood disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This study was supported by the World Premier International Research Center Initiative (WPI), a JSPS KAKENHI Grant-in-Aid for JSPS KAKENHI Grant-in-Aid for Scientific Research (B) (JP 18H02595) (TS), Grant-in-Aid for Challenging Research (Exploratory) 21K19287(TS), JSPS KAKENHI Grant-in-Aid for Scientific Research (A) (JP 21H05036) (TS), JSPS KAKENHI Grant Number JP 23H04941 (TS), AMED Moonshot Research and Development Program, Grant Number JP21zf0127005 (TS), JSPS Fund for the Promotion of Joint International Research 22K213511(TS) and JST, CREST Grant Number JPMJCR24T4, JSPS Grant-in-Aid for Transformative Research Areas (A) 23H04941(TS).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Key Questions Answered:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq wp-block-yoast-faq-block"&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1766178162286"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: &lt;em&gt;How does emotional stress wake the brain so quickly?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: By activating a BNST-to-DpMe circuit that instantly shifts NREM sleep into wakefulness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1766178163874"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: &lt;em&gt;Which neurons are required for this arousal response?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: Glutamatergic neurons in the DpMe are essential for transmitting the wake-up signal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1766178163665"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: &lt;em&gt;Why does this matter for insomnia?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: It identifies a concrete neural pathway that may be overactive in stress-related sleep disruption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Editorial Notes:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list has-background"&gt;&lt;li&gt;This article was edited by a Neuroscience News editor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Journal paper reviewed in full.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Additional context added by our staff.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this stress and sleep research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#3c575354534f5548497c495212484f4957495e5d125d5f12564c" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;YAMASHINA Naoko&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://tsukuba.ac.jp" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;University of Tsukuba&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;YAMASHINA Naoko – University of Tsukuba&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Closed access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1523/JNEUROSCI.1083-25.2025" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;The bed nucleus of the stria terminalis- deep mesencephalic nucleus circuit linking emotion and wakefulness&lt;/a&gt;” by SAKURAI, Takeshi et al. &lt;em&gt;Journal of Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The bed nucleus of the stria terminalis- deep mesencephalic nucleus circuit linking emotion and wakefulness&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bed nucleus of the stria terminalis (BNST), a part of the extended amygdala, integrates emotional and arousal-related signals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While GABAergic BNST (GABA&lt;sup&gt;BNST&lt;/sup&gt;) neurons have been implicated in promoting transitions from non-rapid eye movement (NREM) sleep to wakefulness, their downstream mechanisms remain unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here, we identify a neuronal circuit through which GABA&lt;sup&gt;BNST&lt;/sup&gt; neurons promote arousal via projections to a midbrain region known as the deep mesencephalic nucleus (DpMe), located within the broader mesencephalic reticular formation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In male mice, we used a combination of optogenetics, fiber photometry, neural ablation, and tracing approaches to dissect this circuit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Optogenetic stimulation of GABA&lt;sup&gt;BNST&lt;/sup&gt; terminals in the DpMe during NREM sleep elicited rapid transitions to wakefulness and increased activity of glutamatergic DpMe (GLUT&lt;sup&gt;DpMe&lt;/sup&gt;) neurons, as assessed by &lt;em&gt;c-fos&lt;/em&gt; mRNA expression and calcium imaging. Similarly, an aversive air-puff activated GLUT&lt;sup&gt;DpMe&lt;/sup&gt; neurons, suggesting engagement by emotionally salient stimuli.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ablation of GLUT&lt;sup&gt;DpMe&lt;/sup&gt; neurons markedly attenuated arousal responses triggered by GABA&lt;sup&gt;BNST&lt;/sup&gt; stimulation, underscoring their essential role in this circuit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While monosynaptic rabies tracing revealed local input neurons to GLUT&lt;sup&gt;DpMe&lt;/sup&gt; cells, in situ hybridization identified few &lt;em&gt;Vgat-&lt;/em&gt;positive interneurons among them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings suggest that GABA&lt;sup&gt;BNST&lt;/sup&gt; neurons may influence GLUT&lt;sup&gt;DpMe&lt;/sup&gt; neurons through noncanonical GABAergic mechanisms or via more complex local circuits beyond a simple disinhibition model.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Together, these findings delineate a previously uncharacterized BNST–DpMe circuit that allows emotionally relevant stimuli to override sleep and promote arousal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This pathway may contribute to stress-related sleep disturbances and represents a potential target for therapeutic treatments for sleep disorders associated with emotional dysregulation.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:15:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE9FTzZXdm94cW9FRjRnMERibndvajdHQWszQm91SmdQVGowSExsaUxJbHhXN3h2U3JiQlZrTEZzOXJhbG55ZHJNYTUwaUxlc3pnNm12YVptcm5qMmtkdmUzdmdaNHBmT0w3VGc</guid></item><item><title>R.F.K. Jr.可能将美国儿童疫苗接种时间表换成丹麦-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/19/health/kennedy-childhood-vaccine-schedule-denmark.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:08:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxNWU1LaWZwRU91SFJOV0FXdUk4eWpOUFliM2Q1WlkwSU50aGoycWU0dzdhWWl5aEdTMV8xX3hjNWhUMUp0WkZ0ektSWnM1UHZhVlloZFBUR3c1YjVlb1dOclRMQWVtVGI2WFVfb2gzdEstaHBiWUdFU0pWVjBzRk5LMUhLLUVaOHA0eUdJd1lpeExVWjA</guid></item></channel></rss>