<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>科学家发现女性生育率随年龄下降的新线索--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/09/ivf-fertility-aging-eggs/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QBZ6XQLA2FHBTKZQ4NA3D56O3E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Scientists are making inroads in understanding one of the central mysteries of human reproduction: Why do women’s eggs deteriorate as they age?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="P2SYEPKC7ZBGPLH2JDMF2EFQLI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The broad strokes have been&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;well-known — the ticking of a woman’s biological clock increases risk of miscarriage and infertility, often caused by eggs with the wrong number of chromosomes, the structures that carry DNA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:32:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE5UQXIxZlJtR1AtRUhZQ0JZT2lPZDV1U1ZneFczRmlvSDAwN3h4RVdVbHZQUXhTamZMYVhpSVBIc1F3NU5WTmRtT2JRWkhsV05ZTzdnVFBMMWNSdHNIQXVKaVY0QzJhcnJzMGJLdkJydGo4cEg4VTJMaGRxNlZ1LWM</guid></item><item><title>恢复老化关节的新突破可能有助于治疗骨关节炎- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/new-breakthrough-to-restore-aging-joints-could-help-treat-osteoarthritis</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A study in mice by researchers from Stanford University has traced the loss of cartilage that comes with aging to a single protein, pointing to treatments that may one day restore mobility and ease discomfort in seniors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The protein 15-PGDH has previously been &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/d41573-025-00209-5"&gt;extensively linked to aging&lt;/a&gt;: it becomes more abundant as we get older, and interferes with the molecules that repair tissue and reduce inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That led scientists to consider whether 15-PGDH might be involved in osteoarthritis, where stress on joints leads to the breakdown &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Collagen"&gt;of collagen&lt;/a&gt; in cartilage, causing inflammation and pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/arthritis-affects-thousands-of-kids-and-one-piece-of-advice-is-crucial"&gt;Arthritis Affects Thousands of Kids, And One Piece of Advice Is Crucial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In tests on old mice, knee cartilage that had previously worn down thickened following the introduction of a 15-PGDH inhibitor. In similar tests on young, injured mice, the inhibitor offered protection against the usual effects of injury-induced osteoarthritis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the researchers triggered the equivalent of an anterior cruciate ligament injury in mice and subsequently applied the treatment, osteoarthritis didn't develop, as would normally be expected in these kinds of mouse models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous attempts at cartilage regeneration included the use of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/stem-cells" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73034" data-postid="187978" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;stem cells&lt;/a&gt;, a factor that was no longer necessary when 15-PGDH was inhibited. Instead, &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chondrocyte"&gt;the chondrocyte cells&lt;/a&gt; that make and maintain cartilage were being transformed into a healthier, more useful state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is a new way of regenerating adult tissue, and it has significant clinical promise for treating arthritis due to aging or injury," &lt;a href="https://news.stanford.edu/stories/2025/11/joint-cartilage-aging-osteoarthritis-therapy-research"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; microbiologist Helen Blau. "We were looking for stem cells, but they are clearly not involved. It's very exciting."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_187981" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-187981" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/MouseScans.jpg" alt="Cartilage scans" class="wp-image-187981 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/MouseScans.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/MouseScans-600x420.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-187981" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Treated aged cartilage (far right, stained red) looked much more like young, healthy cartilage (far left, stained red). (Singla et al., &lt;em&gt;Science&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treated mice had a steadier gait, suggesting they were experiencing less pain, and were shown putting more weight on their injured legs – signs that the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/humans-have-a-hidden-salamander-like-ability-to-regenerate-body-tissue"&gt;cartilage restoration&lt;/a&gt; equated improved physical health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same experiment was also tried on human tissue samples taken from people having knee replacement surgery. Again, there were clear signs of regeneration, with the cartilage getting stiffer and showing fewer signs of inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The mechanism is quite striking and really shifted our perspective about how tissue regeneration can occur," &lt;a href="https://news.stanford.edu/stories/2025/11/joint-cartilage-aging-osteoarthritis-therapy-research"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; orthopaedic scientist Nidhi Bhutani. "It's clear that a large pool of already existing cells in cartilage are changing their gene expression patterns."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And by targeting these cells for regeneration, we may have an opportunity to have a bigger overall impact clinically."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While there's still plenty of work to do, this could eventually lead to effective treatments to roll back the damage done by arthritis or aging in general. We could be heading towards a future where hip and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/there-s-now-an-artificial-cartilage-gel-that-s-strong-enough-to-work-on-knees"&gt;knee replacements&lt;/a&gt; are no longer needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides replacing the joints affected, current treatment options for osteoarthritis are limited to pain management. Despite &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/radiation-therapy-reduces-pain-from-the-most-common-form-of-arthritis"&gt;promising research&lt;/a&gt; in recent years, we don't have anything yet that tackles the root cause of the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next steps could include a  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="187978" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trial&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/geroni/igaf122.3994"&gt;A previous trial&lt;/a&gt; of a 15-PGDH blocker to combat &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/protecting-your-muscle-mass-is-vital-for-healthy-aging-heres-why"&gt;muscle weakness&lt;/a&gt; didn't raise any red flags in terms of health and safety, which should speed up the process of trials for similar drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are very excited about this potential breakthrough," &lt;a href="https://news.stanford.edu/stories/2025/11/joint-cartilage-aging-osteoarthritis-therapy-research"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Blau. "Imagine regrowing existing cartilage and avoiding joint replacement."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/science.adx6649"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Science&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:03:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQZTVHMklTWmRhSmJJOVJSY29MZm10MUNCZm1VZGsyV2draEpwRE9oS0hKS3I5VlV4aExCX2ZfQ1VORDRCWWx4aktLclg4MGtqX2tLellMUVl1aHRhTWhXOHRmaVU1enBzQm15UVlJUHJCbmJJeTkwdm9RNS11OU5LcVpwTUhTemZMS3gtRGhWVXhwM255RVB5T1Btdk92ZjlvbTJr</guid></item><item><title>任何有孩子在托儿所的人都知道疾病是多么不方便。嗯，它即将变得更糟。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/technology/2026/01/rfk-jr-day-care-illness-working-parents-vaccines.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="21" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk60wx7s000w3b7bvtghhwpu@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://slate.com/theslatest?utm_source=slate&amp;amp;utm_medium=article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=article_plain_text_topper&amp;amp;sailthru_source=Article-TopperText-CTA"&gt;Sign up for the Slatest&lt;/a&gt; to get the most insightful analysis, criticism, and advice out there, delivered to your inbox daily.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="125" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk60wi1o006xbem2szmezvfz@published"&gt;This week, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention announced &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/05/childhood-vaccine-immunization-schedule-overhaul/"&gt;sweeping changes to the childhood vaccine schedule&lt;/a&gt;, removing broad recommendations for immunization against such diseases as flu, hepatitis A, rotavirus, and meningitis. Until recently, the U.S. vaccine schedule called for routine protection against 17 diseases; the changes lower that number to 11 diseases. There’s &lt;a href="https://theunbiasedscipod.substack.com/p/and-what-have-we-done?utm_source=publication-search"&gt;no new science&lt;/a&gt; that would support such a colossal change, and the American Academy of Pediatricians and public health experts alike continue to recommend the evidence-backed former schedule. The &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/07/cdc-vaccine-recommendations-schedule-revisions/"&gt;unusually unilateral&lt;/a&gt; declaration comes a month after President Donald Trump &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/fact-sheets/2025/12/fact-sheet-president-donald-j-trump-begins-process-to-align-u-s-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/"&gt;issued a memorandum&lt;/a&gt; directing the CDC and the Secretary of Health and Human Services—aka longtime anti-vaccine activist RFK Jr.—to “align U.S. core childhood vaccine recommendations with best practices from peer, developed countries.”&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="150" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk61fvb1001v3b7bwijv9ff6@published"&gt;These “peer, developed countries” mentioned are Denmark, which recommends vaccinations for 10 diseases; Japan, which recommends 14; and Germany, which recommends 15. Fifteen! Fifteen is a lot more than America’s new number, 11, is it not? In the days since the new schedule announcement, vaccine experts have repeatedly pointed out that&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2025/12/26/nx-s1-5656214/childhood-vaccination-denmark-rfk-policy"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Denmark&lt;/em&gt; is actually the outlier&lt;/a&gt; from the “peer” countries for having such a parsimonious schedule. And there’s a key difference between us and Denmark: Denmark has free universal health care. If their health care system was a road, it would be smooth, and they’re able to drive the Porsche that is fewer vaccinations, epidemiologist Katelyn Jetelina writes in her &lt;a href="https://yourlocalepidemiologist.substack.com/p/a-unilateral-change-to-childhood"&gt;Substack&lt;/a&gt;. It would be silly—and dangerous—to attempt to drive that same Porsche through the hazardous terrain that is the U.S. health care system. But that is essentially what we’re doing, she says, by adopting a vaccine schedule akin to Denmark’s.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="203" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk61fvb1001w3b7b9bbyqz78@published"&gt;Because while Denmark has reliable prenatal care, consistent follow-up, and a national health registry that essentially tracks everyone from birth to death, the U.S. … well, the U.S. has literally none of those things. What we do have are the &lt;a href="https://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2025/04/u-s-pregnancy-related-deaths-continuing-to-rise/"&gt;highest maternity mortality rate&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4856058/"&gt;infant mortality rate&lt;/a&gt; among our “peer” countries. What’s more, we’re one of the only countries in the entire world that &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/10/25/upshot/paid-leave-democrats.html"&gt;does not mandate any paid parental leave&lt;/a&gt;, alongside Papua New Guinea, the Marshall Islands, Tonga, and just a few others. Denmark, on the other hand, offers 24 weeks for the mother and 24 weeks for the father, plus a little more for the mother prior to the birth—nearly a &lt;a href="https://www.norden.org/en/info-norden/parental-benefit-denmark"&gt;year in total&lt;/a&gt;. That means that babies are able to stay home longer with their parents, avoiding exposure to diseases that they’re not yet vaccinated for, and that also present a higher mortality risk to infants than to even slightly older children. Americans don’t have the same opportunity. Most licensed child care centers &lt;a href="https://www.parents.com/daycare-for-infants-when-to-start-8622394#:~:text=Most%20licensed%20child%20care%20centers,the%20daycare%20center's%20policies%2C%20including:"&gt;accept babies as young as 6 weeks old&lt;/a&gt;, a choice that many parents are forced to make because they need to return to work (if they can &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2015/10/when-child-care-costs-more-than-rent-women-stay-at-home.html"&gt;afford the child care&lt;/a&gt;, which is a &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2017/01/theres-not-enough-child-care-in-the-u-s-for-all-the-families-that-need-it.html"&gt;whole other discussion&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="134" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk61fvb1001x3b7bka9fdjyn@published"&gt;Day cares are germy places. “Anytime you have a gathering of kids in close quarters, you risk sharing germs,” says Elizabeth Murray, a pediatrician in Rochester, New York. And young children, who are still developing immunity to common germs and also like to stick their fingers in their mouth and eyes, share a &lt;em&gt;lot &lt;/em&gt;of germs. Research shows that in their first three years of life, kids in day cares &lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2024-07-07/kids-who-go-to-childcare-get-sick-more-often-than-others/104053704"&gt;get sick more often&lt;/a&gt; with stomach bugs, ear infections, and upper respiratory infections than kids who are cared for at home (again, an option which, in the States, with our lean parental leave, can be very expensive for parents). The more kids there are in the child care setup, the &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10995-012-1125-5"&gt;higher the rate&lt;/a&gt; of illnesses. Take some vaccines away from that equation—more illnesses still.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="151" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk61fvb2001y3b7bplgieci6@published"&gt;While states &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; still require that kids receive certain vaccines for day care even if they’ve been dropped from the recommended CDC vaccine schedule, it stands to reason that the new recommendations may influence some states to reduce their requirements too. So far, several states including &lt;a href="https://www.news10.com/capitol/cdc-vaccine-schedule-changes/"&gt;New York&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://thebaynet.com/maryland-rejects-cdcs-new-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-will-use-aap-guidelines-instead/"&gt;Maryland&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://lincolnchronicle.org/oregon-other-states-reject-trump-administrations-latest-vaccine-recommendations-for-kids/"&gt;Oregon&lt;/a&gt; have released statements that they’re rejecting the new CDC recommendations for school and day care entry requirements. It’s not yet clear what red states will do, though “we’re likely to see states going in very different directions with their own vaccine recommendations, largely along partisan lines,” says Jason Schwartz, an associate professor of public health at Yale University. A long piece in the Tallahassee Democrat titled “&lt;a href="https://www.tallahassee.com/story/news/2026/01/06/florida-vaccination-rules-children-cdc-guidelines-reduces-recommended-immunizations/88045990007/"&gt;What Florida parents should know about new CDC vaccination guidelines&lt;/a&gt;” ultimately offers little to go by: “We have reached out to the Florida Department of Health to see what its plans are,” the reporter notes.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="40" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk61fvb2001z3b7bnmha974z@published"&gt;Regardless, the wild swings in guidance will inevitably cause confusion, notes Schwartz. And “the more we encounter confusion around vaccines,” he says, “the more likely it is that more kids will not receive vaccines that they otherwise could or should.”&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="171" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk61fvb200203b7bcun3kjm9@published"&gt;What’s certain is that more kids—and families—will suffer in various ways. Even outcomes that fall short of the very &lt;em&gt;worst&lt;/em&gt; outcome can still be horrible. Murray points out rotavirus, which lost its general recommendation status with the new schedule. While it’s not a major cause of death, the virus &lt;a href="https://www.medpagetoday.com/pediatrics/vaccines/119330"&gt;comes with high costs&lt;/a&gt;: extremely brutal symptoms of diarrhea and vomiting for children, days of hospitalization, and the high medical bills that come with that. Not to mention the missed days of work—you can’t send your kid to child care when they are sick. “Boy, I definitely remember when we would admit a whole lot of children to the hospital with rotavirus,” says Murray. The vaccine, which was developed in 2006, “wiped it out. I haven’t seen rotavirus in well over a decade.” If rotavirus vaccination rates go down, that’s likely to change. Then there could soon be yet another bug to worry about when parents have to send their infants to day care so that they can head back to &lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;work.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="The Slatest" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmk60wi1o0070bem2jelg1zib@published"&gt;


    &lt;div class="newsletter-signup__intro newsletter-signup__intro--centered"&gt;
          &lt;img alt="" class="newsletter-signup__img" hidden data-src-light="https://dot.cdnslate.com/static/media/components/newsletter-signup/the-slatest.49f353b.png" data-src-dark="https://dot.cdnslate.com/static/media/components/newsletter-signup/the-slatest-dark.ca73d21.png"&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Get the best of news and politics&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Sign up for Slate's evening newsletter.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxPbjhoZVBPUEt6TnBqS1NfeHNVRkZDeE5lcEJuNWdQaGxMLUNTOVhnRjVxZ2pBdkdfYWN5R3QzcXgtUVV1czlLcktTTVgwVmYtc2NMRFU0UVBSNW80UDdEQ09RMm52QjZjb2dlVG41MFNIZTNSOExLdTJLVC1sbF9FeWp3NVlRbGktTE9QR2MxR1VlZ3lT</guid></item><item><title>阿尔茨海默氏症疗法应该针对特定的基因，研究人员说-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2026/jan/09/alzheimers-therapies-target-apoe-gene-variants-researchers-say</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;New therapies for Alzheimer’s disease should target a particular gene linked to the condition, according to researchers who said most cases would never arise if its harmful effects were neutralised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The call to action follows the arrival of the first wave of drugs that aim to treat Alzheimer’s patients by removing toxic proteins from the brain. While the drugs slow the disease down, the benefits are minor, and they &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/article/2024/aug/22/uk-health-regulator-rejects-lecanemab-as-treatment-for-alzheimers" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;have been rejected&lt;/a&gt; for widespread use by the UK’s National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (Nice).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In searching for alternative therapies, scientists at UCL say drug developers should focus on two risk-raising variants of a gene named Apoe. Therapies designed to block the variants’ impact have “vast potential” for preventing the disease, they claim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Dylan Williams, a genetic epidemiologist at UCL, said: “Most Alzheimer’s disease cases would not arise without the contribution of just this single gene: Apoe. We need to think about it as a direct target. Almost all potential Alzheimer’s cases could benefit from Apoe-related interventions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;More than half a million people in the UK, and more than 40 million worldwide, are living with Alzheimer’s disease, the most common form of dementia. Several genes contribute to Alzheimer’s risk and lifestyle is important too: smoking, obesity, diabetes, high blood pressure and cholesterol all make the disease more likely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Williams and his colleagues analysed medical records from more than 450,000 people of European ancestry to calculate how much Alzheimer’s disease arose due to different variants of the Apoe gene. People inherit two copies of the gene – one from each parent – and there are three main variants: Apoe2, 3 and 4.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Scientists have long known that people with two copies of Apoe4 are high risk for Alzheimer’s, though 40% to 70% never develop the disease. The Apoe3 variant is widely considered neutral and the rare Apoe2 variant is regarded as protective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But Williams said we should see it another way. Compared with carrying two copies of Apoe2, both Apoe3 and Apoe4 raise the risk of Alzheimer’s, he said. Writing in the journal &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s44400-025-00045-9" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;npj Dementia&lt;/a&gt;, the team calculate that without these variants, 72% to 93% of Alzheimer’s cases, and about 45% of all dementia, would not have occurred. “If interventions could eliminate the detrimental effects [of Apoe3 and 4], we could expect to prevent most Alzheimer’s disease and a large proportion of all dementia,” they write.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;That is a big if. The Apoe gene is crucial for moving cholesterol and other fats around the body and brain, so knocking it out entirely is likely to cause problems. Future therapies might edit the gene variants, or dampen down their activity, but those are neither imminent nor risk-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Another problem is that the vast majority of people – more than 99% in the study – carry Apoe3 or Apoe4. So preventing Alzheimer’s would mean treating nearly the entire population, possibly through invasive gene editing of the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The study received a mixed reception. Tim Frayling, professor of human genetics at the University of Geneva, said claiming more than 90% of Alzheimer’s would not occur without the Apoe gene’s effects was like saying more than 90% of road traffic deaths would not occur without the contribution of cars. “People should not worry if they have the risk versions of the gene, because 99.4% of us do,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props="{&amp;quot;index&amp;quot;:11,&amp;quot;listId&amp;quot;:4156,&amp;quot;identityName&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;morning-briefing&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;description&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Our morning email breaks down the key stories of the day, telling you what’s happening and why it matters&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;First Edition&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;frequency&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Every weekday&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;successDescription&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;We'll send you First Edition every weekday&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;theme&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;news&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;idApiUrl&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://idapi.theguardian.com&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;hideNewsletterSignupComponentForSubscribers&amp;quot;:true}"&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But Tara Spires-Jones, professor of neurodegeneration at the University of Edinburgh, said understanding the risk factors that made the brain vulnerable to Alzheimer’s was “essential for developing effective treatments and prevention strategies”, adding that Apoe was one of the most important genetic risk factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Sheona Scales, of Alzheimer’s Research UK, said: “Evidence around Apoe3 contributing to Alzheimer’s and dementia risk is significant, as this has been largely thought of as having a neutral effect on risk. However, it’s important to note that not everyone with these Apoe gene variations will go on to develop dementia, as other risk factors also have an influence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This research raises lots of interesting questions, such as how Apoe3 and Apoe4 could drive Alzheimer’s risk, their effects in people of non-European ancestry, and whether targeting these variants could be a promising avenue for treatment and prevention of Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Because of the complexity of Alzheimer’s risk, Apoe testing is not available on the NHS for people worried about their risk of developing Alzheimer’s in the future. If you are worried about your dementia risk, you should speak to your GP.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:05:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxNMnFnTXlQUlBPVERraFJNS29sM3I2NXY0cUVtZFFoUXprbGZiSU53R0QyRE1JWE5sS1pwMjFUUFVKRDNfQzdLQ0RjRDdUMGFlX09USFNfZHI3b1hycXpaZGtNc0d0Zjd3MkNuOXA0WFJVejhiTUdjSnViNXZHeDdQOUpvekt5SlJIVGpVS0N4VGFaRzdQbUhfaW8yckw5YzZ6Q1U0Y0VVLTZ2a2ZQcnFz</guid></item><item><title>建议卫生专业人员佩戴口罩级口罩-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2026/jan/09/health-professionals-respirator-grade-masks-who-advise</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Surgical face masks provide inadequate protection against flu-like illnesses including Covid, and should be replaced by respirator-level masks – worn every time doctors and nurses are face to face with a patient, according to a group of experts urging changes to &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/world-health-organization" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt; guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There is “no rational justification remaining for prioritising or using” the surgical masks that are ubiquitous in hospitals and clinics globally, given their “inadequate protection against airborne pathogens”, they said in &lt;a href="https://whn.global/a-call-for-the-universal-use-of-respirators-in-healthcare/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;a letter to WHO chief Dr Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“There is even less justification for allowing healthcare workers to wear no face covering at all,” they said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;At the height of the Covid pandemic an &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2025/sep/08/disposable-face-masks-covid-chemical-timebomb" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;estimated 129bn&lt;/a&gt; disposable face masks were being used around the world every month, by the public and healthcare workers, with surgical masks the most widely available and recommended by most health authorities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Respirators designed to filter tiny particles – such as masks &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/dec/30/masks-best-covid-protection-ffp2-ffp3" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;meeting FFP2/3 standards&lt;/a&gt; in the UK or N95 in the US – should instead be standard practice for medical interactions, they said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;As additional evidence emerged over the course of the pandemic, officials in many countries &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jan/21/wear-medical-grade-masks-if-you-cant-self-isolate-britons-told" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;switched to recommending those masks as more effective&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The proposals would result in fewer infections in patients and health professionals, and reduce rates of sickness, absence and burnout in the health workforce, the authors contended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;gu-island name="InteractiveBlockComponent" priority="critical" deferuntil="idle" props='{"url":"https://interactive.guim.co.uk/uploader/embed/2021/01/facemaks-zip/giv-3902CGt23miACpMx/","scriptUrl":"https://interactive.guim.co.uk/embed/iframe-wrapper/0.1/boot.js","alt":"Diagram showing the difference between a surgical face mask and FFP respirator mask","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0},"elementId":"11ac5918-9f2f-403f-b158-8eb58d75336a","isMainMedia":false}'&gt;&lt;figure id="11ac5918-9f2f-403f-b158-8eb58d75336a" class="element element-interactive element--inline element-inline dcr-w422y2" data-alt="Diagram showing the difference between a surgical face mask and FFP respirator mask" data-testid="interactive-element-Diagram%20showing%20the%20difference%20between%20a%20surgical%20face%20mask%20and%20FFP%20respirator%20mask" data-spacefinder-role="inline"&gt;&lt;a data-name="placeholder" href="https://interactive.guim.co.uk/uploader/embed/2021/01/facemaks-zip/giv-3902CGt23miACpMx/" class="dcr-1eupayo"&gt;Diagram showing the difference between a surgical face mask and FFP respirator mask&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Adam Finkel of the University of Michigan School of Public &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/health" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;, one of the letter’s organisers, said surgical masks were not designed to stop airborne pathogens but “invented to stop doctors and nurses from sneezing into the guts and the hearts of patients”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Surgical masks are to respirators what the typewriter was to the modern computer, said Finkel, who was chief regulatory official at the US Occupational Safety and Health Administration between 1995 and 2000: “Obsolete.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The letter came out of discussions at an &lt;a href="https://unpolitics.global/next-steps" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;online conference&lt;/a&gt; organised last year called Unpolitics, looking at the implementation of evidence-based policies. It was authored by seven clinicians and scientists, including Finkel, and has been endorsed by almost 50 senior clinicians and researchers, and more than 2,000 members of the public, including clinically vulnerable patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There could be “off-ramps”, where governments or establishments decide respirators are not necessary, based on factors such as community infection rates, and ventilation or air filtration devices in a room, the letter says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While the suggested guidance would apply only in healthcare settings, where the risk of infection is higher, it is likely to provoke controversy. Face masks &lt;a href="https://www.economist.com/britain/2020/08/08/with-face-masks-britain-imported-an-american-culture-war" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;became a culture war issue&lt;/a&gt; during the Covid pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In December, Tory leader &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/dec/09/nhs-leader-calls-for-revival-of-mask-wearing-amid-tidal-wave-of-flu" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Kemi Badenoch said&lt;/a&gt; she had been “slightly traumatised by all the mask wearing that we had to do during Covid” in response to comments by an NHS leader saying people with flu symptoms “must wear” a face mask in public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The WHO cannot mandate global policies, but the signatories argue that an update to its infection prevention and control guidelines to recommend respirators could have a profound impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;They also suggest that the WHO’s procurement infrastructure could help increase access to respirators even in poorer countries, with production of surgical masks phased down over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Surgical masks are still “better than nothing”, Finkel conceded, with studies suggesting they block approximately 40% of Covid-sized particles in the air, compared with 95% for respirators.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;He says the comparative reduction in risk can be thought of like falling off a wall of four inches rather than four feet: “You can still trip and break an ankle at four inches, but you’re much better off.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Critics of the group’s arguments point to &lt;a href="https://www.cochrane.org/evidence/CD006207_do-physical-measures-such-hand-washing-or-wearing-masks-stop-or-slow-down-spread-respiratory-viruses" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;a lack of randomised controlled trials&lt;/a&gt; showing that physical measures slow the spread of respiratory viruses. Finkel and the other authors say such trials are simply not possible, for example because people in a trial will not wear masks 24/7 and could be exposed to pathogens while unmasked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Instead they say physical tests showing that respirators stop particles, conducted in laboratories, offer sufficient evidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="eaf47ec1-39ae-46e9-a57b-b83d49c107fe" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;FFP2 face masks being tested at Moldex-Metric, a German protective workwear manufacturer.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Thomas Kienzle/AFP/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="6e178cb4-df19-43ff-ac13-09a13bc02403" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":21,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"World agrees pandemic accord for tackling outbreaks of disease","elementId":"6e178cb4-df19-43ff-ac13-09a13bc02403","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/may/20/world-agrees-pandemic-accord-for-tackling-outbreaks-of-disease-who-covid"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0},"isInStarRatingVariant":false}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The WHO has been criticised for being slow to describe Covid-19 as &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/australia-news/2025/nov/03/australia-prime-ministers-prize-for-science-lidia-morawska-covid-michael-wear-aboriginal-and-torres-strait-islander-knowledge" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;spreading via “airborne” particles&lt;/a&gt; and the letter also calls for it to revisit earlier statements and “unambiguously inform the public that it spreads via airborne respiratory particles”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Trisha Greenhalgh of the University of Oxford, &lt;a href="https://journals.asm.org/doi/10.1128/cmr.00124-23" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;whose research&lt;/a&gt; is cited extensively in the letter and is one of its signatories, said: “A germ that does not get inside someone cannot make them sick. By sealing against the face, respirators force airflow to pass through them, filtering out the airborne germs. Respirators are designed to fit closely around the face and meet high filtration standards. Medical masks, in contrast, fit loosely and leak extensively.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The letter’s supporters include members of the &lt;a href="https://whn.global/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;World Health Network&lt;/a&gt;, prominent US epidemiologist Eric Feigl-Ding, and Guardian columnist George Monbiot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A WHO spokesperson said the letter required “careful review”. They said the organisation consulted widely with experts from different health and economic contexts when producing guidance on personal protective equipment for health workers, adding: “We are currently reviewing WHO’s Infection Prevention and Control guidelines for epidemic and pandemic-prone acute respiratory infections, based on the latest scientific evidence to ensure protection of health workers.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:50:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQM1JlU3o5Zm5nWlBPNGNicmtqbnByaEIzTWd4aGNwUHc0WUJvT0ZQcTRZdnNWc0ZhRWtZSkxwaEppQzBhQkUxWUw5Q2tQajJBVDVsTUZ3SXVGWFoyYUVzbTh2eXNvc3ZxR00wZ0JvQTlKRFU1Yld0ajBJRGpHaDRtd0h4UzB1aF9NcndlTGlPUHF1bjZhYzQ1eUNlc29tbzdWd2Y0RmZTdUNlYXdGZUdjWmRWUQ</guid></item><item><title>研究人员揭示了导致癌症发病率飙升的令人担忧的原因： “没有更多的禁忌” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/researcher-uncovers-alarming-reason-contributing-063000948.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Cigarettes, combined with air pollution and agricultural chemicals, have led to a concerning spike in cancer in Lebanon, according to one researcher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ali Mokdad led a global &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(25)01635-6/abstract" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:survey;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;survey&lt;/a&gt; on cancer rates, finding that his native country of Lebanon is experiencing the fastest increase in incidence and deaths. &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/goats-and-soda/2025/10/22/g-s1-94470/cancer-rates-deaths-lebanon" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:NPR summarized;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;NPR summarized&lt;/a&gt; his research, which found that the frequency of new cancer cases in the country spiked 162% from 1990 to 2023, and cancer-related deaths increased by 80% over that period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Though pollution and agricultural chemicals are contributing to the issue, Mokdad told the news outlet that a lot of the cancer can be attributed to a strong smoking culture in the nation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"There is no more taboo about smoking," Mokdad said. "Everybody smokes. Kids smoke in front of their parents. Yesterday, I went with some of my friends for dinner. You come home, you stink of tobacco."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why is this study important?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;NPR noted that cancer rates are also increasing worldwide. While smoking may be the main culprit in Lebanon, we are now confronting a number of pollutants and chemicals that are increasing our risks for different types of cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;For instance, air pollution, which Mokdad noted is prevalent in Beirut, has been linked to a number of health problems, including respiratory issues and cancer. In fact, one new study found that women who live in more polluted areas suffer increased risks for breast cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Airborne microplastics — which can be inhaled — also put people at risk for lung cancer, per another recent paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's being done about cancer-causing pollutants?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It's tough to prevent exposure to all cancer-causing pollutants, but one positive step is to quit smoking if you currently do. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/tobacco/campaign/tips/quit-smoking/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:resources and tips;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;resources and tips&lt;/a&gt; to help smokers kick the habit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Another thing anyone can do to reduce air pollution in our cities is to opt for carbon-free modes of transportation, such as &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/journeys/save-money-on-transportation/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:biking;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;biking&lt;/a&gt;, e-biking, or walking. Using public transportation can also help decrease pollution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Reducing the amount of new microplastics entering the environment will help limit our exposure. The best way to do this is to &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/journeys/use-less-plastic/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:stop using;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;stop using&lt;/a&gt; so many single-use plastics. Some easy swaps include reusable water bottles and shopping totes, and bringing your own sturdy container to restaurants for leftovers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Get TCD's &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/newsletter/?utm_source=recV8k9A4K32ORkwb" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletters;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletters&lt;/a&gt; for easy tips to save more, waste less, and make smarter choices — and earn up to $5,000 toward clean upgrades in TCD's exclusive &lt;a href="https://links.thecooldown.com/rewards-club" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Rewards Club;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Rewards Club&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxNUUd6eHRkQlI4UW9kVXlMd0dDcExoS0JZY015cGZGX1hJTWsya3NmblNjNmhBWHNNYkZjXzg5S080S3VmSEVrQVh5U0p6YkNXTTBVaUN3N0VPZ1NOOGwtUFUyejVtcUlNQkhmeGRxM2Q4cWJSR1pPQ3ZQVzF4NnJIV1E4UVlMZkhoTGZSU2IxSWl6LTFNdHAyRkNlM2JBRVlZ</guid></item><item><title>斯诺霍米什县King的潜在麻疹暴露情况提示-《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/visit-from-south-carolina-family-with-measles-leads-to-alert-in-wa/</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitwFBVV95cUxNcXFxQ2k1RUNSbmhRYVZtbDZpRGx1Y1lSejg4MkUtUno1emhNUzBaWGdnMnZQQjdqV0dpVDdtVXdlMl8xTW9JYVBxR2dFXzRuTXhXNlRlOWF5OWpVUkpCVnNNVnA0YlZyTVhhUGJfT1Z2Mkd0ZXdDM1lTUEhiRnlsNWw0TDBOX1hyQlBUaE9kZElKaU5BbWFuT0JIbDdhZDM1UWphc2VHQlJzdFJ6d1ZJcFc2X3VwVTQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Potential measles exposures in King, Snohomish counties prompt alert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwFBVV95cUxNbTlSNC1jalJ2NFlQc2thdDVfRWN1dVRobWN6dFdQLUV3dHBWWGlrdThEX2E3cHloZE94RkFJamxmamphNE53bnVQMVBsRlNpWDhzbXlZeXBVMEs1Z3g2OFpld2k1VllkU1Q0TDMtYkV6X3Z2VThfM3I4WkhhZ09tdFN3OE9RY0VBdXltSU9jOUFpbzZ6b2hTU0loYXRlQ290TkRwbWEtUUJGcWlGZy1BS1V3UW9FdmhtNFU00gHPAUFVX3lxTE1nNXA2MUJqRHpvS3J6ZG9wQkFmTjRON01WeV9GS1BXb2dQVmdNRF9mdGRpaDlidEN2YkNTNXpUcE9SdWRaV1BBT1M3bi1ZSDU3U0Z0ZGxHcC0tVjRxblR1R1QyZE1qaXYxbHFRYWJ1Z2s2cEVtR3dpd1NveXJEa0hMaTBDNm9Wci1kMTltaG1Xdk0yYWJYVnhQSnlhMllXN1dWYmNMdjE2UWVqR2UtdU1VcTBWZVEzRzlXWVZTZS01UHdVZ0pfdnl1MlRRQ3M2OA?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Several possible measles exposures in King, Snohomish Counties&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;KIRO 7 News Seattle&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxQWnBjaW9MZi1GZEtSV1RPMmZ6QWxMUnA3Nnlab21mQU04MWlwblExS2Z4NGxIeUFjSVJGaDRmQVFQU0FUWnh1bm51VmQ3dHl6eTZlRGFUaUJvRVlFZjQzdXFXaXk3ekFEWlI5OVNEQm1hRkVHNGx6MFh4NGVWZzJlalVNb0RZbnlVSm45d2dGV3NyNE9WenFoQlVSREQ4M3JPVmlr?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Health officials: Three confirmed measles cases in SnoCo over holidays&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Everett Herald&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMic0FVX3lxTFBUVkJVeGZJdzcwN19EZXJ4bDdhMElheGVkcXlldkktZGUzLVlWNUIwOG9SeG01Zmo4MGdqWk9sSHJKbXdXd1RoaTRnN3luN2doWnd6ZGdySExONl9hUmFXWGNBQ2lXQ3BRZ1ozUUhGTldWNEXSAXhBVV95cUxOQ0pyY095ZGtKeS1BdlpIeGJnb1pMS3pIMkpKYUN1TmpmaEFKWWpMTnlTRnl3SGhhNmVnb0EycTllMDVMSVVkdnhsd250WE5GV0tkWmhFWHIwc29oMlQ0VF96d0xuXzRzanl3eXg4cFBWVTFVUXVCanI?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;3 measles cases confirmed in family visiting western WA for holidays&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;FOX 13 Seattle&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 05:32:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxNcXFxQ2k1RUNSbmhRYVZtbDZpRGx1Y1lSejg4MkUtUno1emhNUzBaWGdnMnZQQjdqV0dpVDdtVXdlMl8xTW9JYVBxR2dFXzRuTXhXNlRlOWF5OWpVUkpCVnNNVnA0YlZyTVhhUGJfT1Z2Mkd0ZXdDM1lTUEhiRnlsNWw0TDBOX1hyQlBUaE9kZElKaU5BbWFuT0JIbDdhZDM1UWphc2VHQlJzdFJ6d1ZJcFc2X3VwVTQ</guid></item><item><title>大脑健康挑战：心灵和身体的医生预约-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2026/well/brain-health-doctor-appointments.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="g-main svelte-19neaxa"&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Congratulations, you’ve reached the final day of the Brain Health Challenge! Today, we’re asking you to do a few things that might feel a bit out of left field — like getting your blood pressure checked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="g-wrapper  svelte-19s2qxj"&gt;   &lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;No, it isn’t as fun as &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2026/01/07/well/brain-health-games-teasers.html"&gt;playing Pips&lt;/a&gt;, but experts say it’s one of the most important things you can do for your brain. That’s because heart health and brain health are intrinsically linked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/02/29/well/live/high-blood-pressure-lower.html"&gt;High blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;, in particular, can damage brain cells, and it’s a significant risk factor for stroke and dementia. When blood pressure is too high, it places stress on the walls of arteries in the brain. Over time, that added stress can cause the blood vessel walls to thicken, obstructing blood flow. In other cases, the increased pressure causes the artery walls to thin and leak blood into the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;These changes to the blood vessels can sometimes cause a large stroke to occur. More commonly, the damage leads to micro-strokes and micro-hemorrhages, which cause fewer immediate problems and often go unnoticed. But if someone has hypertension for years or decades, these injuries can build up, and the person may start to experience cognitive impairment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;High blood pressure “is known as a silent killer for lots of reasons,” said Dr. Shyam Prabhakaran, the chair of neurology at the University of Chicago. “It doesn’t cause you any symptoms until it does.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Because the damage accumulates over many years, experts say that managing blood pressure in midlife matters most for brain health. Hypertension can be addressed with medication or lifestyle changes, as directed by your doctor. But the first thing you need to do is know your numbers. If your blood pressure comes back higher than 120/80, it’s important to take it seriously, Dr. Prabhakaran said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;While you’re at it, there are a few other aspects of your physical health that you should check on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Your eyes and ears are two of them. &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/08/08/well/mind/hearing-vision-dementia-risk.html"&gt;Hearing and vision loss&lt;/a&gt; have both been shown to increase the risk of dementia. Experts think that with less sensory information coming in to stimulate the brain, the regions that process hearing and vision can start to atrophy. What’s more, people with sensory loss often withdraw or are left out of social interactions, further depriving them of cognitive stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Oral health can also affect your brain health. Research has found a connection between regular flossing and reduced odds of &lt;a href="https://newsroom.heart.org/news/regular-dental-flossing-may-lower-risk-of-stroke-from-blood-clots-irregular-heartbeats?preview=df8b&amp;amp;preview_mode=True"&gt;having a stroke&lt;/a&gt;. That may be because good oral health can help to reduce inflammation in the body. The bacteria that cause gum disease have also been tied to an &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32280099/"&gt;increased risk of Alzheimer’s&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;And have you gotten your shingles vaccine? There is &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11485228/"&gt;mounting evidence&lt;/a&gt; that it’s a powerful weapon for protecting against dementia. &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-025-08800-x"&gt;One study&lt;/a&gt; found that it lowered people’s odds of developing the condition by as much as 20 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;To wrap up this challenge, we want you to schedule a few medical appointments that benefit your brain, as well as your body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;After five days of &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2026/well/brain-health-mind-diet-recipes.html"&gt;feeding&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2026/well/brain-health-exercise-workout.html"&gt;exercising&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2026/01/07/well/brain-health-games-teasers.html"&gt;challenging&lt;/a&gt; your brain, you are well on your way to better cognitive health. Thanks for joining me this week, and keep up the good habits!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 01:01:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNOGN4VzJjWTZad0wwRWVJbWF2b1V5TkF2UHJhYXlpQXJaSzgydWlDajRGR3pZV3lBNlNhZjZxdzNFZ3ZvXzJUZXNuUU5oT1Z3RVo1cTlFNXpDSHdibTN0aGN2bDFBM0dhRVVpUk8wdF9aQTNiTlp1NVpEaE54Tjh3RTdFOV92cVJuWnNn</guid></item><item><title>维生素A的阴暗面：常见营养素如何帮助肿瘤逃避免疫系统- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/vitamin-as-dark-side-how-a-common-nutrient-can-help-tumors-evade-the-immune-system/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:49:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxQdE8yUjktbVBqRGo3UklzQUtrdldLbVh0SXZkckdhWGhTZ0JwaHUwYXFzYV9NLVpjX09ER1ljbEtXMWxRRVhGbFFYX3BnNWYyWnc2b00zXzdGMWEwZEN1Z3lNT2liRndZazNLMXROenY0Y21fMGFjZHRkRkxMQVVlaml1NmV1NmliT01ncWxTal81XzNjNnZKems0UEQzc0w5OE1jQUxoUG1CclQx</guid></item><item><title>纽约市流感病例在十年来达到最高水平后下降-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/08/nyregion/nyc-flu-cases-drop-january.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:28:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxPbWtYUDR6aG9UTDB2NF9hdXJOT2FUcktlLVhORTdaOVBQeWhyV0otUzg0NWxIYmRIUkhwbkhmaEl2MGtJS1I0LVE3N2JJLU9EaUlSaDZfa094Tm84Nm9pZUJBX2E3UVlfQWtRUEpwN2d1amdiS1hQUm5pX09HM25qVQ</guid></item><item><title>新一组副作用较少的潜在糖尿病药物可以重新编程胰岛素抵抗细胞，使其更健康- Phys.org</title><link>https://phys.org/news/2026-01-group-potential-diabetes-drugs-side.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:30:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTFBiSmgzSE1Ncm9yd1IxeWpDZll3ZW9TcHNpd01ua1RJbFUwUW5Ga2E5UTNnOXhXWFFwM0lxbTB6ZFRRZkZpZzVDQi1OdVpYNjdlYW1IU3Q1bHdZUTRfVTA1WmVsUUhkOEUtNGFWTEZWRUxqN1Z5MWRVZ1FB</guid></item><item><title>57迷人和令人不安的医学照片，不是每个人都能处理的（新图片） -无聊的熊猫</title><link>https://www.boredpanda.com/creepy-medical-cases-pics/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-content modal-body"&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="weekly" value="119509170107975610"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Weekly&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; The week’s finest content carefully selected to bring you the best articles directly [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="daily" value="119509170234852486"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Daily&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; Our top news, meme articles, and a dose of the best content delivered straight to your inbox. [every day] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="119509170245338276"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Funny&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; The funniest articles of the week that had our audience in stitches [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="119509170229609595"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Animals&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; A delightful mix of top animal photos, memes, and a sprinkle of pet wellness articles [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="119509170255824063"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Good News&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; A dose of uplifting news delivered directly to your inbox. Pure positivity guaranteed [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="154827377563666414"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Best Deals&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; Exclusive discounts, our top shopping articles and ever more impressive deals directly to you [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="119509170240095383"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Art&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; The most captivating photographs, incredible art pieces, and amusing comics—all in one curated collection of the finest art articles [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="119509170272601317"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Parenting Stories&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; Discover relatable and unbelievable parenting anecdotes from the daily journey of raising a child [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="119509170267358426"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Brainy Panda&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; The most interesting trivia and quizzes in your inbox [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="163332909941392922"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;BP Daily&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; BP Daily offers readers unbiased, nonpartisan reporting, analysis, and informed opinion in the areas of politics, policy, democracy, ethics, crime, and world news. [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bored Panda</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:26:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiY0FVX3lxTE1wTE95TWY5UFM1R0s5S3g5bFJ3eExrTGloUjZ2UUpEYzZhQkZUYWNUYThsWHNDM0JqTzJLRVdFV1AyUDdMeFlHZEhtWVFjV3hQMF8tRG9FbzJyQjFwTXAxM2RMZw</guid></item><item><title>您是否正确服用补充剂？以下是他们的剂量限制指南-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2026/jan/08/supplements-vitamins-safety-dosage-limit-guide</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;here are more than &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/drugs/news-events-human-drugs/fdas-regulation-dietary-supplements-dr-cara-welch" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;100,000&lt;/a&gt; supplements on the US market – capsules, powders, tablets and gummies sold to improve or maintain health. Supplements can contain vitamins, minerals, botanicals and amino acids on their own or in various combinations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The consumption of these products is &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10421343/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;surging&lt;/a&gt;. But it’s a common misunderstanding that these products are entirely safe, says Dr Pieter Cohen, an internist and associate professor at Harvard Medical School. Excessive amounts of nutrients can cause health problems, so it’s critical to know if you’re using the correct dosage of high-quality products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Here’s what experts say about navigating the world of supplements, and what happens if you take too much of some common ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="choose-supplements-and-dosage-carefully" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose supplements and dosage carefully&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Ideally, the nutrients we need come from the food we eat, says Dr Denise Millstine, director of integrative medicine at the Mayo Clinic Arizona. But that’s not always possible for various reasons, like a lack of access to nutritious foods or the effects of certain medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="de198331-d196-4414-a927-b0bac06b0c1d" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":5,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Is it true that… you should take vitamin C when you’ve got a cold?","elementId":"de198331-d196-4414-a927-b0bac06b0c1d","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2025/dec/08/is-it-true-that-you-should-take-vitamin-c-when-youve-got-a-cold"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":10,"display":2,"theme":4},"isInStarRatingVariant":false}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Some people may need a supplement; some people need to be careful that they’re not getting too much of a supplement,” says Joan Blake, a registered dietitian and clinical instructor at Boston University. “It’s all over the place.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There are so many of these products for sale, and so many variants of what’s on a label, that shopping and selecting even a single supplement can be “dizzying” for consumers, says Millstine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;For some nutrients, there’s a &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/HealthInformation/ODS_Frequently_Asked_Questions.aspx" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;recommended dietary allowance&lt;/a&gt; (RDA) – an amount to aim for daily, set in the US by the Food and Nutrition Board of the National Academies of Sciences, Engineering, and Medicine. The RDA can vary by sex, age and medical status. There’s also a tolerable upper intake level (UL), which is the maximum safe daily limit. Consuming more than the UL can cause health problems, depending on the nutrient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Additionally, in the US, “there’s no vetting of products before they’re sold to ensure that the label is accurate,” says Cohen, whose&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2815523" data-link-name="in body link"&gt; research&lt;/a&gt; suggests contents and quantity labelling are often inaccurate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There is limited government oversight over vitamins and supplements. The US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/drugs/news-events-human-drugs/fdas-regulation-dietary-supplements-dr-cara-welch#:~:text" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;does not approve&lt;/a&gt; supplements or their labelling before they are sold. The only way to know if what’s listed on the label is accurate is if the product has been certified by the &lt;a href="https://www.nsf.org/consumer-resources/articles/supplement-vitamin-certification" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;National Sanitation Foundation&lt;/a&gt; (NSF) or &lt;a href="https://www.usp.org/verification-services/verified-mark" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;United States Pharmacopeia&lt;/a&gt; (USP), says Cohen. These are non-profits with “high-quality, third-party certification programs”, he explains. You can use &lt;a href="https://info.nsf.org/certified/dietary/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;their&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.quality-supplements.org/verified-products" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;websites&lt;/a&gt; to find verified products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="check-with-your-doctor-before-taking-any-new-supplement" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check with your doctor before taking any new supplement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Because the recommended amount differs from person to person, it’s critical to speak with a healthcare provider before starting something new. You need to know how the product might interact with anything else you’re consuming, like a medication or another supplement, explains Cohen. Adverse health effects could arise, or medications can become less effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Supplements can also affect blood tests, leading to inaccurate results, explains Dr Fernando Carnavali, an associate professor of internal medicine at the Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai. He says it’s important to continue to discuss any vitamin or supplement use with your physician in case of evolving research about potential interactions, benefits or harms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It’s best to use vitamins and supplements with caution, just as you would with over-the-counter medications like Tylenol, says Millstine. It’s also a good idea to stick to studied doses. She recommends using the National Center for Complementary and Integrative Health &lt;a href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; for information on dosing. The US Department of Agriculture also &lt;a href="https://www.nal.usda.gov/human-nutrition-and-food-safety/dri-calculator" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;has a tool&lt;/a&gt; for calculating the amount of vitamins and minerals you need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Conversely, do not take dosing advice from the person selling the product, due to a risk of bias, says Millstine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Carnavali suspects that because vitamins and minerals are &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2023/nov/13/natural-remedies-medication-true-self" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;perceived as natural&lt;/a&gt;, people are less likely to share what they are taking with their medical providers. It’s not uncommon for a patient to come in with questions about their health, only to learn that their vitamin and supplement habits were causing symptoms. “We’re not here to judge – we’re here to guide you,” says Carnavali.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-happens-if-you-take-too-much" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What happens if you take too much?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multivitamins: &lt;/strong&gt;Multivitamin supplements contain at least three vitamins and one mineral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There’s no regulation of what nutrients must be included or how much. &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/MVMS-HealthProfessional/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;According&lt;/a&gt; to the National Institutes of Health, some of these supplements contain vitamins and minerals in amounts higher than the established UL. Accordingly, there’s a risk of &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17209210/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;excess nutrients&lt;/a&gt;, especially if you’re taking a multivitamin with other supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;What &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17209218/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;harm might occur&lt;/a&gt; depends on the excessive nutrient in question. “Multivitamins can be tricky because you need to look at each of the components, and there are just so many of them,” says Millstine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There are risks associated with certain individuals. For example, the NIH &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/MVMS-HealthProfessional/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;states&lt;/a&gt; that smokers and former smokers might want to avoid multivitamins with large amounts of beta-carotene or vitamin A, which are linked to an increased risk of lung cancer in smokers. For people who are pregnant, more than &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/pubs/Scoop%20Winter%202022.pdf" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;2,800micrograms (mcg)&lt;/a&gt; of vitamin A a day can increase the risk of birth defects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;People who take blood thinners should speak with their doctor before using a multivitamin containing vitamin K, which can decrease the effectiveness of those drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin D: &lt;/strong&gt;“Vitamin D can become quite toxic when taken excessively,” says Millstine. High levels are associated with harms like nausea, vomiting and excessive urination. Extremely high levels are linked to kidney failure, irregular heartbeat and death. The NIH notes that high levels are &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminD-Consumer/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;“almost always&lt;/a&gt;” caused by excessive supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Individual requirements can differ, Millstine says. According to the NIH, &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminD-Consumer/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the RDA&lt;/a&gt; for adults between ages 19 and 70 is around 15mcg, or 600 International Units (IU). The upper limit for the same group is 100mcg, or 4,000 IU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If your healthcare provider recommends you take vitamin D, it’s advisable to start at the standard dose, then recheck your levels in three months, says Millstine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Omega-3 &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;fatty &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;acids: &lt;/strong&gt;Omega-3 fatty acids are found in certain foods, like fatty fish and chia seeds. Supplements &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/feb/03/an-omega-3-dose-a-day-could-slow-ageing-process-healthspan-trial-finds" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;like fish oil&lt;/a&gt; or fish liver oil &lt;a href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/health/omega3-supplements-what-you-need-to-know#:~:text" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;contain&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2025/apr/07/do-fish-oil-supplements-work" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;two types&lt;/a&gt; of omega-3 fatty acids: docosahexaenoic acid, or DHA, and eicosapentaenoic acid, or EPA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Experts &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Omega3FattyAcids-Consumer/#:~:text" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;haven’t established&lt;/a&gt; recommended amounts for these two types, but the FDA recommends limiting the combined total to no more than 5 grams daily from dietary supplements. High doses can increase the risk of bleeding and stroke, &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/drugs-supplements-fish-oil/art-20364810#:~:text=Taking%20high%20doses%20of%20fish,increase%20the%20risk%20of%20stroke." data-link-name="in body link"&gt;according&lt;/a&gt; to the Mayo Clinic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A low-quality omega-3 product comes with more risks of side effects, ranging from heartburn to nausea, explains Millstine. These supplements can contain other elements, like vitamins A and D, and &lt;a href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/health/omega3-supplements-what-you-need-to-know" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;dosage can vary&lt;/a&gt; from product to product, so it’s important to check the label.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"index":29,"listId":6039,"identityName":"well-actually","description":"Practical advice, expert insights and answers to your questions about how to live a good life","name":"Well Actually","frequency":"Weekly","successDescription":"You are subscribed","theme":"lifestyle","idApiUrl":"https://idapi.theguardian.com","hideNewsletterSignupComponentForSubscribers":true}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;For instance, if you’re taking a 1,000mg fish oil capsule with a 300mg omega-3 content, it’s worth checking what else is in the product, says Millstine. Non-EPA/DHA elements can cause issues like gastrointestinal symptoms and increased risk of bruising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Another omega-3 fatty acid, alpha-linolenic acid (ALA), is found in plants. Apart from the food you eat, you can get ALA from flaxseed oil supplements. The recommended amount of ALA for adults is between 1.1 grams to 1.6 grams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calcium: &lt;/strong&gt;The typical recommendation for adults is 1,000mg to 1,200mg of calcium daily, divided into no more than around 500mg at a time, says Millstine. The &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Calcium-Consumer/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;upper limit&lt;/a&gt; varies depending on your age and medical status. Calcium can negatively interact with other supplements and medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Too much supplemental calcium can &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4708574/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;cause kidney stones&lt;/a&gt;. While research is &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/heart-attack/expert-answers/calcium-supplements/faq-20058352" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;mixed&lt;/a&gt; and more is needed, some &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7910980/#sec5-nutrients-13-00368" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; suggest calcium supplements can increase the risk of heart disease, specifically in postmenopausal women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;According to the &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/vitamins-and-minerals/calcium/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;National Health Service&lt;/a&gt;, more than 1,500mg of calcium a day can lead to stomach pain and diarrhea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin C: &lt;/strong&gt;Vitamin C is one of the more overused supplements, because so many people use it to avoid sickness, Blake says. While it may slightly shorten the duration of a cold, &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK279544/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; suggests that it won’t prevent a cold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Extra vitamin C simply exits the body during urination. But chronic excessive use can lead to gastrointestinal issues like nausea and diarrhea, explains Blake. Doses greater than &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/ency/article/002404.htm" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;2,000mg&lt;/a&gt; a day can lead to stomach aches, diarrhea and kidney stones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Millstine advises about 500mg to 1,000mg per day. “The problem with taking too much is it’s just not helping you, so why would you stress your kidneys in that way?” she asks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin B12: &lt;/strong&gt;The NIH recommends &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminB12-Consumer/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;2.4mcg&lt;/a&gt; of B12 daily for most adults, though personalized doses can vary. It’s available in different types of supplements, many of which have very high doses of B12.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While rare, excessive B12 can be associated with symptoms like anxiety, agitation, flushing and headaches, says Millstine. It can interact with medications like gastric acid inhibitors and metformin. Other forms of vitamin B, &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/australia-news/2025/jul/27/what-is-vitamin-b6-toxicity-and-what-are-the-symptoms-of-taking-too-much" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;like vitamin B6&lt;/a&gt;, can be more toxic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Magnesium: &lt;/strong&gt;Magnesium supplements come in various forms, including magnesium oxide, citrate and chloride. These have different effects: For example, magnesium citrate is used as a laxative, so those with more sensitive stomachs might want to avoid it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Generally, the RDA for adults is about 300mg to 400mg (depending on age and sex). The &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Magnesium-HealthProfessional/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;UL for magnesium&lt;/a&gt; via supplements and medications specifically is 350mg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While there’s &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Magnesium-HealthProfessional/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;no risk&lt;/a&gt; linked to too much magnesium in food, high doses of magnesium might cause nausea, abdominal cramping and &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJM199104113241502" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;diarrhea&lt;/a&gt;. Very large doses can &lt;a href="https://medicine.tufts.edu/news-events/news/can-magnesium-supplements-improve-health" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;be fatal&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;People with kidney disease can’t excrete excess magnesium and should not take it unless it’s been discussed with their healthcare team, says Millstine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Probiotics: &lt;/strong&gt;There is &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Probiotics-Consumer/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;no official&lt;/a&gt; recommendation for the use of probiotics by generally healthy individuals. Blake recommends speaking with a registered dietitian nutritionist to determine which strain and dosage is right for you. Possible negative side effects include eczema and inflammatory bowel disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If you can tolerate probiotics, excessive use may not be toxic, but there could be other downstream effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Probiotics can limit your ability to get to your natural, healthy microbiome,” says Millstine, because high-dose supplements can hinder the diversity of your gut bacteria. “I caution people to really consider if they need probiotics.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creatine: &lt;/strong&gt;Creatine supplements can cause some bloating and GI symptoms, as well as nausea, says Millstine. She recommends sticking to 4 to 5 grams per day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Research suggests that higher doses of creatine &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/exercise-and-fitness/what-is-creatine-potential-benefits-and-risks-of-this-popular-supplement" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;do not offer&lt;/a&gt; any advantages. Because there’s &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/10999421/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;mixed evidence&lt;/a&gt; of a negative effect on kidneys, people with &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31859895/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;kidney disease&lt;/a&gt; are especially advised to speak with their healthcare provider before trying it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collagen peptides: &lt;/strong&gt;Collagen peptides are smaller pieces of collagen and can come in powder and pill form. Collagen peptides can possibly help with &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/15/6/1332" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;joint &lt;/a&gt;and &lt;a href="https://linkinghub.elsevier.com/retrieve/pii/S2405844023021680" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;skin health&lt;/a&gt;, though much more research is needed to support these claims, says Carnavali.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Though there’s no standardized dose, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31096622/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;some research&lt;/a&gt; shows between 2.5 grams to 15 grams daily is safe. However, research not sponsored by supplement manufacturers is scarce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Millstine’s primary caution is not to use collagen peptides in place of a more complete protein powder, because they lack essential amino acids needed for overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:12:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxNU2toeFNBZk1PN3NmSFU2OGtlSW9feGR2NXZmUUV3UGowY1IydE9jZjQ5QkJQRlJicmtkYjJhTWlieDg0VmdVUXljTlo5LXk5Uk1NaDhGd0tYZW9MbjlCaFg0RnFhck9zbGxFRmZRbGE2UnZZbU9Jd295VjQ4UUlaQzJrUWVLUlBXQTJNcUtESWpZU0hvMzQ2aUt0VQ</guid></item><item><title>州长韦斯·摩尔（ Wes Moore ）法案将允许马里兰州绕过联邦疫苗接种时间表-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/dc-md-va/2026/01/08/maryland-vaccine-bill-wes-moore/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="UCBJFNNCTRFBLFMENM4UI2COEM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The administration of Maryland Gov. Wes Moore (D) on Thursday proposed legislation that would empower the state’s health secretary to issue vaccine recommendations and bypass federal guidance — making it the latest state to reject the Trump administration’s &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/05/childhood-vaccine-immunization-schedule-overhaul/"&gt;overhaul of the childhood vaccine schedule&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxOSlFwVE9wZDN1NmZmV2NLX3Z4WkE5ZmZRRDk3R0lzcWJzWkJUSVJXaHZRdHFDeEdHaDA4ZEVVVEtnWGZ5LUREWUNTTFRNVVN6RTV4WlpVTFdhckV4b29kQnk1cDlDWkN2azRHeG1yeDlnZEtPdWtoUW1ibHVMQ0psbFE4LVNUbk1Ebm1n</guid></item><item><title>随着疾病预防控制中心改变疫苗建议，西澳流感病例呈上升趋势，其中许多是儿童-西雅图时报</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/wa-flu-season-is-in-full-swing-especially-among-young-and-old/</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxQanFGbVpEUTFmU3FDVUtFeHZqcmJmeUgxQUQ1UjJvMDdsekZHRWlreFpXYlNnN1p5OTRzbndWMkxlYTdqQXI3MXZDZXhpMTVqRDNwdTRHenF1YUFZdzVHVE9oRm1RM1F0czBuSlRTaHJ0YThDdUlRYWk2TFlDMEhYaEUxNXpfaE8yYm1CNFZvclJFc01PRFVYSnhRS0pWOWFyMzhoRVhJU0JoRWZLV2lPWg?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;WA flu cases are on the rise, many of them kids, as CDC changes vaccine recommendations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi-AFBVV95cUxNWTVWaXc2N1B1aUtJbUxCdm9XaG53OEtqbWo3ODR6VWlYLXFQYWhybHRYN3QxQXVHZFFudmtudnh1RXg2ajBtaE5xWHM4QUdHWHJ3eFVGSElIN3RZeHZ5UlN6SGhfSHl3OVg4UEd4T2x3aUt3bjRTd3JRMmRGLUJZdWFpR1VnRlpGTWRvSzNkQ2lhNGNNT2FVZ3lFVDRlWHQ4Ym8wVW92TDA2My1IY1diWjAyQTNfUTJGZms0OHNQc0xqR05FR1p4NVY4RU9rTmU3OGJXdW9wczBZZ3RibjVkX2pGbkwwZ2ZCYVducHZvdTNfVjBxd0pZZw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Respiratory illness positivity rates, including flu, spike across the Inland Northwest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;KREM&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixgFBVV95cUxNLURjRzNmUlF1cTg3ZFYxY3E4YWU3a2J0dVNldUhFR0ctbXFmbWwyTFltQ2R0WGpwMmhINF9Qdk9GNXducWNDU25oLXkzUEF6aURvcHEzLW5vTmlEVmstY2hqbDhMcFhzenFZVm1WVnpjLXlCODRPVG9MckRXQzJiNy10VUZDZC04MjFnYjBRZWI4aTBrRHh3dndsaW4xNVhnSFpPVW0zYWhIbDNDVjAzRkNTNVJseHBxdVdGbmhKSGZWWWpabVE?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Rising cases in Kitsap signals potential for severe flu season ahead&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Kitsap Sun&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxQanFGbVpEUTFmU3FDVUtFeHZqcmJmeUgxQUQ1UjJvMDdsekZHRWlreFpXYlNnN1p5OTRzbndWMkxlYTdqQXI3MXZDZXhpMTVqRDNwdTRHenF1YUFZdzVHVE9oRm1RM1F0czBuSlRTaHJ0YThDdUlRYWk2TFlDMEhYaEUxNXpfaE8yYm1CNFZvclJFc01PRFVYSnhRS0pWOWFyMzhoRVhJU0JoRWZLV2lPWg</guid></item><item><title>明尼苏达州支持全面的儿科疫苗接种计划，打破CDC - Star Tribune</title><link>https://www.startribune.com/minnesota-backs-full-pediatric-vaccine-schedule-breaking-with-cdc/601560183</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt; &lt;p data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;Vercel Security Checkpoint&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="hide-mobile" data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;|&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;iad1::1767908057-IHUZ2SGwsshf8dQPLBYPeRZpT8YFEHbO&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Star Tribune</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:34:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPbUdZYjlQZjJfZVRxQmpOcTgwUUlJMUc2ZEVpYXNMdjhiRjZnN0Z5Q05JYzNiN0FEUUNQYkpQOXlVNEJvLXBpMmNZQTYyLTYxQmdFRjBLMWMwNWI2RmtoOWxaQ3NnVlBVSWxSeVYyOFZRTlF1dmdXR1FJVHpZbnFlWGVfSkVIR3FNdk10X2pZRkc2VzJMbHRVZ1VzcHh0a3hHR1BWRnpn</guid></item><item><title>许多脱离GLP-1药物的人在2年内体重恢复，评论建议- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/08/health/weight-loss-drugs-regain-scli-intl-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5f98wz001y26qmfecph2fk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Many people who stop using &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/18/health/glp1-muscle-loss-strength-training-wellness"&gt;weight loss drugs&lt;/a&gt; will return to their previous weight within two years, a new review of existing research has found.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5f9faw0000356py33edjst@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            This rate of weight regain is significantly faster than that seen in those who have lost weight by changing other lifestyle factors, such as diet and exercise, rather than relying on GLP-1 medications, researchers from the University of Oxford report in a paper published Wednesday in &lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/392/bmj-2025-085304" target="_blank"&gt;The BMJ journal&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fkzou000c356pocpgenws@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            GLP-1, which stands for glucagon-like peptide-1, is a hormone naturally made by the body that helps signal to the brain and the gut that it’s full and doesn’t need to eat any more.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fpgkz000i356pt8amw7e4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Weight loss drugs mimic the action of this hormone by increasing the secretion of insulin to lower blood sugar.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fpkxg000k356p69fnqkq1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            They also slow the movement of food through the digestive tract, which helps people feel full more quickly and for longer, and they work in the brain to reduce appetite.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fokxr000f356pgyrh4tl1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            GLP-1 medications, which include Ozempic, Wegovy, Mounjaro and Zepbound, have proven to be highly effective for weight loss.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fpmuj000n356pro7yu60n@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            However, University of Oxford researchers analyzed the results of 37 studies involving more than 9,300 adults.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5k1n7w0001356pcmpsngwq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            They found that “weight regain after stopping drugs was faster than after ending behavioural weight loss programmes such as diet and exercise support by approximately 0.3 kg (0.7 pounds) per month,” they said in a statement.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fyky00014356p0gm7dopb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This isn’t a failing of the medicines — it reflects the nature of obesity as a chronic, relapsing condition,” said study lead author Sam West, a postdoctoral researcher at the Nuffield Department of Primary Care Health Sciences, University of Oxford, in the statement.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fz9vk0017356p45rpngmw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It sounds a cautionary note for short-term use without a more comprehensive approach to weight management.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5gc8ku001k356p3piyag86@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Adam Collins, associate professor of nutrition at the University of Surrey in England, who was not involved in the study, called the paper “timely and important.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5gea6m001q356pnn8cjwzx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Collins underlined that weight regain is a common issue in all weight loss interventions, but the paper shows that this problem is amplified with GLP-1 medications.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5jadq8000a356phy0vv64b@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Collins also offered some possible explanations as to why this is the case.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5ge7ma001n356p9zuttxyr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Artificially providing GLP-1 levels several times higher than normal over a long period may cause you to produce less of your own natural GLP-1, and may also make you less sensitive to its effects,” he said in a statement shared with CNN by the Science Media Centre.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5ghh5e001v356pkhpefric@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Collins added that this isn’t a problem when taking these drugs, but taking away this source of GLP-1 then makes overeating “far more likely.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5ghhz5001x356pw8cc62ry@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Like any addict, going cold turkey is a real challenge. This is further exacerbated if the individual in question has relied solely on GLP-1 to do the heavy lifting during weight loss,” he said, rather than making behavioral changes.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fxsq20011356pq0qkx2xj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Marie Spreckley, obesity researcher and public health nutritionist at the University of Cambridge in England, who was not involved in the study, cautioned that the paper’s long-term conclusions rely on modeled projections, rather than observed data, as the follow-up period for stopping treatment with newer medicines is limited to about 12 months.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5g8lgu001d356p6sx73bi1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “As a result, longer-term statements, including full weight regain within two years, rely on extrapolation beyond the available data,” she said in a statement shared with CNN by the Science Media Centre, meaning that comparisons with behavioral changes should “be interpreted as suggestive rather than definitive.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5ldt43000h356pidoptxdt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “In real-world terms, the findings reinforce that obesity management typically requires long-term planning. If people stop medication, many are likely to need ongoing nutritional and behavioural support, and health services should anticipate that cardiometabolic benefits may lessen as weight is regained,” Spreckley said, adding that this highlights “the need for further research into effective, scalable strategies for long-term weight maintenance alongside pharmacotherapy.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5gf8ep001t356p4pqp2x8f@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            GLP-1 medications have become widely used in recent years, and &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/18/health/glp1-muscle-loss-strength-training-wellness"&gt;more than 15 million Americans&lt;/a&gt; are now losing weight with the drugs.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5gkizp0023356pbk9lk4wu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            And &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/01/20/health/glp-1-medications-benefits-risks-beyond-weight-loss-diabetes"&gt;a study&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;published in January 2025&lt;/a&gt; suggested that popular GLP-1 medications approved for weight loss, diabetes and heart disease may have untapped potential to reduce the risks of substance abuse disorders, psychosis, infections and some kinds of cancer and dementia.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5glten0026356pnsrwfkat@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            However, it is important to remember that using&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;the drugs to suppress appetite&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;doesn’t just contribute to&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;fat loss but also to reduced muscle mass.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5gpd4l002k356pzrhw1isl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38937282/" target="_blank"&gt;Studies have indicated&lt;/a&gt; that anywhere between 15% to 60% of the weight people lose is lean muscle mass, meaning that those who are using the drugs are advised to engage in a weekly exercise routine that includes strength training to stave off too much muscle loss.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5gr8ef002m356pvitgyoe9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It is particularly important for those 65 or older, who are already at risk of age-related loss of muscle mass, strength and function.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:33:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNRnMtZ1VCWlpLOExIR0luRjZSNnplR0s1dkhWVVhMeGtna0ExTElLU25HSnNkZ0lEamlPNFlWc2dZNk9SeUhyTzcyaWR0ZEZWdzJQSVd5WVk5bmN5M09mQ1NaYTlhOF9FRnJJaTJoaTRFRTJUVHFFWVFVSTZrcmZ3dWY0a093bnE2</guid></item><item><title>排名第一的茶叶营养师推荐更好的大脑功能-真正简单</title><link>https://www.realsimple.com/number-1-tea-dietitians-suggest-for-better-brain-function-11877337</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="realsimple-sc-page_1-0" class="comp realsimple-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--summary realsimple-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dietitians point to green tea’s unique combination of EGCG catechins, L-theanine, and low-dose caffeine as the reason it best supports brain health over time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Compared to black tea or coffee, green tea delivers brain benefits with less caffeine, making it easier to drink throughout the day without jitters.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The biggest brain health perks come from consistency—aim for one to three cups of green tea a day, brewed gently and enjoyed regularly, rather than occasional drinking.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When it comes to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/brain-boosting-habits-11762153" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;brain health&lt;/a&gt;, most people first consider their &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/what-is-good-sleep-hygiene-8730838" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;sleep quality&lt;/a&gt;, meal choices, or lifestyle to keep them sharp. However, what you sip on throughout the day, whether it's &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/how-much-water-to-drink-day" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;water&lt;/a&gt;, soda, or tea, can actually impact how well your brain functions, too. A few popular teas contain compounds that support your memory and attention, but there is one that consistently comes up in dietitian recommendations.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; We asked nutrition experts to identify the top tea for brain health, and explain in simple terms why it works so well. Their answer probably won’t surprise you: Green tea is widely available and backed by a significant amount of research. Here’s why they recommend drinking it regularly to keep your mind sharp, plus some clever ways to fit more green tea into your daily routine. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--meetourexpert mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--meetourexpert mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-meetourexpert callout--bordered" data-text="Meet the Expert" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://totaste.com/about/lindsey-schoenfeld/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Lindsey Schoenfeld&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;, &lt;/strong&gt;RDN, a registered dietitian nutritionist, professional chef, and co-founder of To Taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vandanasheth.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Vandana Sheth&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;, &lt;/strong&gt;RDN, CDCES, FAND, a registered dietitian nutritionist with a focus on plant-based nutrition and diabetes care&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-best-tea-to-drink-for-brain-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; The Best Tea to Drink for Brain Health &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/teas-for-brain-health-11779146" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;several teas offer cognitive benefits&lt;/a&gt;, dietitians say one consistently shows up in research. “My top pick is green tea (including &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/recipe-collections-favorites/popular-ingredients/what-is-matcha" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;matcha&lt;/a&gt;),” says Vandana Sheth, RDN, a registered dietitian nutritionist and former national media spokesperson at The Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics. “Although many teas are good for brain health, green tea stands out because of its unique combination of bioactive compounds.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Lindsey Schoenfeld, RDN, &lt;em&gt;a &lt;/em&gt;registered dietitian nutritionist, professional chef, and co-founder of To Taste, agrees. “Green tea takes the gold! When it comes to brain health, green tea tends to get the most attention,” she says. In fact, several long-term studies link regularly drinking green tea with a lower risk of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/age-brain-declines-study-11706222" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;cognitive decline&lt;/a&gt;, and “its natural compounds may help protect brain cells as we age,” Schoenfeld adds.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; So, what makes &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/green-tea-vs-black-tea-11822262" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;green tea different from black tea&lt;/a&gt;? “Green tea provides catechins, especially EGCG, along with L-theanine and a small amount of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/shopping-storing/beverages/how-much-caffeine-per-day" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;caffeine&lt;/a&gt;,” Sheth explains. “This combination supports calm focus, mental clarity, and long-term brain health in a way most other teas do not.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; L-theanine specifically promotes a feeling of relaxation without drowsiness, and helps smooth caffeine's effects, Sheth points out.&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Additionally, the green tea-specific catechins provide both &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/fruits-with-more-antioxidants-than-green-tea-11739371" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;antioxidant&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/anti-inflammatory-drinks-8707182" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;anti-inflammatory benefits&lt;/a&gt; that support brain cells. “This combination makes green tea especially good for sustained attention and cognitive health across the lifespan,” she says.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Drinking black tea can help your brain health, too. But unlike black tea, green tea leaves are minimally oxidized, which helps preserve higher levels of catechins like EGCG. That means you’re getting more of the compounds linked to long-term neuroprotection.&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Green tea also has &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/matcha-vs-coffee-8550568" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;less caffeine&lt;/a&gt; (about 25–40 milligrams per cup, compared to 40–70 milligrams), which means it’s easier to drink more of it midday than black tea or coffee. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-to-drink-more-green-tea"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How to Drink More Green Tea &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Green tea supports your brain health without overstimulation, but how much do you need to drink to reap the drink's benefits? Here’s what the experts say about fitting this brain-boosting tea into your daily life.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Brew the Perfect Cup &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; First, you need to make sure you’re &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/how-to-steep-tea-7153209" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;brewing your green tea correctly&lt;/a&gt; to maximize it's brain-boosting potential. “Sounds funny, but it's so important!”  Schoenfeld shares&lt;em&gt;. “&lt;/em&gt;Use hot, simmering water, not boiling water, and steep for 2–3 minutes max. This will keep it slightly sweet and not bitter.” (For reference, that means brewing your tea in water that’s around 160–180°F.)&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Overheating or over-steeping green tea can degrade its most brain-supportive compounds. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Focus on Consistency &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; But consistency matters more than chasing the perfect cup of tea, according to Schoenfeld. “Find a green tea you like, and it becomes much easier to turn tea into an &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/daily-habits-that-will-make-you-happier-11862093" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;everyday habit&lt;/a&gt; rather than another wellness chore. The best tea for brain health is really the one you enjoy drinking.” Most research suggests aiming for one to three cups a day to deliver cognitive benefits over time. You’ll notice more impact when the tea is consumed regularly, rather than sporadically.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Replace Other Drinks &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; There are so many opportunities to drink (or eat) green tea instead of something else. “Swap your second cup of coffee for brewed &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/matcha-vs-green-tea-11687240" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;green tea or matcha&lt;/a&gt;; add matcha to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/recipe-collections-favorites/healthy-meals/heathy-breakfast-smoothies" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;smoothies&lt;/a&gt; or oatmeal for a gentle mental boost; sip green tea after meals as part of a calming routine; or keep tea bags or single-serve matcha at work for consistency,” says Sheth.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Keep a Pitcher in the Fridge &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Make iced green tea to have on hand in a pinch—and mix it up with lemon, citrus peel, or fresh mint. “Keep it lightly sweetened, or free of artificial ingredients and added sugar,” says Schoenfeld, who suggests swapping one sweetened drink a day for green tea or a simple matcha latte. “Finally, find a friend who enjoys tea, as &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/microhabits-for-better-health-11759744" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;wellness habits&lt;/a&gt; tend to be easier to establish when you are connected with friends,” she concludes.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Real Simple</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:23:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxQam9fZ0ZzU2JBa0lpaW12X2xoOThJVmw0NnBWVHp2c1dDN1MyY0VGVGp4UGE0SFVhRktoQUIxYlBTT3RkcW5YMUxVSjk1MVpNQUJmLWNjLXlzeTRBUUJ4azI0NFpaX0llQzZfemV3U2psLWFlQkZXZXR5WVdNWVdYSkk5MlJrX1g3V0dSQWdIdTRXOTdXTHZQUA</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，前GLP-1使用者在约18个月后体重减轻-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2026/01/08/ozempic-wegovy-weight-regain-glp1/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TALWJZN7MVCWVB42PAZTOJELIY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;People who stop taking GLP-1 drugs such as Ozempic and Wegovy for weight loss are projected to regain their shed pounds within about 1½ years, a review of existing research has found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3C6KPGWDSZETLNXE7AKMF52ZZM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The paper also found that former users of a wider&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;list&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;of&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;weight-loss drugs regain weight four times more quickly than those who had used behavioral techniques like dieting or exercise. For sustained health benefits after coming off the drugs, scientists say, it is necessary to make lasting changes to your diet and exercise regime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:33:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQVDBHS1ZSM004Qnpyc3ZGU3RVMHNjVnk2NUx6SEEwT1FuRkJpLVpLU2E1ZnR5azB1UlNyQ0VyRjlEVDJNTmlVY0NhYm8wX2xkQXhrb3hmR0Vqb0gzeWZBaEFPZ29la2JSbDRwdnlCaGxELTNxaDJMSEpvZGRZVHkxWV9BNTlTNkJOS2RHREJn</guid></item><item><title>孟菲斯国际机场确诊麻疹病例，卫生部门表示- WREG.com</title><link>https://wreg.com/news/local/measles-case-confirmed-at-memphis-international-airport/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>WREG.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:54:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQaFdOQU1teDlfWjRzZVFHdTJ3MjN6QktzbTZuVGFPeWpZNkItMDgwcHhTZHRHckFqX1doOHBrYjlLME5odXpkdEdFVlNEVHRrSTBBcUNLSFZPYTBzbjcwUTRxWE1JUHVDX3EyWmZiSHNId3RWT1JnU290TFkxMUpYMEdfZFYyNmVKcWNlWtIBkgFBVV95cUxPektmRDBubm83MElTWVl0cUpVT3RzRmFkS3lkS3N5VjhKSVY1Q0FZMF9jcmlpSjllLTRJWjU4LXVZdVltRjRRVVREb3lHWlg0akRmWmpXc2pldTVxSE1NTWtTZVNFT3VDTWVwVFBnbmdUZ3A3SHh1d0VwUHhVS1BmaGd1US1hNmppc0FaSUF3WDg2UQ</guid></item><item><title>卫生官员警告孟菲斯机场可能有麻疹暴露- FOX13孟菲斯</title><link>https://www.fox13memphis.com/news/health-officials-warn-of-potential-measles-exposure-at-memphis-airport/article_92b468bf-2b48-4d33-b064-a721e1a36c9e.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;MEMPHIS, Tenn. - Shelby County health officials warned Thursday the potential of a measles exposure at Memphis International Airport after a traveler arrived with symptoms of the contagious disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a news release, the county's Health Department (SCHD) said that person came from a different state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials they were working with state and federal partners to identify people who might have been exposed to the disease. "The measles virus spreads easily through the air when an infected person coughs or sneezes," the health department said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_top" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SCHD said people who were at the airport during the following times might have been exposed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;11 p.m. Dec. 30-2 a.m. Dec. 31, 2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Noon-6:30 p.m. Jan. 3, 2026&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;SCHD said there are no confirmed cases in Shelby County risk to the public is low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Shelby County Health Department issued the following advice for those who might have been exposed to the measles:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;The following usually begin &lt;strong&gt;7–14 days after exposure&lt;/strong&gt; but can take up to 21 days to appear:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fever&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cough&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Runny nose&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Red or watery eyes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;White spots inside the mouth&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;A red rash that usually starts on the face and spreads&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you have symptoms that could be measles, do NOT go to a doctor’s office, urgent care, or emergency room without calling ahead first.&lt;/strong&gt; Measles spreads very easily, and going in without notice could expose others.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you have symptoms:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Call your healthcare provider first&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Follow their instructions about where and how to get care safely&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Stay home and avoid contact with others&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;What to Do If You Were at the Airport&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Check whether you have had the measles (MMR) vaccine. If you are unsure, contact your healthcare provider.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Watch for symptoms for 21 days after your possible exposure&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you are not vaccinated and were at the airport during the exposure dates/times, contact the Shelby County Health Department at 901-222-9243.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;People who have not been vaccinated against measles should receive at least one dose of the MMR vaccine, unless your healthcare provider has told you shouldn’t receive it. Those who work in healthcare settings should receive two doses, 28 days apart. If you are unsure whether or not you have received the MMR vaccine, contact your healthcare provider to determine your vaccination status and if you should be vaccinated against measles.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Currently, there are no measles cases in Shelby County and the threat to the public is considered to be low."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="inline-asset inline-html  subscriber-hide tnt-inline-asset tnt-inline-relcontent tnt-inline-html tnt-inline-relation-child tnt-inline-presentation-default tnt-inline-alignment-default tnt-inline-width-default"&gt;&lt;div class="html-content"&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Download the FOX13 Memphis app to receive alerts from breaking news in your neighborhood.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.fox13memphis.com/mobile-apps/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLICK HERE TO DOWNLOAD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trending stories:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="clearfix"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>FOX13 Memphis</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:12:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6gFBVV95cUxQaGJ0ZjE1b3JQaEphYUlnYWVBOXEtYnlVQWFCd2ZFSm1LZmZZN3pnZ0RtMnlIXzhKRXJTNFdoV2luOVN2N2Viam1ubS1pdWRqWDFTVDBmT3BXM1hTUkk3UTV3UTRxZjVHU3JqTkUzMTRYODEtWG1EM2UzSUNIbEFLVlpCT0syNDZJQXVJQmVrZ3A4Y0tVSDdWOUJVYmVLaENYWUZFYlM0c2h5NFJ4dndyQ2NKQTZfdTdEMmk4V3ZDOG5lZEpIdThrX0VEU0hQMWwzYk5uNHlnREM2SUhXZmZQMFhBam9FMFlSVWc</guid></item><item><title>Claude L. Brozzo ， 98岁， Jasper - Dubois County Free Press, Inc.</title><link>https://duboiscountyfreepress.com/claude-l-brozzo-98-jasper/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content single-content"&gt;
	
&lt;p id="isPasted"&gt;Claude L. Brozzo passed away on January 3, 2026, at Brookside Village, Jasper.




&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="isPasted"&gt;He was born July 28, 1927 to Lawrence C. and Frandia Robbins Brozzo in Giles, Wisc.





&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="isPasted"&gt;After graduating from high school in 1945, he spent four years in the Tuberculosis Ward at Grandview Hospital in Ironwood, Mich. He was fighting the same disease that claimed the life of his mother in 1945. He vowed that if he survived, he would make his life’s work to help others with communicable diseases. After discharge from the hospital, he graduated from an X-Ray technician school. He was employed with the Indiana State Board of Health for 42 years. First as a traveling X-Ray Technician, then as a Public Health Investigator of communicable diseases, and finally retiring as an epidemiologist.





&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On July 28, 1951, his 24th birthday, he married Cecilia La Claw. They met while she was a nurse’s aide at Grandview Hospital. She preceded him in death on October 3, 2017.





&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Claude is survived by his daughters, Claudette Brozzo (William Long) of Paoli and Cathy (Rick) Stenftenagel of Jasper; grandsons, Aaron (Amy) Stenftenagel of Jasper, Derick (Keisha) Stenftenagel of Jasper, Jesse Long (Kara Davis) of Louisville, Kirk ( Audra) Stenftenagel of Jasper; great-grandchildren, Ayden, Alec, Asher, Kip and the only great-granddaughter, Spencer; and brother, Jack Brozzo of Ironwood, Mich.





&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Claude is preceded in death by his wife; parents; brothers; Raymond and Joseph Brozzo; sisters, Betty MisKovich and Shirley Brozzo; and grandsons, James Matthew and Dylan.





&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A celebration of life will be announced at a later date. For condolences, visit &lt;a href="http://mcadamsmortuary.com"&gt;mcadamsmortuary.com&lt;/a&gt;


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Dubois County Free Press, Inc.</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:08:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibEFVX3lxTE5ydWxiUmdxZHhlUGNEWkJtYjVZRXpIV0FMQWwxVEZOT1FCajI4aXZ3SWxLYThmYUV1dTJZZEdra0ZpRGdGWDFyOEwtd28xZXNvVzEzRGY5b21uNS1GblZtMGc0bnNMSDE4T1pIUg</guid></item><item><title>Parkview在呼吸道疾病增加的情况下实施访客限制-减少15</title><link>https://www.wane.com/top-stories/parkview-implements-visitor-restrictions-amid-rise-in-respiratory-illnesses/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>WANE 15</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:51:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxNOERGODFuY29RS3ZtMUl4alhwNzJRdEdTVklBaEhZUTV4TS1mMHI5dnpCVjh5ZDFGYzdsMFNTaFpEU3BLd2V0ZVZWYmJwSjRtS0dCajA3bW1NT2FLWkkxbThMNGNKRGQxbTRycmxfeXBkVjl3emNydHAyQzlyeE00WTJaTE5zeGhBZF9PenVOQ2JueEFZT25IdmpmeTYxMkxxQjBVdmdTdldKMlo2RXfSAbMBQVVfeXFMT1JoR1UxeTBUQThxdTh6NFIyV2tGM2V2c1R1VHZDQURiemN1R1ZXRkJMLVlUcTRMUU9EVWQ2YkZsMjZNeEExSmozbGotNDlMLVNfSGpqV0JyTURtMzFhZEhsZ0tZT3ZkLUpqS0hIM2VTLWdoLTZKLUhZQ3pobFF4djhQTzZNLXFwYnQybzZrYU13Zlk5SVJRc2w3Ymh1QjlrS1RBUFQ0elgxRHR4V0lsbVlHcnc</guid></item><item><title>最好的健康零食，以增加您的蛋白质摄入量，抑制渴望和更多- TODAY.com</title><link>https://www.today.com/shop/best-healthy-snacks-today-show-rcna252605</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e1627b" class="body-graf"&gt;We're just a week into the new year, which means &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/shop/january-winter-essentials-2026-rcna252341" target="_blank"&gt;sticking to our resolutions&lt;/a&gt; is top of mind. Whether you're hoping to &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/shop/best-sources-of-protein-rcna224857" target="_blank"&gt;up your protein intake&lt;/a&gt; or just cut back on the junk food, adding some &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/diet-fitness/healthy-snacks-rcna177830" target="_blank"&gt;healthy snacks&lt;/a&gt; to your pantry will help you stay on track to meet your 2026 goals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4b4283" class="body-graf"&gt;From protein bars to &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/food/groceries/best-beef-jerky-rcna81398" target="_blank"&gt;jerky&lt;/a&gt;, our team has personally taste-tested just about all of the viral snacks generating buzz in the health sphere right now. Dozens of bags, bars and bites later, Shop TODAY editorial director Adrianna Brach emptied the office snack drawer in Studio 1A to share the full list. Because of their straightforward ingredients and high nutritional value, a lot of these favorites meet the criteria for popular diets, from keto and paleo to &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/shop/best-gluten-free-food-gifts-rcna204870" target="_blank"&gt;gluten-free&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/shop/best-vegan-gifts-rcna226974" target="_blank"&gt;vegan&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a2564d" class="body-graf"&gt;To get the thumbs up on the picks seen on TODAY, we tapped two TODAY contributors: nutrition and health expert &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/food/joy-bauer" target="_blank"&gt;Joy Bauer&lt;/a&gt; and fitness expert &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/author/stephanie-mansour-tdpn101363" target="_blank"&gt;Stephanie Mansour&lt;/a&gt;. So, rest assured that you can fuel up on these snacks guilt-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f7643f" class="body-graf"&gt;Feeling hungry? Keep scrolling to browse the &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/shop/eating-well-snack-awards-2025-rcna221740" target="_blank"&gt;best healthy snacks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="/shop/best-healthy-snacks-today-show-rcna252605?cid=bc_npd_td_qr_genshoptoday#anchor-972872" id="anchor-972872" class="scrollLink"&gt;&lt;h2 class="body-heading"&gt;Healthy snacks seen on TODAY&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-a39ce6"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd67384" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-day-out-cookie-dough-protein-balls-(8-pack)" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Sneak some extra protein in with these surprisingly nutritious cookie dough balls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grams of protein:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;12&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Grams of sugar:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;11&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Flavors:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3febb8" class="body-graf"&gt;It’s cookie dough, but make it way more nutritious! These protein balls are a favorite for those with a sweet tooth. Each pack contains four protein balls, 12 grams of protein and 11 grams of sugar. These are smart to have on hand for busy days when you want to curb cravings and tide yourself over ‘til your next meal. These are the standout pick for Mansour from our list. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9c3d6e" class="body-graf"&gt;“I personally can’t wait to get my hands on the Day Out Protein Balls — YUM!” Mansour exclaims.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-9db0dc"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd58429" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-promix-nutrition-protein-puff-bars-(12-pack)" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;This protein bar combines high protein content with a coconut-forward flavor that shines through. The brand recommends eating it before or after the gym. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grams of protein:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt; 14 or more&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Grams of sugar:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;5 or less&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Flavors:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;16&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e61750" class="body-graf"&gt;If you're hoping to get more protein in the coming year, we've got you. These bars were a standout among Shop TODAY editors who tried them out against a bunch of other &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/shop/ranked-best-protein-bars-rcna231453" target="_blank"&gt;popular protein bars&lt;/a&gt; because they're nothing like the chalky, heavy options you might be accustomed to. They're more like rice crispy treats, with at least 14 grams of protein and under five grams of sugar per serving in each of the 16 flavors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-06fccc"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd67395" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-the-only-bean-crunchy-dry-roasted-edamame-beans-(variety-pack)" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Try sea salt, sriracha and buffalo-flavored dry roasted edamame beans in this variety pack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grams of protein:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;13 or more&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Grams of fiber:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;5&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Flavors:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-60ca9a" class="body-graf"&gt;Have you ever tried dry roasted edamame beans? These are so much better for you than chips or other salty junk food, but they have that crunch and flavor to satisfy your cravings. As a bonus, they're plant-based and have less than 3 grams of net carbs, which makes it a smart choice for anyone on a vegan, dairy-free or keto diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5a6074" class="body-graf"&gt;"These are good! Some varieties are higher in sodium/salt than others, which may be a concern to viewers with high blood pressure," notes Bauer. "But overall, great protein-rich pick and I eat ‘em."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-f97326"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd62879" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-siete-grain-free-sea-salt-tortilla-chips" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;These vegan, gluten-free and paleo tortilla chips are made with avocado oil and are free of dairy, soy and grains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Servings per container:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;5&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-860d99"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd67413" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-siete-grain-free-nacho-tortilla-chips" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;These dairy-free and grain-free chips are made with cassava flour and avocado oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Servings per container:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;1 or 5&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-37d440" class="body-graf"&gt;If you want a more traditional chip without the guilt, Bauer says she stocks her house with Siete's options. They're made with cassava flour, so they're grain-free, and they use avocado oil instead of vegetable oil. Because of that, they have less carbs than your average tortilla chips, and they're also paleo and vegan. Instead of queso or dip, try pairing these with a fresh salsa to get extra vegetables or fruit in and keep it light.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-679502"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd67407" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-solely-organic-mango-whole-fruit-gummies-(5-bags)" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;There's just one ingredient in these gummies: mango!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flavors:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;9&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-e64c13"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd57368" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-solely-organic-mango-fruit-jerky-(12-strips)" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;One ingredient makes up these leather strips: mango. Truly — that's it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flavors:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;12&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5a2b9c" class="body-graf"&gt;Another snack straight from Bauer's own pantry, these treats from the aptly-named brand Solely have just one ingredient: mango. They come in a whole fruit gummy variety and there's also a faux jerky that's kind of like a fruit leather. They're naturally sweet, so no sugar is added. This is a great alternative to fruit gummies or candy for kids and the chewy texture is really satisfying to gnaw on. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-32448b"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd67414" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-vermont-smoke-&amp;amp;-cure-oven-roasted-seasoned-turkey-sticks-(24-count)" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;These single-ounce meat sticks are the perfect snack for a quick hit of protein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grams of protein:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;9&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-debdaf"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd67415" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-chomps-original-turkey-sticks" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;This smoky, mildly spicy meat stick is made with 100% antibiotic-free turkey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grams of protein:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;12&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-2ce041" class="body-graf"&gt;These &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/shop/jack-links-mrbeast-meat-snacks-launch-rcna231411" target="_blank"&gt;meat snacks&lt;/a&gt; will hit the spot — and pack a ton of flavor and protein in while they're at it! Bauer recommends these turkey meat stick varieties from Vermont Smoke &amp;amp; Cure and Chomps, which are both low carb and have zero grams of sugar. Right now, Chomps is having a site-wide sale, so you can stock up on favorites for the new year at a discount.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="/shop/best-healthy-snacks-today-show-rcna252605?cid=bc_npd_td_qr_genshoptoday#anchor-fc064c" id="anchor-fc064c" class="scrollLink"&gt;&lt;h2 class="body-heading"&gt;More editor-approved healthy snacks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-f3353a"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd67445" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-wegmans-rosemary-turkey-stick" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;This turkey meat stick has an herbal rosemary flavor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grams of protein:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;9&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7d543a" class="body-graf"&gt;A bonus pick from Bauer? Wegman's jerky snack with 9 grams of protein per stick. "I reallyyy like Wegmans' brand of rosemary turkey sticks," Bauer vouches. "I love and keep in the house."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-457823"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd67473" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-lorissa's-kitchen-herb-a-licious-turkey-stick" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;These meat sticks are seasoned with a blend of herbs and spices, and slow-smoked for an amazing taste.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Features:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;8 grams of protein and 0 grams of sugar per stick&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Includes:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;No preservatives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-339176" class="body-graf"&gt;Commerce editor and producer, &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/author/julie-ricevuto-tdpn196438" target="_blank"&gt;Julie Ricevuto&lt;/a&gt;, is also a fan of Lorissa's Kitchen jerky, saying it's one of the more delicious options she's tried in addition to the 8 grams of protein and 0 grams of sugar. "I love eating the turkey stick after a workout to sneak in some extra protein!" she says. The brand also boasts other flavors, like &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Lorissas-Kitchen-Premium-Grass-Fed-Finished/dp/B0D1CX3FKQ?tag=besthealthysnacksrcna252605-20" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-commerce-encoding="true" data-seller-id="tdrg118312"&gt;beef jerky&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?xs=1&amp;amp;id=96128X1550925&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lorissaskitchen.com%2Fproducts%2Fchicka-boom-chicken-stick&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.today.com%2Fshop%2Fbesthealthysnacksrcna252605" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-commerce-encoding="true" data-seller-id="null"&gt;chicken jerky&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-f749b5"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd58443" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-chobani-low-fat-greek-yogurt-drink" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;This shake lets you sip your way to your daily protein intake. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grams of protein:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;20 &lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Size:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;10 oz&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="styles_prosConsContainer__HAJ1f" data-testid="listicle-product__pros-cons-container" data-activity-map="product-article-body-chobani-low-fat-greek-yogurt-drink"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_prosConsChild__YRDyW"&gt;&lt;p class="styles_prosConsLabel__0oo4d"&gt;What we like&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="styles_prosConsItems__XysO1"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Doesn't taste chalky&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Easy to grab-and-go&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_prosConsChild__YRDyW"&gt;&lt;p class="styles_prosConsLabel__0oo4d"&gt;Something to note&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="styles_prosConsItems__XysO1"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some disliked the consistency&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4d4cf3" class="body-graf"&gt;“I first tried this drink at an event a few months ago and was pleasantly surprised at how delicious it was,” says associate editor &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/author/kamari-stewart-tdpn162401" target="_blank"&gt;Kamari Stewart&lt;/a&gt;. “I’ve tried several high-protein yogurts over the years and they all taste either too thick, too chalky or both. This drink goes down smoothly and I would’ve never suspected it was high protein if I didn’t see the label.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-84f72a"&gt;&lt;div id="tdpd224450" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-gimme-snacks-organic-roasted-seaweed" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;These snacks have just 30 calories per pack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-34b64c" class="body-graf"&gt;If you pull open the snack drawer in Shop TODAY’s office at 30 Rock, you’ll find a jaw-dropping quantity of these seaweed snacks. Writer &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/author/emma-stessman-tdpn196906" target="_blank"&gt;Emma Stessman&lt;/a&gt; likes snacking on them for a salty, vegan-friendly option.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-17d8fb"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd58438" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-barebells-protein-bars" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;With a witty fitness-inspired name, this bar is easy to pack into any gym back for a pre- or post-workout fuel session. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grams of protein:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;20&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Grams of sugar:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;1&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Quantity:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;4, 12 bars per box&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Flavors:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;Chocolate dough, birthday cake, wild cherry, key lime pie, salty peanut, more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="styles_prosConsContainer__HAJ1f" data-testid="listicle-product__pros-cons-container" data-activity-map="product-article-body-barebells-protein-bars"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_prosConsChild__YRDyW"&gt;&lt;p class="styles_prosConsLabel__0oo4d"&gt;What we like&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="styles_prosConsItems__XysO1"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Creamy, slightly sweet&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Soft texture&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_prosConsChild__YRDyW"&gt;&lt;p class="styles_prosConsLabel__0oo4d"&gt;Something to note&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="styles_prosConsItems__XysO1"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prone to melting in the heat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-64b69e" class="body-graf"&gt;For a post-run snack, writer &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/author/jannely-espinal-tdpn233977" target="_blank"&gt;Jannely Espinal&lt;/a&gt; likes these protein bars from Barebells. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3d7759" class="body-graf"&gt;"The texture is soft and not chewy, it’s slightly sweet and doesn’t leave any crumbs behind,” Espinal reports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-81aecf"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd57458" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-lesser-evil-organic-pink-himalayan-salt-popcorn-8-oz" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Fiber and protein work together in popcorn to keep you fuller for longer periods of time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Size:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;8 oz. bag&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Flavors:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;White cheddar, watermelon, pink lemonade, himalayan gold, himalayan sweetness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-cb97ad" class="body-graf"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/diet-fitness/is-popcorn-healthy-rcna173013" target="_blank"&gt;Popcorn&lt;/a&gt; is a healthy, whole-grain snack that satisfies. This option from Lesser Evil is often spotted on the desks of editors around our office and contains just three ingredients: organic, non-GMO popcorn, coconut oil and Himalayan salt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-25e617"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd58440" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-good-gummies-protein-gummies" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;For a protein snack that's reminiscent of your favorite childhood sweet, turn to these nutritious gummies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grams of protein:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;15&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Quantity:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;12 pouches per package; about 15 gummies per package&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Flavors:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;Watermelon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="styles_prosConsContainer__HAJ1f" data-testid="listicle-product__pros-cons-container" data-activity-map="product-article-body-good-gummies-protein-gummies"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_prosConsChild__YRDyW"&gt;&lt;p class="styles_prosConsLabel__0oo4d"&gt;What we like&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="styles_prosConsItems__XysO1"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Travel-friendly packaging&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_prosConsChild__YRDyW"&gt;&lt;p class="styles_prosConsLabel__0oo4d"&gt;Something to note&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="styles_prosConsItems__XysO1"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Only one flavor&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Not widely available&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c7ad91" class="body-graf"&gt;“My husband recently got into Good Gummies and I usually steal a few when he breaks them out,” says senior partnerships editor &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/author/francesca-cocchi-zabloudil-tdpn234143" target="_blank"&gt;Francesca Cocchi Zabloudil.&lt;/a&gt; “We both love sour gummy candy, so it’s nice to have an option with some nutrition benefits.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="anchor-8f5cb1"&gt;&lt;div id="rcpd57446" class="" data-testid="article-product-unit"&gt;&lt;div class="listicleProduct dn-print  product__grid-container--small" data-activity-map="listicle-product-article-body-ballerina-farm-farmer-protein-powder" data-testid="product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product__grid-row"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_accordion__Z2nEy styles_accordion__Coahi undefined styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion" data-title="What to know"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="styles_accordion__content__09JIS styles_accordion__content__9AV2h styles_closed__PAn2s" data-testid="accordion__content" role="listbox" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Nicknamed "liquid gold" by the brand, this protein powder utilizes cow colostrum as one of its main ingredients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="productSpecs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grams of protein:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;24 per serving&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Size:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;36.7 oz&lt;/span&gt; | &lt;strong&gt;Flavors:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;Strawberry crème, vanilla bean, creamy chocolate, maple cinnamon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="styles_prosConsContainer__HAJ1f" data-testid="listicle-product__pros-cons-container" data-activity-map="product-article-body-ballerina-farm-farmer-protein-powder"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_prosConsChild__YRDyW"&gt;&lt;p class="styles_prosConsLabel__0oo4d"&gt;What we like&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="styles_prosConsItems__XysO1"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Delicious flavors&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Easy to incorporate into diet&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_prosConsChild__YRDyW"&gt;&lt;p class="styles_prosConsLabel__0oo4d"&gt;Something to note&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="styles_prosConsItems__XysO1"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Not widely available in-store&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-935012" class="body-graf"&gt;“Sometimes after dinner or in the afternoon — if I need something that’s going to keep me full until my next meal — I just mix some protein powder with water or almond milk,” says Stessman. “I’ve been loving the Ballerina Farm powders because the flavors taste like real chocolate and vanilla, instead of artificial versions... You don’t even need a blender bottle, I just do it right in a mug and it’s super smooth.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="/shop/best-healthy-snacks-today-show-rcna252605?cid=bc_npd_td_qr_genshoptoday#anchor-1f2acc" id="anchor-1f2acc" class="scrollLink"&gt;&lt;h2 class="body-heading"&gt;Meet the experts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bfe855" class="body-graf"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our team features a range of qualified experts and contributors in our broadcast segments to reveal the latest in trends, remarkable sale events and all things shopping across a variety of categories. Products were independently chosen by members of the Shop TODAY team along with Adrianna Brach&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;, Joy Bauer and Stephanie Mansour.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="anchor-d406ee" class="break-above body-ul body-list-el"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.today.com/author/adrianna-brach-tdpn170651" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adrianna Brach&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is the editorial director at Shop TODAY, with over a decade of experience as an editor covering beauty, fashion and shopping.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul id="anchor-f1f395" class="break-above body-ul body-list-el"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.today.com/author/joy-bauer-tdpn2501" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy Bauer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, M.S., R.D.N., C.D.N., is one of the nation’s leading health authorities. She is the longtime nutrition and healthy lifestyle contributor for TODAY.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.today.com/author/stephanie-mansour-tdpn101363" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stephanie Mansour&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is TODAY’s fitness contributor, a certified personal trainer and a yoga and Pilates instructor. She also leads workout routines and challenges in the &lt;a href="http://Stephanie%20Mansour%20is%20our%20TODAY%20Fitness%20contributor,%20a%20certified%20personal%20trainer%20and%20a%20yoga%20and%20Pilates%20instructor.%20She%20also%20leads%20workout%20routines%20and%20challenges%20in%20our%20new%20Start%20TODAY%20app." target="_blank"&gt;Start TODAY app&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul id="anchor-1d545e" class="break-above body-ul body-list-el"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.today.com/shop/shop-today-editorial-team-rcna187940" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shop TODAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a team of shopping editors and writers who spend hours every day finding the best new products, tried-and-true favorites and more finds available on Amazon that are worth shopping, according to our high standards.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;a href="/shop/best-healthy-snacks-today-show-rcna252605?cid=bc_npd_td_qr_genshoptoday#anchor-ebc16d" id="anchor-ebc16d" class="scrollLink"&gt;&lt;h2 class="body-heading"&gt;How do you add Shop TODAY as a Preferred Source on Google?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-01bf72" class="body-graf"&gt;Google’s new &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/life/how-to-set-up-google-preferred-sources-rcna227229" target="_blank"&gt;Preferred Sources&lt;/a&gt; feature allows users to manually select their favorite publishers and news outlets for a more customizable experience tailored directly to the reader. Once you’ve opted to receive our content, you’ll begin seeing more of our recent and trending articles displayed within your Top Stories news feed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9fdc0f" class="body-graf"&gt;The easiest way to add us as a preferred source is to &lt;a href="https://www.google.com/preferences/source?q=today.com" target="_blank"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; and type in “&lt;a href="http://today.com/" target="_blank"&gt;TODAY.com&lt;/a&gt;.” Once the box is checked and you’ve refreshed the page, Shop TODAY content will start appearing in your feed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="/shop/best-healthy-snacks-today-show-rcna252605?cid=bc_npd_td_qr_genshoptoday#anchor-083ed1" id="anchor-083ed1" class="scrollLink"&gt;&lt;h2 class="body-heading"&gt;How we chose&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c97bc3" class="body-graf"&gt;The Shop TODAY editors and writers search the internet to find the best products out there. We interview expert sources, comb through customer reviews and even use our own personal experiences to make shopping easier for our readers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-088639" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;As an editorial team, we independently create content and determine coverage based on research, reporting and what we think TODAY.com readers would like to read about. The goal of our content is to provide a service and inform readers who are on the hunt for the latest products to help make their life better. Items are sold by retailer, not TODAY. Pricing and availability are accurate as of publish time. &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/shop/everything-you-need-know-about-shop-today-t161374" target="_blank"&gt;Learn more about Shop TODAY&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TODAY.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:17:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTFBjYjRZR3lsSE5yaFRCZmlwUnZJMlZmM0g3cHNmMjVrQVBFTTgyVklCb3lsNlBTbHFGZENCXzNhM2Ixd0FJdVFuZ2toUGFyR3I0QW1hN3hMR3YxY1BDMktJWEpUUFBhMUZMV091SzNYRTdYX2ExXzZz</guid></item><item><title>为什么你应该放下手机，做白日梦--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2026/01/08/health-benefits-of-daydreaming/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QWTVMIX7YNG6HO3LH2QXNA4QQY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;At any bus stop or while waiting in line, most people will have their heads down looking at their phones. Recent research found that many people &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/interactive/2025/phone-brain-health/" target="_blank"&gt;check their phones at least 50 times per day&lt;/a&gt;. But studies suggest that if you resist that urge and let your mind wander instead, there could be some serious benefits. Giving yourself time to daydream seems to be good for your well-being, for problem-solving and maybe even for your relationships.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:02:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxPQWlLX0xiUXQ5cjhBM3JrNWNyWXNMVWhWUjd1aHhvV1ZYNGRQVVdDMU5CS1RCTzczMk1CWldTbzFHeEFPdFR3ZFA3d1FJOUxfRHBDdThTbUxRN3hPQ0VEenJkTG4xd2Jzb3dfTFdGS2JtRVhab0ZXamExTllWcGNXSUdJVjdVSnJTS1E</guid></item><item><title>年轻人的结肠癌发病率正在飙升。以下是原因，以及如何降低风险-《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/colon-cancer-rates-are-spiking-among-young-people-heres-why-and-how-to-lower-your-risk/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-content" class="article-content entry-content"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;DALLAS — Dr. Bethany Malone has treated a lot of colorectal cancer patients. The youngest, not counting those with genetic conditions, was 19 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colorectal cancer used to be considered a cancer of older age. Not anymore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients in their teens and early 20s still aren’t the norm, exactly, but are becoming more common.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I have not gone a year in practice without taking a colon cancer out of someone in their 20s,” Malone said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malone is a colon and rectal surgeon and the associate program director for the general surgery residency at Texas Health Harris Methodist Hospital Fort Worth. Her experience in North Texas reflects a worldwide trend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colorectal cancer — which includes cancer of the colon and of the rectum — is considered early onset when diagnosed in people under the age of 50. While the majority of diagnoses are still among people aged 65 or older, early onset rates have been increasing worldwide, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7994182/" target="_blank" class="content-link external"&gt;particularly in high-income countries&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a 2023 report, the American Cancer Society wrote that the trends of decreasing incidence in older people and increasing incidence in younger people are “&lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/content/dam/cancer-org/research/cancer-facts-and-statistics/colorectal-cancer-facts-and-figures/colorectal-cancer-facts-and-figures-2023.pdf" target="_blank" class="content-link external"&gt;rapidly shifting the patient population younger&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2020, “Black Panther” actor Chadwick Boseman died from colon cancer at age 43. More recently, former Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders choreographer Criscilla Anderson &lt;a href="https://www.dallasnews.com/arts-entertainment/pop-culture/2025/12/04/former-cowboys-cheerleaders-choreographer-criscilla-anderson-dies-after-cancer-battle/" target="_self" rel="noopener" class="content-link external"&gt;died of colon cancer&lt;/a&gt; at age 45.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what medical experts say about the rising rates of colorectal cancer in younger people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Why are colorectal cancer rates rising among younger people?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical experts say there isn’t one reason why colorectal cancer rates are rising in the below-50 age groups. But there are some contributing factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, it’s not because of genetics. Dr. Radhika Kainthla, a medical oncologist at Parkland Memorial Hospital in Dallas, said that about 20% of early onset colorectal cancer patients have a genetic tie-in. That means 80% do not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There’s a misconception a lot of times that if it’s a young person being diagnosed with cancer, it must be genetic,” Kainthla said. “But that’s not actually what we’re seeing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All three experts who spoke with The Dallas Morning News pointed instead to a combination of environmental factors and lifestyle factors, such as diets high in red meat, diets packed with ultra-processed foods and lack of regular exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malone at Texas Health Fort Worth said fiber intake especially tends to be low for Americans, which can increase the risk for colorectal cancer. Fiber does a lot of work in the gut, Malone said, including feeding a healthy microbiome and helping to flush carcinogens out of the body before they’re absorbed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malone noted that the “lifestyle” factors are not always easily controllable. The U.S. food system has shifted significantly toward ultra-processed foods, which tend to be low in necessary nutrients such as fiber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="userMessagingInset" class="user-messaging animate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are also environmental factors at play, said Dr. Emina Huang, a professor of surgery and a colorectal surgeon at UT Southwestern Medical Center. For instance, living near a superfund site — which are hazardous waste sites — has been shown to increase the risk of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;How can I reduce my risk of colorectal cancer?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reducing the risk of colorectal cancer, the three experts said, comes down to a lot of the standard advice that medical professionals recommend for general health, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three experts said that folks should focus on getting regular exercise, avoiding smoking, moderating alcohol intake and eating a diet that’s low in red meat but rich in fruits, vegetables and fiber.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obesity is also a risk factor for colorectal cancer, the experts said, although Malone cautioned against focusing on weight loss alone. Restrictive diets may also end up being low in fiber, which is harmful rather than helpful for colorectal cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And, of course, patients should pay attention to their bodies and seek medical care if they notice abdominal pain or changes in their bowel movements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;When should I start getting screened for colorectal cancer?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because of the rising rates of colorectal cancer among younger people, the U.S. Preventive Services Task Force advises regular screenings beginning at age 45. The gold standard of screening is a colonoscopy, but stool tests and scans can also be used for screening.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;p&gt;The age 45 recommendation, however, is for patients who have a standard risk for colorectal cancer. Some people may be at higher risk due to personal or family history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with a first-degree relative — a sibling, parent or child — diagnosed with colorectal cancer or colorectal polyps may be advised to begin screenings at a younger age. In general, medical professionals advise beginning screening when a patient is 10 years younger than their relative was at the age of diagnosis. For instance, if your father was diagnosed with colorectal cancer at age 48, you should begin screenings at age 38.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients with such a family history should start screenings no later than 40.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Similarly, patients who have personal histories of Crohn’s disease or ulcerative colitis are at higher risk of colorectal cancer, too, and should also begin screenings at an earlier age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kainthla, at Parkland, also noted that there are other types of screenings besides colonoscopies, such as blood tests and stool tests, that may be a useful option for some patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What are the warning signs of colorectal cancer?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical experts are quick to point out that, for most young people, abdominal or gastrointestinal symptoms are unlikely to indicate colorectal cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, some symptoms should serve as red flags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common early symptoms are stomach pain that doesn’t go away, changes in bowel movements with no improvement or blood in the stool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, these symptoms can indicate hemorrhoids or other relatively benign conditions. However, if a patient is treated for a benign condition but symptoms do not improve, that’s a sign that something more may be going on.&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;p id="userMessagingIn-story"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        
&lt;p&gt;©2025 The Dallas Morning News. Visit &lt;a href="https://dallasnews.com" target="_blank"&gt;dallasnews.com&lt;/a&gt;. Distributed by &lt;a href="https://tribunecontentagency.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Tribune Content Agency, LLC.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;
  
  
  
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0gFBVV95cUxQN3ZlQm5PU01PZ1IycDdsTktZRkZKWmlTWXVSaUV3Q09CcmJQWWZlS0pyRVhrZmlLVkhFU0ttb0hnU0FoMVRsWWcyUzg0WEZLTHpYdXVicUFpMFBWaWRibGhKUTNjWkFDZzRyUVpmYjRzOWc0TE9leFRJU2RFV2U1WmZLN0UyRVVPbWhkX0hHMnk4eFJlVjJlTkRub2Z3LTJyR2V3OE9FaVAtcGF4cE5qODd4clJRNlA4dFp1VDU0cGt6NWt0Vkdhb0FXc1JqN25yZUE</guid></item><item><title>广泛使用的农药与帕金森病风险增加一倍以上有关- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-widely-pesticide-linked-parkinson.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:54:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQcHZSYzZrQ3NiZUZpVm5HWm9zX0JEZEtqYTltZS1rWm03TEpQY3pTZWhmM3Jzc3F0eTByOGpfUlcxaUttM1lQd0hoUk5BY2V6SkpFaXJ0RmR5U1UyQXdnb25OOXkwak1KdWdPMWxKMlJTWE5weVRDQktBY1ZoM282N0NiQQ</guid></item><item><title>巴西人的寿命已超过110岁，科学家们想知道原因- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2026/01/260107225527.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why do a small number of people live beyond 110 years while most never reach 100? Scientists have pursued this question for decades, but clear answers remain scarce. According to Dr. Zatz and her co-authors, part of the problem lies in the narrow focus of existing research. Many large genomic databases are dominated by relatively homogeneous populations, leaving major gaps when it comes to admixed groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This gap is especially limiting in longevity research, where admixed supercentenarians may harbor unique protective variants invisible in more genetically homogeneous populations," explains Mateus Vidigal de Castro, first author of the Viewpoint and researcher at the Human Genome and Stem Cell Research Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brazil's Unmatched Genetic Diversity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brazil's population history sets it apart from nearly every other country. Portuguese colonization beginning in 1500, the forced migration of roughly 4 million enslaved Africans, and later waves of European and Japanese immigration produced what the authors describe as the richest genetic diversity in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early genomic research involving more than 1000 Brazilians over age 60 uncovered around 2 million previously unknown genetic variants. Among older Brazilians alone, researchers identified more than 2,000 mobile element insertions and over 140 HLA alleles missing from global genomic databases. A later study expanded this picture further, reporting more than 8 million undescribed genetic variants across the Brazilian population, including over 36,000 thought to be potentially harmful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;An Extraordinary Group of the World's Oldest People&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research team has built a rare and valuable cohort. Their ongoing longitudinal study includes more than 160 centenarians, among them 20 validated supercentenarians, drawn from diverse regions of Brazil with wide-ranging social, cultural, and environmental backgrounds. Participants included Sister Inah, who was recognized as the world's oldest living person until her death on 30 April 2025 at age 116.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cohort also included the two oldest men in the world. One passed away last November at age 112, while the other is currently 113 years old.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Longevity Beyond Medical Access&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What makes this group especially informative is not just their age. When researchers first contacted them, several Brazilian supercentenarians were still mentally sharp and able to manage basic daily tasks on their own. Many spent most of their lives in underserved areas with little access to modern healthcare. This allows scientists to study biological resilience that developed largely without medical intervention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Families That Defy the Odds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One family in the study provides a striking example of inherited longevity. A 110-year-old woman in the cohort has nieces aged 100, 104, and 106, making it one of the longest-lived families ever documented in Brazil. The oldest niece, now 106, was still competing as a swimming champion at age 100.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This pattern matches previous findings showing that siblings of centenarians are between 5 and 17 times more likely to reach extreme old age themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can families like this help separate genetic influences from environmental or epigenetic ones? "Investigating such rare familial clusters offers a rare window into the polygenic inheritance of resilience and may help disentangle the genetic and epigenetic contributions to extreme longevity," notes Dr. de Castro.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Makes Supercentenarians Biologically Different&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Viewpoint also brings together recent research on the biological traits that distinguish supercentenarians from the general population. Their immune cells maintain protein recycling systems that function at levels similar to much younger people. Cellular cleanup processes remain active and efficient, helping prevent the buildup of damaged proteins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Single-cell analyses show an unusual expansion of cytotoxic CD4+ T cells that behave more like CD8+ immune cells. This immune profile is rarely seen in younger individuals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A recent multi-omics study of a 116-year-old American-Spanish supercentenarian identified rare or exclusive variants in immune-related genes such as HLA-DQB1, HLA-DRB5, and IL7R, along with variants tied to protein maintenance and genome stability. The authors argue that immune aging in supercentenarians should be seen not as overall decline, but as a form of adaptation that preserves function. Interestingly differently from the American-Spanish super old woman, who followed a mediterranean diet , the Brazilian supercentenarians refer no food restriction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COVID-19 Survival at Extreme Old Age&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the most compelling demonstrations of resilience occurred during the COVID-19 pandemic. Three Brazilian supercentenarians in the cohort survived infection in 2020 before vaccines were available. Laboratory analyses showed strong IgG responses and neutralizing antibodies against SARS-CoV-2, along with immune-related proteins and metabolites linked to early host defense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How people over 110 mounted effective immune responses to a brand-new virus that proved deadly to millions of younger individuals remains a key question. The authors suggest that preserved immune function, intact protein maintenance systems, and overall physiological stability together make supercentenarians powerful models for studying resilience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brazil's Global Standing in Extreme Longevity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brazil's role in longevity research is further underscored by global statistics. Three of the ten longest-lived validated male supercentenarians are Brazilian, including the oldest living man, born on 5 October 1912. This is especially notable because extreme longevity is far less common in men, who typically face higher cardiovascular risk, more chronic illness, and different hormonal and immune aging patterns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having access to both male and female supercentenarians who lived most of their lives without modern medicine offers a rare chance to study resilience in a group that is usually underrepresented.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Among women, Brazilian supercentenarians rank prominently as well. The number of Brazilian women in the top 15 longest-lived worldwide exceeds that of more populous and wealthier countries, including the United States.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next Steps in Longevity Research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research effort goes beyond sequencing DNA. Scientists are also developing cellular models from selected participants to conduct functional experiments and multi-omics analyses. Rather than simply confirming results from less diverse populations, the goal is to identify protective genetic variants and biological mechanisms that may be specific to Brazil's population. These findings could inform precision medicine approaches that are globally relevant while better reflecting human diversity. In collaboration with Prof. Ana Maria Caetano de Faria from the Universidade Federal de Minas Gerais, the team will also study the immune profiles of this cohort in greater depth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The authors urge international longevity and genomics groups to expand recruitment to include ancestrally diverse and admixed populations such as Brazil, or to provide financial support for genomic, immunological, and long-term studies that improve scientific understanding while promoting equity in global health research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resilience as the Core Insight&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supercentenarians offer more than examples of unusually long lives. They demonstrate resistance, adaptability, and resilience, traits that may be just as important as lifespan itself. Rather than simply enduring old age, these individuals appear to actively counter many biological features of aging, offering clues that could improve quality of life as populations grow older.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"International longevity and genomics consortia should expand recruitment to include ancestrally diverse and admixed populations, such as Brazil's, or provide financial support for genomic, immunological, and longitudinal studies that deepen scientific insight and enhance equity in global health research," states Dr. Mayana Zatz, corresponding author and Professor at the University of São Paulo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Viewpoint brings together current knowledge on supercentenarian biology with insights from an exceptional Brazilian cohort. By integrating genomic, immune, and clinical findings, the authors present a strong case for expanding longevity research beyond traditionally studied populations and reveal patterns that remain invisible in genetically homogeneous groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:47:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE9yM3pTZldxX3M2Yk1uaFRVSmhwbjhiTnRxLWhEX2JGZjdpT293LVVSekw2MEppMUdrekVFWmxEZmkxXzVORWE1ek5zRVh6WjluNU0xa1hqNXZSRzQtT2lOdEVCdHotV3pudEhzaHNZNA</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法，如果您正在服用GLP-1药物， 7种最佳蛋白质- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/best-proteins-to-eat-when-taking-a-glp-11879983</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dietitians recommend proteins like chicken, salmon, dairy, eggs and lentils while on a GLP-1 medication.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spread protein across meals to preserve muscle, support energy and help meet your daily needs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pair protein with fiber and healthy fats for balanced, sustainable weight-loss meals.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re taking a GLP-1 medication, you may notice you’re getting full faster, eating less or even forgetting to eat altogether. While this appetite shift can support weight loss, it also makes choosing the right foods—especially protein—more important than ever.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; GLP-1 medications work by slowing stomach emptying, reducing appetite, increasing feelings of fullness, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/lifestyle-tweaks-healthy-blood-sugar-levels-11792895" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;improving blood sugar control&lt;/a&gt; and helping regulate hunger signals in the brain, explains &lt;a href="http://drlisayoung.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Lisa Young, Ph.D., RDN&lt;/a&gt;. Together, these effects lead to reduced food intake and weight loss.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Because GLP-1 medications can significantly decrease how much you eat, some people may unintentionally fall short on calories and key nutrients. Over time, this can contribute to low energy intake, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/warning-signs-of-a-nutrient-deficiency-11742311" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nutrient deficiencies&lt;/a&gt;, fatigue, weakness and muscle loss.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Protein plays a particularly important role in healthy weight loss and overall health. “Protein helps preserve lean muscle mass during weight loss, supports metabolism and strength, increases satiety and plays a key role in immune function, healing and hormone production,” says Young. Without enough protein, you may lose muscle in addition to fat, which can negatively impact your metabolism, physical function and long-term health.&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Eating balanced, high-protein meals throughout the day can help you meet your protein needs and support healthy, sustainable weight loss, adds &lt;a href="https://joinvineyard.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Summer Kessel, RD, CSOWM, LDN&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; But which proteins are best while taking a GLP-1 medication? We spoke with five dietitians to share their top high-protein foods to focus on while using a GLP-1.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-chicken-breast"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 1. Chicken Breast &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Chicken breast is a high-quality, lean protein, meaning it’s rich in protein while relatively low in fat. With 32 grams of protein per 3.5-ounce serving, chicken breast tops the list as one of the best protein choices if you’re taking a GLP-1 medication.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; It’s a quick, versatile option that can help you meet your protein needs, preserve muscle mass and support feelings of fullness.&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; High-protein foods also have a greater thermic effect of food, meaning your body uses more energy to digest and metabolize them. This increased energy expenditure may further support weight loss.&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And don’t worry, you don’t have to stick to plain chicken and broccoli to see results. Keep meals interesting with flavorful options like &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/275280/sheet-pan-lemon-pepper-chicken/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Lemon Pepper Chicken&lt;/a&gt; or a comforting &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/chicken-florentine-casserole-8691410" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Chicken Florentine Casserole&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-salmon"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 2. Salmon &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A 3.5-ounce serving of salmon provides about 22 grams of protein along with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-protein-for-heart-health-11803980" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;heart-healthy omega-3 fats&lt;/a&gt;, making it a smart choice for supporting both weight loss and overall health while taking a GLP-1 medication.&lt;span data-cite="5" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Research supports its cardiovascular benefits, too. One large cohort study found a 27% lower 10-year risk of heart disease among people with high seafood intake—defined as two or more servings of fish per week—compared with those who consumed little seafood. Most of this protective effect was attributed to the omega-3 fatty acids found in fish.&lt;span data-cite="6" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Aim for two to three servings of salmon or other fatty fish per week. For an easy, GLP-1-friendly lunch, try &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/salmon-salad-11782563" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;salmon salad&lt;/a&gt; with a pita or on toast, mixed with cooked grains or enjoyed as a dip with whole-grain crackers and vegetables.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3-cottage-cheese"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 3. Cottage Cheese &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Cottage cheese is everywhere—and for good reason. “Cottage cheese is a high-protein, low-calorie food,” explains &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/katielounsberry" class="pseudoStyle" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Katie Lounsberry, RD, LDN&lt;/a&gt;. One cup of low-fat cottage cheese delivers about 24 grams of protein for just 180 calories.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Some varieties of cottage cheese are &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/get-vitamin-d-without-supplement-11806255" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;fortified with vitamin D&lt;/a&gt;, an essential nutrient for hormone production, energy and bone health.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This is especially important for people taking GLP-1 medications: one recent study examining nutrient intake among GLP-1 users found that 99% did not meet the recommended daily allowance for vitamin D.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fortunately, most cottage cheese varieties contain small amounts of fat, which can help improve vitamin D absorption, notes &lt;a href="https://www.tjpnutrition.com/about-tjp" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Kara Craddock, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;. You can also pair it with another fat source, such as nuts or seeds, to further support absorption. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; New to cottage cheese? Start with a simple &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/cottage-cheese-berry-bowl-8710522" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Cottage Cheese Berry Bowl&lt;/a&gt; or use it as a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/savory-cottage-cheese-bowl-8763804" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;high-protein topping&lt;/a&gt; for salads.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-4-strained-greek-style-yogurt"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 4. Strained (Greek-Style) Yogurt &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Greek yogurt is high-protein, easy to digest and gentle on the stomach, especially helpful for people experiencing nausea or early fullness,” explains &lt;a href="https://www.integrativeweightandwellness.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Erin Jowett, M.S., RD, LDN&lt;/a&gt;. A 1-cup serving of plain, low-fat strained (Greek-style) yogurt boasts an impressive 25 grams of protein for only 164 calories.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Beyond protein, strained (Greek-style) yogurt is also an &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7944074/foods-with-more-calcium-than-milk/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;excellent source of calcium&lt;/a&gt;, supplying roughly 270 milligrams per 1-cup serving.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Adequate calcium intake is especially important during weight loss, as weight loss increases bone turnover and may reduce bone mineral density over time.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Strained (Greek-style) yogurt is easy to enjoy on its own as a meal or snack, or to incorporate into recipes, suggests Lounsberry. Use it to add protein to dressings, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/250924/avocado-yogurt-dip/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;dips&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/8028179/tzatziki/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;sauces&lt;/a&gt; or smoothies and help meet your daily nutrition goals.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-5-eggs"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 5. Eggs &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Nearly all the experts we spoke with recommended eggs—and rightfully so. “Eggs are a compact, complete protein source with excellent bioavailability,” explains Jowett. Two large eggs provide about 12 grams of high-quality protein.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “They’re easy to prepare, well-tolerated and provide essential nutrients like choline, which supports liver and metabolic health during weight loss,” she adds. Choline plays a key role in liver function by helping prevent fat accumulation and supporting transport and removal of excess cholesterol and triglycerides.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Enjoy your eggs sunny-side up or incorporate them into delicious recipes like &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/sun-dried-tomato-feta-egg-bites-8404224" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Sun-Dried Tomato Egg Bites&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/breakfast-stuffed-peppers-8654722" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Breakfast Stuffed Peppers&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-6-lentils"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 6. Lentils &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For a plant-based protein option, lentils are an excellent choice. One cup of cooked lentils provides about 18 grams of protein and an impressive 16 grams of fiber.&lt;span data-cite="14" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Fiber supports the body’s natural production of glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1), which helps promote fullness and satiety.&lt;span data-cite="15" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Beyond appetite control, fiber is also excellent for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-your-gut-health-impacts-your-body-8695122" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;gut and metabolic health&lt;/a&gt;, says Craddock. Fiber supports gut health by helping move food through the digestive tract and feeding beneficial gut bacteria. It also slows digestion and enhances insulin sensitivity, contributing to better blood sugar control.&lt;span data-cite="15" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Lentils are easy to prepare and versatile in the kitchen. Try incorporating them into recipes like &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/250341/lentil-burgers/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Lentil Burgers&lt;/a&gt; and a cozy &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/277566/instant-pot-lentil-soup/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Instant Pot Lentil Soup&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-7-protein-shakes-or-ready-to-drink-protein-beverages"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 7. Protein Shakes or Ready-to-Drink Protein Beverages &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_63-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Liquids can be easier to tolerate, especially when appetite is low or you don’t feel your best. While protein shakes shouldn’t be your primary source of protein, they can be a practical tool to help meet daily protein needs. Protein shakes may be especially helpful during the early weeks of GLP-1 use or shortly after an injection, notes Jowett. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_64-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; That said, supplementation isn’t necessary for everyone. Kessel emphasizes that people taking GLP-1 medications do not need protein supplements if they’re able to meet their needs through food alone. “Protein shakes serve a purpose for convenience, taste preference, schedule constraints or if you’re unable to eat enough protein from solid food sources.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_67-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When choosing a ready-to-drink protein beverage, look for options that provide 20 to 30 grams of protein per serving. If finishing a full shake at once feels uncomfortable, try splitting it into two smaller servings to improve tolerance.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_68-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-tips-when-taking-a-glp-1-medication"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_69-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Tips When Taking a GLP-1 Medication &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_70-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See a Registered Dietitian.&lt;/strong&gt; Knowing what foods to prioritize and how to prevent under-fueling or nutrient deficiencies while taking a GLP-1 medication can be challenging. Lounsberry stresses the importance of working with a registered dietitian. “A dietitian can help you get proper nutrition while still losing weight, which will lead to better outcomes in the end,” she explains.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Layer Your Proteins.&lt;/strong&gt; Jowett recommends “protein layering,” or topping protein-rich foods like strained (Greek-style) yogurt with other protein sources, such as pumpkin seeds. This boosts protein and micronutrients without adding much volume, she explains.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eat Protein First.&lt;/strong&gt; Start meals with protein before you feel full to help ensure you meet your protein needs, especially when appetite is reduced.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t Rely on Hunger Cues. &lt;/strong&gt;While listening to hunger cues is typically helpful, GLP-1 medications can blunt appetite signals. “Having a bit of structure matters when appetite is muted,” says Jowett. Rather than waiting to feel hungry, aim to eat on a regular schedule to meet your nutritional needs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot-inline"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t Skimp on Carbohydrates.&lt;/strong&gt; Carbohydrates are essential for energy, performance and overall nutrition—even during weight loss. “Carbohydrates help your body use the protein you eat efficiently, have the energy to train harder in the gym and taste great,” says Kessel. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prioritize Strength Training. &lt;/strong&gt;Along with adequate protein, strength training is critical for preserving muscle mass, says Young. Aim for at least two strength training sessions per week.&lt;span data-cite="16" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_71-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_73-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_74-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_75-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Focusing on small, protein-rich meals and snacks throughout the day can help preserve muscle, support energy and make weight loss feel more sustainable. Because appetite is often reduced with GLP-1 medications, prioritizing protein early in meals and spreading intake across eating occasions can help you meet your needs without feeling overly full. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_76-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_77-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While protein plays a key role during GLP-1-assisted weight loss, it’s only one part of a well-rounded nutrition plan. Building simple meals that combine protein with fiber-rich carbohydrates and healthy fats helps nourish your body, support long-term health and promote sustainable weight loss.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE5jZG9tTkh2ampFV0FpYUNacjNHOU8yZ3cwbVNoM1JoY21XUFpkekdBNUpGRzVzWmlBR3FCRWJ0Zm5fYUg3bzdjclJBdHZUSGRrOG4xRWN0a0VKTl82MDlDNmFBZE4wNTFDeXprN1RfLUxmVHBDdHdrY2d3c3RvMGM</guid></item></channel></rss>