<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>两兄弟患有相同的遗传性疾病。他们的保险仅为其中一名患者提供改变生命的治疗-《独立报》</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/gene-therapy-brothers-insurance-chicago-b2820259.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 gryCYY sc-jbiisr-1" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 dFpFuY"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 dmMyEN"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 fXvmgM"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 juUDRT"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 cqPbFA"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 rAFIl sc-hez36s-16 jZSKtc"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 PdmgT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 hJPJVF"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 dDhojf"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 cUJDWn"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 jEZjIj"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 jEZjIj"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 jEZjIj"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 gunhQQ"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 dLkuvY sc-aja53j-7 eMEmGu"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 dHXFkr"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 jrwZqm"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 hUgQwJ sc-culv3z-0 eifaJK sc-a5wy94-0 hyKPon"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="big-letter"&gt;F&lt;/span&gt;or Alison Joseph, watching her 9-year-old son Noah splashing around in the swimming pool this summer for the first time was bittersweet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overjoyed that Noah had learned to swim, the mom was simultaneously reminded that her other son, 10-year-old Hunter, couldn’t join in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Hunter sees his younger brother and how well he's doing,” Alison told&lt;em&gt; The Independent&lt;/em&gt;. “And I think there is some sadness that he wants to be able to play outside longer, and do all the things that his brother is now finding so much easier.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Noah and Hunter both have Duchenne muscular dystrophy (DND), the most severe form of the genetic disorder. The disease causes muscle degeneration and weakness due to a mutation in the gene that produces dystrophin, a protein that protects muscle fibers from breaking down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disease, which mostly affects boys, gets worse over time. It makes it difficult to walk, run, jump, and play, with children often delayed in reaching milestones like crawling, walking and talking. The boys will likely use wheelchairs when they are teenagers, and life expectancy ranges between 30 and 40 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 bVpsol"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/04/15/16/IMG_2079.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/04/15/16/IMG_2079.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/04/15/16/IMG_2079.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Hunter, 10, (left) and brother Noah, 9, (right) were diagnosed with Duchenne muscular dystrophy in 2017. Noah received pioneering gene therapy in March this year, which has significantly helped his mobility, his parents said. But Hunter’s insurance claim for the same treatment was denied." class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-9989"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 bpFomM hgzWpY"&gt;Hunter, 10, (left) and brother Noah, 9, (right) were diagnosed with Duchenne muscular dystrophy in 2017. Noah received pioneering gene therapy in March this year, which has significantly helped his mobility, his parents said. But Hunter’s insurance claim for the same treatment was denied.&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 CXMrn"&gt; (Alison Joseph)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In March, Noah received &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/news/fda-ap-washington-patients-pfizer-b2362590.html"&gt;pioneering gene therapy &lt;/a&gt;to improve his mobility and quality of life through Alison’s &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/news/patients-health-insurance-employees-people-mercer-b2813474.html"&gt;health insurance plan&lt;/a&gt;. But when Hunter’s application was submitted in late May, authorization for exactly the same treatment was denied. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The reason on our denial letters is that it's not medically necessary,” the mom-of-three said from her home in Winnetka, just outside Chicago. “It was very blindsiding. They didn't ever deny my other son, it was approved the first go. So I was very taken aback.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alison, a physician, and her husband William, who works in finance, are now grappling with how to move forward following the decision from health insurance giant, Blue Cross Blue Shield. They say they have been put in an impossible and “heartbreaking” situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Independent &lt;/em&gt;contacted Blue Cross Blue Shield for comment, and asked why the treatment was only covered for Noah when both boys have the same disease. &lt;em&gt;The Independent &lt;/em&gt;also asked the company whether it would reconsider the denial in Hunter’s case and to respond to accusations that the decision was “unfair.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“To protect our member’s privacy, we do not publicly discuss individual cases,” a Blue Cross Blue Shield spokesperson said. “We do want our members to know that medical experts, including doctors, are involved in reviews to ensure the treatments and services our members receive are evidence-based and not duplicative. Decisions are guided by nationwide best practices for care, helping to identify what has proven successful for members in the past.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With every passing day, Hunter’s condition gets worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“His muscle is wasting away every day,” Alison, 44, said. “He's going to be in a wheelchair in the next few years and it just doesn't seem right that they are not going to allow him to get this treatment. They're wasting his time. And it’s just not fair.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brothers were diagnosed with DND in 2017 after tests showed Hunter had elevated liver enzymes, which is indicative of the condition. Three months later, when further tests showed the levels had not returned to normal, a specialist delivered the devastating diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DND is a genetic disorder and so Noah and 12-year-old brother Carter were tested following Hunter’s diagnosis. Carter did not have the disease, but Noah’s results came back positive. It was a triple blow for Alison, who not only had to process the fact that two of her children had the life-limiting illness but that she was a carrier of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The parents and their eldest son Carter have had to go through the pain of witnessing Hunter and Noah gradually decline over the years, as DND has no cure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in 2023, there was a glimmer of hope when the gene therapy, &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.parentprojectmd.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ELEVIDYS-FAQ-for-community.pdf"&gt;Elevidys&lt;/a&gt;, manufactured by Sarepta Therapeutics, received accelerated approval from the U.S. Food and Drug Administration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 ethnCd"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/04/15/22/IMG_4651.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/04/15/22/IMG_4651.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/04/15/22/IMG_4651.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Alison and husband William, pictured with their boys Hunter, Noah and Carter. Both of the younger boys were diagnosed with Duchenne muscular dystrophy in 2017, which has no cure" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-9990"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 bpFomM hgzWpY"&gt;Alison and husband William, pictured with their boys Hunter, Noah and Carter. Both of the younger boys were diagnosed with Duchenne muscular dystrophy in 2017, which has no cure&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 CXMrn"&gt; (Alison Joseph)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new treatment, which comes with a $3.2 million price tag, helps improve muscle function and motor skills. So far, over 900 patients have had the treatment, the company says, but given how novel the medicine is, critics say there is limited evidence that the benefits of the treatment outweigh the risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But doctors are cautiously optimistic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“All these newer gene transfer therapies are opening doors for these boys to possibly live longer and lead a good quality of life,” said Dr Aravindhan Veerapandiyan of Arkansas Children’s Hospital. “It’s changing the trajectory of the disease, changing the trajectory of their lives, improving the quality of life for the boys and their families.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elevidys is not without controversy. It was approved by the FDA in 2023 but limited to children between 4 and 5 years old, who are able to walk. In 2024, the treatment was expanded to include patients 4 years and older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Public Citizen, a nonprofit which acts an ethics watchdog for clinical trials, &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.citizen.org/article/failed-trials-yet-full-fda-approval-of-a-duchenne-muscular-dystrophy-gene-therapy/"&gt;said the FDA approval was “ill-advised”&lt;/a&gt; because it was “not supported by favorable FDA scientific reviews”. Nor did clinical trials demonstrate that children with the disease “maintained or regained gross motor abilities”, the group added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was heightened concern in July when the FDA told Sarepta to suspend distribution of the drug while the agency investigated the death of an 8-year-old boy. The FDA subsequently concluded the death was “unrelated to the gene therapy product itself” but the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.fda.gov/news-events/press-announcements/fda-recommends-removal-voluntary-hold-elevidys-ambulatory-patients"&gt;agency has still recommended the company pause&lt;/a&gt; distribution of the drug in patients who cannot walk. However, this doesn’t apply to Noah or Hunter, who can both still walk and play with their older brother, Carter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Alison and William, Elevidys was worth trying. “We had very serious conversations with our doctors, but we also know the natural progression of the disease,” Alison said. “So we were willing to take that risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Noah has had “very obvious and noticeable improvements” since his treatment in March at &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.archildrens.org/blog/revolutionary-gene-therapies"&gt;Arkansas Children’s Hospital&lt;/a&gt; in Little Rock, his parents said. Elevidys was administered as a one-time infusion.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“End of day fatigue and leg pain was something that he complained of frequently, and he has not complained of it once since getting gene therapy,” Alison said. “He learned how to swim this summer. His overall endurance is so much better.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hunter, meanwhile, continues to suffer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“So many people now will say,&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;Oh my gosh, Noah's doing so well… We can't believe he's swimming, he's this, he's that,” Alison said.&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“&lt;/em&gt;And, I'm like, Oh my gosh, please don't let Hunter hear… because I know that he's thinking that he's not able to do those things. And it's just heartbreaking.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before Noah’s treatment was given the green light by the insurance company, both boys underwent their routine, annual cardiac MRIs to take a closer look at their hearts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 bLBZUf"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/04/15/11/IMG_5130.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/04/15/11/IMG_5130.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/04/15/11/IMG_5130.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Noah has had “very obvious and noticeable improvements” since his treatment in March at Arkansas Children’s Hospital in Little Rock, his parents said. Noah (left) with his brothers, Hunter (right) and Carter (center)" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-9991"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 bpFomM hgzWpY"&gt;Noah has had “very obvious and noticeable improvements” since his treatment in March at Arkansas Children’s Hospital in Little Rock, his parents said. Noah (left) with his brothers, Hunter (right) and Carter (center)&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 CXMrn"&gt; (Alison Joseph)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A cardiologist determined that the risk with the treatment was greater for Hunter than it was for Noah, whose MRI showed normal cardiac function for a child. Therefore, the family decided that Noah should have the treatment first. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We collectively made a decision that the safest thing to do is give it to his brother,” Alison explained. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The insurance company gave the green light for Noah’s treatment on November 1, 2024, and he received it a few months later in March 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After Noah’s treatment went well, doctors, including cardiologists, then gave their approval in April for Hunter to have the same treatment. BCBS denied coverage for the treatment in June.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We were so excited that they gave us the green light. It was like, Oh my gosh, let's go. Let's do it,” Alison recalled. “We told Hunter, ‘It’s your turn,’ never expecting the insurance to say no.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mom asked: “I mean, how could they say no to him when they already said yes to his brother and he successfully had it?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago, after digging through health insurance paperwork, Alison and William claim that after Noah received approval from BCBS in November 2024 for Elevidys, the insurance firm “quietly” updated company policy on January 1, 2025 to exclude the children’s specific DND mutation from coverage for the gene therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I don't think it's coincidence,” Alison said. “I think that they knew that we had another child and we were going to be seeking this out [again.]” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The insurance company did not address the allegation when&lt;em&gt; The Independent&lt;/em&gt; contacted them for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The parents are running out of options to get their son the life-improving treatment unless BCBS reconsiders the claim. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They have appealed the decision with the insurance giant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The couple has also contacted representatives in Arkansas, where Hunter would receive the gene therapy treatment, and in their home state of Illinois.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arkansas state representatives Andrew Collins and Tippi McCullough both offered the family assistance, while Arkansas U.S. Senator Tom Cotton supported the family in reaching out to the federal Office of Personnel Management, Alison said. The parents have also consulted with a lawyer to weigh their options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I am starting to feel helpless,” said Alison. “I feel like we have tried to make the best decisions for them all these years, and now the choice has been taken away from us.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time is not on Hunter’s side and the gene therapy is his best chance of having the most comfortable life possible, his parents said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is the age when the boys really do start to decline pretty quickly,” said Alison. “We have seen a significant decline in him in the last few months, which is just so scary.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The therapy can stop the disease’s progression. We are just watching him decline before our eyes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:19:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxQbVVUTE1Xd2lCUXhjRktNckNSYVh1Wk8wbjVMMFU0ZFBLMndQdVduMHM3SGphSHV4Z0ZTMUlDbURQZVJfMmZQM2tKUm9UQXEyME8tSlUtQjlRc3JKcG9kQlhkNl9PNTczSURhZW1pYjkxRjBNdE1ONzBsakdCcmZjNkNrNjYtRVZwVnJMVUQ1X3U0X3R4S0dZRkVPZGlScWdiakZlZ0ZB</guid></item><item><title>沉默的杀手会增加您中风和痴呆的风险。以下是控制方法-美国国家公共广播电台</title><link>https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/09/07/nx-s1-5532108/the-silent-killer-increases-your-risk-of-stroke-and-dementia-heres-how-to-control-it</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-87407" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        J Studios/Getty Images/Digital Vision
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;By age 40, more than half of Americans have high blood pressure, but many are unaware of it. Hypertension has long been known as the silent killer. When it's left untreated it can be deadly. And it's considered a silent threat since most people have no symptoms. You can't feel the pressure in your blood vessels increasing.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;New&lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/CIR.0000000000001356" target="_blank"&gt; recommendations&lt;/a&gt; from the American Heart Association aim for &lt;a href="https://newsroom.heart.org/news/new-high-blood-pressure-guideline-emphasizes-prevention-early-treatment-to-reduce-cvd-risk" target="_blank"&gt;early treatment&lt;/a&gt;, including lifestyle changes and medications, once systolic blood pressure rises above 130/80 mm Hg, (which stands for millimeters of mercury, a measure of pressure). Experts say it's clear that the sooner you take action, the more you can protect yourself. &lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Hypertension is a leading cause of heart disease, which is the&lt;a href="http://cdc.gov/heart-disease/data-research/facts-stats/index.html#:~:text=Heart%20disease%20is%20the%20leading,lost%20productivity%20due%20to%20death." target="_blank"&gt; #1 cause of death of both men and women&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. High blood pressure also increases the risk of kidney disease and dementia. And, research shows that hypertension can lead to damage in small blood vessels in the brain, which is linked to cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"There's a really enormous preventive health opportunity in treating hypertension earlier," says &lt;a href="https://www.med.upenn.edu/apps/faculty/index.php/g275/p8561973" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Jordana Cohen&lt;/a&gt;, a nephrologist and hypertension specialist at the University of Pennsylvania. She says millions of adults in the U.S. could benefit from medications and lifestyle changes.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"If you catch it early, and treat it early, you can end up with many more years of healthy life expectancy," Cohen says, pointing to a reduced risk of heart attacks, strokes, kidney damage and dementia.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The new guidelines point to decades old advice about the benefits of a low-sodium diet, which can be challenging to follow, given &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/08/07/nx-s1-5495308/ultra-processed-food-upf-rfk-cdc#:~:text=Ultra%2Dprocessed%20foods%20still%20make,:%20Shots%20%2D%20Health%20News%20:%20NPR" target="_blank"&gt;more than half the calories&lt;/a&gt; consumed in the U.S. come from ultra-processed foods, which tend to be high in salt.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The new guidelines also emphasize lifestyle strategies including exercise, limiting alcohol consumption, and stress reduction in the form of meditation, yoga, or deep breathing. For people with systolic blood pressure ( the upper number) in the 130s, the recommendation is to start with these diet and lifestyle-related changes, then move to medication if blood pressure doesn't improve.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;For people who hit the risky range of a systolic blood pressure of 140 or higher, which is considered stage 2 hypertension, evidence shows starting on high blood pressure medications is beneficial.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"For all people with a blood pressure over 140/ 90, mm Hg, we recommend beginning with two medications," Dr. Dan Jones, chair of the guideline writing committee at the Heart Association, told NPR. Research shows one medication alone is often not enough to lower blood pressure to the optimal range, he says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Jones says even when people are aware they have hypertension, more than half don't manage to lower it to the normal range, which is 120 /80 mm Hg or lower. Some of the challenges include side effects of the medications and individual differences in how well the medication works, as well an unwillingness to take medicines among some people. In addition, some people struggle the everyday hurdles of making lifestyle changes. Jones points out that healthcare providers also use a &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/CIR.0000000000001191" target="_blank"&gt;risk calculator&lt;/a&gt; to estimate a person's individual risk of heart disease, as part of a treatment plan.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;When George Solomon was told about the risks of high blood pressure he was hesitant to take medications. "I felt fine," he says. Then, at age 63, he had a stroke.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Solomon had retired from a career in law enforcement, and was settling into a new routine, making time for exercise and hobbies, such as splitting wood on his farm. One day in the spring of 2023, he started to feel off.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;" I went upstairs to watch TV, and when I sat down in the chair, I couldn't get back up. I had a sensation that came up across my back," he recalls and he lost feeling in his arm and leg. An ambulance took him to Duke University Hospital, near his home, where he underwent treatment and rehab for a stroke.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;He estimates that he's now about 80% recovered, and back to exercising and working on his farm. He realizes now that he needs healthy lifestyle habits and medications to prevent another stroke.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;" I feel I'm on the right path ," he says. He's lost weight and he's doing more cardio and strength training. He's sharing his story in hopes it encourages others to take action.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Medications: what's out there, what's coming&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There are several types of medications used to treat hypertension. They include diuretics that help the body get rid of extra salt and water, ACE inhibitors that help block the production of a hormone called angiotensin II, and help relax the blood vessels and calcium channel blockers that &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/treatments/22316-calcium-channel-blockers" target="_blank"&gt;slow down the movement of calcium into cells&lt;/a&gt;, which can help lower pressure.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But many people with hypertension don't get enough reduction with current medications, and University of Pennsylvania's Cohen says there's a lot of interest in a new class of medication that works by targeting the hormone aldosterone, which helps regulate fluid and sodium in the body. Too much of the hormone is one cause of high blood pressure. The drug is not yet on the market, but new study results could pave the way for a new treatment option.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"In hypertension, we haven't seen anything new that's effective since the nineties," Cohen says. So another tool in the toolkit for treatment could be beneficial, she says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A study &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2507109" target="_blank"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in the New England Journal of Medicine found the aldosterone blocking drug, known as baxdrostat, was effective in lowering blood pressure in many people who have difficulty controlling their hypertension.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The study included about 800 people who, despite taking two or three medications, still had not lowered their blood pressure to the normal range. "What we saw is that after 12 weeks of treatment, there was about a ten point improvement in blood pressure in the patients treated with baxdrostat, over the placebo effect, Dr. Jennifer Brown, a cardiologist at Brigham and Women's Hospital, who is one of the researchers behind the study, told NPR. The study was sponsored by drugmaker Astra Zeneca, which plans to &lt;a href="https://www.astrazeneca.com/media-centre/press-releases/2025/baxdrostat-demonstrated-statistically-significant-clinically-meaningful-reduction-sbp-patients-hard-control-hypertension-baxhtn-phase-iii-trial.html" target="_blank"&gt;share its data&lt;/a&gt; with regulatory authorities by the end of the year.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;A 10 point drop in systolic blood pressure is linked to about a 20% reduction in the risk of heart attacks and strokes, and also a decreased risk of dementia.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7AFBVV95cUxON0FqaW1lNEhfVU1yZHp0d0FLNUFkcGNUd0lBRWhXZFFETzYtbEdSTml6NnhSQlREYVU0bE11MjRoVFJmN1lZY0Riek14QkphN2JKMlJRVTZ3a0F3T1JtTjZpWl9FLVlzSFM5TkVpSWdyTXRmYlVHSV8xNHpsdDZXZTNUNzBrYWJYdGZJeGUyZXJ3dm42N255blIwYkJpbjNBLU5FaWs3VDNqWldWWm9pR2lEaUM2MTVGWHFiNEdmRVdycUFvZzJ4WS1SR2N2VGI5blJZSXVYa09laDFUQ2pGOVJKeXdDakVlX01TNw</guid></item><item><title>实验性大脑刺激可能有助于关闭慢性疼痛的“火灾警报” - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/07/health/pain-management-brain</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/action-bar/instances/cmf339p9w000r27nu57pq8zu8@published" data-label-id-prefix="action-bar-start-of-article" class="action-bar" data-dynamic-breakpoint-placement='{"extraLarge":{"placement":".layout-article-elevate__left"}}' data-expand-conditions='{"follow":{"extraLarge":{"alwaysExpand":true}},"shareOptions":{"large":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"medium":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"extraLarge":{"withAction":"follow","maxNumOfActions":2}}}'&gt;
    &lt;p class="action-bar__overlay"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet" tabindex="-1"&gt;
        
            
            &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet--action" data-title="share options"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/social-share/instances/cmf339p9w000u27nub3p0du4e@published" class="social-share_labelled-list"&gt;
    &lt;div class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links vossi-social-share_labelled-list" data-type="share-links"&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.facebook.com/dialog/share?app_id=80401312489&amp;amp;href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F07%2Fhealth%2Fpain-management-brain&amp;amp;display=popup" data-type="facebook" aria-label="share with facebook" title="Share with Facebook"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-facebook-circle" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.04139 1.33301C11.7458 1.33301 14.7488 4.33601 14.7488 8.04042C14.7488 11.3884 12.296 14.1632 9.08943 14.6663V9.97928H10.6523L10.9497 8.04042H9.08943V6.78225C9.08943 6.25182 9.34934 5.73475 10.1825 5.73475H11.0283V4.08409C11.0283 4.08409 10.2607 3.95309 9.52685 3.95309C7.99476 3.95309 6.99336 4.88165 6.99336 6.56269V8.04042H5.29031V9.97928H6.99336V14.6663C3.78677 14.1632 1.33398 11.3882 1.33398 8.04042C1.33398 4.33601 4.33699 1.33301 8.04139 1.33301Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Facebook&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F07%2Fhealth%2Fpain-management-brain" data-type="x" aria-label="share with x" title="Share with X"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-x-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.99386 8.11503L0 0.666992H4.74756L8.44753 5.27039L12.4004 0.687719H15.0151L9.71175 6.84331L16 14.667H11.2666L7.2603 9.6887L2.98317 14.6532H0.354296L5.99386 8.11503ZM11.9565 13.287L2.91105 2.04698H4.0571L13.0912 13.287H11.9565Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Tweet&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;a class="social-share_labelled-list__share" href="mailto:?subject=CNN%20content%20share&amp;amp;body=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A%0Ahttps%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F07%2Fhealth%2Fpain-management-brain" data-type="email" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="share with email" title="Share with email"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-email-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 24 24" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M2 6C2 4.89543 2.89543 4 4 4H20C21.1046 4 22 4.89543 22 6V18C22 19.1046 21.1046 20 20 20H4C2.89543 20 2 19.1046 2 18V6ZM4 6H20V9.11604L12 11.9396L4 9.11604V6ZM4 11.237V18H20V11.237L12.3328 13.943C12.1174 14.019 11.8825 14.019 11.6672 13.943L4 11.237Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Email&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/07/health/pain-management-brain" data-type="copy" aria-label="copy link to clipboard" title="Copy link to clipboard"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-hyperlink" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.64373 10.3574C5.38338 10.0971 5.38338 9.67496 5.64373 9.41461L9.88637 5.17197C10.1467 4.91162 10.5688 4.91162 10.8292 5.17197C11.0895 5.43232 11.0895 5.85443 10.8292 6.11478L6.58654 10.3574C6.32619 10.6178 5.90408 10.6178 5.64373 10.3574Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M4.22952 8.94321L5.64373 7.52899C5.90408 7.26865 5.90408 6.84654 5.64373 6.58619C5.38338 6.32584 4.96127 6.32584 4.70092 6.58619L3.28671 8.0004C1.98496 9.30215 1.98496 11.4127 3.28671 12.7144C4.58846 14.0162 6.69901 14.0162 8.00075 12.7144L9.41497 11.3002C9.67532 11.0399 9.67532 10.6178 9.41497 10.3574C9.15462 10.0971 8.73251 10.0971 8.47216 10.3574L7.05795 11.7716C6.2769 12.5527 5.01057 12.5527 4.22952 11.7716C3.44847 10.9906 3.44847 9.72426 4.22952 8.94321Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.94356 4.22916L7.52935 5.64338C7.269 5.90373 6.84689 5.90373 6.58654 5.64338C6.32619 5.38303 6.32619 4.96092 6.58654 4.70057L8.00075 3.28635C9.3025 1.98461 11.4131 1.98461 12.7148 3.28635C14.0165 4.5881 14.0165 6.69865 12.7148 8.0004L11.3006 9.41461C11.0402 9.67496 10.6181 9.67496 10.3578 9.41461C10.0974 9.15426 10.0974 8.73215 10.3578 8.4718L11.772 7.05759C12.553 6.27654 12.553 5.01021 11.772 4.22916C10.9909 3.44812 9.72461 3.44811 8.94356 4.22916Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Link&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__open" data-type="open" aria-label="open social share" title="Open social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-share-os" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19 12c.394 0 .714.32.714.714v8.572c0 .394-.32.714-.714.714H4.714A.715.715 0 014 21.286v-8.572a.715.715 0 011.429 0v7.857h12.857v-7.857c0-.394.32-.714.714-.714zm-7.664-9.79a.73.73 0 011.024 0l.076.075 4.916 4.854c.183.18.27.449.188.69a.734.734 0 01-1.216.314L12.57 4.5v11.786c0 .357-.357.714-.714.714s-.714-.359-.714-.714V4.5L7.372 8.143a.73.73 0 01-1.102-.091c-.21-.289-.149-.694.106-.946l4.884-4.821z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__close" data-type="close" aria-label="close social share" title="Close social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-close" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19.787 18.758l-6.792-6.781 6.746-6.735a.728.728 0 00-1.028-1.03l-6.747 6.737-6.711-6.7a.728.728 0 00-1.028 1.03l6.71 6.698-6.723 6.712a.727.727 0 101.027 1.03l6.725-6.714 6.793 6.782a.725.725 0 001.028 0 .727.727 0 000-1.03"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;


  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmf3seete00023b6qa70m4epl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    &lt;span class="editor-note__prefix"&gt;EDITOR’S NOTE:&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;em&gt;Chief Medical Correspondent Dr. Sanjay Gupta’s new &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Doesnt-Have-Hurt-Smart-Pain-Free/dp/1668014475" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;book&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, “It Doesn’t Have to Hurt,” is available now. Watch “Dr. Sanjay Gupta Reports: It Doesn’t Have to Hurt.” at 9 p.m. ET on September 7 on CNN.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339p9w000t27nuevq5g6b2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Edward Mowery&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;lived with excruciating pain for years: Picture being put into a hot frying pan, he said, and then someone holding you down on that pan forever. The fiery, shooting pain got so bad that he quit his job, stopped playing sports and had to abandon his beloved death metal band just as the group was taking off.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0002336nltj4gub3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “At one point, I didn’t have any feeling in my arms or hands or anything,” said Mowery, 55, who lives in New Mexico. “I couldn’t put one note on a guitar, much less play like I do.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0003336njik3uz57@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But everything changed when doctors tried a cutting-edge approach to pain management. If they can refine the technique to make it less intrusive and demonstrate that it works on others, doctors think this technique could radically transform the way people manage debilitating and otherwise untreatable chronic pain — no opioids or pain blockers required.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf3cdhuw00013b6ql4jg0a0b@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The state of the art right now for picking a medication for an individual patient is trial and error” when it comes to pain, said &lt;a href="https://www.ucsfhealth.org/providers/prasad-shirvalkar" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Prasad Shirvalkar,&lt;/a&gt; a neurologist at the University of California San Francisco. “Trying to be your own guinea pig, that’s essentially what we’re doing right now in pain medicine.” Finding something more precise that could stop a pain signal in the brain before it could be felt in the body would be a huge shift.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0004336nnq26ipeo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            An estimated &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/72/wr/mm7215a1.htm#:~:text=Chronic%20pain%20(i.e.%2C%20pain%20lasting%20%E2%89%A53%20months)%20is,pain%20surveillance%20data%20(7)." target="_blank"&gt;50 million adults&lt;/a&gt; in the United States experience chronic pain, defined as lasting for more than three months. Of them, about 8.5% are like Mowery, living with chronic pain that interferes with day-to-day life, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/72/wr/mm7215a1.htm#:~:text=CDC%20analyzed%20data%20from%20the,experienced%20high%2Dimpact%20chronic%20pain." target="_blank"&gt;US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;



  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0005336nk0xbmr40@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Mowery says he was a rambunctious kid and got injured a lot while skiing and playing soccer.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0006336n0ydza4oo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Altogether he says he’s had 34 surgeries, including 11 painful knee surgeries, as well as foot, back and neck surgeries. The bigger problem, though, started with a part of his body that hadn’t even been injured.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0007336nh8x1jdxs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            About a week after a routine knee replacement in 2009, his right foot started to feel like it was on fire.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf3cfa2s00033b6qlj8cjssh@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            He spoke with “all kind of doctors, trying to figure out what was going on,” but nobody could explain the pain. Some didn’t even believe that he was in pain, assuming he was an opioid addict looking for pills. “That’s the one thing, when they put me on all these meds, I wasn’t addicted to all the meds, I was addicted to getting rid of the pain,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0008336nqaoyvnmj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For eight long years, he said, doctors couldn’t figure out what was causing the pain. But in 2017, when his foot turned purple and black, he went to a pain specialist in Albuquerque who took one look and told him he had complex regional pain syndrome, or CRPS.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0009336nrqkamk7d@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            CRPS is a &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/crps-complex-regional-pain-syndrome/symptoms-causes/syc-20371151" target="_blank"&gt;kind of neurological&lt;/a&gt; pain, often in the extremities, that can develop after a surgery, stroke, injury or heart attack that is out of proportion to the severity of an initial injury. It can make blood vessels dilate or constrict, leading to skin discoloration, swelling and temperature changes.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000a336nwbujq0mg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Mowery says doctors explained that when the acute pain from his knee went away, his brain essentially missed that feeling.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000b336n47hzf0oz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Because I’d been in pain for so long, my brain was so used to being in pain that it said, ‘Oh, you need to have this back,’ ” he said. “Manufactured pain from the brain with no stimulus. It’s unreal.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000d336n9nf72hap@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Doctors put him on a variety of pain medications, including morphine and oxycodone, that he didn’t like because he felt so out of it. At one point, he took 17 pills&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;a day, but nothing worked for long. Always athletic, Mowery ended up relying on a walker or a wheelchair to get around﻿.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000e336nzkwj4749@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It’s really depressing. You would think they’d call CRPS the suicide disease,” Mowery said. “A lot of times, I was sitting there just going, ‘what am I going to do? There’s nothing out there for me.’ “
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000f336n55d8sui1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            He spent years searching the internet for clinical trials and finally found one at the &lt;a href="https://clinicaltrials.ucsf.edu/complex-regional-pain-syndrome" target="_blank"&gt;University of California San Francisco&lt;/a&gt;. The description of the research seemed vague but he filled out the questionnaire anyway and, within 40 minutes, he said, he got a message urgently asking him to come to San Francisco.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000g336nj1fv360i@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Relief from his years of agony would soon come after doctors persuaded him to let them drill several holes in his head.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000i336n53tp9dpk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Shirvalkar says he has long wanted to solve the puzzle that is pain. He had success treating neurological conditions but less success treating their chronic pain.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000j336ny7sk3osl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “There are people that have been failed by all available therapies. They’ve tried over 25 different medications. They have had multiple injections and nerve blocks.&lt;br&gt;They’ve even had spinal cord stimulators or peripheral stimulators, and nothing can alleviate their suffering,” Shirvalkar said. “We started appreciating that the brain must be generating or perpetuating these pain signals in a person. So the question becomes, how can we identify what these signals are and really try to suppress or short-circuit them?”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000k336nt8q95cgg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Acute pain, like when someone stubs a toe, affects the brain differently from chronic pain, he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000l336nz8ffq1oi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I think of chronic pain as a fire alarm. The alarm is helpful for acute pain. We want to be able to know when there’s an emergency,” he said. “In chronic pain, it’s as if the fire alarm is going off, but we can’t identify the fire.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000m336ntcsrk4b8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When pain becomes chronic, it rewires the brain.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000n336nwajlih0t@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It starts to take on these other dimensions that include mood and motivation and involve attention and memory, and so we really have to address the cognitive aspect of it,” Shirvalkar said. “It tells me that when someone has developed chronic pain, treating it with a single drug or injection or some monotherapy probably isn’t going to work.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000o336nozb470wh@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            With the help of a $7.56 million grant from the National Institutes of Health, Shirvalkar and a team at UCSF have been exploring &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/tests-procedures/deep-brain-stimulation/about/pac-20384562" target="_blank"&gt;deep brain stimulation&lt;/a&gt;, a technology sometimes used with people who have Parkinson’s disease, to treat pain conditions like Mowery’s.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000p336n3gw7kjmf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            With Parkinson’s, doctors implant electrodes in the brain that produce electrical impulses to disrupt the abnormal signals that cause tremors, stiffness and slow movement. Shirvalkar wondered if they could also use the a version of the device to redirect or suppress the brain’s pain signals to the body.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000q336n0imd0qt3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There were a few challenges with this approach. The device sends signals around the clock in someone who has Parkinson’s, but Shirvalkar thought a constant signal wouldn’t work for chronic pain because the brain can become acclimated to the impulses and essentially override them.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000r336n8go3iat6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Another challenge was figuring out what part of the brain was sending pain signals.&lt;br&gt;There’s no one central location that does this, and it could be different in different people.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000s336nht0x1lb3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Yet another challenge would be to quickly sense when the brain was about to send out a pain signal – or even anticipate it – and shut it down quickly.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000t336nour7em6d@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The team used computational models and AI to essentially detect a biomarker that could track how severe a person’s chronic pain would be, similar to how an A1C level can tell whether someone has diabetes and how severe it is.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000u336n61kdkkqv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But to learn whether deep brain stimulation could work for pain, the team first had to persuade Mowery that he should have another surgery. He was reluctant to have another procedure. This trial would require three.
    &lt;/p&gt;





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000v336nh5r2h5l4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It took Mowery about 18 months to decide the trial was right for him – time in which the worsening pain essentially wore him down.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000w336nv9uxvdk5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In the first surgery, doctors would map Mowery’s brain to determine where the pain came from. Another surgery would remove the temporary probes from the first procedure. A final procedure placed permanent probes in the correct areas.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000x336n14blzlb7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For the first part of the trial, Mowery spent 10 days in the hospital while doctors created a grid of more than 100 points on his head to try to find different circuits or certain activation for pain by watching and stimulating his brain. Even with eight- to 10-hour days probing his brain, it wasn’t until day five or six that the researchers had their “eureka moment.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000y336n7qs30a2h@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “All of a sudden, Ed says, ‘Wow, my pain just washed off of me,’ ” Shirvalkar said. “I was blown away. I didn’t know what to say.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv000z336no3jsng0d@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Concerned that it could be the placebo effect, the doctors kept testing to make sure they had the right targets. Shirvalkar quickly became confident that they had picked the right areas when Mowery&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;immediately felt the pain in his feet, legs and lower back dissipate.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0010336ni6ns5086@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “When it comes to actually understanding what’s driving someone’s chronic pain, we say there’s no pain center, right? But it tells us if chronic pain is this complex lock, it tells us that yes, that there is a key to be found. So it gives us hope.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0011336nkebbazkf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Much more research will be done to see if this technology can work for everyone or whether there would be even better technology that would be less invasive.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0012336n73vanbcn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In August, Shirvalkar and his team &lt;a href="https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2025.08.11.25333010v1" target="_blank"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; the results of their tests of this technique on six people. The team followed the patients for 22 months and were even able to randomize the trial so some got the stimulation and some did not. Those who got stimulation reported a reduction in pain of about 60%, while the placebo group got no such relief.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0013336ny5uk6pb2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Mowery has resumed his normal daily activities, including playing his guitar. He can monitor what’s going on in his brain with an iPad app and just has to periodically charge the device that sends the signals to his brain.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf34e62j00023b6q3mcwjbg4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            He’s not totally pain-free, he says: He’ll have a bad day sometimes, but it’s infrequent.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf34emfl00043b6qt9bgfvpr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            He says Shirvalkar’s work changed his life.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0014336nibiqkgof@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The way it detected pain, the way it turns off pain, the way I’m getting off all these medications, I feel like I owe him my life,” Mowery said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0015336nx5jcpwir@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Mowery felt so much better that, in June, he &lt;a href="https://braininitiative.nih.gov/news-events/blog/congressional-briefing-highlights-brain-initiative-research-addiction" target="_blank"&gt;accompanied Shirvalkar&lt;/a&gt; to Washington to testify before Congress’&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Neuroscience Caucus about the impact of the NIH BRAIN Initiative on addiction research and on this pain treatment alternative.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf34frk500063b6qz2dgn0un@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Shirvalkar is concerned about future funding amid the current political environment and other funding cuts at the NIH.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0016336n8chdi69f@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “NIH funding is always a concern. Fortunately, we’re doing OK for the time being,” Shirvalkar said. “We’ll have to wait and see.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0017336nnss8pwu7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Mowery hopes that his experience will provide enough of an example so people can see the possibilities of such medical research.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmf339tsv0018336nhav4nuge@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I have been called a medical astronaut before, and my sister is an actual astronaut, and she finds that funny,” Mowery said. “It’s a miracle.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMia0FVX3lxTFBCWjVCVk9XbkZoVjhKUkNNWWNXeHdITmx0b3pMWllObTZqZjY0d2NfWjVxUWxXbEZRTnJERVcteFdvbEswNWNqMElmRUZKTXdMZERKdk1QOVhUWkJfSy1xVVdzeWtMdE9oOU5j</guid></item><item><title>为什么越来越多的老年人在跌倒后死亡？ -《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/07/health/falls-deaths-elderly-drugs.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 09:02:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE4tWnFPT0pMZGMwa0ZUQXNFdkw0T2FqaUV6eWtaOUVPcDZvekFSeUkxbUtwRHJTbVBteVBvQUFRWExGT3ZoY1BJV0xkRU5yNGJtamhsZFZKdExnaEQyckZKaGdaTDZpYWpCVFIzc2NZZlBMQ0dsdnZzOGhhdVdCZw</guid></item><item><title>反疫苗运动的奇怪历史- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20250905-the-strange-history-of-the-anti-vaccine-movement</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 ilQTUs"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"The annihilation of the smallpox, the most dreadful scourge of the human species, must be the final result of this practice," Jenner wrote in 1801. And he would be proved right. In 1980, after a decades-long public health campaign that included widespread vaccination, the World Health Organization (WHO) declared &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.who.int/health-topics/smallpox" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;smallpox had been eradicated&lt;/a&gt;. It remains the only infectious disease where this has been achieved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A sleugh of other vaccines have been developed against other diseases, from influenza to human papillomavirus infections that cause certain cancers and the Sars-COV-2 virus behind Covid-19. In the past 50 years, an estimated &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(24)00850-X/fulltext" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;154 million lives have been saved by vaccines&lt;/a&gt;, according to one recent study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Yet, opposition to vaccines – or hesitancy about accepting them – &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.mdpi.com/2076-393X/12/1/31" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;is widespread&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c1jgrlxx37do" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;on the rise&lt;/a&gt; in many parts of the world, even percolating into the uppermost branches of governments responsible for &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c62q41qm9pvo" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;improving public health&lt;/a&gt;. This week, US health secretary Robert F Kennedy Jr was quizzed by the Senate Finance Committee over his vaccine policies, resulting in fiery exchanges. On the same day, the surgeon general of Florida also announced plans to &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c62q41qm9pvo" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;end vaccine mandates in the state&lt;/a&gt;. (&lt;i id="read-more-about" class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt;Read more about &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c1jgrlxx37do" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;&lt;i id="why-vaccine-distrust-is-on-the-rise" class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt;why vaccine distrust is on the rise&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;So, is this a recent phenomenon, or has distrust in vaccines been around for as long as the jabs themselves? Why do they face protests from relatively small, but vocal, segments of the public? And how have these arguments evolved? This is a look at the long, and strange history of the anti-vax movement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Back in the early 1800s, a series of controlled experiments by Jenner and other doctors quickly showed inoculation to be extremely effective, granting immunity against smallpox in well over 95% of those vaccinated. Public health authorities worldwide took action to roll it out. In the UK, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vaccination_Act" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;a series of Vaccination Acts&lt;/a&gt;, passed in 1840, 1853 and 1871, made immunisation for children first free, then compulsory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 09:01:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxOYlpHZkJTV0V4bFNwVWNTNXMxdXJ1UzhZd09sNTVVX0RUaUlJb0pVWjBWaDNLT1ZNRjJMUGRXVVJhYnhXVE5XejRaSnVTSk9tZzRRR3h0dXplTlpvLVpONVRIZXVpbFdPZVpybmk4aGpxeTdrUUZ2SXpJU0hYcWc1RkZUTGNWSVpuUGo0d29IZHRMeXRUVGNn</guid></item><item><title>在亚马逊上购买Halle Berry的亲密和健康产品- TMZ</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2025/09/07/halle-berry-respin-intimacy-products/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;header class="article__header"&gt;
                              &lt;h1 class="article__header--headline-title"&gt;Halle Berry's Respin Intimacy Products on Amazon&lt;/h1&gt;
                    &lt;h2 class="article__header--headline-fragments"&gt;
                          &lt;span class="article__header--hf1 text-uppercase h3"&gt;Feminine Care for Down There&lt;/span&gt;
                          &lt;span class="article__header--hf2 text-uppercase h1"&gt;Buy Halle Berry's&lt;/span&gt;
                          &lt;span class="article__header--hf3 text-titlecase h2"&gt;Intimacy &amp;amp; Wellness Line&lt;/span&gt;
                      &lt;/h2&gt;
        
        
        
                  &lt;p class="date-wrapper"&gt;
                        Published &lt;time class="published-datetime" datetime="2025-09-07T00:01:50-07:00"&gt;September 7, 2025 12:01 AM PDT&lt;/time&gt;
                                                                            &lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/header&gt;

      &lt;div class="article__blocks clearfix"&gt;
        
        
    

    &lt;section id="cb-69afc7455beafe40d27089d11e6fb865" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;TMZ may collect a share of sales or other compensation from links on this page.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    &lt;section id="cb-c8596854810190486e68d2351a75ab27" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tmz.com/people/halle-berry/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Halle Berry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is ending the stigma when it comes to feminine health and wellness ... and is getting real about intimacy care. That's why she created Respin, a company catered to midlife women and their evolving intimate needs.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    &lt;section id="cb-f90dd54520e4fdb54befe0711b2f742d" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;And with her latest launch, Halle partnered with intimate wellness brand Joylux to craft a line of products that she says she can't live without. Whether you need a little boost in the bedroom or some relief from frequent hot flashes, Halle has got you covered. Plus, you can shop all of Joylux and Respin's products on their &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/4fu1Mox"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon storefront&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    

    

    

    &lt;section id="cb-217b018c916c4361d82030dce6ca5733" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Ready to get it on? Don't forget &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/41AEtn4"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Respin x JoyLux LET’S SPIN Intimacy Gel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;... for a much more pleasurable experience.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;
&lt;a id="continued" class="continued-anchor"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;

    &lt;section id="cb-90e985f3a29b0e3d72b1f28f56ba7415" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;If intimacy has become uncomfortable due to dryness or hormonal changes, this ultra-premium OB-GYN designed gel was created to enhance overall comfort by moisturizing and supplementing the body’s natural lubrication. It’s non-irritating, pH-balanced and cleanly formulated with skin-loving ingredients like hyaluronic acid and aloe.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    

    

    

    &lt;section id="cb-f4c586f7120a16ad594c6d2efc2e27f7" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Halle swears by the &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/3HnKM6J"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Respin x Joylux vFit PLUS Menopause Kit&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;… which includes an intimate wellness device that she says changed her life.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    &lt;section id="cb-b62d4b75a454d71f46cc74438b39b8c6" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Previously available only through doctors, this device utilizes advanced red-light technology as well as sonic pulsation and gentle heat for pelvic floor health and wellness. By promoting improved hydration, sensation and tone, you’ll experience noticeable improvements within just a few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    

    

    

    &lt;section id="cb-12ede9c7c42f29a7ba4f903e86a0cadb" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Lather up with the &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/4oKuQfR" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" title="https://amzn.to/4oKuQfR"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Respin SHEbar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, formulated especially for the vaginal area.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    &lt;section id="cb-ba50fec78dc0121f0f9f856593a0bf5d" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;This french-milled non-soap cleansing bar has a rich and luxurious lather that is light and velvety ... but won’t leave residue behind. It’s enriched with coconut, argan and avocado oils for a gentle, smooth and nourishing cleanse, crafted just for your delicate tissue.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    

    

    

    &lt;section id="cb-c64ddc9504ffa6dc44e86ec567ffc3d2" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;If you’ve got a vFit Plus, the &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/45IHBja" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" title="https://amzn.to/45IHBja"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Respin Photonic Gel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is an absolute must-have.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    &lt;section id="cb-6f0227a3e1d25df077333102c6c212bc" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;It’s been scientifically proven to increase light power by 45% and enhance your vFit performance and comfort. As a balanced pH water-based gel, it’s infused with effective, clean, light-reflecting ingredients including sodium hyaluronate and gluconolactone.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    

    

    

    &lt;section id="cb-d9ce454ecaaa2e5ae972db0e6708df06" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;If hot flashes have you heated up, cool down with the&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/41vnrXv"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Respin coldHER Cooling Pads&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    &lt;section id="cb-73966fce90129622b086537512f4ce61" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;These convenient and discreet pads utilize innovative Phase Change Material to rapidly pull heat from your body. Just place them inside your bra…or wherever you need cooling…and instantly feel relief. When you’re done, the material goes back to solid at room temperature…so you can use them over and over again.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    

    

    

    &lt;section id="cb-cc8cc771592f80968154cbae5b5f745e" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;If your intimate areas are in need of a little extra hydration, &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/4fwEUov"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Respin revitalizHER Hydrating Serum&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is exactly what you’re looking for.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    &lt;section id="cb-7550a37195da11885e0c48e860531ae6" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;This pH-balanced serum uses gentle ingredients like coconut oil, beeswax, and powerful antioxidants to soothe, soften, rejuvenate and hydrate irritated skin in your most sensitive areas. It supports all-over freshness, helping you stay comfortable and confident all day.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

    

    &lt;section id="cb-026aa1889e6aa0660cbb3923f1cd8af1" class="canvas-block canvas-block-permalink canvas-text-block canvas-text-block-permalink canvas-text-block--default  canvas-block-is-last " data-context='{"section":"permalink","name":"text_block"}'&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;All prices subject to change.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/section&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TMZ</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 07:01:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTFBERmlycDZlaERWNFN3Q0o3eGg0VGNrSGQtdndXdEZVdk9pcGtDNzN6U1pPeVBkcm9yMGkxYXlQZDEtbjRZOENPSkxTazRvMURUS2lmVWtHbFNOSk1aM0NCcFRPWS1Yb3lfb2hXd0dvLUhRTnFEMGRV</guid></item><item><title>可怕的研究发现六种流行的人造甜味剂可能与痴呆症有关-找出哪种-爱尔兰之星</title><link>https://www.irishstar.com/culture/food-drink/terrifying-study-finds-six-popular-35862759</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="article-body" class="ArticleBody_article__AwrJE" data-testid="body"&gt;&lt;h1 class="HeadingOne_heading-one__mmNWJ  __className_59ead2"&gt;Terrifying study finds six popular artificial sweeteners could be linked to dementia - find out which&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 class="LeadText_lead-text__wd_PA __className_7ae2e9" data-testid="leadtext"&gt;An eight-year long observational study found links between the consumption of artificial sweeteners and a significant decline in memory and cognitive skills for middle-aged adults&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX ImageEmbed_image-lead__Ti3qQ" data-testid="leadimage" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="35862757"&gt;&lt;figure class="Figure_figure__Uce4f"&gt;&lt;img src="https://i2-prod.irishstar.com/article35862757.ece/ALTERNATES/s615/0_GettyImages-1303134474.jpg" alt="Sugar" loading="eager" srcset="https://i2-prod.irishstar.com/article35862757.ece/ALTERNATES/s508/0_GettyImages-1303134474.jpg 508w, https://i2-prod.irishstar.com/article35862757.ece/ALTERNATES/s615/0_GettyImages-1303134474.jpg 615w,
          https://i2-prod.irishstar.com/article35862757.ece/ALTERNATES/s1023/0_GettyImages-1303134474.jpg 1023w" sizes="(max-width: 508px) 508px, (max-width: 615px) 615px, 1023px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;A new study reveals some no- and low-calorie sweeteners may being linked to cognitive decline&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: Getty)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;While many choose artificial sweetener options &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.irishstar.com/culture/food-drink/beetroot-juice-lower-blood-pressure-35844046" target="_blank" aria-label="as a way to make a healthy choiceLink opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt;as a way to make a healthy choice&lt;/a&gt;, new research shows that sweetener alternatives &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.irishstar.com/culture/food-drink/gallbladder-cancer-symptoms-cause-35805319" target="_blank" aria-label="may not be as healthy as advertisedLink opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt;may not be as healthy as advertised&lt;/a&gt;. In fact, these options may have unexpected consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;A study published in an issue of Neurology on Sept. 3, 2025, investigated the association between low- and no-calorie sweeteners (LNCSs) and cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;The researchers conducted an observational study following the same group of participants over the course of eight years. Their findings suggest that the &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.irishstar.com/culture/food-drink/" target="_blank" aria-label="consumptionLink opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt;consumption&lt;/a&gt; of artificial LNCSs and sugar alcohols are associated with an accelerated rate of cognitive decline as they observed over the long-term study period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span data-testid="readmore" class="ReadMore_readmore-prefix__xS44r __className_7ae2e9"&gt;READ MORE: &lt;span class="ReadMore_readmore-link__eF9pN"&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.irishstar.com/culture/food-drink/mcdonalds-extra-value-meal-prices-35857274" data-tmdatatrack="read-more" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="35857274" data-tmdatatrack-source="editorial" tabindex="0"&gt;McDonald's makes major price change to menus across the US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="readmore" class="ReadMore_readmore-prefix__xS44r __className_7ae2e9"&gt;READ MORE: &lt;span class="ReadMore_readmore-link__eF9pN"&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.irishstar.com/culture/food-drink/unique-overnight-oats-recipe-thats-35848464" data-tmdatatrack="read-more" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="35848464" data-tmdatatrack-source="editorial" tabindex="0"&gt;'Unique' overnight oats recipe that's packed with protein for a healthy breakfast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;In a country where the average American eats 17 tablespoons of added sugar per day, per the &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/sugar/how-much-sugar-is-too-much#:~:text=Let's%20face%20it.,%2C10%2Dpound%20bowling%20balls." target="_blank" aria-label="American Heart AssociationLink opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt;American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt;, artificial sweetener options have its benefits. They have fewer calories, can lower the risk of tooth decay and cavities, and generally &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/nutrition-and-healthy-eating/in-depth/artificial-sweeteners/art-20046936" target="_blank" aria-label="don’t raise blood sugar levelsLink opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt;don’t raise blood sugar levels&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;However, this new research pinpoints areas of concern if certain LNCSs are used regularly in large quantities over long periods of time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="HeadingThree_heading-three__PBHLs  __className_59ead2"&gt;The results of the study&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.neurology.org/doi/10.1212/WNL.0000000000214023" target="_blank" aria-label="The studyLink opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt;The study&lt;/a&gt; observed over 12,500 Brazilian adults with an average age of 52 over the course of eight years, and the researchers measured the participants’ self-reported dietary intakes of seven different low- and no-calorie sweeteners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BoxStyles_box-container__Qk3WH BoxStyles_non-commercial__aiWwo" data-testid="non-commercial-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Participants were given cognitive tests throughout the study to track and measure their memory, language, and thinking skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;They found that the artificial sweetener tagatose was not associated with cognitive decline in participants. However, the other six sweeteners were linked with cognitive decline:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="UnorderedList_unordered-list__gzblI" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="unordered-list"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Aspartame&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Saccharin&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Acesulfame-K&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Erythritol&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Sorbitol&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;Xylitol&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;For the consumption of these six sweeteners, the decline was specifically linked to memory and verbal fluency domains. Also, they found that there was a faster decline in memory for participants with diabetes who consumed LNCSs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;According to the results, the impact of this decline was greater in those under the age of 60, and there were no significant associations for those ages 60 and up. This signals the importance of focusing on the types and amounts of sweeteners consumed earlier in life as they may have significant effects on memory later in life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;For the participants who were consuming greater amounts of the sweeteners, it was found that they had the faster decline in overall thinking and memory skills compared to those consuming the lowest amounts. For those consuming greater amounts, the decline equaled about 1.6 years of aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;Co-author and associate professor of geriatrics at the University of Sao Paulo Dr. Claudia Suemoto told &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.today.com/health/diet-fitness/artificial-sweeteners-cognitive-decline-study-rcna228871?cid=eml_thisistoday_20250904" target="_blank" aria-label="TODAYLink opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt;TODAY&lt;/a&gt;.com, “It is important to remember that cognitive performance peaks around the third decade of life, between 25 and 30 years old, and after that there is a very slow, gradual decline in function. What our study shows is that sweetener consumption may accelerate this natural process, even in middle-aged adults.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="HeadingThree_heading-three__PBHLs  __className_59ead2"&gt;Some limitations of this study&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;One area of concern for this study is that not all artificial sweeteners were included. Also, the results were self-reported by the participants, which may leave a margin of error for the accuracy of these results if some didn’t remember their dietary intake correctly on certain days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;In the &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.aan.com/PressRoom/Home/PressRelease/5281" target="_blank" aria-label="press releaseLink opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; for this study, Suemoto stated, “More research is needed to confirm our findings and to investigate if other refined sugar alternatives, such as applesauce, honey, maple syrup or coconut sugar, may be effective alternatives.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;It’s also important to note that this study found links between LNCSs and cognitive declines; the study does not prove these artificial sweeteners cause the decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;The &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.sweeteners.org/isa-statement-on-new-study-on-sweeteners-and-cognitive-health/" target="_blank" aria-label="International Sweeteners AssociationLink opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt;International Sweeteners Association&lt;/a&gt; released a statement in regards to this study, saying, “This research is an observational study, which can only show a statistical association, not a direct cause-and-effect relationship.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph"&gt;The association pointed out that global authorities have consistently confirmed the safety of LNCSs. “These organisations conduct comprehensive safety assessments based on the totality of scientific evidence, not just a single study,” the association states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Irish Star</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 03:03:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPQ1M2VXo3LWhhQTUxX0pOYlBuYkJfZVRGUGQ0S2ExNkhVR2pGVkpSc1cyOUVpdFh1aVlNU3FSWVpHdFRrNC1oT1VYM3cwOXhjLUppMTc3X3d4Tmt2VERrRzA1R0JWb0ZSa3NXWTdHVXE1N1ZsY044VXNhZWR4d0p3QVNpbEdWZTk5Q3B3Zm80eW9iZw</guid></item><item><title>医生透露了现在要做的六件事来抵御癌症......即使你有这种疾病的家族史-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-14635571/family-history-cancer-reduce-risk-getting-disease.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For the millions of people with a family history of &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-939c17f0-1f84-11f0-b6a2-a344cd87ec8b" class=""&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;, l&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=""&gt;iving in fear of a diagnosis may be the norm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While cancer is genetic - the root cause stems from a person's genetic code - it is not always hereditary (passed down from parents to children). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class=""&gt;But what &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;could&lt;/span&gt; be inherited are genetic code mutations that increase someone's likelihood of being diagnosed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For example, the BRCA1 and BRCA2 genes, which increase the risk a person will &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14632737/six-silent-cancers-quietly-surging-men-women-subtle-symptoms.html"&gt;develop breast and ovarian cancer&lt;/a&gt;, are hereditary - but not all types of cancers are associated with specific genes, and not all familial connections are weighted equally in terms of risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The National Cancer Institute estimates up to 10 percent of cancers may be caused by inherited genetic changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Helen Messier, a physician-scientist who studies genomics, cancer prevention and precision medicine, told the Daily Mail that any family history of cancer can be cause for concern. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But, she adds, close relatives (like a sister or mother) indicate a higher risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said having one cousin who was diagnosed, for instance, has 'little genetic influence on your own risk,' but having 'several aunts or uncles with cancer - particularly the same cancer - can be suggestive of a familial syndrome.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above graph shows the national trends in cancer death rates between 2018 and 2022 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Family cancer syndrome&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Hereditary (or family) cancer syndrome is a rare disorder in which family members have a higher-than-average risk of developing certain types of cancer. The disorder is caused by inherited genetic variants in cancer-related genes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One sign a family may be affected is if multiple members get diagnosed with the same kind of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Messier explained that, during a routine visit, physicians will typically take a family history of cancer dating back at least three generations. If there is any history of early-onset cancers, the doctor will usually suggest genetic counseling and testing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While there is no outrunning genetics, experts say there are ways to lead a healthier life and reduce your risk of developing cancer yourself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The key to prevention is a combination of healthy lifestyle and staying proactive with checkups, said Dr Cedrek McFadden, a surgeon and associate professor at the University of South Carolina School of Medicine Greenville.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts reveal six ways you can reduce your risk of developing genetic cancers that run in your family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A multitude of research has linked physical activity to lower cancer risk, including cancers of the breasts and colon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-large health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Exercise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;No matter the type of cancer in your family, Dr McFadden and Dr Messier both suggest regular exercise to reduce your own risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They said people should aim to get 150 minutes of exercise a week - or about 20 to 30 minutes per day, five days a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'But don’t let perfect be the enemy of good,' Dr McFadden said. 'Even a brisk 20-minute walk most days adds up. Just move; your body will thank you for it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group floatRHS"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dr. Helen Messier told the Daily Mail diet can be a key way to reduce cancer risk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He also said if lung cancer, specifically, runs in your family, exercise is key as 'healthy lungs love movement.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Messier added: 'Exercise controls insulin, soothes inflammation, helps balance hormones and maintains weight - all fundamental cancer-prevention mechanisms.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A multitude of research has linked physical activity to lower cancer risk.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One 2022 study in Cancer Cell International found physical activity may reduce the risk of colon cancer, which impacts about 107,000 people per year, by 23 percent when comparing people who exercise the most to those who exercise the least.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2019 study published in the World Journal of Gastrointestinal Oncology suggested physical activity could prevent nearly 15 percent of colon cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For breast cancer, which will see about 320,000 new cases this year, a 2016 analysis published in the European Journal of Cancer found the most physically active women had a 12 to 21 percent lower risk than those who were least physically active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And a 2020 study in the British Journal of Cancer found women who reported the most exercise per week had a 23 percent decreased risk of breast cancer compared to those who exercised the least.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-large health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Diet &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Messier said a clean and healthy diet can be crucial for reducing all types of cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said if colon cancer runs in your family, avoiding processed meats like bacon, sausage and deli products can help. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A diet high in fiber, fruits, vegetables and whole grains has also been found to lower colon cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr McFadden echoed those sentiments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He told the Daily Mail: 'If [a parent] had colon cancer, it's worth cutting back on processed meats... and even limiting red meat in general.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I tell my patients to lean into a fiber-rich diet... Your gut bacteria thrive on that, and over time, that supports a healthier colon.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Overall, both experts said no food is a magic bullet, but the Mediterranean diet 'gets a lot of praise for a reason'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It includes 'lots of plant-based foods, healthy fats like olive oil, lean proteins and fewer processed snacks or sugary drinks.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The doctors agree that, 'Basically, if it grew from the ground, it’s probably good for you.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Messier also &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/article-12471615/DR-MICHAEL-MOSLEY-eating-olive-oil-nuts-fish-Living-like-Med-good.html"&gt;said a 'Mediterranean-type diet abundant in the plants is the gold standard - packed with vegetables, legumes, whole grains, healthy fats such as olive oil and lean proteins like fish.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Minimize ultra-processed foods, sugars and alcohol. Foods high in phytonutrients, such as berries, cruciferous vegetables, turmeric and green tea also may be protective.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Avoiding alcohol and maintaining a healthy weight are also two factors to consider when trying to cut your familial cancer risk, Dr Messier said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above is a map from the Environmental Protection Agency. It shows radon levels across the country, which reveal 25% of Americans live in areas where levels are considered unsafe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-large health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Avoid toxins&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Messier told the Mail that even if you have never smoked, a close family member who was a smoker and was eventually diagnosed with lung cancer could still put you at risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lung cancer is estimated to affect about 227,000 people in 2025, with 124,000 deaths. People exposed to secondhand smoke have a 20 to 30 percent increased risk of lung cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Both doctors advise quitting smoking, avoiding secondhand smoke and steering clear of all tobacco products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They also urge people to avoid other toxins - particularly radon. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Messier and Dr McFadden recommend testing your home for radon, a radioactive gas that has no color, smell or taste. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The gas - which comes from the natural decay of uranium, a radioactive element found in nearly all soils - is present in both indoor and outdoor air and there is no known safe level of exposure to the substance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Studies show &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/sciencetech/article-14305279/map-radioactive-gas-hotspots-linked-cancer.html"&gt;radon exposure is the second most common cause of lung cancer&lt;/a&gt; in the US after smoking, leading to about 21,000 deaths each year, according to the EPA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Angelina Jolie (pictured) had her breasts, ovaries and fallopian tubes removed after testing positive for a gene that increases breast and ovarian cancer risk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Bailey Hutchins of Tennessee, died of colon cancer at 26 years old&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-large health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Genetic testing &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Charles Oyesile, a medical research physician, told the Daily Mail people with a family history of cancer should consult with an oncologist and genetics counselor to assess their individualized risk given their family history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Testing can help determine the best course of action - whether that is undergoing genetic testing to see if you are a carrier of any cancer-related genes, or starting cancer screenings at an earlier age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While genetic tests won't prevent cancer, they can tell you if you are at a heightened risk, which could help you make certain life choices - such as exercising more, quitting smoking, following a cleaner diet or undergoing certain preventative procedures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In addition to the BRCA genes, a blood test can identify genetic variants in the APC gene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This tumor suppressor gene is crucial for preventing the development of colon cancer. Mutations in the APC gene can lead to familial adenomatous polyposis, an inheritable condition that causes polyps in the colon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This, in turn, raises the risk of colon cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr McFadden said, 'In some cases, a genetic test can tell us which screenings you actually need and when. Don’t guess - ask your doctor. We’d much rather have that conversation now than after something shows up later.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-large health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Prophylactic surgery&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Having prophylactic surgery to remove organs that increase your risk of cancer is one way to fend off a familial pattern of disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For example, if genetic testing shows you carry the BRCA1 or BRCA2 gene, you may opt for a prophylactic double mastectomy (removal of the breasts) or oophorectomy (removal of the ovaries) - procedures Angelina Jolie had when she found out she was a carrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Jolie underwent genetic testing because her mother battled cancer for nearly a decade and died at 56. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When she tested positive for the BRCA1 gene, doctors estimated Jolie had an 87 percent risk of breast cancer and a 50 percent risk of ovarian cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She chose to have both breasts removed and get implants in 2013. Her chances of developing breast cancer dropped to 5 percent, she &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2013/05/14/opinion/my-medical-choice.html"&gt;wrote &lt;/a&gt;in a piece for The New York Times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Two years later, she had her ovaries and fallopian tubes removed to prevent ovarian cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other types of preventive surgeries include a colectomy - where part or all of the colon is removed to prevent colorectal cancer.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-large health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Preventative screenings &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Screenings also won't prevent cancer, but they can help detect the disease in earlier stages - and an early-stage diagnosis means the cancer may be easier to treat and could have a higher survival rate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If your grandmother, mother or sister was diagnosed with breast cancer, Dr Messier suggests talking to your doctor about beginning screenings like mammograms earlier than the generally recommended starting age of 40 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr McFadden said a colonoscopy to screen for colon cancer may be warranted earlier than recommended - typically 45 years old - if a sibling was diagnosed with the cancer before the age of 50.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'That's where personalized screening plans come in,' he said, 'and they can make a big difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'[Screenings are] not one-size-fits-all. If it’s colon cancer, you might start colonoscopy earlier. If it’s breast or prostate cancer, we might begin mammograms or PSA testing sooner.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 02:49:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNQmFzX0VXa1NlYU45VFRoeG9TYUZralpXMjVHUHdzdG9PMnZDaDlZMFBOV3BCZHQzZ2o3V1VtSlE0OXlhMjVxc2w1ZkdveVZvVUJERGFJbnVjdlRoT0Y4ZDAyNlByYjk4eTNGWjZTVWZiUUxrX3JvMVBWanZlWmRNS0VNZHV5dXg0aDZlUkVzcEFSVGlWSU0zTHUwX0c0ajJ0aHVwSTA1bEFKdw</guid></item><item><title>医生透露了现在要做的六件事来抵御癌症......即使你有这种疾病的家族史-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-14635571/family-history-cancer-reduce-risk-getting-disease.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For the millions of people with a family history of &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-939c17f0-1f84-11f0-b6a2-a344cd87ec8b" class=""&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;, l&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=""&gt;iving in fear of a diagnosis may be the norm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While cancer is genetic - the root cause stems from a person's genetic code - it is not always hereditary (passed down from parents to children). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class=""&gt;But what &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;could&lt;/span&gt; be inherited are genetic code mutations that increase someone's likelihood of being diagnosed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For example, the BRCA1 and BRCA2 genes, which increase the risk a person will &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14632737/six-silent-cancers-quietly-surging-men-women-subtle-symptoms.html"&gt;develop breast and ovarian cancer&lt;/a&gt;, are hereditary - but not all types of cancers are associated with specific genes, and not all familial connections are weighted equally in terms of risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The National Cancer Institute estimates up to 10 percent of cancers may be caused by inherited genetic changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Helen Messier, a physician-scientist who studies genomics, cancer prevention and precision medicine, told the Daily Mail that any family history of cancer can be cause for concern. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But, she adds, close relatives (like a sister or mother) indicate a higher risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said having one cousin who was diagnosed, for instance, has 'little genetic influence on your own risk,' but having 'several aunts or uncles with cancer - particularly the same cancer - can be suggestive of a familial syndrome.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above graph shows the national trends in cancer death rates between 2018 and 2022 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Family cancer syndrome&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Hereditary (or family) cancer syndrome is a rare disorder in which family members have a higher-than-average risk of developing certain types of cancer. The disorder is caused by inherited genetic variants in cancer-related genes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One sign a family may be affected is if multiple members get diagnosed with the same kind of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Messier explained that, during a routine visit, physicians will typically take a family history of cancer dating back at least three generations. If there is any history of early-onset cancers, the doctor will usually suggest genetic counseling and testing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While there is no outrunning genetics, experts say there are ways to lead a healthier life and reduce your risk of developing cancer yourself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The key to prevention is a combination of healthy lifestyle and staying proactive with checkups, said Dr Cedrek McFadden, a surgeon and associate professor at the University of South Carolina School of Medicine Greenville.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts reveal six ways you can reduce your risk of developing genetic cancers that run in your family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A multitude of research has linked physical activity to lower cancer risk, including cancers of the breasts and colon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-large health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Exercise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;No matter the type of cancer in your family, Dr McFadden and Dr Messier both suggest regular exercise to reduce your own risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They said people should aim to get 150 minutes of exercise a week - or about 20 to 30 minutes per day, five days a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'But don’t let perfect be the enemy of good,' Dr McFadden said. 'Even a brisk 20-minute walk most days adds up. Just move; your body will thank you for it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group floatRHS"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dr. Helen Messier told the Daily Mail diet can be a key way to reduce cancer risk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He also said if lung cancer, specifically, runs in your family, exercise is key as 'healthy lungs love movement.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Messier added: 'Exercise controls insulin, soothes inflammation, helps balance hormones and maintains weight - all fundamental cancer-prevention mechanisms.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A multitude of research has linked physical activity to lower cancer risk.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One 2022 study in Cancer Cell International found physical activity may reduce the risk of colon cancer, which impacts about 107,000 people per year, by 23 percent when comparing people who exercise the most to those who exercise the least.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2019 study published in the World Journal of Gastrointestinal Oncology suggested physical activity could prevent nearly 15 percent of colon cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For breast cancer, which will see about 320,000 new cases this year, a 2016 analysis published in the European Journal of Cancer found the most physically active women had a 12 to 21 percent lower risk than those who were least physically active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And a 2020 study in the British Journal of Cancer found women who reported the most exercise per week had a 23 percent decreased risk of breast cancer compared to those who exercised the least.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-large health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Diet &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Messier said a clean and healthy diet can be crucial for reducing all types of cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said if colon cancer runs in your family, avoiding processed meats like bacon, sausage and deli products can help. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A diet high in fiber, fruits, vegetables and whole grains has also been found to lower colon cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr McFadden echoed those sentiments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He told the Daily Mail: 'If [a parent] had colon cancer, it's worth cutting back on processed meats... and even limiting red meat in general.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I tell my patients to lean into a fiber-rich diet... Your gut bacteria thrive on that, and over time, that supports a healthier colon.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Overall, both experts said no food is a magic bullet, but the Mediterranean diet 'gets a lot of praise for a reason'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It includes 'lots of plant-based foods, healthy fats like olive oil, lean proteins and fewer processed snacks or sugary drinks.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The doctors agree that, 'Basically, if it grew from the ground, it’s probably good for you.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Messier also &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/article-12471615/DR-MICHAEL-MOSLEY-eating-olive-oil-nuts-fish-Living-like-Med-good.html"&gt;said a 'Mediterranean-type diet abundant in the plants is the gold standard - packed with vegetables, legumes, whole grains, healthy fats such as olive oil and lean proteins like fish.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Minimize ultra-processed foods, sugars and alcohol. Foods high in phytonutrients, such as berries, cruciferous vegetables, turmeric and green tea also may be protective.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Avoiding alcohol and maintaining a healthy weight are also two factors to consider when trying to cut your familial cancer risk, Dr Messier said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above is a map from the Environmental Protection Agency. It shows radon levels across the country, which reveal 25% of Americans live in areas where levels are considered unsafe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-large health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Avoid toxins&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Messier told the Mail that even if you have never smoked, a close family member who was a smoker and was eventually diagnosed with lung cancer could still put you at risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lung cancer is estimated to affect about 227,000 people in 2025, with 124,000 deaths. People exposed to secondhand smoke have a 20 to 30 percent increased risk of lung cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Both doctors advise quitting smoking, avoiding secondhand smoke and steering clear of all tobacco products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They also urge people to avoid other toxins - particularly radon. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Messier and Dr McFadden recommend testing your home for radon, a radioactive gas that has no color, smell or taste. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The gas - which comes from the natural decay of uranium, a radioactive element found in nearly all soils - is present in both indoor and outdoor air and there is no known safe level of exposure to the substance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Studies show &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/sciencetech/article-14305279/map-radioactive-gas-hotspots-linked-cancer.html"&gt;radon exposure is the second most common cause of lung cancer&lt;/a&gt; in the US after smoking, leading to about 21,000 deaths each year, according to the EPA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Angelina Jolie (pictured) had her breasts, ovaries and fallopian tubes removed after testing positive for a gene that increases breast and ovarian cancer risk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Bailey Hutchins of Tennessee, died of colon cancer at 26 years old&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-large health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Genetic testing &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Charles Oyesile, a medical research physician, told the Daily Mail people with a family history of cancer should consult with an oncologist and genetics counselor to assess their individualized risk given their family history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Testing can help determine the best course of action - whether that is undergoing genetic testing to see if you are a carrier of any cancer-related genes, or starting cancer screenings at an earlier age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While genetic tests won't prevent cancer, they can tell you if you are at a heightened risk, which could help you make certain life choices - such as exercising more, quitting smoking, following a cleaner diet or undergoing certain preventative procedures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In addition to the BRCA genes, a blood test can identify genetic variants in the APC gene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This tumor suppressor gene is crucial for preventing the development of colon cancer. Mutations in the APC gene can lead to familial adenomatous polyposis, an inheritable condition that causes polyps in the colon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This, in turn, raises the risk of colon cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr McFadden said, 'In some cases, a genetic test can tell us which screenings you actually need and when. Don’t guess - ask your doctor. We’d much rather have that conversation now than after something shows up later.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-large health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Prophylactic surgery&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Having prophylactic surgery to remove organs that increase your risk of cancer is one way to fend off a familial pattern of disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For example, if genetic testing shows you carry the BRCA1 or BRCA2 gene, you may opt for a prophylactic double mastectomy (removal of the breasts) or oophorectomy (removal of the ovaries) - procedures Angelina Jolie had when she found out she was a carrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Jolie underwent genetic testing because her mother battled cancer for nearly a decade and died at 56. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When she tested positive for the BRCA1 gene, doctors estimated Jolie had an 87 percent risk of breast cancer and a 50 percent risk of ovarian cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She chose to have both breasts removed and get implants in 2013. Her chances of developing breast cancer dropped to 5 percent, she &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2013/05/14/opinion/my-medical-choice.html"&gt;wrote &lt;/a&gt;in a piece for The New York Times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Two years later, she had her ovaries and fallopian tubes removed to prevent ovarian cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other types of preventive surgeries include a colectomy - where part or all of the colon is removed to prevent colorectal cancer.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-large health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Preventative screenings &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Screenings also won't prevent cancer, but they can help detect the disease in earlier stages - and an early-stage diagnosis means the cancer may be easier to treat and could have a higher survival rate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If your grandmother, mother or sister was diagnosed with breast cancer, Dr Messier suggests talking to your doctor about beginning screenings like mammograms earlier than the generally recommended starting age of 40 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr McFadden said a colonoscopy to screen for colon cancer may be warranted earlier than recommended - typically 45 years old - if a sibling was diagnosed with the cancer before the age of 50.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'That's where personalized screening plans come in,' he said, 'and they can make a big difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'[Screenings are] not one-size-fits-all. If it’s colon cancer, you might start colonoscopy earlier. If it’s breast or prostate cancer, we might begin mammograms or PSA testing sooner.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 02:37:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNQmFzX0VXa1NlYU45VFRoeG9TYUZralpXMjVHUHdzdG9PMnZDaDlZMFBOV3BCZHQzZ2o3V1VtSlE0OXlhMjVxc2w1ZkdveVZvVUJERGFJbnVjdlRoT0Y4ZDAyNlByYjk4eTNGWjZTVWZiUUxrX3JvMVBWanZlWmRNS0VNZHV5dXg0aDZlUkVzcEFSVGlWSU0zTHUwX0c0ajJ0aHVwSTA1bEFKd9IBrwFBVV95cUxQXzdrallfV2hLcGlkeFVmNE9FMlYxRVpqSTlQeGpJVzhGbm0xdERTQkdCYWphbG1PelpSTG44VTY5VHR4eEowSkNEUVY2eEJTY2U4Z1N5MEhpQks2d0laMEFLSThoME5jZ1NXMDk5aVRESF9BVnM1akp4dU9EUXRobTBWT09fOC1TMDZabnhXX3hkQXI2U3I0RXAxRGhub1BjNjBNQkpFNWNYVGN0NE9z</guid></item><item><title>卫生官员确认大县首例麻疹病例- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51371310/health-officials-confirm-first-measles-case-in-grand-county</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;MOAB — Health officials on Saturday reported the first case of measles in Grand County.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Southeast Utah Health Department confirmed an unvaccinated individual under the age of 18 was diagnosed after being exposed outside the county, according to a press release from the department. It said no &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public health officials are actively conducting contact tracing to notify those who may have been exposed to the individual. The health department said there were no exposures in Grand County schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials are asking anyone who experiences the following symptoms of measles (which normally appear after 7-14 days), especially those who are unvaccinated or were exposed to a known case, to contact their health care provider:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;High fever&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cough&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Runny nose&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Red, watery eyes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A rash that starts on the face and spreads downward&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best way to prevent the illness is receiving the measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) vaccine, which is "safe and highly effective, providing lifelong protection for most individuals," the release said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last month, two school-aged children in Washington County tested positive for measles, according to the Southwest Utah Public Health Department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The children's schools were notified of potential exposure and all unvaccinated children and adults who believe they had been exposed to the disease were encouraged to stay home for 21 days after exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 02:29:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPbXNuUDVHb3VSM1ZySTBPMTR6LURUTHZfOGw5Y1B4UDdQTElkbUhsTEJqWU54QXZ1anl1WUxaY0lHOWEyLTVsaER1NXBjV2VHMWZGdUNQSzZCMWp3S1FxZEtOTE1CRjdaMGl0OWhGcnNKeDNDQWI5YVhWNjNXNUpnUzdXT29kVmlpSjJRa0hnbHVZdGlZQ3JSMnZDbHo</guid></item><item><title>致命的“接吻虫”蔓延到美国各地；哪些州受到影响，以及如何保护自己免受南美锥虫病的侵害？ -印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/deadly-kissing-bugs-spreading-across-us-which-states-are-affected-and-how-to-protect-yourself-from-chagas-disease/articleshow/123742147.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heads up, the bugs are here!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s a tiny but mighty threat silently crawling into our lives: the kissing bugs. These blood-sucking insects are spreading across the United States of America, and carrying a sneaky parasite called Trypanosoma cruzi, the culprit behind Chagas disease. Often overlooked, this disease can lead to serious cardiac and intestinal troubles down the line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC now reports kissing bugs in 32 states, and human cases have popped up in several, including California and Texas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Kissing bugs and Chagas: What’s going on?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chagas disease, also known as American trypanosomiasis, is caused by the parasite T. cruzi, typically transmitted when an infected kissing bug bites and then defecates near the entrance site. If you accidentally rub feces into the bite, eyes, or mouth, the parasite can sneak in. Symptoms in the early (acute) stage are often mild or unnoticeable; think fever, fatigue, headache, or eyelid swelling (the hallmark “Romaña’s sign”). But many cases go undiagnosed until the chronic phase, years later, when a frightening 20–30% can develop serious heart problems like heart failure or arrhythmias, or digestive issues. Antiparasitic treatments exist, but they’re most effective early on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Which US states are affected?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kissing bugs (scientists call them triatomine insects) have now been reported across 32 states, with human cases confirmed in eight, including California, Texas, Arizona, Louisiana, Missouri, Mississippi, Arkansas, and Tennessee. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In California, most sightings happen in the Sierra Nevada foothills, Los Angeles, and San Diego deserts, where wild mammals (opossums, raccoons, rats) thrive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Key pointers:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;32 states have documented kissing bugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human infections confirmed in at least eight states: California, Texas, Arizona, Louisiana, Tennessee, Missouri, Mississippi, and Arkansas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;California: Especially bugs in Southern California are carrying T. cruzi, with infections noted in Los Angeles and San Diego counties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Texas: The state has become a hotspot, with 50 locally acquired human cases (2013-2023), dogs in certain kennels showing up to 31% infection rates, and kissing bugs testing positive in 30-50% of samples.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Southern states in general: Due to abundant wildlife and suitable ecological conditions, these states are seeing more kissing bug activity. Wildlife like raccoons, opossums, armadillos, and others help sustain the parasite cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How does Chagas disease spread?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A kissing bug bites, often around the face, and then drops infected feces near the wound. If you scratch or touch it, the dangerous parasite Trypanosoma cruzi enters your body. It can also spread via contaminated blood, organ transplants, or mother-to-baby transmission. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Symptoms to watch out for&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Chagas has two phases:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Acute phase:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Often mild or unnoticed. Could include fever, fatigue, headache, vomiting, or eyelid swelling. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Chronic phase:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; May take decades to develop. Serious heart trouble (like heart failure or arrhythmias), enlarged digestive organs, and nerve issues. Drug treatments work only in the early stages. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What can you do to protect yourself?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Identify the culprit:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Kissing bugs are flat, dark brown or black, often with red, orange, or yellow stripes or solid lighter shades around their edges. They have a pointed, cone-shaped head and long, thin legs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Fortify your home:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Seal cracks and crevices around doors, windows, and walls. Install sturdy screens and keep outdoor lighting to a minimum at night. Keep pet sleeping areas clean; bugs often get in via dirty or pet-filled spaces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Handle bugs safely:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Never touch kissing bugs with your bare hands. Instead, trap them carefully using gloves and a container, and then contact local health or pest control authorities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Monitor symptoms and get tested:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; If you experience unexplained fever, fatigue, swollen eyelids, or other unusual signs, especially if bitten by a bug, see a doctor and ask about Chagas. Blood tests can confirm infection; early antiparasitic treatment (like benznidazole or nifurtimox) can clear the parasite if caught early.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Protect pets and loved ones:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Pregnant women or those receiving blood transfusions should be extra cautious, as Chagas disease can be transmitted congenitally or through contaminated blood/organs. Additionally, dogs are common victims, especially in kennels, and can even become reservoirs, passing the parasite back into the bug population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="78"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Coronavirus outbreak: How to protect yourself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="80"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="81"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 01:50:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAJBVV95cUxQSXQtZS1sbk9UX29qZm43WDlRV3RybU5QWGRvTTk2X0U4N3lWcTlMSVNTZnExOEVYbjNBaGZ5MnpHMlhHT0ZkOHh2Zl9ld2xpcVhQNTBVZUR6Z2V4RFZVSGkwaEtVTmR6bUJxM2pfdlN2ZnNSWXI3b2FpYm0wdUNzeHRSUU45M2lSOE1oM3ZLOS1JZGZfMDlzSTlCMnpJVlFVWWxFV1ZhSXlpdXRsc0Q2YWo3RmhabXJoMnhaOVNVT0JLbjVjMHlYMU1Tb1UyOHJZUmtKdURZNWJidERvdlJpOWF0YlRrSzBueEgtTV81Z3RrNGxScHpHNmhPWjBhS09ZUnFaSnZvVlZnWGNJS2N1b3E2S2hTbUNVZzhqMkR1bWhnbVh3ZjE2c3RHdzYyX29LX3REZFViUG4</guid></item><item><title>含糖饮料改变肠道DNA ，但Technion研究发现效果可以逆转-研究-耶路撒冷邮报</title><link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/nutrition/article-866545</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="menu-title" role="button" aria-expanded="false" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;p&gt;JERUSALEM POST EN ESPANOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="arrow "&gt;&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" fill="none" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;path stroke="#CB133E" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round" stroke-width="1.7" d="m5.335 13.333 5.333-5.334-5.333-5.333"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Jerusalem Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 00:23:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTE5SS0U2MjVqUUhQaVEzR3Fhb3lnZTFhaVRpWElXRDBVSlFXajVKR0VVTTJEanlPVHZHaHlUWXdDdlVvc2lIVi1VQVdsM2pKNVdtSElTYzE3aXVOdTN5UGVYekxCZDI3R3gzVGVNODhwZ21haE1L</guid></item><item><title>卡通：骨刺科- Daily Kos</title><link>https://www.dailykos.com/stories/2025/9/6/2341987/-Cartoon-Department-of-bone-spurs</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story__details"&gt;
      
      
      &lt;p class="story__timestamp"&gt;
                  &lt;span class="timestamp story__date--short" data-localize-time data-epoch-time="1757199302000" data-time-zone="-0700" data-time-format="%A, %b. %d, %Y"&gt;Saturday, Sep. 06, 2025&lt;/span&gt;
          &lt;span class="timestamp story__date--long" data-localize-time data-epoch-time="1757199302000" data-time-zone="-0700" data-time-format="%A, %B %d, %Y"&gt;Saturday, Sep. 06, 2025&lt;/span&gt;
          at &lt;span class="timestamp" data-localize-time data-epoch-time="1757199302000" data-time-zone="-0700" data-time-format="%l:%M:%S%P %Z"&gt; 3:55:02pm PDT&lt;/span&gt;

      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p id="react-story-stats"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Kos</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 00:16:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxOMWtJa1o2V1lYZV9ERVZUN2FyNnBKdnc3bjBjVmxnNW11LU5ENjA1N3ZoLU9icUgxcFN1NjhuT1ladHZrMjhsVkxmQmNVeHhubUJUNDVkdXdQQWJaOHBSc3o4Y0Y5Z3Q3WGlNc2I2WVlqaHZiT1JsSWNWUFhpWW1vZWZOMEFMbXFteUdR</guid></item><item><title>旅行者在注意到“反乌托邦”趋势接管公共海滩后感到沮丧： “这太过分了” - yahoo.com</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/traveler-frustrated-taking-notice-dystopian-001000947.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A Redditor's day at the beach became a little less relaxing after spotting an ad flying over the water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Anticonsumption/comments/1mg7q2u/saw_someone_complaining_about_boat_ads_at_the/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:A photo;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;A photo&lt;/a&gt; of the banner, seen flying above Ocean City, Maryland, was shared on Reddit's &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Anticonsumption/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:r/Anticonsumption;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;r/Anticonsumption&lt;/a&gt; subreddit, where readers decried advertising's reach into seemingly all aspects of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Credit: Reddit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Saw someone complaining about boat ads at the beach," the OP wrote. "May I introduce you to sky ads?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Although the site was viewed by some commenters as "&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Anticonsumption/comments/1mg7q2u/comment/n6mq4he/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web3x&amp;amp;utm_name=web3xcss&amp;amp;utm_term=1&amp;amp;utm_content=share_button" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dystopian;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;dystopian&lt;/a&gt;," a number of social media posts have shown that advertising is now actually a regular occurrence at beaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Posts on Reddit and TikTok sparked outrage by showing a digital billboard moving across the water on a boat the size of a barge. Another Reddit post showed a similar digital billboard being towed across the water, also just off the Florida coast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It's not just beaches, either. Whether you're stuck in traffic, pumping gas, or just going to school, you could now potentially be inundated with advertising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Last year, money spent on advertising in the United States increased 5.6% over 2023 to an estimated &lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bethannkaminkow/2024/04/21/as-ad-spend-rises-marketing-budgets-switch-to-commerce/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:$360 billion;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;$360 billion&lt;/a&gt; — and that doesn't even include political advertising. All that comes with a high cost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Advertising pushes an overall culture of consumerism, where people strive to get the best and latest products. Companies, in turn, create more and more products to sell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://normative.io/insight/reduce-manufacturer-carbon-emissions/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:manufacturing and production sector;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;manufacturing and production sector&lt;/a&gt; is responsible for roughly 20% of global carbon pollution, and more than half of the world's energy usage. It also contributes greatly to the trillions of pieces of plastic that pollute our planet and waterways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Purpose Disruptors, a London-based organization dedicated to advertising, created a metric called "&lt;a href="https://www.purposedisruptors.org/advertised-emissions" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:advertised emissions;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;advertised emissions&lt;/a&gt;", which measures the carbon pollution that results from increased sales due to advertising. In 2022, its research found, the United Kingdom generated nearly 230 million tons of "advertised emissions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Not surprisingly, consumerism isn't favored by many &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Anticonsumption/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:r/Anticonsumption;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;r/Anticonsumption&lt;/a&gt; posters, and this beach billboard drew considerable ire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"I've heard of carrier pigeons," &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Anticonsumption/comments/1mg7q2u/comment/n6p1zx7/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web3x&amp;amp;utm_name=web3xcss&amp;amp;utm_term=1&amp;amp;utm_content=share_button" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:one commenter wrote;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;one commenter wrote&lt;/a&gt;, "but this is too much."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/future-newsletter/?recW3q8XDvUSYnLYh" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;good news&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;useful tips&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>yahoo.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 00:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxOQ01YT1hETGwyOFF2dlIydi03eTIwem1uTmFabFlQaDRubHViZ0J1bHV3MGs5aG45c3U0ZXBDM1NrZDBPWExUUS1LS0pIeThocVJ0eGdoSFVhNkJIeDdfMDJuVndjQy13NFBnN3d0NW80XzZOT3F2Vlh1N1hYWW5ZMkoydHo1Q2J0aDNBRDJ1UnBIT25mc0YwT1F3</guid></item><item><title>NI HEALTH ： Ballynahinch MAN希望更广泛地获得新的MND药物- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/ckgejpg45xxo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 dfvxux"&gt;My time is precious - new MND drug could give me more with my family&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gyQxwn"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250828-055926-c20c0c03f5-2.28.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/092f/live/72ff2e90-8a48-11f0-94f4-77b666520245.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/092f/live/72ff2e90-8a48-11f0-94f4-77b666520245.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/092f/live/72ff2e90-8a48-11f0-94f4-77b666520245.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/092f/live/72ff2e90-8a48-11f0-94f4-77b666520245.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/092f/live/72ff2e90-8a48-11f0-94f4-77b666520245.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/092f/live/72ff2e90-8a48-11f0-94f4-77b666520245.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/092f/live/72ff2e90-8a48-11f0-94f4-77b666520245.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/092f/live/72ff2e90-8a48-11f0-94f4-77b666520245.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC Conaire Quinn in his garden, he is wearing a green t-shirt and is smiling at the camera. He has short brown hair that's greying on the side and has a brown beard. " class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;BBC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Conaire Quinn wants as many people has possible to have access to a ground-breaking drug &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A Ballynahinch man hopes a new treatment for a rare form of Motor Neurone Disease (MND) can give him more quality time with his family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Conaire Quinn, 38, who has a nine-year-old daughter Autumn, said time is not on his side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Mr Quinn wants the ground-breaking drug, Tofersen, made freely available to as many people as possible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He received his first treatment through a lumbar puncture procedure at Altnagelvin Hospital in mid-August.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250828-055926-c20c0c03f5-2.28.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/c922/live/734bdc60-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/c922/live/734bdc60-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c922/live/734bdc60-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/c922/live/734bdc60-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/c922/live/734bdc60-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/c922/live/734bdc60-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/c922/live/734bdc60-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c922/live/734bdc60-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Conaire Quinn Conaire Quinn with his daughter Autumn. Conaire is sitting on her lap at a seating area. Autumn has short brown hair and is wearing a blue print dress. Conaire is wearing a hawaiian t-shirt. He has short brown hair and a beard and is wearing a baseball cap (on backwards) and a floral garland around his neck. " class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Conaire Quinn&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Conaire Quinn, pictured here with his daughter Autumn&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Mr Quinn first noticed something was wrong "around Covid time when I felt my foot dropping". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He said when he was walking he was stumbling slightly and after the pandemic he could not get upstairs and suffered with abdominal pains and cramps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The final straw that made Mr Quinn visit the doctor was when he was at a Manchester United match and had to be pulled up from the terrace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"They said straight away that this was a neurological thing," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"I came out thinking it was a sports injury but I ended up having a crutch and I've had it ever since."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Mr Quinn said he had a family history of MND on his mother's side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"It sounds silly but I was wanting the diagnosis because it was getting played down. It was making me feel like it wasn't what it was," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Dr Gavin McCloskey says it's an exciting time to see new treatments being opened up for people&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Tofersen has the ability to slow or halt symptoms for those with a rare form of MND, which is caused by a variation in the SOD1 gene. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Altnagelvin Hospital consultant, Gavin McCloskey, said there are about 50 new cases of MND in Northern Ireland every year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Access to the drug will only apply to one person every one to two years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"This is the first new treatment that's been available for MND for 30 years," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"It's a new class of treatment that works to act on reducing the effect of the abnormal gene which then, hopefully, would reduce the damage that's done to nerves and slow down the rate of progression. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"So it's a very exciting time with this new avenue of treatments being opened up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Dr McCloskey believes it "changes the narrative" in the story of MND, with new treatments which "can affect the disease progression and lead to a reduction in new symptoms".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 eOFjmw"&gt;'Breakthrough' treatment &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Mr Quinn said he hopes it will prolong his independence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He said he's felt dramatic differences with regard to his fingers, hands, arm strength and leg strength. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"This (new treatment) will help me have time with my family and my daughter because I'll want to go on holidays and go to the park whereas if it keeps progressing quickly it'll make me unable to do those things," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Mr Quinn said the new drug is a "breakthrough" not only for him but also possibly his family and others. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"If I'm trailblazing it and getting the treatment, they'll know what is to come and how they can get the treatment and get access to it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250828-055926-c20c0c03f5-2.28.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/eb24/live/a5a34810-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/eb24/live/a5a34810-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/eb24/live/a5a34810-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/eb24/live/a5a34810-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/eb24/live/a5a34810-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/eb24/live/a5a34810-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/eb24/live/a5a34810-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/eb24/live/a5a34810-8b63-11f0-88ed-05f699bf7f27.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Conaire Quinn Conaire is on a red disability scooter wearing a white t-shirt and Hawaiian shirt over it and his daughter Autumn, wearing a black dress is standing beside him. " class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Conaire Quinn&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Conaire has had to use a crutch and mobility devices since his diagnosis &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 eOFjmw"&gt;'You don't get time back'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The MND Association is currently leading a UK-wide campaign to make Tofersen more readily available and to ensure there are enough specialist staff to administer it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;During the summer, the charity unveiled a melting ice sculpture in Parliament Square, London, of a person with motor neurone disease to symbolise the condition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A petition with 21,000 signatures was given to MP Karin Smyth, a health minister, calling on the government to urgently provide the drug to those who need it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The MND Association said more than 30 patients were currently taking Tofersen through an early access programme, which is being offered free by its developer Biogen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;However, the charity said about 20 patients cannot receive the drug because there is no local service able to administer it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;For Mr Quinn, it is all about access to the new treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"Time is very precious. And over the last couple of years that's the most important message. You don't get time back."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The Department of Health (DoH) said Toferson is not currently commissioned in the UK but it is being appraised by NICE (the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The department said while it was not yet clear when NICE will publish a decision, typically treatments recommended for routine use in England are also available in Northern Ireland and that the department will seek to "make the treatment available" if so. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;It added that when a request for treatment falls out of this arrangement, it will "consider requests from trusts to fund treatment on an individual patient basis".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 23:00:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE4yZUdxMXZQUk1lRmdlMU1CYWJGUjVSSmNqeXhWa2Y1ZmprYUJiMVlVZFVRc3MwUGhyR09QSjVuSDZ2eFlCTVcxeTBzUEJqTC1RdmowMkJ1cXVzUdIBX0FVX3lxTFBLako0YmdjQjdqck8tQVZteUFXMEtRaHVrUXNYOWs4OGVpQmJCTnBldmRTWmQ2ZHo2aTE4RFF5bG94ZWlpM0M1TEdvcEhBVjAyVXJHYmdQLVVYdjZNMlFZ</guid></item><item><title>县官员称，在威克县高中发现活跃的肺结核病例- WRAL.com</title><link>https://www.wral.com/news/local/active-tuberculosis-wake-county-high-school-sept-2025/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;
					
						&lt;p&gt;An active case of tuberculosis was found at a Wake County high school, just several weeks into the new schoolyear, according to a Wake County spokesperson.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Wake County, in an email, told WRAL that they were notified that a person with active tuberculosis was present at Leesville High School sometime last week. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
								&lt;p class="exco-player" feature="vendor.exco.player" id="d8af3f9c-ad37-4890-8ed5-bb0ce702acdf"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;The county is working with the Wake County Public School System to identify anyone who may have been in close contact with the person. Those people will be contacted directly with instructions for tuberculosis testing. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;We are working to find out how many people might have been affected by this case. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Tuberculosis (TB) is a serious disease that affects the lungs or other parts of the body, such as the brain, kidneys or spine. It is spread through the air when someone with TB coughs, sneezes, sings or speaks, according to county's website. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;TB is not spread by shaking hands, kissing, sharing glasses, plates, utensils, clothing, sheets or furniture. While TB can be spread when someone coughs or sneezes, it cannot be spread throughout the air outside. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;TB symptoms may include: &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
								&lt;p class="opscoad-Mobile_In_Content" data-unit="wral-v4/news/local/active-tuberculosis-wake-county-high-school-sept-2025"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;p class="opscoad-article_in_read" data-unit="wral-v4/news/local/active-tuberculosis-wake-county-high-school-sept-2025/"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							
							
						
					
						&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;a bad cough that lasts three weeks or longer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;pain in the chest&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;coughing up blood, spit&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;weakness or fatigue&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;weight loss, no appetite&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;chills, fever, sweating at night&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;More information on tuberculosis can be found &lt;a href="https://www.wake.gov/departments-government/health-human-services/public-health-and-medical-services/communicable-diseases-and-pests/tuberculosis"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;h2&gt;Related coverage&lt;/h2&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wral.com/lifestyle/health/tuberculosis-rise-nc-2025/"&gt;Tuberculosis cases on the rise in NC after more than 30 years of decline&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
					
				&lt;/div&gt;

        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WRAL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 22:25:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxQUWtqOFlsdzBKQVFocjhlc0p6NzJ4QTlZdVIxVzg2NWFYbGYtOUhHaUtUQVVIU2Q5VUxnMzFKMW1XZzhSOVVoZTlVcWxTbWdNOXo4SDkzRjh3RjZRaExVNTB4cXBzN1BDLW13cERCdmdZSXdmTGc4R2RGanBqOW9JY2JjbWxQTEYxMUliS1pvYw</guid></item><item><title>改革本身与在会议上提出新冠肺炎索赔的医生的距离- bbc.com</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c62z4rd87nlo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Reform UK has distanced itself from a conference speaker who suggested that Covid vaccines were linked to the King's and the Princess of Wales' cancers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Aseem Malholtra, an adviser to US health secretary Robert F Kennedy Jr, said: "One of Britain's most eminent oncologists Professor Angus Dalgleish said to me to share with you today that he thinks it's highly likely that the Covid vaccines have been a significant factor in the cancers in the royal family."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Wes Streeting, the health secretary, said that it was "shockingly irresponsible" of Reform to allow Dr Malholtra at the conference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The party said that it "does not endorse what he said but does believe in free speech".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;In his speech in Birmingham, at an event titled "Make Britain Healthy Again", Dr Malholtra also claimed that studies show that mRNA vaccines could alter genes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Dr Malhotra, a cardiologist, also said taking the Covid vaccine was more likely to cause harm than the virus itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"It is highly likely that not a single person should have been injected with this," he added, before going on to say that the World Health Organization had been "captured" by Microsoft founder Bill Gates and urged for it to be replaced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He hit out at health minister Stephen Kinnock, who called Dr Malhotra an "anti-vax conspiracy theorist".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;On the stage, he asked the audience: "Have you heard anything anti-vax or conspiracy theory so far here?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Dr Malholtra's views have been discredited by many medical professionals and are not supported by scientific evidence, and the NHS says that Covid vaccines meet all strict safety standards. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The link between the Covid jab and cancer has previously been dismissed by academics and oncologists after claims it had led to "turbo cancers".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Professor Brian Ferguson, professor of viral immunology at the University of Cambridge, accused Dr Malholtra of repeating an "outlandish conspiracy theory only serves to undermine the credibility of those spreading it".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He continued: "There is no credible evidence that these vaccines disrupt tumour suppressors or drive any kind of process that results in cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"It is particularly crass to try to link this pseudoscience to the unfortunate incidents of cancer in the royal family."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The King's cancer diagnosis was first announced in February 2024. The palace has said he is receiving treatment, but has not said what type of cancer he has.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Catherine announced her diagnosis in March 2024, and &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cx2m8g2vp41o" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;went into remission&lt;/a&gt; in January. She, too, did not specify the type of cancer she had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Streeting warned that "we are seeing falling numbers of parents getting their children vaccinated, and a resurgence of disease we had previously eradicated". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"It is shockingly irresponsible for Nigel Farage to give a platform to these poisonous lies. Farage should apologise and sever all ties with this dangerous extremism."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A Reform UK spokesman told the BBC: "Dr Aseem Malhotra is a guest speaker with his own opinions who has an advisory role in the US government. Reform UK does not endorse what he said but does believe in free speech."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>bbc.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 21:34:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBkUHJvTERTaElmbUZSSkl6T3RoN1RmOTI4LU5rcHNPdm9QWVBDLU8tSHNrM3Y4TGg5d1I3aWozMFh1bDYzb0t4TjVJZHJoaUhIMkJfU1hHOEVuZ9IBX0FVX3lxTFBOdVBlak9XdDFrd1hKUXJFUERjWGgzYVJ2VGlndlNSMzFyRE11S1dELUpVajNpYmhxNXpGd0JWNnFoRGxGN1lRbW4xaVhsZFVKQ2R6WEhHeEpURXQzckxJ</guid></item><item><title>马里兰州在流感季节临近时保护疫苗的获取- WTOP</title><link>https://wtop.com/maryland/2025/09/maryland-to-protect-access-to-vaccines-with-flu-season-approaching/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="schema-summary"&gt;In the midst of states thinking about removing vaccine mandates, Maryland will protect access to vaccines for all of its residents with flu season approaching.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;div id="Entry-content" class="entry-content Entry-content "&gt;
                                                
                                
                &lt;p&gt;With some states thinking about removing vaccine mandates, Maryland will protect access to vaccines for all of its residents with flu season approaching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maryland residents can go to their providers and pharmacies to get their vaccinations, and get advice on what types of vaccines to get to protect themselves from viruses and illnesses.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The CDC recommends to those 6 years and older to get the flu shot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This comes in the midst of the &lt;a href="https://wtop.com/health-fitness/2025/08/fda-approves-updated-pfizer-covid-shots-but-limits-access-for-some-kids-and-adults/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Food and Drug Administration approving updated COVID-19 shots&lt;/a&gt; from Pfizer, Moderna and Novavax, which is limited for some kids and adults with one high-risk health condition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The federal government’s rapid changes and unnecessary swirl around vaccine policy is harmful for Marylanders and all Americans, and could result in disastrous public health outcomes,” Maryland Gov. Wes Moore said &lt;a href="https://governor.maryland.gov/news/press/pages/Maryland-Protects-Access-to-Vaccines-for-All-Marylanders.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;in a release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moore added that the state is prepared to deal with the challenges of federal vaccine guidance with U.S. Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. trying to advance anti-vaccine policies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He signed a law in 2024 that would allow pharmacists to give those 3 years and over COVID-19 and flu vaccine without a prescription, a release said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The health, safety and well-being of Marylanders and their loved ones are our North Star, and we will do everything in our power to ensure they have access to life-saving medicines like vaccines,” Moore said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts is following Maryland’s playbook in protecting &lt;a href="https://wtop.com/national/2025/09/states-move-to-protect-vaccines-in-the-face-of-attempts-to-remove-mandates/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;vaccine access for its residents&lt;/a&gt;, despite Florida being on the verge of being the &lt;a href="https://wtop.com/national/2025/09/florida-will-work-to-eliminate-all-childhood-vaccine-mandates-in-the-state-officials-say/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;first state to to get rid of school vaccine mandates&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About 8 in 10 U.S. adults said kids should be vaccinated to go to school, &lt;a href="https://wtop.com/national/2025/09/what-polls-show-about-americans-views-on-childhood-vaccine-mandates/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;according to a Harvard/SSRS poll&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Vaccines continue to be one of the most powerful public health tools for safeguarding our people and communities against disease,” Maryland Department of Health Secretary Dr. Meena Seshamani said.&lt;/p&gt;
                
                
                &lt;p class="After-content"&gt;
                                    &lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;p class="single-page__signature bottom"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Get breaking news and daily headlines delivered to your email inbox by signing up &lt;a href="https://wtop.com/newsletter-signup/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="single-page__signature bottom"&gt;© 2025 WTOP. All Rights Reserved. This website is not intended for users located within the European Economic Area.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WTOP</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 21:33:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPNDc4aDY4emdzWGZZYmc2OUd5ZTZuTnVWd193aVpWOE1laVJkN2lnR0tJUi01eTRNWFNQRG5MeXBfVS1nLURLby1kV3JwM3Q1T21hVFd1OFJkTUZ2Rk9fdDNOVzRSSU1wQThYWEh2OTA1VWFLUnZMcFNJYnNwTVBYeUtwNkxUR2tmaTR4T1FSZHJJMUN1TFdUaFYyMUl5UXhyR3RN</guid></item><item><title>纳洛酮在丹佛健康展关于药物使用的展览中拯救生命- Denver7</title><link>https://www.denver7.com/news/front-range/denver/naloxone-saves-life-at-denver-health-exhibit-about-substance-use</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="RichTextArticleBody-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;DENVER — The opioid crisis continues to devastate communities of color.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new Denver Health study shows Black, Hispanic and Asian adults are far less likely to use naloxone, the medication that can reverse an opioid overdose. Experts say the problem is related to a lack of access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That reality was never clearer than Thursday at the Denver Public Library, where &lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.denver7.com/news/local-news/new-denver-health-exhibit-aims-to-break-addiction-stigma-during-national-recovery-month" target="_blank"&gt;an exhibit aimed at breaking substance use stigma&lt;/a&gt; became the setting for a life-saving rescue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One of the customers of the library came and was talking to some of our staff, and then sat down in the library and fell asleep, but we heard some snoring, and people were checking in on him,” said Brooke Bender, administrative director at Denver Health’s Center for Addiction Medicine. “Eventually, we didn't hear anything else, and the library social worker had stopped by to check on him. They seemed to have known him, that he was a regular visitor of the library.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the man became unresponsive, Bender and peer-support specialists acted quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“She couldn't get him to respond, and so we jumped into action, and we had the naloxone there at the table as part of our booth, and grabbed that and were able to bring him back,” Bender said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From there, library staff called 911, and Denver Health paramedics rushed the man to the emergency department, where he survived.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It saved his life. It was a surprising event that we didn't expect to happen when we were there, sharing pictures and stories of people in recovery,” Bender said. “But it was a powerful reminder that what we're doing really matters, and that this can happen anywhere at any time, and that all of us can be responsible for saving a life if we have naloxone at our fingertips.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Bender, the lesson is simple: “Having naloxone with you, even if you don't use substances yourself, gives you the opportunity to support someone else who might need that help. There should be no stigma about taking naloxone whenever you have the opportunity, so that you can carry it and save a life if you need to, right?”&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;How naloxone works and why community access matters&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naloxone is simple to use and does not require medical training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You do not need to be a medical professional to use this,” Bender said. “Many of the people that we've talked to in the community this week, when we were sharing our 'Stories in Black and White' exhibit, said that they've saved several of their friends and family's lives.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using naloxone is very straightforward. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The Naloxone comes in an easy-to-open package. If you just tear off the packaging, there's no cover for the nasal spray. I just took the nasal spray and took it to the person's nose when they're lying down, and put it in one of their nostrils and squeezed,” she explained. “We wait for two to three minutes to see if that's taken effect, if there's any response, if the heart's beating, and check for signs of stability, and if there are none, then you take another dose and put it in the other nostril and spray.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="rte2-style-ul"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Denver Health created a video demonstrating how to administer naloxone. You can watch it in the video player below&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="HtmlModule"&gt;
    &lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TDQ4cbItN3s?si=wujx880sqRuAoyTo" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Bender, expired naloxone can still work and should not be discarded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Expired naloxone can still work and should be used. We should not be throwing away expired naloxone that can still save someone's life.”&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breaking down barriers&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.healthaffairs.org/doi/10.1377/hlthaff.2025.00263" target="_blank"&gt;Research from Rocky Mountain Poison and Drug Safety&lt;/a&gt; highlights ongoing disparities in naloxone access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our study looked at the different steps it takes to go from someone becoming aware that naloxone is a thing, that it can help, to them having it on their person when it would be necessary,” said Dr. Joshua Black, senior statistical research scientist. “The main takeaway is that the disparity persists. Disparities have to be addressed all along that pathway in various ways that we can do that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black said cultural context is key to outreach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We cited some other research in our study showing that with Hispanic groups, just taking something that was written for English and translating it to Spanish isn't enough, because the way that things are said needs to be culturally meaningful to that group,” he said. “Engaging with individuals who are part of the community, who are peers, would enable whatever is developed to resonate more effectively with that community.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For many people, stigma remains a major obstacle, not only in seeking help but in carrying naloxone. Black argues for new distribution strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“So moving out of a healthcare out of a retail setting and having harm reduction present where people are, rather than having them come to where the medicine is, would be another way to get over the stigma," Black said. &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;A message of preparedness and hope&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Bender and Denver Health, the work goes well beyond emergencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It's important to just be prepared and to really know how to use it and be prepared to use it,” Bender said. “In a crisis, it can feel a little jarring, and so it's good to have some repetitive practice… all those steps over and over, just to have it fresh in your mind.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The value of peer support is also clear, especially for those experiencing these situations for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This just goes to show the value of people who have lived expertise and the role that they can play in helping folks that may not have experience with that know what to do in that situation,” Bender said. “We know these things are working, and we just need to expand access."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="RichTextModule"&gt;
    
        &lt;div class="RichTextModule-items"&gt;&lt;figure class="Figure" itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
    
        &lt;div class="Figure-container"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://ewscripps.brightspotcdn.com/dims4/default/f6f08cc/2147483647/strip/true/crop/1280x164+0+0/resize/1280x164!/quality/90/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fewscripps-brightspot.s3.amazonaws.com%2F89%2F1f%2F24a7fd4148bdbb43d0f3cf167766%2Fcolin-image-bar.jpg" alt="colin image bar.jpg" srcset="https://ewscripps.brightspotcdn.com/dims4/default/f6f08cc/2147483647/strip/true/crop/1280x164+0+0/resize/1280x164!/quality/90/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fewscripps-brightspot.s3.amazonaws.com%2F89%2F1f%2F24a7fd4148bdbb43d0f3cf167766%2Fcolin-image-bar.jpg 1x,https://ewscripps.brightspotcdn.com/dims4/default/23da2f3/2147483647/strip/true/crop/1280x164+0+0/resize/2560x328!/quality/90/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fewscripps-brightspot.s3.amazonaws.com%2F89%2F1f%2F24a7fd4148bdbb43d0f3cf167766%2Fcolin-image-bar.jpg 2x"&gt;&lt;p class="Figure-credit" itemprop="author"&gt;Denver7&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;div class="Form"&gt;&lt;p class="Form-title"&gt;Denver7 | Your Voice: Get in touch with Colin Riley&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class="Form-description"&gt;Denver7’s Colin Riley is a multimedia journalist who tells stories impacting all of Colorado’s communities, but specializes in reporting on transportation and our state’s senior population. If you’d like to get in touch with Colin, fill out the form below to send him an email.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
        
        
    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Denver7</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 21:16:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxPMm5oOFFkVkplZUluckZzMnBBVnhJc1hiM3NEOGlCaFh5dWRCMXp6T281Ym9GUW5BVmpQQTR3dWo0YUs2dEhaMUtBc0RIQVo3elc4M3IzamM3VFZUc0FJMmNKdVZ1NFB4WnlRLVFHcFpiQjRIMFZoYUtTbkJkNW1PQWt2bUQtZE1tblY4Z3RfNlJhNFBBdVFPOHpkdTdvYTBhNGNaM2U0VTdYNnJKaWJtQlBR</guid></item><item><title>在马桶上滚动手机会增加没有人愿意谈论的健康风险- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/scrolling-phone-toilet-raises-health-183203910.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study suggests that bringing your smartphone into the bathroom could raise your risk of hemorrhoids by nearly 50%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers at Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center (BIDMC) in Boston found that adults who use their phones while sitting on the toilet face a 46% higher risk of developing &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/digestive-health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:the painful condition,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;the painful condition,&lt;/a&gt; according to findings published this week in the journal PLOS One.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study surveyed 125 adults undergoing colonoscopies and compared their bathroom habits. Of the participants, 66% admitted to using their phones on the toilet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/how-avoid-getting-office-chair-butt-from-prolonged-sitting-work" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:How To Avoid Getting 'Office Chair Butt' From Prolonged Sitting At Work;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How To Avoid Getting 'Office Chair Butt' From Prolonged Sitting At Work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who said they took their phone into the bathroom were 46% more likely to have hemorrhoids compared to the others, regardless of age, weight, sex or fiber intake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hemorrhoids, swollen veins in or around the rectum and anus that can cause pain, itching and bleeding, are often linked to straining during bowel movements and prolonged sitting on the toilet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS/mvaj7wvj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read On The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Read On The Fox News App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;A new study surveyed 125 adults undergoing colonoscopies and compared their bathroom habits. Of the participants, 66% admitted to using their phones on the toilet.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;About 37% of participants who brought their phones into the bathroom sat for longer than five minutes, while only 7% of non-users lingered that long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Younger adults, particularly those in their 40s and 50s, were especially prone to the habit compared to those over 60. Respondents said they typically used their &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/tech/technologies/smartphones" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:phones to read news,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;phones to read news,&lt;/a&gt; scroll social media or send texts and emails.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/tech/5-smart-settings-make-your-phone-work-harder" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:5 Smart Settings To Make Your Phone Work Harder;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5 Smart Settings To Make Your Phone Work Harder&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Whether someone is reading email or playing a game, the risk likely comes from how long they’re sitting," said lead author Dr. Chethan Ramprasad, a gastroenterologist at Beth Israel Deaconess and faculty member at Harvard Medical School.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The risk remained even when researchers accounted for other factors, including straining, fiber intake and exercise routines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Researchers surveyed 125 adults undergoing colonoscopies at Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This extended duration may be linked to the passive engagement that smartphones facilitate, potentially resulting in prolonged sitting and increased pressure in the hemorrhoidal cushions," the researchers wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/colorectal-cancer-may-cause-hidden-warning-signs-experts-say" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Colorectal Cancer May Cause These 4 Hidden Warning Signs, Experts Say;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Colorectal Cancer May Cause These 4 Hidden Warning Signs, Experts Say&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toilets keep the rectum and pelvic floor unsupported compared to sitting in a chair, causing more pressure on rectal veins, &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/medical-research" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:according to the researchers.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;according to the researchers.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ramprasad noted that posture can also play a role and that toilet stools, which prop up the feet and put the body in a more natural squatting position to help eliminate straining, can help, but do not solve the underlying problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Sign Up For Our Health Newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Click Here To Sign Up For Our Health Newsletter&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Tools like a Squatty Potty can reduce straining, but they won’t offset the risk of just sitting too long," he said. "If you’re on your phone for 10 minutes, you’re still exposing those veins to pressure."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Adults who bring their phones into the bathroom face nearly a 50% higher risk of hemorrhoids, according to a new study.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hemorrhoids are among the most frequent gastrointestinal complaints in the United States, sending nearly 4 million people to &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:clinics and emergency rooms;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;clinics and emergency rooms&lt;/a&gt; each year, according to BIDMC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:For more Health articles, visit ;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;For more Health articles, visit &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foxnews.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:www.foxnews.com/health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;www.foxnews.com/health&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers called for long-term studies to confirm causality and explore prevention strategies. And while younger participants were more likely to use their phones and had higher hemorrhoid prevalence, they can't say yet if that is because of phone use specifically or other age-related behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, Ramprasad advises to keep things moving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Do what you need to do, then stand up and move on," he said. "Don’t turn the bathroom into a scrolling break."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Original article source:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/scrolling-toilet-may-raise-hemorrhoid-risk-nearly-50-new-study-finds" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Scrolling on your phone on the toilet raises health risk no one wants to talk about;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Scrolling on your phone on the toilet raises health risk no one wants to talk about&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 20:40:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE13aHp6MHdjNU9RWnRsRkd5Rnd1Q0ZIaVpEbUJMdW90eHFFVXVmMWkwZmtKeEZPOWtfX3p3NW5FTXVsU0VUYVNtVU1hWFJmNTlaVDcxSEpCdUJkSlRjY1N5ZkYyWlB6TnJVX05yam1XRU5MaWd3NV9TZnlfdw</guid></item><item><title>一种常见的补充剂可以逆转三氯蔗糖的隐藏危害- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250906013455.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Sucralose is a popular sugar substitute for people who are cutting calories or managing blood sugar levels, but new research by the University of Pittsburgh and UPMC Hillman Cancer Center suggests that the artificial sweetener may not be the best choice for patients undergoing cancer immunotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Publishing recently in &lt;em&gt;Cancer Discovery&lt;/em&gt;, a publication of the American Association for Cancer Research, the study found that patients with melanoma and non-small cell lung cancer who consumed high levels of sucralose had worse response to immunotherapy and poorer survival than those with diets low in the artificial sweetener.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strikingly, supplements that boosted levels of the amino acid arginine mitigated the negative effects of sucralose on immunotherapy in mice, an approach that could now be tested in clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It's easy to say, 'Stop drinking diet soda,' but when patients are being treated for cancer, they are already dealing with enough, so asking them to drastically alter their diet may not be realistic," said lead author Abby Overacre, Ph.D., assistant professor in the Department of Immunology at Pitt and UPMC Hillman. "We need to meet patients where they are. That's why it's so exciting that arginine supplementation could be a simple approach to counteract the negative effects of sucralose on immunotherapy."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Senior author Diwakar Davar, M.D., associate professor of medicine at Pitt and a medical oncologist and hematologist at UPMC Hillman, collaborating with Overacre and their team, used mouse models to show that the negative impacts of sucralose are driven by disruption to gut bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sucralose shifted the composition of the mouse gut microbiome, increasing bacterial species that degrade arginine, which reduced levels of this amino acid in the blood, tumor fluid and stool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Immune checkpoint inhibitor immunotherapies such as anti-PD1 work by ramping up T cell activity so that they can more effectively kill cancer cells. Arginine is essential for T cell function, especially in cancer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"When arginine levels were depleted due to sucralose-driven shifts in the microbiome, T cells couldn't function properly," said Overacre. "As a result, immunotherapy wasn't as effective in mice that were fed sucralose."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In mouse models of adenocarcinoma and melanoma, adding sucralose to the diet inhibited anti-PD1 therapy, leading to larger tumors and poorer survival. But when the researchers gave sucralose-fed mice arginine or citrulline, which is metabolized into arginine in the body, the effectiveness of immunotherapy was restored.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To assess the relevance of these findings for humans, the researchers looked at 132 patients with advanced melanoma or non-small cell lung cancer who received anti-PD1 therapy alone or in combination with chemotherapy. Patients filled out detailed diet history questionnaires that included questions about how often they consumed artificial sweeteners in coffee, tea and diet soda.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We found that sucralose impeded the effectiveness of immunotherapies across a range of cancer types, stages and treatment modalities," said Davar. "These observations raise the possibility of designing prebiotics, such as targeted nutrient supplementation for patients who consume high levels of sucralose."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers hope to launch a clinical trial investigating whether citrulline supplements -- which boost arginine levels more than arginine itself -- affect the gut microbiome and anti-tumor immune response in patients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They are also interested in looking at how other sugar substitutes, such as aspartame, saccharin, xylitol and stevia, impact the immune system and response to immunotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other authors on the study were Kristin Morder, M.S., Madison Nguyen, Drew Wilfahrt, Ph.D., Zakaria Dahmani, Ansen Burr, M.D., Ph.D., Bingxian Xie, Ph.D., Michael Morikone, Ph.D., Hector Nieves-Rosado, M.D., Ph.D., William Gunn, M.S., Drew Hurd, Hong Wang, Ph.D., Steven Mullett, Kaitlin Bossong, Stacy Gelhaus, Ph.D., Dhivyaa Rajasundaram, Ph.D., Lawrence Kane, Ph.D., and Greg Delgoffe, Ph.D., and Jishnu Das, Ph.D., all of Pitt or UPMC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This research was supported by the National Institutes of Health (DP2AI177967, S10OD023402, S10OD032141, R01CA206517, R01AI138504, T32GM008208, U01 CA271407, R01 CA257265, U01 CA268806 and P50 CA254865), the Damon Runyon Cancer Research Foundation and Gateway for Cancer Research (G-22-800).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 20:18:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE1NYjRRNHFvRGNBUHRBUlFKcnlhZ0VoRWZrMy1zNHBPUzlpZnR5ZU9VNDFkZjBlOU5LQ05JVDhhbkV5My0ycTZnR1BfeW0wTU5saExCN1FKS3NHaV9PalNjZXotYmJSajJpQUI5NEJiSQ</guid></item><item><title>卡通：雪鸟-科斯岛日报</title><link>https://www.dailykos.com/stories/2025/9/6/2341833/-Cartoon-Snowbirds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story__details"&gt;
      
      
      &lt;p class="story__timestamp"&gt;
                  &lt;span class="timestamp story__date--short" data-localize-time data-epoch-time="1757184902000" data-time-zone="-0700" data-time-format="%A, %b. %d, %Y"&gt;Saturday, Sep. 06, 2025&lt;/span&gt;
          &lt;span class="timestamp story__date--long" data-localize-time data-epoch-time="1757184902000" data-time-zone="-0700" data-time-format="%A, %B %d, %Y"&gt;Saturday, Sep. 06, 2025&lt;/span&gt;
          at &lt;span class="timestamp" data-localize-time data-epoch-time="1757184902000" data-time-zone="-0700" data-time-format="%l:%M:%S%P %Z"&gt;11:55:02am PDT&lt;/span&gt;

      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p id="react-story-stats"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Kos</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 19:40:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE1Id1lVV0hJWnMwZFJiYzB5Ylk2UUxRYXJtaXRfVUdXOWg4TVdDUV9Jc3pmODBlNlBXN2xoc2o1ZmU2NzlBZG1wWDlGYWg3bG1CRHFLeC1CSXl3bHNDRGxmTTU2WXlnSFJ1bUxvV3lpQ1ZFN211WkdN</guid></item><item><title>营养师制定的5天高蛋白、高纤维膳食计划- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/5-day-high-protein-high-fiber-meal-plan-11803586</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__table-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;table class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__table"&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th colspan="3" class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__title"&gt;Meal Plan at a Glance &lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Breakfast/ A.M. Snack&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Lunch/ P.M. Snack&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Dinner/ Evening Snack&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody data-check="0"&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Blueberry &amp;amp; peanut chia pudding/ Hard-boiled egg &amp;amp; nuts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;High-protein black bean salad&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Charred shrimp pesto bowls/ Dark chocolate&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Blueberry &amp;amp; peanut chia pudding&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Marry Me white bean salad/ Edamame&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Crispy salmon bowl/ Chai energy balls&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Black bean &amp;amp; cheese quiche/ Apple&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;High-protein black bean salad&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Taco-stuffed sweet potato/ Yogurt parfait&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Black bean &amp;amp; cheese quiche/ Apple &amp;amp; nut butter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chopped Cobb salad&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chicken &amp;amp; broccoli pasta/ Chai energy balls&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Black bean &amp;amp; cheese quiche/ Yogurt parfait&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chopped Cobb salad/ Edamame&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Turkey fajita bowls&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 1 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_1-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Charred Shrimp, Pesto &amp;amp; Quinoa Bowls.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (478 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (181 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (596 Calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner ( 429 Calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Evening Snack ( Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 oz. dark chocolate (70-85%)  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;:  1,803 calories, 97 g fat, 90 g protein, 161 g carbohydrates, 52 g fiber, 1,821 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;:  Omit morning snack and evening snack. Add  ¼ cup scrambled egg whites to breakfast. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/everything-bagel-cottage-cheese-snack-jar-with-bell-peppers-chickpeas-11715522" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Everything Bagel Cottage Cheese Snack Jar with Bell Peppers &amp;amp; Chickpeas&lt;/a&gt; to afternoon snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 2 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_2-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Chai Energy Balls.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Stacy Allen, Food Stylist: Chelsea Zimmer, Prop Stylist: Christina Daley&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (478 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (379 Calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (224 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1¼ cups frozen edamame (in pods), warmed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (526 Calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Evening Snack ( 206 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1,812 calories, 91 g fat, 102 g protein, 176 g carbohydrates, 48 g fiber, 1,093 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;:  Reduce afternoon snack portion of edamame to ¾ cup and omit evening snack. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/everything-bagel-cottage-cheese-snack-jar-with-bell-peppers-chickpeas-11715522" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Everything Bagel Cottage Cheese Snack Jar with Bell Peppers &amp;amp; Chickpeas&lt;/a&gt; to morning snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 3 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_3-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Black Bean &amp;amp; Pepper Jack Quiche.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jen Causey, Food Stylist: Emily Nabors Hall, Prop Stylist: Julia Bayless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (332 Calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (78 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (596 Calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_64-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (510 Calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_67-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_68-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Evening  Snack ( 301 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_70-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_71-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1,815 calories, 83 g fat, 97 g protein, 186 g carbohydrates, 45 g fiber, 1,737 mg sodium.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_72-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_73-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;:  Omit evening snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_74-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_75-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/everything-bagel-cottage-cheese-snack-jar-with-bell-peppers-chickpeas-11715522" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Everything Bagel Cottage Cheese Snack Jar with Bell Peppers &amp;amp; Chickpeas&lt;/a&gt; to afternoon snack. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_76-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_77-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 4 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_78-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_4-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Chopped Cobb Salad.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_79-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt;  Breakfast (332 Calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_81-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_82-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack ( 268 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_83-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 small apple + 2 Tbsp. natural peanut butter &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_84-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_85-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch ( 481 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_87-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_88-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (530 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_90-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_91-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Evening Snack ( 206 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_93-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_94-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1,816 calories, 82 g fat, 94 g protein, 195  g carbohydrates, 38 g fiber, 1,428 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_95-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_96-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Reduce to 1 Tbsp. peanut butter at morning snack. Omit evening snack. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_97-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_98-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/everything-bagel-cottage-cheese-snack-jar-with-bell-peppers-chickpeas-11715522" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Everything Bagel Cottage Cheese Snack Jar with Bell Peppers &amp;amp; Chickpeas &lt;/a&gt;to afternoon snack. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_99-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_100-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 5 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_101-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_5-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Ground Turkey Rice Bowl.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jen Causey, Food Stylist: Margaret Monroe Dickey, Prop Stylist: Hannah Greenwood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_102-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (332 Calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_104-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_105-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack ( 301 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_107-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_108-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch ( 481 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_110-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_111-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (135 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_112-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;¾ cup frozen edamame (in pods), warmed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_113-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_114-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (570 Calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_116-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_117-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;:  1,818 calories,  74 g fat, 110 g protein, 202 g carbohydrates, 40 g fiber,  1,501 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_118-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_119-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;:  Omit morning snack. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_120-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_121-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 1 oz. dark chocolate (70-85%) and 1 Tbsp. almonds to evening snack. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_122-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_124-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-faq mntl-sc-block-universal-faq"&gt;&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-faqs-8e0770b8-feed-4a69-8360-61a503a5ca21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__title"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content mntl-accordion js-accordion"&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="1"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_1-0-section-0"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Is it OK to mix and match meals if there’s one I don’t like?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes! This meal plan is meant to serve as inspiration. It doesn’t need to be followed exactly to reap the benefits. When choosing recipes, we made sure to check the calories, fiber, protein and sodium to align with the parameters of this plan and be within our sodium limits. If you’re making a recipe swap, it may be helpful to choose a recipe with similar calories, fiber, protein and sodium levels. For more inspiration, check out these delicious &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/7953165/easy-high-protein-high-fiber-dinner-recipes/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;High-Protein, High-Fiber Dinners That Are Easy to Make&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="2"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_2-0-section-1"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Can I eat the same breakfast or lunch every day?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_2-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Definitely, it’s fine to eat the same breakfast or lunch every day. The breakfasts range from 332 to 478 calories, while the lunches span 379 to 596 calories. These ranges are fairly close, though if you’re closely monitoring your calories or other nutrients, like protein, you may want to adjust a snack or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="3"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_3-0-section-2"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Why is there not a 1,200-calorie modification?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_3-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We no longer provide modifications for 1,200-calorie days in our meal plans. The 2020-2025 Dietary Guidelines for Americans suggests that limiting calories to 1,200 per day is too low for most people to meet their nutritional needs, plus it’s unsustainable for long-term health and well-being.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_125-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-health-benefits-of-a-high-protein-high-fiber-diet"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_126-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Health Benefits of a High-Protein, High-Fiber Diet &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_127-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Protein is found in every cell in our body. Because of this, it’s essential for countless bodily functions like bone and muscle health, digestion and energy production. While most people get enough &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/sneaky-signs-youre-not-getting-enough-protein-11790921" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;protein&lt;/a&gt;, certain factors like activity level, age or health goals may amp up your needs. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_128-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_129-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; On the flip side, diets that are too high in protein can sometimes lack fiber, which may lead to digestive troubles.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Striking the right balance of both protein and fiber is key to keeping your body healthy and running smoothly. Fiber brings its own powerful set of benefits. Diets rich in &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/287742/10-amazing-health-benefits-of-eating-more-fiber/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;fiber&lt;/a&gt; have been linked to healthier weight loss and long-term weight control, a lower risk of type 2 diabetes and heart disease, reduced odds of certain cancers, more regular bowel movements and even a longer life. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_130-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_131-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Together, protein and fiber help you feel full and satisfied after meals, support digestion and keep your energy steady throughout the day. Talk about a winning combo for health and well-being! 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_132-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_133-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-generic" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;How We Create Meal Plans&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Registered dietitians thoughtfully create EatingWell’s meal plans to be easy-to-follow and delicious. Each meal plan meets specific parameters depending on the health condition and/or lifestyle goal it is targeting and is analyzed for accuracy using the nutrition database, ESHA Food Processor. As nutritional needs differ from person to person, we encourage you to use these plans as inspiration and adjust as you see fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQWWt4NmtLT0V1eFFiWTd6bDc3MnhmSElSZFp3dkIyS19aQTJ6RThRampPay1pQjJNSHZnU2VzbWRHZ1I0NkV6NFM1aVhFbVRYOVdmY3NPZEI3RjlScXVSN3dXTHQxSFlLQ2JOVU1yOU5YRFRZR2ZGbzZDR2MxdVpXUA</guid></item><item><title>在32个州（包括俄亥俄州）发现了致命的寄生虫“接吻虫” -以下是须知事项- WKRC</title><link>https://local12.com/news/nation-world/deadly-parasitic-infection-kissing-bug-bugs-parasite-pandemic-disease-chagas-who-cdc-health-organization-disease-control-spread-spreading-states-symptoms-symptom-signs-sign-treatment-medicine</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText-module_storyText__FWhP"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CINCINNATI (WKRC) - Health authorities sounded the alarm for a deadly parasitic infection that has already infected eight people, with the insect source being found in 32 states, including Ohio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC and WHO have been encouraged to officially declare Chagas disease endemic in the United States following the eight infections, per &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/09/03/health/deadly-kissing-bug-parasite-is-now-in-30-us-states/" target="_blank" title="https://nypost.com/2025/09/03/health/deadly-kissing-bug-parasite-is-now-in-30-us-states/" class="themeColorForLinks"&gt;New York Post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is a disease that has been neglected and has been impacting Latin Americans for many decades, but it’s also here in the United States," said medical epidemiologist Norman Beatty, an expert on the disease, in an interview with the &lt;a href="https://www.latimes.com/science/story/2025-09-01/chagas-disease-the-deadly-disease-youve-never-heard-of-but-is-here" target="_blank" title="https://www.latimes.com/science/story/2025-09-01/chagas-disease-the-deadly-disease-youve-never-heard-of-but-is-here" class="themeColorForLinks"&gt;Los Angeles Times&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disease's carrier, known as kissing bugs, are small insects that consume blood from people and animals, particularly around their face (hence the name).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;32 states have reports of the bugs being present, including Ohio and Indiana. 12 of them have local cases of only animals being bitten by the bug, and one had a local case of only humans being bitten by the bug. Five states reported local cases of animal and human bites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chagas disease begins with "absent or mild and non-specific symptoms" like fevers, headaches, enlarged glands, muscle pain, and chest pain as the parasites flow through the bloodstream, per the&lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/chagas-disease-(american-trypanosomiasis)" target="_blank" title="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/chagas-disease-(american-trypanosomiasis)" class="themeColorForLinks"&gt; World Health Organization's website&lt;/a&gt;. Occasionally, early symptoms could include "purplish swelling of the lids of one eye" or a skin lesion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The symptoms get much more intense the longer the parasites remain in the body, largely collecting in the heart and digestive muscles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One to three decades after infection, up to a third of patients suffer from cardiac disorders and up to 1 in 10 suffer from digestive (typically enlargement of the oesophagus or colon), neurological or mixed alterations," the website read. "In later years these patients may experience the damage to the nervous system and muscles of the heart and digestive system, leading to cardiac arrhythmias, progressive heart failure, and sudden death, among other clinical manifestations and complications."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disease is treatable, but is much more effective in the early stages of infection. According to the &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/chagas-disease/symptoms-causes/syc-20356212" target="_blank" title="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/chagas-disease/symptoms-causes/syc-20356212" class="themeColorForLinks"&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;, the disease may become untreatable if it becomes chronic, at which point the only option is treating symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WKRC</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 18:44:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizgJBVV95cUxQTE9vaWt6NE9CekVVOE4xLXdzSk85OHhoWFlvU0ZSZlNtZGNpQ0VubHplWm5uenNSTVltUmJSV3dvRVFVQ0ZCSElzWkZCdzlmT0FsQkZrNzlQRDFvS3FwMHZPSWFGeEpUMXA0RnNaMDFNX2tRaHV2a013NW5ydVc5VDZoc3N1Vm5hWFExZzdvVm1lUUFPNWFzOS1KQXRWLVUxenpERW4xV2hOVWJJaURoNmE1eXptbWRTN0pCbUdPbVljaExRb3VPRFUyMjFtemdfZzBDaDBudEVGdGVfN1lUV0tEbmpPVG9EMmthdnJRSjBONkhoWVR2NXpSM3ZsTlRlemZ0T2tDWmdITldmcUJkV0hNS195VjBZUUlNMjV6Y3Z0SUk4ZXM0YmVONTcwVE90OG8xSXpiTjI4THNYZkxESzg0cnRfSDAwRFBaVTJR</guid></item><item><title>如果您使用人工智能进行治疗，以下是专家推荐的5件事-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/09/06/ai-chatbots-therapy-tips/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JOLKNZK2FFHTJHJUGLV4KGUPPM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Many people are turning to generative artificial intelligence for answers to work or school questions. But some are also using it for a more personal and intimate kind of help: Therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="PGL32EQTC5F2DCBSZZPAECWAUY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;While talking with chatbots may help some people, &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/02/23/ai-mental-health-therapy/" target="_blank"&gt;at least anecdotally&lt;/a&gt;, research and hard data are lacking. There have also been reports of generative&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;AI chatbots causing or contributing to serious harm, including cases linked to &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/08/19/ai-psychosis-chatgpt-explained-mental-health/" target="_blank"&gt;psychosis&lt;/a&gt; or even &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2025/08/28/meta-ai-chatbot-safety-teens/" target="_blank"&gt;suicide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxNMk5EWHJsQUd5eENJaFZ5S0UweUJJOEh0cnBnbXFidUJHeHp3LTlTa2ZVVnROSDdhUmtZcFVGZUdjS3p2NGhWRjVNRlZOT1M2ekx3Vmt5cVVUWDBONkJybzQ5a2hHME1qRXJZRW1raVhBSnRxWU41d0lvWXRsdVE4MUNB</guid></item><item><title>刚果宣布爆发新的埃博拉疫情。以下是须知事项-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/congo-ebola-kasai-outbreak-73c01a467e3f7b5e3e19abec17c65a39</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:55:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOX1JyU3lXYlRjTndFOFUtZXNBczBUS0Qwa0Rjbld6NzhRc0w4amNzclZKcm5GYklqa3FNdFA3bnVsajJpa292dEdOTXVfT1RjUUxIOG8yTE9oWjN3ejZMdWJoanJCTHhXUzZZd1ZiNDZRX2FqYzRhVGZ3Vkh1OE1mTVBTY25yeUNRcWlVNUoyZw</guid></item><item><title>营养师喜欢这种高蛋白零食减肥- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/best-high-protein-snack-for-weight-loss-11803891</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;High-protein snacks like strained (Greek-style) yogurt help you stay full between meals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Protein supports metabolism by preserving muscle and boosting calorie burn.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Choose yogurt low in sugar and saturated fat, and add fiber-rich fruit or nuts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Protein is everywhere these days. From bars to shakes to cereal, it seems every product is fortified with it. But not all protein-rich snacks are created equal. Some offer solid nutrition, while others come with extra ingredients that can work against your health goals—especially if weight loss is one of them.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; So what’s the best pick? We asked dietitians to share the No. 1 high-protein snack for weight loss. Their answer: &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8015607/greek-yogurt-benefits/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;strained (Greek-style) yogurt&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-makes-it-so-effective"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What Makes It So Effective &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Just one 6-ounce container of plain, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/surprising-ingredient-for-high-protein-vegetarian-meals-8649419" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nonfat strained (Greek-style) yogurt&lt;/a&gt; packs 18 grams of high-quality protein.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “This substantial amount of protein promotes feelings of fullness, reducing the likelihood of overeating later in the day,” says &lt;a href="https://www.nutritionnowcounseling.com/about-1" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Lauren Manaker, M.S., RDN, LD, CLEC, CPT&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Protein works in several ways to help you lose weight. First, it increases satiety, or how full you feel when you eat. But that’s only the beginning. Protein requires lots of energy to digest and absorb. So, your body burns more calories to process protein-rich foods than carbohydrates or fats. Last but not least, protein also helps maintain calorie-burning muscle for a faster metabolism.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And there’s more. Strained (Greek-style) yogurt also contains &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/2053111/can-probiotics-help-you-lose-weight/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;probiotics&lt;/a&gt;, live bacteria that support your gut and have also been linked to weight loss.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; And it boasts a robust nutrient profile (hello, calcium, magnesium, phosphorus and potassium!).&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Strained (Greek-style) yogurt is great for weight loss on its own. However, for an even more satisfying snack, dietitians recommend pairing it with fresh fruit and a healthy fat, like chopped nuts, seeds or a drizzle of nut butter. Try mixing &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/261071/yogurt-with-blueberries/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;yogurt with blueberries&lt;/a&gt; as an excellent base. Or, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/252990/homemade-plain-greek-yogurt/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;make your own&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-shopping-tips"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Shopping Tips &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; There’s certainly no shortage of options when it comes to strained (Greek-style) yogurt. However, nutrients can vary from brand to brand. Here’s what to look for.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High in protein: &lt;/strong&gt;Choose brands that pack 16 grams or more of high-quality protein, says &lt;a href="https://enjoyfoodenjoylife.com/about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Nicole Rodriguez, RDN&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Low or no added sugar:&lt;/strong&gt; Rodriguez recommends opting for a plain variety. However, if you’re an “on the fence” yogurt connoisseur, there are many brands with very low added sugar that may suit your taste. Stick to those with no more than 5 g of added sugar or less. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Probiotics: &lt;/strong&gt;These are &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/2059033/best-and-worst-foods-to-eat-for-gut-health/" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;good-for-your-gut bacteria&lt;/a&gt;. For the best bang, look for &lt;em&gt;Lactobacillus&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Bifidobacterium&lt;/em&gt;. Research reveals they may specifically help with weight loss.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; You’ll find them listed on the ingredient list. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Little saturated fat: &lt;/strong&gt;Like protein, all fats aren’t created equally. For optimal heart health, the 2020-2025 Dietary Guidelines for Americans recommend limiting saturated fat to a maximum of 10% of total calories.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Rodriguez suggests choosing a brand that contains no more than 0.5 g of saturated fat per serving.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-tips-for-weight-loss-snacks"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Tips for Weight Loss Snacks &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;“Snacks that support weight loss should mimic the same composition as meals that support weight loss,” says Rodriguez. “They should be anchored with high-quality protein and rounded out with a naturally fibrous food and heart-healthy (plant-based) fat.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Here are a few other rules of thumb that can make your high-protein weight-loss snack work even harder for you:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus on fiber: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/287742/10-amazing-health-benefits-of-eating-more-fiber/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Fiber&lt;/a&gt; fills you up, so it may help you eat less.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; So, add some fiber-rich berries, pears or any of these other &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-high-fiber-fruits-8639024" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;high-fiber fruits&lt;/a&gt; to your yogurt or smoothie. They’re also a great way to add natural sweetness. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lean on healthy fats: &lt;/strong&gt;Fat is digested slowly, so it keeps you fuller for longer. Think &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/the-best-healthy-fats-for-weight-loss-8417296" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;healthy unsaturated fats&lt;/a&gt; from mix-ins like nuts, seeds, nut butters and even &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/8057914/avocado-recipes-to-make-forever/" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;avocados&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be choosy about allergy-friendly alternatives: &lt;/strong&gt;If dairy allergies are an issue, there are protein-rich plant-based strained (Greek-style) yogurt alternatives. Look for brands with at least 10 g of protein per serving. Just be cautious of the fat content, specifically saturated fat, which hangs out in coconut yogurt. Instead, opt for soy or oat-based yogurts fortified with a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/291111/the-10-best-vegan-protein-sources/" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="5"&gt;plant-based protein&lt;/a&gt;, like pea or soy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-spotlight--1-2-post mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight--1-2-post mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight mntl-block theme-1-2-post"&gt;&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight__heading_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight__heading mntl-text-block"&gt;Try These High-Protein Snacks&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When weight loss is a goal, high-protein snacks can help you stay full and satisfied, especially strained (Greek-style) yogurt. It’s the top dietitian-approved high-protein snack to help you lose weight. Need help sifting through the plethora of options on store shelves? Look for one that’s low in saturated fat and added sugars. Or choose plain, unsweetened strained (Greek-style) yogurt and add your own healthy mix-ins like high-fiber fruits and a healthy fat, like chopped nuts. They’ll make your snack even more satisfying and delicious!&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxOd0I0bmVBV2lpWHJwVFVrSTBHSzFsenFkNUdOUU5XX2RocGkxSTFaclZQM1B2Mmp2YjFBZ1BTYVJxcUlabk9XQl91OFJvdk8zbFBLUDl0a1prdzlHQWVMUWxDQ3dPcGxRNHNzZnpLYjdIalA2eFZiU3BSbWJMcjFHZw</guid></item><item><title>接受13英寸手术的青少年揭示了她现在的样子-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15036929/Teen-controversial-surgery-grow-13-inches-reveals-looks-like-now.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Chandler Crews knew she didn't want to live her entire adult life less than four feet tall. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The 31-year-old from &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/maryland/index.html" id="mol-cca3bd10-8423-11f0-bf95-b956380475ae"&gt;Maryland&lt;/a&gt; was born with achondroplasia, a genetic condition that most commonly results in short stature and is characterized by short limbs, a normal-sized trunk, an enlarged head, and a prominent forehead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It stems from a mutation in the FGFR3 gene, which leads to slowed bone development, particularly in the long bones of the arms and legs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Though it's the most common form of dwarfism, there are fewer than 50,000 people with achondroplasia in the US. The condition is generally diagnosed shortly after birth, as in Crews's case, but for some people, it may not be diagnosed until later in childhood, when a child's growth is not as expected for their age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Both her parents and two siblings are of average height, and like around 80 percent of children with achondroplasia, Crews inherited the condition due to a mutation in the FGFR3 gene that occurred at the time of conception. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Growing up with achondroplasia was extremely difficult, Crews says, and she remembers her mother constantly fearing for her life as the condition can cause sudden death syndrome due to brainstem compression and dangerous breathing problems like sleep apnea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her childhood was marred by frequent trips to hospitals for treatments and to meet with various specialists as dwarfism can cause complications, including bowed legs, spinal curvature, ear infections and hearing loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Crews also remembers feeling like a 'show dog' because of her small stature, and people would frequently come up to her to pat her head and give her 'fake' compliments to make her feel better, which she said left her feeling confused and angry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was when she turned 16 and realized she would never grow any taller that Crews decided to undergo 'taboo' limb lengthening surgery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption" aria-label="To enrich screen reader interactions, please activate Accessibility in Grammarly extension settings"&gt;Chandler Crews underwent three limb-lengthening procedures. Left, at her mature adult height of 3'10' and, right, at the end of her treatments, standing just over 4'11″ &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Limb lengthening is controversial in the dwarfism community because it's a painful, expensive, and risky procedure with a high complication rate, and some believe it promotes the idea that short stature is a defect to be 'fixed'. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Writing on her website, Crews said: 'I felt like I was never in my own body. I felt like my energy was wasting time in the body it wasn't meant to be in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I didn't want to wait for the world to change to fit my needs; I wanted to take charge and change for myself and no one else. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I've noticed within the dwarfism community, some may feel that when someone else with dwarfism changes or alters their own body, that it's an insult to everyone with that 'body type.' But it's not. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Just like everyone else in the world, our bodies are our own, and no one, even if you have the same diagnosis as them, should have any say in what you do or don't do.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In August 2010, when she was 16 years old, Crews underwent her first of three limb-lengthening procedures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Leg lengthening for dwarfism or bow legs involves surgically cutting the thigh or shin bone and implanting a device (either an external fixator or internal rod) to slowly pull the bone segments apart over several weeks to months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The bones are extended by around 1 millimeter per day, and during the 'distraction phase,' new bone forms in the gap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After the desired length is reached, the device is removed, and the new bone is left to fuse back together before the individual can regain full mobility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are no precise, readily available national figures on the total number of limb lengthening surgeries performed annually in the US, but the procedure is performed for both dwarfism-related and cosmetic reasons, with cosmetic height-lengthening procedures increasing in popularity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Limb lengthening surgery in the US can be extremely expensive, and Crews estimates her procedures cost close to $2million. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;There are fewer than 50,000 people with achondroplasia in the US. The condition is generally diagnosed shortly after birth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, as she was told the surgeries were necessary to correct her bowed legs and improve her spine health, she was able to have them mostly paid for by insurance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bow legs, also known as genu varum, is a condition where the knees curve outward, causing a gap between them when the feet are together. Left untreated, the long-term consequences of bowed legs in adults can include chronic joint pain, progressive arthritis, instability, and restricted mobility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Crews described the limb lengthening procedure as 'months of twists and turns' with a 'little blood, sweat, and tears.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The initial post-surgery recovery from her first surgery consisted of two to three hours of personal training sessions five days a week and daily exercises and stretches, which she did in her own time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;By the time Crews' bones were in the right position for the fixators to be removed from her first leg lengthening surgery, it was April 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She recalled: 'After removal, I had one month of no weight-bearing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Once I was cleared to fully weight-bear, I did have to re-learn how to walk, so to speak. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I used a walker for about two weeks, then two quad canes for about a week, then down to one. By June, I was walking unassisted.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;In August 2010, Crews underwent her first of three limb-lengthening procedures. Leg lengthening for dwarfism or bow legs involves surgically cutting the bone and implanting a device (either an external fixator or internal rod)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Crews described her first leg lengthening procedure as 'months of twists and turns' with a 'little blood, sweat, and tears'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After starting the process to get her legs lengthened, Crews also went about getting her arms lengthened so they would be in proportion with the rest of her body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She says people with dwarfism who opt to do leg lengthening usually opt to get their arms done too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Getting this procedure done, Crews points out, is important for a range of activities, from being able to drive a car to reaching into the refrigerator comfortably.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For her arm lengthening, Crews had fixators implanted in January 2012 when she was 17 years old and then removed the following August. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said of the procedure: 'This time, I only had fixators on my humerus [the bone of the upper arm], which meant I was mobile [able to walk].&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Because you don't bear weight in your arms, the consolidation or fusing phase can be slower as weight-bearing tends to help bone consolidation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'As for the physical therapy, I did personal training two to three times a week. After removing my fixators, I had about a month of no heavy lifting, pushing, or pulling.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The arm lengthening procedure saw Crews gain four inches in her arms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Crews went in for a second and then third leg lengthening in May 2013 when she was 19 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now, standing at just over 4'11″, the Marylander has been thrilled by the results of her operations. The average height for a woman varies globally, but in the US, it is 5'3.5".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She says: 'In full transparency, I also wanted to be more able-bodied. It was not just about being taller but also more proportionate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'When it came to height (lengthening legs), I didn't want to rely on stepstools and other forms of assistance constantly. Yes, it was my 'norm,' but it never felt like independence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Having longer arms, I can now reach the top of my head (wash it easier, high ponytails, safely use hairstyling tools, etc.), sit a safer distance away from the steering wheel when driving, not have to alter sleeves, deal with feminine hygiene – changing tampons, wiping front-to-back, not needing to use a bidet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'At 4'11' I'm still really short, but I'm what I call (for myself) a "comfortable short."'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a bid to offer hope to other people coping with achondroplasia and similar conditions, Crews has set up a patient advocacy group called The Chandler Project (TCP). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Limb lengthening surgery in the US can be extremely expensive, and Crew estimates her procedures cost close to $2million. However, as she was told the surgeries were necessary to correct her bowed legs and improve her health, she was able to claim them on insurance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption" aria-label="To enrich screen reader interactions, please activate Accessibility in Grammarly extension settings"&gt;Now standing at just over 4'11″, the Marylander has been thrilled by the results of her operations. In a bid to offer hope to other people coping with achondroplasia and similar conditions, Crews has set up a patient advocacy group called The Chandler Project (TCP)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The organization aims to help drive awareness for new research and advancements surrounding pharmaceutical and surgical treatments and offer vital support resources to individuals and their families. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now happy with her help and living independently with less pain, Crews concludes: 'Everyone wants to feel normal, and that’s how I feel now. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I’m honestly so tired of trying to make sure I don’t say ‘normal’ (because the word ‘normal’ is so frowned upon in the dwarfism community). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I’m not a little person, and inside I never felt like I was. I’ve never been a dwarf either. I’m just Chandler and I have achondroplasia. It’s a life-long medical diagnosis I will always deal with and fear of passing on to my future children. Babies have died from complications of achondroplasia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Children have died from complications of achondroplasia. Adults have died from having achondroplasia. No one ever wants to talk about it, but it’s true. Living with achondroplasia is a difficult life, but it’s the only one I have. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I’m working hard to make it my best life and show others they too can control the way they live with this condition.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 15:32:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxQNll3cFRYU0NqZG16WWFWeXF0X0NOSG5TZDhib254SVlMN2pwVHFwY1ZrRGpKbWh3QlNOUDVxcGdNdm40cEoyLVl0d2RWZVlCMmFxNTctZjVydC1jYlhBbUlRdnlwdm1yRWZKYVpxZjVLZHhIaEFIQ0lLOTM0aDVPOEV5XzdIZFA4TFlFSndXZjBvdVJZWjZZZ1JkakRiNFQtVFBLZ3AtUlNva0NUUDFUYTBYeFgyay1NMHprSEx3</guid></item><item><title>接受有争议的13英寸手术的青少年揭示了她现在的样子-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15036929/Teen-controversial-surgery-grow-13-inches-reveals-looks-like-now.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Chandler Crews knew she didn't want to live her entire adult life less than four feet tall. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The 31-year-old from &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/maryland/index.html" id="mol-cca3bd10-8423-11f0-bf95-b956380475ae"&gt;Maryland&lt;/a&gt; was born with achondroplasia, a genetic condition that most commonly results in short stature and is characterized by short limbs, a normal-sized trunk, an enlarged head, and a prominent forehead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It stems from a mutation in the FGFR3 gene, which leads to slowed bone development, particularly in the long bones of the arms and legs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Though it's the most common form of dwarfism, there are fewer than 50,000 people with achondroplasia in the US. The condition is generally diagnosed shortly after birth, as in Crews's case, but for some people, it may not be diagnosed until later in childhood, when a child's growth is not as expected for their age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Both her parents and two siblings are of average height, and like around 80 percent of children with achondroplasia, Crews inherited the condition due to a mutation in the FGFR3 gene that occurred at the time of conception. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Growing up with achondroplasia was extremely difficult, Crews says, and she remembers her mother constantly fearing for her life as the condition can cause sudden death syndrome due to brainstem compression and dangerous breathing problems like sleep apnea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her childhood was marred by frequent trips to hospitals for treatments and to meet with various specialists as dwarfism can cause complications, including bowed legs, spinal curvature, ear infections and hearing loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Crews also remembers feeling like a 'show dog' because of her small stature, and people would frequently come up to her to pat her head and give her 'fake' compliments to make her feel better, which she said left her feeling confused and angry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was when she turned 16 and realized she would never grow any taller that Crews decided to undergo 'taboo' limb lengthening surgery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption" aria-label="To enrich screen reader interactions, please activate Accessibility in Grammarly extension settings"&gt;Chandler Crews underwent three limb-lengthening procedures. Left, at her mature adult height of 3'10' and, right, at the end of her treatments, standing just over 4'11″ &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Limb lengthening is controversial in the dwarfism community because it's a painful, expensive, and risky procedure with a high complication rate, and some believe it promotes the idea that short stature is a defect to be 'fixed'. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Writing on her website, Crews said: 'I felt like I was never in my own body. I felt like my energy was wasting time in the body it wasn't meant to be in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I didn't want to wait for the world to change to fit my needs; I wanted to take charge and change for myself and no one else. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I've noticed within the dwarfism community, some may feel that when someone else with dwarfism changes or alters their own body, that it's an insult to everyone with that 'body type.' But it's not. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Just like everyone else in the world, our bodies are our own, and no one, even if you have the same diagnosis as them, should have any say in what you do or don't do.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In August 2010, when she was 16 years old, Crews underwent her first of three limb-lengthening procedures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Leg lengthening for dwarfism or bow legs involves surgically cutting the thigh or shin bone and implanting a device (either an external fixator or internal rod) to slowly pull the bone segments apart over several weeks to months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The bones are extended by around 1 millimeter per day, and during the 'distraction phase,' new bone forms in the gap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After the desired length is reached, the device is removed, and the new bone is left to fuse back together before the individual can regain full mobility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are no precise, readily available national figures on the total number of limb lengthening surgeries performed annually in the US, but the procedure is performed for both dwarfism-related and cosmetic reasons, with cosmetic height-lengthening procedures increasing in popularity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Limb lengthening surgery in the US can be extremely expensive, and Crews estimates her procedures cost close to $2million. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;There are fewer than 50,000 people with achondroplasia in the US. The condition is generally diagnosed shortly after birth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, as she was told the surgeries were necessary to correct her bowed legs and improve her spine health, she was able to have them mostly paid for by insurance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bow legs, also known as genu varum, is a condition where the knees curve outward, causing a gap between them when the feet are together. Left untreated, the long-term consequences of bowed legs in adults can include chronic joint pain, progressive arthritis, instability, and restricted mobility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Crews described the limb lengthening procedure as 'months of twists and turns' with a 'little blood, sweat, and tears.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The initial post-surgery recovery from her first surgery consisted of two to three hours of personal training sessions five days a week and daily exercises and stretches, which she did in her own time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;By the time Crews' bones were in the right position for the fixators to be removed from her first leg lengthening surgery, it was April 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She recalled: 'After removal, I had one month of no weight-bearing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Once I was cleared to fully weight-bear, I did have to re-learn how to walk, so to speak. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I used a walker for about two weeks, then two quad canes for about a week, then down to one. By June, I was walking unassisted.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;In August 2010, Crews underwent her first of three limb-lengthening procedures. Leg lengthening for dwarfism or bow legs involves surgically cutting the bone and implanting a device (either an external fixator or internal rod)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Crews described her first leg lengthening procedure as 'months of twists and turns' with a 'little blood, sweat, and tears'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After starting the process to get her legs lengthened, Crews also went about getting her arms lengthened so they would be in proportion with the rest of her body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She says people with dwarfism who opt to do leg lengthening usually opt to get their arms done too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Getting this procedure done, Crews points out, is important for a range of activities, from being able to drive a car to reaching into the refrigerator comfortably.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For her arm lengthening, Crews had fixators implanted in January 2012 when she was 17 years old and then removed the following August. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said of the procedure: 'This time, I only had fixators on my humerus [the bone of the upper arm], which meant I was mobile [able to walk].&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Because you don't bear weight in your arms, the consolidation or fusing phase can be slower as weight-bearing tends to help bone consolidation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'As for the physical therapy, I did personal training two to three times a week. After removing my fixators, I had about a month of no heavy lifting, pushing, or pulling.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The arm lengthening procedure saw Crews gain four inches in her arms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Crews went in for a second and then third leg lengthening in May 2013 when she was 19 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now, standing at just over 4'11″, the Marylander has been thrilled by the results of her operations. The average height for a woman varies globally, but in the US, it is 5'3.5".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She says: 'In full transparency, I also wanted to be more able-bodied. It was not just about being taller but also more proportionate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'When it came to height (lengthening legs), I didn't want to rely on stepstools and other forms of assistance constantly. Yes, it was my 'norm,' but it never felt like independence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Having longer arms, I can now reach the top of my head (wash it easier, high ponytails, safely use hairstyling tools, etc.), sit a safer distance away from the steering wheel when driving, not have to alter sleeves, deal with feminine hygiene – changing tampons, wiping front-to-back, not needing to use a bidet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'At 4'11' I'm still really short, but I'm what I call (for myself) a "comfortable short."'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a bid to offer hope to other people coping with achondroplasia and similar conditions, Crews has set up a patient advocacy group called The Chandler Project (TCP). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Limb lengthening surgery in the US can be extremely expensive, and Crew estimates her procedures cost close to $2million. However, as she was told the surgeries were necessary to correct her bowed legs and improve her health, she was able to claim them on insurance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption" aria-label="To enrich screen reader interactions, please activate Accessibility in Grammarly extension settings"&gt;Now standing at just over 4'11″, the Marylander has been thrilled by the results of her operations. In a bid to offer hope to other people coping with achondroplasia and similar conditions, Crews has set up a patient advocacy group called The Chandler Project (TCP)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The organization aims to help drive awareness for new research and advancements surrounding pharmaceutical and surgical treatments and offer vital support resources to individuals and their families. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now happy with her help and living independently with less pain, Crews concludes: 'Everyone wants to feel normal, and that’s how I feel now. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I’m honestly so tired of trying to make sure I don’t say ‘normal’ (because the word ‘normal’ is so frowned upon in the dwarfism community). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I’m not a little person, and inside I never felt like I was. I’ve never been a dwarf either. I’m just Chandler and I have achondroplasia. It’s a life-long medical diagnosis I will always deal with and fear of passing on to my future children. Babies have died from complications of achondroplasia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Children have died from complications of achondroplasia. Adults have died from having achondroplasia. No one ever wants to talk about it, but it’s true. Living with achondroplasia is a difficult life, but it’s the only one I have. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I’m working hard to make it my best life and show others they too can control the way they live with this condition.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 15:32:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxQNll3cFRYU0NqZG16WWFWeXF0X0NOSG5TZDhib254SVlMN2pwVHFwY1ZrRGpKbWh3QlNOUDVxcGdNdm40cEoyLVl0d2RWZVlCMmFxNTctZjVydC1jYlhBbUlRdnlwdm1yRWZKYVpxZjVLZHhIaEFIQ0lLOTM0aDVPOEV5XzdIZFA4TFlFSndXZjBvdVJZWjZZZ1JkakRiNFQtVFBLZ3AtUlNva0NUUDFUYTBYeFgyay1NMHprSEx30gHDAUFVX3lxTE5XZy1NZlhQT2VZT3gxeFh6QW9ET1ZaNHF2b3owTW1pWDhJNFhNcG96OEJhc0RxT0dwQlp1cm05SElta1R3MTE2T1pCamFNS05qZXhPOURYOXRoMkRiRms3NGZ0Nk1ycC1tR3pmUmY5RVI3amVqVEQwSzN6RDlUWi16QzhNMkM2TkFITlNfOUpQV0QyeGFnbTNIN1B4dkZVVHQ5OTFiUDhLVjJscFR3YzhEWDY3MlFUWkFHN0ZXMVhlLS1MNA</guid></item></channel></rss>