<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>缓解坐骨神经痛，继续前进-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/05/well/move/exercise-sciatica-advice.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE9vQXJjLWNWYmdabllIbWR3TnhCd0xrRVRaQTI2TTRSZWNxU29rMUNOaHBEMlo1SHlpQ0g2MmhTRXBOMS1SVTFQYWZ1dHY2czN3SUJPRkVBemJHeVdMQWNSVG94emdKOXNvajdCSlRZcDU2ZWRxMFUxVW5XTS1FTTA</guid></item><item><title>禁止在室内穿鞋的7个理由- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51400597/7-reasons-you-should-never-wear-shoes-in-the-house</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;You probably wouldn't feel comfortable letting a group of sick people wander through your house or allowing guests to spread harmful substances on your carpet for your children and pets to ingest. And you'd likely be horrified if someone deliberately smeared dirt and grime all over your &lt;a href="https://tinyurl.com/DD2502BV" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;beautiful, brand-new carpet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if you're allowing people to wear shoes inside your home, you might as well be inviting these problems. Whether you realize it or not, your footwear can carry serious health risks and cost you a lot in flooring repairs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are seven reasons why a "no shoes" policy might be a smart move for your home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt; Photo: Pixel-Shot - stock.adobe.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;You're bringing in a lot of germs to the home&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Put this at the top of your list of reasons to not wear shoes in your house: It's making you sick. Dr. Charles Gerba, professor of microbiology and environmental sciences at the University of Arizona, told &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/home/health-reasons-why-you-shouldn-t-wear-shoes-house-t129820" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;TODAY Home&lt;/a&gt; just how disgusting the bottoms of your shoes can be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you wear shoes for more than a month, 93 percent will have fecal bacteria on the bottom of them," Gerba said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, your shoes likely have either human or animal waste on them. This happens when you unwittingly step on pet droppings (your own pet's or someone else's) or use a public restroom with, well, pretty filthy floors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aside from waste, Gerba's research team also found E. coli on the bottoms of shoes. If you're lucky, it might be a harmless strain. If not, you could be looking at a nasty bout of diarrhea, a urinary tract infection, respiratory illness or pneumonia, to name a few potential problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gerba added that even if your shoes look clean, these germs can be lurking in the cracks and crevices, where bacteria easily breeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;You're tracking in toxins, too&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though it sounds less gross, this next problem is even more deadly: Your shoes could be tracking in some dangerous toxins, such as lead or pesticides.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The most common place we find lead is in older houses and buildings with lead-based paint," Dr. Daniel Sullivan tells &lt;a href="https://health.clevelandclinic.org/wearing-shoes-in-the-house-is-a-bad-idea" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. "Over time, that paint chips off and lands on the ground, where it turns to dust. You can walk through this dust without knowing it and bring it into your house on your shoes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This suddenly becomes a very serious problem if you have small children who play or crawl on your floors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Don't forget about allergens&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though slightly less scary than toxins, allergens can also make your life miserable at home if your shoes bring them inside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Tree, grass and weed pollen easily get on shoes," Dr. Sullivan says, "and when you walk around your house, the pollen can fly into the air, land on surfaces and aggravate your allergies."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;It creates a mess&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;An obvious reason to not wear shoes in your home is the mess it makes. Any parent knows how aggravating it is to spend a day sweeping and mopping your floors only to have your kids streak dirt and debris inside when they get home from school. A no shoe policy can nip this bad habit in the bud really quickly and spare you of extra housework.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;It's a sign of disrespect in many cultures&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wearing shoes indoors may not seem like a big deal to you, but in some cultures, it's very offensive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wearing shoes inside someone's house is seen as a sign of disrespect in many cultures throughout Asia, Europe, and the Middle East," Melanie Mannarino writes for &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/home-organizing/cleaning/shoes-inside-house" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Real Simple&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a guest, it's best to take cues from your host about whether shoes are welcome inside. If you're unsure, don't hesitate to ask!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Going shoeless is cozier&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unless you have a specific orthopedic need for wearing shoes inside, taking them off is generally far more comfortable. You instantly feel at ease and it sends a message to your brain that you've entered a safe and relaxing place, allowing you to disconnect from the outside world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides, many studies out there support the idea that walking barefoot comes with a host of benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Having direct skin contact with the earth's surface, known as grounding, may transmit electrical charges to the body and elicit positive results," Kim Grundy writes for &lt;a href="https://www.goodrx.com/conditions/musculoskeletal/benefits-of-walking-barefoot?label_override=undefined" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;GoodRx&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another study on &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4378297/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;PubMed Centra&lt;/a&gt;l found that the practice of grounding improved mood and energy for a group of massage therapists. In some cases, it helped reduce pain and inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt; Photo: Adobe.com/Pixel-Shot&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;It wreaks havoc on your flooring&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unless you're a fan of matted, discolored and germ-infested carpet, going shoeless is a smart choice. It's no secret that shoes can wreak havoc on your floors, and carpet, in particular, takes a serious hit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not only does it make your flooring look worn and dirty, but it also traps those germs, toxins and allergens mentioned earlier, creating an unhealthy environment beneath your feet. Besides, you probably don't want to waste time and money replacing your beautiful floors more often than necessary!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt; Photo: Adobe.com/Ziyan&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Find beautiful flooring at Giant Carpet One&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Giant Carpet One has friendly experts who can help you choose the right flooring for your home. Visit your local &lt;a href="https://tinyurl.com/DD2502BV2" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Giant Carpet One&lt;/a&gt; to see and feel your options, from carpet to luxury vinyl, hardwood, tile and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever your budget, you'll find something you love that works for your family. For more information or to find a showroom near you, check out Giant Carpet One.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 15:04:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxOQnlncm83RlpRcmJscXZ2Rk91c2p6bnBlNnBkY01LNWszWFplZnhhTjlxZEFSXzNUU0paUmlFYXRoM21ONzQ3a2xYOHRFUW5GVEZnRXRoZDVfZzh5R3NMaXFmMWsyQmphTWJteDF4aWdJOTBxRXlfWmk1bThnSWczM2hRZ2ViYTZlbXJqTG82MXc</guid></item><item><title>医生揭示了可能预示焦虑发作的令人惊讶的症状- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/doctors-reveal-surprising-symptoms-may-133900874.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;Surprising Physical Symptoms of an Anxiety Attack&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;Olga Rolenko - Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every single person experiences &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/mental-health/a65531608/anxiety-disorder-symptoms/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:anxiety;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;anxiety&lt;/a&gt; at one point or another. When you're waiting in line, stuck in traffic, or awaiting the results of a test you are likely to feel your stress levels start to creep up. In addition to feeling anxious in understandably stressful situations, nearly one in five Americans also have an anxiety disorder, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.nami.org/about-mental-illness/mental-health-conditions/anxiety-disorders/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:National Alliance on Mental Illness;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;National Alliance on Mental Illness&lt;/a&gt;, making it the most common mental health concern in the US. But how can you distinguish between occasional feelings of anxiety and anxiety that may require treatment? Knowing the physical symptoms of anxiety is a great place to start.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you're experiencing anxiety, you may feel irritable, tired, restless, and simply out of balance, according to &lt;a href="https://www.providence.org/doctors/profile/749434-david-arthur-merrill" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:David Merrill, M.D., Ph.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;David Merrill, M.D., Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a psychiatrist at the Pacific Neuroscience Institute in Santa Monica, CA. While these feelings are easy to associate with anxiety, physical symptoms that mimic a &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a31698322/coronavirus-vs-flu-vs-allergies/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:cold, flu, allergies;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;cold, flu, allergies&lt;/a&gt;, or even a &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/life/a22789047/hangover-cures/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:hangover;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;hangover&lt;/a&gt; are not—even though they could be connected. Dr. Merrill said that these mental and physical symptoms may be linked in an ongoing cycle of anxiety. For example, anxiety could cause digestive problems, and those effects could, in turn, worsen your anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meet the experts: &lt;a href="https://www.providence.org/doctors/profile/749434-david-arthur-merrill" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:David Merrill, M.D., Ph.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;David Merrill, M.D., Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a psychiatrist at the Pacific Neuroscience Institute in Santa Monica, CA; &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1134283468/joseph-d-laino" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Joseph Laino, Psy.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Joseph Laino, Psy.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a clinical psychologist and clinical assistant professor of psychiatry at NYU Grossman School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here, mental health experts share the most common physical ways that your body can manifest anxiety, plus how to address these symptoms and the anxiety behind them so you can feel better fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Physical symptoms of anxiety&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Rapid heart rate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anxiety is part of the body’s built-in alarm system, alerting us to danger in the surrounding environment, according to &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1134283468/joseph-d-laino" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Joseph Laino, Psy.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Joseph Laino, Psy.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a clinical psychologist and clinical assistant professor of psychiatry at NYU Grossman School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A part of the brain called the amygdala rings that alarm during a perceived threat and it causes a cascade of effects—such as a surge of the hormones cortisol and adrenaline—meant to prep us to flee or fight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That can increase your heart rate and &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a30915774/what-causes-high-blood-pressure/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:blood pressure;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;, and even lead to heart palpitations, Dr. Laino said. “That reaction is essential to our health and preservation, because a surge of anxiety can propel us to move quickly,” he explained. But when that alarm button seems stuck in the “on” position, it can exacerbate these reactions, which are designed to be temporary.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Chills or sweating&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of the fight-or-flight response, you may experience a sudden temperature change, Dr. Merrill said. That’s because another part of the brain involved in anxiety is the hypothalamus, which regulates body heat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because of that, you could have chills, &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a20484754/6-common-causes-of-hot-flashes-that-arent-menopause/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:feel drenched in sweat;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;feel drenched in sweat&lt;/a&gt;, or weirdly, both at the same time. That effect could also come from the way muscles fire up during an anxiety response, he added, as one more way to get you ready to take on threats. That’s why you may have odd &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a22586222/body-aches-causes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:muscle aches;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;muscle aches&lt;/a&gt; in conjunction with the hot or cold flashes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Shortness of breath&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your heart and lungs work in concert to keep you going strong, so when one is affected, the other is likely to be, too. If you’re experiencing a sudden rise in heart rate, that could lower your oxygen intake and your lungs see that as a tip-off to power up, so they start working harder, Dr. Merrill said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is why, in extreme anxiety—like a &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/mental-health/a19863296/panic-attack-symptoms/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:panic attack;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;panic attack&lt;/a&gt;—you’ll not only have a rapid heart rate, but also shortness of breath, and the advice with those is to try and implement deep breathing so that both can get corrected,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, if you’re having chest pains, the symptoms don’t subside, or it feels worse after a few minutes, seek immediate medical attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Nausea or indigestion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the parts of the brain and certain hormones being associated with anxiety, the central nervous system plays a major role in the stress response as well. Dr. Merrill noted that there are more nerve fibers in the gut than anywhere else in the body. That’s why, when you feel excited, you have those butterflies—it’s your nervous system responding to stimulus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another hormone, serotonin, steps in here as well, he added. Most of your serotonin—the “happy chemical” that send signals between nerve cells—is in your gut, and when emotional distress happens, it can throw off your nerve signaling and serotonin response. The result? Belly problems. “Any kind of emotional imbalance like anxiety is likely to create stomach issues, such as &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a46706659/how-to-ease-nausea-naturally/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:nausea;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;nausea&lt;/a&gt;, indigestion, and upset stomach,” Dr. Merrill said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Constipation or diarrhea&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the body prepares to respond to a threat, it shuttles resources like blood flow to what it considers necessary for short-term mobilization. What’s not needed when you’re in the middle of a fight or you’re sprinting away from danger? Digestion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As your blood flows toward muscles, vision, and hearing to react to threats, your motility can change,” said Dr. Merrill. That often results in &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a30896279/constipation-symptoms-causes-treatment/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:constipation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;constipation&lt;/a&gt; but can also swing in the other direction toward diarrhea. In some cases, you may toggle between the two. Related effects can include &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a20472936/best-remedies-for-gas-and-bloating/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:bloating;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;bloating&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a29542143/smelly-farts/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:excessive gas;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;excessive gas&lt;/a&gt;, abdominal pain, and cramping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Tingling, sharp pains, and tightness&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Merrill explained that because the central nervous system is connected to the peripheral nervous system, when there’s anxiety in the brain, it sends out signals all along the connections throughout your body. Much like your muscles, heart, and lungs are prepped for a threat, your nerves fire up to ensure the rest of your body is ready to jump or punch, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Because your nerves are activated, that can create an effect anywhere along those nerve systems,” said Dr. Merrill. “You may have &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a32631827/tingling-in-feet/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:tingling fingers or toes;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;tingling fingers or toes&lt;/a&gt;, for example, or the hairs on your arms stand up like you’re scared.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a nerve fires suddenly, there could be sharp pain or tightness as well—especially in areas where the nerves are in tighter clusters, like your lower back, jaw, or neck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to deal with your symptoms and ease your anxiety&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;So once you start to notice and recognize physical manifestations of your anxiety, what should you do about them? For starters, mindfulness-based practices can help, especially if they involve some type of physical movement that benefits both body and mind. Dr. Merrill suggested &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/fitness/workouts/g30417941/best-yoga-stretches/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:yoga;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;yoga&lt;/a&gt; or tai chi, for example, because they incorporate breathwork and movement in their practices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In terms of treatment, Dr. Laino suggested talking with your healthcare provider about both your symptoms and anxiety as a possible cause to ensure you’re getting an accurate diagnosis from a trained professional.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of all, take it seriously. “Just because a symptom is linked to anxiety doesn’t mean it should be ignored,” Dr. Laino said. “There are various medications and talk therapies that can help people who suffer with acute, chronic, or post-traumatic anxieties.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Best of all, as your anxiety knots get loosened, it’s likely many of your physical issues will start to ease as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 14:51:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQckNFOXZxZnE4ejNFQU1qVXRTczZfMm1YOEF3T0tBSWlYb05kTUxOU0dteENYczE0QzBhUkt1djFCQ2NlNzR4LWxOZlUzbDVvbmJvZm82ekV1Q1NYbV9ySlh1MWJ4RXZjYWtsazV0UVY1a3Zwd1AxejFrbHJOYk9ub2c2cW1XWm9BMnc</guid></item><item><title>白发和癌症之间的联系-对话</title><link>https://theconversation.com/how-grey-hair-and-cancer-may-be-linked-268405</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="grid-ten large-grid-nine grid-last content-body content entry-content instapaper_body inline-promos" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Grey hair is an inevitable hallmark of ageing. It’s a visual reminder of the passing years and all the bodily changes that accompany it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But emerging scientific research is challenging this simple narrative – revealing that those silver strands on our heads could be an outward sign of our body’s own intricate defences against &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/cancer-14"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41556-025-01769-9"&gt;new study&lt;/a&gt; in mice has uncovered the remarkable ways in which our bodies manage cellular damage – a process key in both ageing and cancer. In ageing, cellular damage gradually weakens and disrupts cell function. In cancer, unrepaired or faulty cells can trigger abnormal growth and tumour formation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The work here has highlighted a surprising connection between the loss of pigment in our hair and the mechanisms that can keep deadly cancers at bay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/ctm2.1720"&gt;Melanocyte stem cells&lt;/a&gt; are at the heart of this discovery. These cells reside deep within the hair follicles and serve as a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/ctm2.1720"&gt;reservoir for melanocytes&lt;/a&gt; – the pigment-producing cells responsible for hair and skin colour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under normal circumstances, our melanocyte stem cells &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2217/mmt.15.4"&gt;replenish these pigment-producing&lt;/a&gt; cells through cyclical regeneration, a process characterised by repeated phases of activity, resting and renewal in sync with the natural cycles of hair growth and loss. This grants a steady supply of pigment and thus vibrant hair colour throughout most of our lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But every day, our cells endure assaults on its own DNA (the genetic material inside our cells) from sources such as ultraviolet radiation, chemical exposure and even our own cellular metabolism process. This &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1053/j.seminhematol.2016.11.001"&gt;cellular damage&lt;/a&gt; contributes to both ageing and to the risk of cancers – such as melanoma, a type of skin cancer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This new study sheds light on what happens when melanocyte stem cells deep within the supportive niche of the hair follicle sustain DNA damage – particularly a type of damage called double-strand breaks. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When this happens, the melanocyte stem cells can undergo a process called &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41581-022-00601-z"&gt;“seno-differentiation”&lt;/a&gt;. In essence, this means that the stem cells irreversibly mature into pigment cells – then disappear from the stem cell pool, leading to the gradual appearance of grey in our hair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="align-center "&gt;
            
            &lt;figcaption&gt;
              &lt;span class="caption"&gt;DNA damage can cause some of these stem cells to irreversibly mature and turn grey.&lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;span class="attribution"&gt;&lt;a class="source" href="https://www.shutterstock.com/image-photo/close-gray-hair-unrecognizable-man-combing-2563295985"&gt;Beti Argi/ Shutterstock&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;
          &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This protective process is tightly regulated by internal signalling pathways which allow the cells to communicate with each other. By removing these mature cells from the stem cell population, this prevents the accumulation and possible future spread of genetic mutations or DNA changes that could promote cancer. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a sense, each grey hair is a small victory of bodily self-sacrifice: a cell choosing to bow out rather than risk turning malignant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Cancer link&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story doesn’t end there, however. Not all DNA damage triggers this protective process. In their experiments, the researchers exposed melanocyte stem cells in mice to potent cancer-causing chemicals as well as UV radiation. Remarkably, under these stressors, melanocyte stem cells were found to bypass seno-differentiation altogether. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, signals from the surrounding tissues actually encouraged the damaged cells to self-renew and continue dividing – despite carrying genetic damage. This created a cellular environment ripe for the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2217/mmt.15.4"&gt;emergence of melanoma&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This research suggests that the fate of melanocyte stem cells appears to hinge on both the specific kind of damage they receive and on the molecular cues present in their micro-environment. Stressors such as chemicals or UV light, which cause the cells’ DNA strands to break, also cause the melanocyte stem cells to self-destruct by default. This same process causes grey hair. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But when under the influence of cancer cells, these damaged melanocyte stem cells persist – creating seeds from which melanoma can grow. Scientists describe this dynamic as &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41556-025-01769-9"&gt;“antagonistic fates”&lt;/a&gt; – where the same stem cell population can take two dramatically different paths depending on the circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Importantly, these findings reframe grey hair and melanoma not as unrelated outcomes, but as twin fates of the body’s ancient struggle to balance tissue renewal and avoid cancer. Greying is not itself a shield against cancer, but instead a byproduct of a protective process that eliminates risky cells. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conversely, when the control mechanisms falter or are subverted by carcinogens, the door is left open for malignancy. This new understanding may also help begin to explain why we’re more likely to &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12943-024-02020-z"&gt;develop cancer as we get older&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, it’s crucial to note the limits of these findings. Much of the pivotal evidence comes from experiments in mice. This means research still needs to be conducted in humans to understand if our melanocyte stem cells also function in a similar way. Biological differences between species, as well as complexities of human lifestyles and genetics, mean the picture for our own hair and cancer risk is nuanced. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, these discoveries open exciting avenues for both cancer research and ageing science. Understanding the signals that nudge stem cells toward differentiation or risky expansion could someday enable therapies to reinforce the body’s natural  safeguards, potentially lowering cancer risk as we age. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are broader implications as well. This information could help explain why some people develop melanoma even without having been exposed to clear &lt;a href="https://www.macmillan.org.uk/cancer-information-and-support/melanoma/causes-and-risk-factors-of-melanoma"&gt;risk factors&lt;/a&gt; – and why &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41416-019-0721-1"&gt;cancers and tissue degeneration&lt;/a&gt; so often go &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.semcancer.2011.09.001"&gt;hand-in-hand&lt;/a&gt; in later life. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story of grey hair is not just about vanity or the inevitable march of time. It’s about evolution, adaptation and the ceaseless vigilance of our bodies’ internal guardians. Those silver strands may be telling us something profound: that amid the competition between ageing and cancer, sometimes it’s worth sacrificing a pigment cell for the sake of the whole organism.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

        

        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Conversation</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 14:09:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE0yaEJsNnc5d0FCcWIwSHZLdkVYVGFaeDVHTEI0UTFSeTNIYV9PNjZWdUZoTkxiQ00tMHYybTZEQ0pyNVdIc2JzR2lsUHVQb2FLQlhDbG95R1hzaUFicEQxOF96S2NhbkFmNkY3dFA1bnZsQ2hFOGJFWnJ5blpVdw</guid></item><item><title>您呼吸的空气可能会对您的大脑产生什么影响-《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/what-the-air-you-breathe-may-be-doing-to-your-brain/</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxOWlhxX3VzN3BjR01lRlVid2pIWU1xWXRpMWhsVzExMlRGTVZ1akp6blJhMVVZb01oRS1kTzFoT3F2NUQzLVlmZ3JYcXdscTNnVXBmcDEzRXlnLWVZRGRIUHF2amY1YklxM1V3YnM5bHZyWnJvQXlGdTFhdWlMcXZXRmdlb0p4bW10aVJkRDNqcjNYTm5scmdLYjdNS2hYSGhHT0pv?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;What the air you breathe may be doing to your brain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqNggKIjBDQklTSGpvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoRUtEd2lXaUxqMkR4R1ZabDAzSVlJN0ppZ0FQAQ?hl=en-US&amp;amp;gl=US&amp;amp;ceid=US:en&amp;amp;oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View Full Coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 14:06:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxOWlhxX3VzN3BjR01lRlVid2pIWU1xWXRpMWhsVzExMlRGTVZ1akp6blJhMVVZb01oRS1kTzFoT3F2NUQzLVlmZ3JYcXdscTNnVXBmcDEzRXlnLWVZRGRIUHF2amY1YklxM1V3YnM5bHZyWnJvQXlGdTFhdWlMcXZXRmdlb0p4bW10aVJkRDNqcjNYTm5scmdLYjdNS2hYSGhHT0pv</guid></item><item><title>所以你的保险让你的医生失望了。现在该怎么办？ -《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/life/so-your-insurance-dropped-your-doctor-now-what/</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOaXlyNmRNeFFlZER0WEg0U3RRVmVnTWg5WUN6QTlhVVVaTGs0Y1JCcXZmcFZPemlqMWJQVVFjRHp4SGZfOGxKS1FzT3p6ZGQ2OU5uRlFMdWFRWENmS1gzcG5jSjZpZnIyWjJmRGdEcldXTHhpeDZMLTBraGtUSThEQk9vR291b3BB?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;So your insurance dropped your doctor. Now what?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqNggKIjBDQklTSGpvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoRUtEd2pFLXZEdUR4RWdFNk1KWDBTX3RpZ0FQAQ?hl=en-US&amp;amp;gl=US&amp;amp;ceid=US:en&amp;amp;oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View Full Coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 14:00:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOaXlyNmRNeFFlZER0WEg0U3RRVmVnTWg5WUN6QTlhVVVaTGs0Y1JCcXZmcFZPemlqMWJQVVFjRHp4SGZfOGxKS1FzT3p6ZGQ2OU5uRlFMdWFRWENmS1gzcG5jSjZpZnIyWjJmRGdEcldXTHhpeDZMLTBraGtUSThEQk9vR291b3BB</guid></item><item><title>每个人都在谈论检测50种癌症的血液测试。我试过了。-加拿大雅虎新闻</title><link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/everyones-buzzing-blood-test-detects-130037787.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"No &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/james-van-der-beek-jenna-122503435.html" data-ylk="slk:cancer;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; signal detected." The blood test results popped up in my online health portal without much fanfare. A doctor would chat about them with me later, congratulating me on the "phew"-worthy result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I took the Galleri mult-cancer early detection (MCED) test about a year ago in 2024 as part of my longevity-focused stay at &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/went-bougie-medical-resort-shocking-115009427.html" data-ylk="slk:Canyon Ranch;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;Canyon Ranch&lt;/a&gt;, a &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/people-spend-20-000-resort-114006254.html" data-ylk="slk:luxury wellness retreat;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;luxury wellness retreat&lt;/a&gt; in Tucson, Arizona. Galleri – which &lt;a href="https://www.galleri.com/patient/faqs#tab-448492-448507" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:costs $949;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;costs $949&lt;/a&gt;, and is not currently FDA-approved – is a blood test that studies DNA fragments shed into the bloodstream. Patients need a prescription before pulling up their sleeves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;GRAIL, the company behind Galleri, recently &lt;a href="https://grail.com/press-releases/grail-pathfinder-2-results-show-galleri-multi-cancer-early-detection-blood-test-increased-cancer-detection-more-than-seven-fold-when-added-to-uspstf-a-and-b-recommended-screenings/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:presented findings;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;presented findings&lt;/a&gt; from a study across 25,000 healthy adults over the age of 50. The test, the company says, found cancers at earlier stages and in organs that don't have routine screening. Galleri discovered cancer signals in 216 people, and 133 of them indeed had cancer. It also correctly predicted the cancer's origin 92% of the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"We're able to isolate those DNA fragments, sequence them and look for those tumor-specific markers from the blood," says &lt;a href="https://grail.com/stories/member/megan-hall/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Megan Hall;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Megan Hall&lt;/a&gt;, the vice president of medical and corporate affairs at GRAIL. If a "cancer signal" is detected, it also provides a cancer signal origin prediction, or a clue to the providers and the patient which organ that signal could be coming from. If that origin was the pancreas, for example, doctors would know where to start looking for the possible cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"The key plain takeaway: (This type of testing) &lt;em&gt;may&lt;/em&gt; complement current screening by identifying lethal cancers that are otherwise undetected earlier and with limited downstream burden," says &lt;a href="https://www.feinberg.northwestern.edu/faculty-profiles/az/profile.html?xid=46749" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Mohamed Abazeed;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Mohamed Abazeed&lt;/a&gt;, chair and professor of radiation oncology at Northwestern University, who was not involved with the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The big question: Is this the future of cancer treatment? A simple blood test? It's not that easy. The new research from the company, while promising, isn't going to get you out of your recommended colonoscopies and mammograms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;'Just waiting to find' these hidden cancers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Multiple companies are trying to detect cancer via blood test. But GRAIL is the one you're hearing about in the mainstream thanks to its funding of large, international prospective clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"It was clear to me, as we were running the study, that we were picking up some novel cancers at an early stage that we previously had no means of detecting," says &lt;a href="https://www.ohsu.edu/providers/nima-nabavizadeh-md" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Nima Nabavizadeh;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Nima Nabavizadeh&lt;/a&gt;, a radiation oncologist at the Oregon Health and Science University and author of GRAIL's Pathfinder 2 study presented at the European Society for Medical Oncology Congress in October.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;We only widely screen for five cancers in the United States: &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/25-old-survived-breast-cancer-120101005.html" data-ylk="slk:breast;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;breast&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://health.yahoo.com/conditions/cancer/colon-cancer/articles/colon-cancer-rising-people-under-090528300.html" data-ylk="slk:colorectal;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;colorectal&lt;/a&gt;, prostate, cervical and lung cancer, the latter in only high-risk patients. But 70% of cancer deaths come from those without a recommended screening test. That's where Galleri hopes to split the difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is the Galleri blood test the future of cancer treatment? It's not that simple. The new research from the company, while promising, isn't some cure-all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"These are largely cancers that we're normally, outside of these blood tests, just waiting to find them, either incidentally or because somebody has symptoms associated with them," Nabavizadeh says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The test doesn't pick up some cancers as well, like prostate cancer, though there's already an effective diagnostic tool for that known as the PSA test. Why does Galleri detect certain cancers better than others? Some shed more DNA than others, i.e. head and neck and pancreatic cancers versus prostate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Interest in the test has grown: More than 15,000 healthcare providers have prescribed it, and health systems like Rush University Health System in Chicago, Community Health Network in Indiana and Mercy in Missouri offer it, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dana-farber.org/find-a-doctor/elizabeth-betsy-odonnell" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Elizabeth O'Donnell;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Elizabeth O'Donnell&lt;/a&gt;, director, of the Multi-Cancer Early Detection Clinic at Dana-Farber Cancer Institute, says this testing is "a really good starting point for potentially addressing a massive unmet need in medicine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;span class="exclude-from-newsgate"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read up: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/people-spend-20-000-resort-114006254.html" data-ylk="slk:People spend $20,000 at this resort to uncover secrets about their health. Is it worth it?;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;People spend $20,000 at this resort to uncover secrets about their health. Is it worth it?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;'A positive blood test is not a diagnosis'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Beware that Galleri does and can pick up &lt;a href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/what-does-indolent-mean-2615124" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:indolent cancers;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;indolent cancers&lt;/a&gt; – i.e. slow-growing ones like Chronic lymphocytic leukemia – which you and your provider may decide not to treat, or just keep an eye on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"We want to make sure that we are detecting those more aggressive cancers that really do warrant treatment," says Hall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Overall, doctors both involved with and not involved with the study aren't concerned about the Galleri test and &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/got-14-medical-tests-done-114820202.html" data-ylk="slk:overdiagnosis;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;overdiagnosis&lt;/a&gt;, or sending people down a path of unnecessary endless treatment. About 1% of people receive a positive cancer detection signal, which means 99% live their lives and go about their normal recommended screenings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But "a positive blood test is not a diagnosis," says &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Furldefense.com%2Fv3%2F__https%3A%2F%2Fsylvester-doctors.umiamihealth.org%2Fprovider%2Fgilberto-lopes%2F525521__%3B!!KVu0SnhVq1hAFvslES2Y!Po6LVm_mkQeeRLU-lubF15akAxeMBhaGjo-_uW72uqYt38KJquUP2WWe2PzvIGf-MJlNemIYg-6AJQN4zFXL1SjN%24&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CDOliver%40usatoday.com%7C1fc10029a25741e2b32208de1887632c%7Cbc924c8d3e164e88bf26d7fcfb14f2d5%7C0%7C0%7C638975167322703916%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=It6sRta3RI5Gq7%2FPOxUsWFB9j3wXs7D613riXu6gFcs%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Gilberto Lopes, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Gilberto Lopes, MD&lt;/a&gt;, chief of medical oncology with Sylvester Comprehensive Cancer, part of the University of Miami Health System. "You still need imaging, sometimes a biopsy. That takes time and resources." Health systems and providers need to prepare for patient questions and anxiety, too, especially regarding positive results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;span class="exclude-from-newsgate"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speaking of: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/went-bougie-medical-resort-shocking-115009427.html" data-ylk="slk:I went to this bougie medical resort. A shocking test result spiked my health anxiety.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;I went to this bougie medical resort. A shocking test result spiked my health anxiety.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;The uncertain FDA approval path for Galleri&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;GRAIL is bullish about FDA approval for Galleri, which could make it more accessible if private insurers and Medicare reimburse doctors for running the tests. But according to Abazeed, the FDA will want to see evidence that earlier detection means fewer late-stage cancers or a reduced risk of death. And that still isn't available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If the data bears out, it's a game-changer. But "real-world implementation, however, will require more including standardized diagnostic algorithms, confirmatory imaging and biopsy and proper safeguards to ensure consistent follow-up," Abazeed says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Something must change when it comes to cancer care, O'Donnell says. Sure, people are living longer with cancer, but cures come when you find diseases early. "Anybody who's been in practice long enough knows that we need to be doing something differently," O'Donnell says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;My negative results didn't surprise me. I wasn't exhibiting &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/watch-signs-skin-cancer-experts-110015317.html" data-ylk="slk:cancer symptoms;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;cancer symptoms&lt;/a&gt; and the test is geared toward those 50 and older anyway (I was 32 at the time), given that age is the biggest risk factor for developing cancer. But it was still nice to know that a deadly cancer wasn't hiding in a random organ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Before you take the test yourself, make sure you read up on all the caveats and chat with a trusted healthcare provider first. The "no cancer signal detected" sentence was comforting for me and the other 99% – but not a lifetime guarantee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on USA TODAY: &lt;a href="https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/health-wellness/2025/11/05/galleri-early-cancer-detection-blood-test/87009742007/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Galleri early cancer detection blood test: I tried it.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Galleri early cancer detection blood test: I tried it.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Canada</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:00:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxPY1M3Qk9vMzJOU01ZQ0ZXSy1OV1h3VFNnTlJoMWVRb05zS25pZS1QWGxaVlgxSWxGa3ZpSmRITk9RUGUycnROanAyNlNOV1h3LUdQWTFrTU5zRVNyYnlWVlNlcFo2aEZaaDYySU5pT3VBNm45YXB3eE05M215MUFHMVJnTQ</guid></item><item><title>独家：研究机构FutureHouse推出人工智能科学家和营利性分拆- Endpoints News</title><link>https://endpoints.news/research-institute-futurehouse-debuts-ai-scientist-kosmos-and-for-profit-spinoff/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="epn_content"&gt;
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Neu­ro­sci­en­tist Math­ieu Bour­denx con­sid­ered him­self fair­ly skep­ti­cal that AI mod­els would ac­tu­al­ly be able to think and rea­son over ex­per­i­ments like a sci­en­tist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; That was …&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="epn_limit" data-gt="r"&gt;
    &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://endpoints.news/wp-content/themes/endpoints-rakia/assets/svg/epn_logo.svg" alt="Endpoints News"&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Sign up to read this article for free.&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Get free access to a limited number of articles, plus choose newsletters to get straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

                            
                        &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Endpoints News</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxNZG00ZDQtR19YYWFCWDRiR3B1WHZYUUlhQ3pSdzhrNnVJQUQ5Tzk1M3kxdC1fcGFiaURTdE9oZVJIR1M2NDlWM1F1VFBHLV96WHNWNW5DM2JLLWM3NXRBeUFMM0FBNWd4YUN4MWp6cmdMYk1PZWRScGhpNkhISDhMVHd5MnFuM01lcGh3Q1IzLXpwQXRHVGZ3dWw3YWxva1RSNTRvWFdCdw</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现了可以降低血压的令人惊讶的因素： “可能具有显着的长期健康益处” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/scientists-discover-surprising-factor-decrease-113000334.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Scientists recently uncovered a heartening effect of beetroot juice on the elderly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Researchers discovered that beetroot juice notably lowers blood pressure in older people. According to &lt;a href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/beet-juice-lowers-blood-pressure-in-older-people-by-changing-their-oral-microbiome/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Good News Network;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Good News Network&lt;/a&gt;, the University of Exeter followed prior research that had "shown [how] a high nitrate diet can reduce blood pressure … [and] the risk of heart disease."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As beetroot juice is rich in nitrates and nutrients that nourish a healthy heart, it is especially significant for those of higher ages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"When older adults drank a concentrated 'shot' of beetroot juice twice a day for two weeks, their blood pressure decreased – an effect not seen in a younger group used for comparison," said Good News Network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The key difference between age groups was the alteration in the oral biome of subjects under thirty versus those above sixty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;By suppressing bacteria that could become harmful, the juice itself changed the makeup of what was in the older test subjects' mouths, and in turn, they "experienced a notable decrease in the mouth bacteria Prevotella … along with an increase in the growth of bacteria known to benefit health, such as Neisseria."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This discovery falls in line with previous understandings of how nitrate-heavy foods can positively influence the crucial inner workings of the human body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Evidence has shown that not only do nitrates help with heart health, but they also provide other benefits such as higher protection from metabolic diseases and more efficient food processing, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6147587/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:per the NCBI;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;per the NCBI&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Studies like this one bring a sense of hope for those looking to maintain the long-term health of their bodies, and as more research goes into &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/journeys/eat-cleaner-cheaper-food/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dietary changes;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;dietary changes&lt;/a&gt; that people can implement, more pivotal discoveries will arise as a result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Study author Anni Vanhatalo, professor at the University of Exeter, emphasized that "encouraging older adults to consume more nitrate-rich vegetables could have significant long term health benefits," though she made sure to clarify "that if you don't like beetroot, there are many nitrate-rich alternatives like spinach, rocket, fennel, celery and kale."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/hacks-newsletter/?recSjQHScZxzWsTyu" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for easy tips to &lt;strong&gt;save more&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;waste less&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQd0ljSmEzbHBGQ2pRU1ZQVHhweGItczBudHZRdUZOWldsOXp0cm1ENGN1dHQ1eWJxSWh6czRRcTBuTy1qRE1rdngxdEdfTWxaUm8zWkhnZHRmbEZMMThtOWk4NExvbEpxRDRLWV9tZ2J1Ni1GdDVST1NYajBtM2thT0lrRmVmSkpuMGhXUXlDUlVVMUNITGxhbmNpWjlsZw</guid></item><item><title>救命！我婆婆带了一位惊喜客人，强迫我离开我的家。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/11/family-advice-in-laws-surprise-allergies.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="22" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhjl20l5001jodkvsgzr2y5v@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dear Prudence is Slate’s advice column. For this edition, Leah Prinzivalli&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;a Slate features editor,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;will be filling in as Prudie. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSd_tjeEx47o2lIrDSg1Ioh_9shU0REmIAAtvoVHZj_FWz76AA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Submit questions here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(It’s anonymous!)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhjl26w700153b793ytv8lxb@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Prudence,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="19" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhjl22xp000o3b79vvvat57s@published"&gt;Recently, my mother-in-law came for a visit. I am seriously allergic to dogs and cats (I wish I weren’t!).&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="72" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhl39j3b000d3b79fxxwgg66@published"&gt;My mother-in-law has a Chihuahua, “Chari,” who accompanies her everywhere. She assured us that Chari would be staying with a dog sitter. Well, surprise! My MIL showed up with the dog in tow, claiming he “wouldn’t be able to stand being apart from his Mommy.” I ended up having to stay at my sister’s, and a cleaning service had to be hired to purge the house after my MIL and Chari left.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="87" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhjl22zk000p3b79f52tyy01@published"&gt;I am furious with my husband for siding with his mother over me. She lives three hours away, not three states, and it wouldn’t have been the end of the world for him to have insisted she go home due to my allergies. He thinks I made too big a deal over the situation, and even that maybe some exposure to the dog might have helped me develop some “immunity!” How can I get it into his head that he needs to support me in the future?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhjl231d000q3b79hf9z10uz@published"&gt;—Forced Out&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhjl233d000r3b79l3b1u6a6@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Forced,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="239" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhjl235d000s3b79jru5xfku@published"&gt;I really wish I could get a glass of wine with you and hear about a million more details about your relationship with your mother-in-law, husband, and even this poor, anxious dog. But in the absence of knowing how you feel about these mammals, I’ve developed a conspiracy theory: Is it possible your MIL brought Chari on purpose, knowing you’d have to leave, because she was craving some solo time with her son? That’s exactly the kind of stunt I could see some of today’s overzealous #BoyMom parenting influencers pulling in 20 years when their beloved little princes grow up and get married. If there’s part of you that thinks bringing Chari was a bit of light bioterrorism in service of mother-son time, I’d gently float the idea that your husband makes a solo visit out to his mom soon, or plans another trip with just her. Even if the next visit is still a trip to your house, ask him to make sure to carve out a special activity or meal for just the two of them and inform his mom ahead of time about the plan. He should make the special activity something she’ll definitely want to do, and it shouldn’t allow dogs. It doesn’t sound like your MIL is willing to make accommodations for you, but maybe she’ll make them to visit a museum or attend a play with her son, and you’ll reap the benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="78" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhjl2377000t3b79on2aibkz@published"&gt;Another possibility: Despite what I’m sure were clear explanations about your pet allergy, maybe your MIL didn’t quite comprehend that you would actually have to leave your house to accommodate her. There’s a small part of me that thinks now that she knows she inconvenienced you so deeply, she’d be too embarrassed to ever repeat this behavior. But my guess is she would have checked herself into a pet-friendly hotel or Airbnb immediately if that were the case.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="170" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhl68n3500153b793pocml8o@published"&gt;So you’re right: The bigger issue here is that you need to compromise with your husband. Before the next visit, you two need to get on the same page about what you mean when you say he needs to support you. When you found out she was bringing the dog, was your first suggestion that she turn around and go home? I could see why she and your husband might bristle at that. I’m not sure it’s fair to insist that supporting you meant making her turn right around and go home. But making you leave wasn’t a fair solution either. It sounds like what you might need from him is an apology and an affirmation that he believes you when you say your allergies are real and challenging (sure, &lt;a href="https://www.cedars-sinai.org/blog/the-pros-and-cons-of-allergy-immunotherapy.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;immunotherapy for allergies exists, but it’s not at all a simple process&lt;/a&gt;). And he might need &lt;em&gt;you &lt;/em&gt;to affirm that you do want to spend time with his mom as long as her visit doesn’t put you at medical risk.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="104" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhjl239i000u3b79aolh8zo2@published"&gt;Whether the dog is just a dog and not a chemical agent meant to run you from your home, I’d like to issue all three of you a reminder that pet-friendly hotels and Airbnbs exist. A pet-friendly accommodation is a glaring third option that doesn’t involve anyone being chased from their house or canceling what I’d imagine was a much-anticipated trip. If there aren’t any near you, a friend, neighbor, or even local vet will know of a dog sitter who will be willing to watch Chari in the future. I wish all four of you many years of stress- and sneeze-free visits ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhjl95h5001p3b79g8hyhzv5@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Leah&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmhjl9aae002b3b796iu9wm1z@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Classic Prudie

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="79" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhjl973400203b7922z2wfxp@published"&gt;I have been married 10 years and together for 13. My stepdaughters “Gracie and Nikki” are 28 and 25 respectively. Gracie and I have a good relationship, while her sister can barely be civil towards me. As a teenager, Nikki treated me as her own personal maid, chauffeur, and chef. She had zero respect and would stomp off screaming if asked to demonstrate any. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/10/dear-prudence-cruel-free-nanny.html"&gt;I took a lot of “walks” when she had her friends drop in without warning…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmhjl20l5001modkvokvo1wg2@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQVnJDWml3clZFLWl3cW55eWxsRXduX1czRFlobTVKYUlMUExBZXkwUVdWanhCbmcxNTNFUjFnenE2NFNQQTJhUjlsdGRKZ0p1UzhMcmdPSmJmOFJDbEE3ZVpQZ3RtOG5wZFBMYldPWll0d21XLVZEdTB1a2xQTWp4NVNmZUE</guid></item><item><title>晚睡？您的就寝时间可能会预测心脏病发作；以下是科学的说法-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/sleeping-late-your-bedtime-might-predict-a-heart-attack-heres-what-science-says/articleshow/125104489.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleep is essential for keeping the human body and heart in balance. It regulates blood pressure, metabolism, and overall cardiovascular function. Yet, in modern life, many people go to bed later because of long work hours or time spent on digital devices. Scientists are now learning that when we sleep may be just as important as how much we sleep. While poor or short sleep has long been known to raise the risk of heart problems, recent research has begun to explore whether bedtime itself plays a role. A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/cardiovascular-medicine/articles/10.3389/fcvm.2021.709468/full" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;new study published in Frontiers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; found that people who regularly go to bed after midnight on weekdays have a higher risk of heart attack. This discovery suggests that the timing of sleep could directly affect heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How our body clock keeps the heart in rhythm&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The human body follows a 24-hour internal clock known as the circadian rhythm. This clock helps control when we feel awake or sleepy and regulates vital functions such as blood pressure, hormone levels, and heart rate. The heart and blood vessels work in line with this natural rhythm, staying more active during the day and resting at night. When people stay up well past midnight, they interfere with this built-in schedule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Over time, this disruption can place extra strain on the cardiovascular system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Fix Your Sleep Naturally! Sadhguru’s 5-Step Routine for Deep Rest&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the Frontiers study, researchers found that people who regularly went to bed late on weekdays were more likely to experience a heart attack. Interestingly, this pattern did not appear on weekends, suggesting that weekday routines, combined with early wake-up times, may increase the heart’s workload. These results show that bedtime can influence heart health independently of sleep duration, highlighting the importance of aligning sleep with the body’s natural rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What the research revealed about bedtime and heart risk&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study examined information from 4,576 adults who took part in the Sleep Heart Health Study, which tracks sleep patterns and cardiovascular outcomes. Participants reported their usual bedtime and wake-up time for both weekdays and weekends. Their bedtimes were grouped into four ranges: before 10:00 pm, between 10:01 pm and 11:00 pm, between 11:01 pm and midnight, and after midnight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Researchers followed them for more than ten years to see who developed myocardial infarction, the medical term for heart attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results showed a clear pattern. Those who went to bed after midnight during weekdays were much more likely to have a heart attack than those who slept between 10:01 pm and 11:00 pm. Even after accounting for other risk factors such as smoking, body weight, high blood pressure, diabetes, alcohol use, and total sleep duration, the link remained strong. People with late weekday bedtimes had about a 63 per cent higher risk of heart attack. Interestingly, going to bed very early, before 10:00 pm, also carried a slightly higher risk, forming a U-shaped pattern where both extremes of bedtime appeared less favourable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why late nights can harm the heart&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are several reasons why staying up late might increase heart risk. First, delaying sleep disrupts the production of melatonin, a hormone that helps control blood pressure and supports repair of blood vessels during the night. Low melatonin levels can lead to higher blood pressure and more inflammation in the arteries. Late nights are also often linked to shorter and poorer-quality sleep, reducing the amount of deep rest the body needs to recover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who stay up late may also adopt habits that harm the heart, such as eating late, being less physically active, and spending long hours exposed to bright screens. These behaviours can increase blood sugar and cholesterol levels, encourage weight gain, and heighten stress hormone activity. Over time, such changes can damage blood vessels and make heart attacks more likely. Laboratory studies have shown that irregular sleep timing raises cortisol, impairs glucose control, and increases blood clotting which are all factors that contribute to cardiovascular disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How regular sleep habits can protect the heart&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings suggest that a consistent bedtime may help protect against heart problems. Going to bed around the same time each night supports the body’s internal clock and allows the cardiovascular system to rest and repair properly. Health researchers are beginning to recognise that sleep timing should be considered alongside diet, exercise, and smoking in assessing heart-disease risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Late-night lifestyles have become common in modern society, with technology, shift work, and flexible schedules often pushing people to stay awake longer. This pattern can create “social jet lag”, where a person’s biological clock is constantly out of sync with daily routines. Over time, this misalignment may increase blood pressure, disturb metabolism, and raise the risk of obesity and diabetes, all key contributors to heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public-health experts suggest that improving sleep habits could be a simple but effective way to support heart health. Going to bed at a steady, reasonable hour and getting enough rest may help maintain healthy blood pressure, balance stress hormones, and lower inflammation. Although more research is needed to prove that changing bedtime directly reduces heart-attack risk, the current evidence makes one thing clear: the time we go to sleep could be just as important for heart health as how long we stay asleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for informational purposes only and should not be considered medical advice. Please consult a healthcare professional before making any changes to your diet, medication, or lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/do-you-have-a-habit-of-cracking-your-neck-that-quick-relief-could-be-dangerous-and-cause-a-stroke/articleshow/125102931.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Do you have a habit of cracking your neck? That quick relief could be dangerous and cause a stroke&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwJBVV95cUxNcmlPbUNQUjhWcE9XYkZ2S1QzQXpZRzJQTzN5LU9CRS1EeW5wNkhXV2lFaGozMnVXZHNiQnQ5Mi1kNDNyNGhqVkVPTk14UG5RYkQtQ2tSVGVJWHZ4VmEtbUw2X0hYZkZURXRnakRtWHFHTUd6UXBwQWNJLTBFOXZiNUVTenlSUmI2Wm9LVmZKc1RRZWQ1Q21NOThXeVlIaDNNb2RpVm9IWlJwWHpVMUd4MzcycGR1WUV4bFhjWWZOT3c0OXZ3a2NGWmREUlYzckdFNFVLN3hHdnl4czFkdGJoMGxLMzNOSjM4MUVCWm9hQUVtNGZybUVERVpPMkxMWnVRU1Ewd1pNYU9Uak3SAZACQVVfeXFMTW01STc2N2g5Nk9mNGVYRVZ6SlpJcVZUUDlEVzlLQjU2ZTdNVVZUcmZrdHFZbUtRR1dQSlA2NzFuU2FBVWUybUo3VjQ1N3FEck5QQU9pV2tjUHVWamF5S1BndnBRd3NvSmFzSWowUGNkUjJvVzdscFlkRk9yWEpDa3A1QkJHQzZiSzhnMlJQM2pxRC0tSE1EX25fbjNsY3hXV1g4UlA1THFGTUtMN3lZQksyNnZCOUZQSm5FaXdka1c0TzNkYjRDWW9Ydmk1VWh1dFA1dXM1ZVlhdjJZZXZiRjBOODZUdUQzUUxVeFBYRFphNC1mVGw2bm1yc0FhUTJUUDdyNUxFSWJDcjQwaEJObF8</guid></item><item><title>她现年89岁，是顶级营养专家。这是她一天吃的东西。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/11/05/marion-nestle-what-she-eats/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YQFKSYRYJZBB5K3BEFMNTOE3NI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;For more than three decades, Marion Nestle has been telling people what to eat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VHLZ7QR3YJCYJOXI7DYALFLYUQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In the late 1980s, she edited the first Surgeon General’s Report on Nutrition and Health, then went on to co-write the federal government’s Dietary Guidelines for Americans and co-found New York University’s influential food studies program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 10:32:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxPRmJxTngyUzFmaUQ3T19iYk81bUc1QUs5eUJ4WjVTOXRxd3FYX3hxbDdYbzhwZFpDazNrdGtwT0pyc0NkcnowbmFBaVZvbk94bDhzdVdLbUVUeVAzSDMtZS1HWDhKMDV6Ujd3OUpnRzhGMnNWQmNIb2VjUDQyRFpic3QyUFloUQ</guid></item><item><title>阿尔茨海默氏症的血液检测在这里-有线</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/blood-tests-for-alzheimers-have-arrived-but-how-effective-are-they-and-can-they-really-change-patients-lives/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="lead-in-text-callout"&gt;Last month, The&lt;/span&gt; US Food and Drug Administration &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.roche.com/investors/updates/inv-update-2025-10-13b" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.roche.com/investors/updates/inv-update-2025-10-13b"}' href="https://www.roche.com/investors/updates/inv-update-2025-10-13b" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;approved&lt;/a&gt; a new blood test for assisting the diagnosis of Alzheimer’s disease. Produced by Roche, Elecsys pTau181 measures the concentration of a specific molecule—a phosphorylated form of the tau protein—in the blood. Tau is one of two proteins, the other being amyloid, that become malformed and accumulate in the brains of patients with certain types of dementia. It is believed that the buildup of these proteins interferes with the communication of brain cells, leading to these patients’ symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The test had already received authorization in July for marketing in Europe and is thus the first early screening system for Alzheimer’s for use in primary care settings approved in the planet’s two major pharmaceutical markets. It is an opener in what should soon become a crowded field, as there are several other tests in advanced stages of testing and approval.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;How Do Such Tests Work?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Elecsys pTau181 looks in the blood plasma for a form of the tau protein that has a phosphate group attached, which is often found in elevated amounts in Alzheimer’s patients. This molecule is an indirect marker of the plaques of amyloid and neurofibrillary tangles of tau observed in the brains of patients with the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Some other tests have also been approved, though not for early screening. These assess other biomarkers that relate to these two proteins. One test, called Lumipulse and made by the Japanese company Fujirebio, looks at the ratio between another form of phosphorylated tau (pTau217) and a key protein fragment that forms amyloid plaques (amyloid beta peptide 1-42).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The bottom line is that these tests offer clues to the probable presence of amyloidosis in the brain, which then needs to be diagnosed with greater accuracy using more invasive tests, such as a PET (positron emission tomography) scan and cerebrospinal fluid analysis by lumbar puncture, considered the clinical gold standard for diagnosing amyloid pathology in living patients. Even these, however, come with some degree of uncertainty; true diagnostic certainty can only be had with a post-mortem dissection of the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;Why Approve These Tests Now?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;In the past, confirmation of an Alzheimer’s diagnosis was not that important, as there were no drugs or therapies that could alter the course of the disease. But with the &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/alzheimers-drugs-benefits-risks-lecanemab-donanemab/"&gt;approval of new Alzheimer’s monoclonal antibody treatments&lt;/a&gt;, the landscape has changed in the past few years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;To use these medicines, you need a way to confirm which patients can benefit. And since the drugs ideally yield the best results when used early on in the disease’s progression, a relatively inexpensive and minimally invasive diagnostic test will be extremely useful. Subjecting all elderly people with suspected symptoms of cognitive decline to PET scans and cerebrospinal fluid sampling is impractical, so this is where blood testing for Alzheimer’s comes in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;Just How Useful Are These Tests?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Elecsys pTau181 is the first test to be approved for use as a community-screening tool. The idea is for it to be administered at the primary care level—so, for instance, by a primary care physician or general practitioner. The test has been shown to have a good “negative predictive value”—that is, it is effective at accurately indicating who &lt;em&gt;does not&lt;/em&gt; have amyloid disease. In settings where the overall prevalence of amyloid disease is low, a negative result from this test is 97.9 percent reliable. This makes it useful for selecting which patients to put forward for further testing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The results are similar to those of other tests that have already been approved in recent months, such as Lumipulse from Japan’s Fujirebio, which in trials has shown a negative predictive value of about 97 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;However, there is an important limitation to note: for all blood tests for Alzheimer’s, there tends to be a relatively large proportion of patients (15-30 percent is a common estimate) who fall into a gray area of uncertainty, in which the levels of identified biomarkers do not allow for either a positive or a negative answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0wFBVV95cUxOZjdFRXh3cVpfdmhBQ1F0d1F0Ym1va2NscElSMG5kSHBoeTJwNFFSMGxoWVl6X251M00xaDhzbEVNTHBPYnY5X3hHZzNZR2hVazQ1eTZ1a0tTb3hNcHpnQkpYNlk3SFRxdEg5RlhUbnJnQl9pSHh2QWVhMllFeFNkcU9xamp2T29pNDQ1X2hXeFhIWTVLX05Ralc0NjgzVW44eTNyREJlUV8yejBEU29XYXk2OFI3Q015V3ZsdFVscWdyOV9FMzdrVExqcjBrOUhJa2ZN</guid></item><item><title>购物者在旧货店扫描背包内的二维码后惊呆了： “花了一个小时，但发现了黄金” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/articles/shopper-stunned-scanning-qr-code-200000835.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Patience is definitely a virtue when it comes to thrift shopping, as one Redditor proved with an incredible backpack they found for only $7.99. The designer brand retails for hundreds online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Took an hour, but gold was found," the Redditor&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ThriftStoreHauls/comments/16cp9qy/took_an_hour_but_gold_was_found/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:posted;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; posted&lt;/a&gt; along with photos of the impressive find. The black, Italian-made Moncler backpack includes a special QR to verify the item with its unique garment code. "Almost all newer Moncler items have a QR code/number you can scan or input to authenticate," the Redditor &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ThriftStoreHauls/comments/16cp9qy/comment/jznghqj/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:explained;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;explained&lt;/a&gt; in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Credit: r/ThriftStoreHauls / Reddit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Credit: r/ThriftStoreHauls / Reddit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The high-end brand specializes in accessories and apparel, with prices for new &lt;a href="https://www.moncler.com/en-us/women/accessories/bags-and-small-accessories?ds_cid=71700000059010378&amp;amp;gclid=CjwKCAjw9-6oBhBaEiwAHv1QvH_ZoJ4OIFTn_BRpgL-enks1O483FR70j1I99KlmdukjhpyWIHWLLxoC6HYQAvD_BwE&amp;amp;gclsrc=aw.ds" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:backpacks and bags;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;backpacks and bags&lt;/a&gt; starting over $600. "It's going for $525 online at Neiman Marcus," one commenter&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ThriftStoreHauls/comments/16cp9qy/comment/jzlq2qi/?utm_source=reddit&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:reported;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; reported&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Although the backpack appears to be in good shape overall, one commenter&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ThriftStoreHauls/comments/16cp9qy/comment/jzm8vc3/?utm_source=reddit&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:shared;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; shared&lt;/a&gt; a helpful tip to touch up the slight wear on the piece. "A small bit of black leather dye balm for the edging will have it looking brand new." With a few simple stitches or a bit of paint or dye, thrift shoppers can breathe&lt;a href="https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=0492e84f-6397-486c-91dc-0692ccce3542&amp;amp;siteId=us-y4p&amp;amp;pageId=1p-autolink&amp;amp;contentUuid=68eb8718-5aeb-36cc-a6f5-b22e825d3512&amp;amp;featureId=text-link&amp;amp;merchantName=Skillshare&amp;amp;linkText=new+life&amp;amp;custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsImxhbmRpbmdVcmwiOiJodHRwczovL3d3dy5za2lsbHNoYXJlLmNvbS9lbi9ibG9nLzYtdXBjeWNsaW5nLWlkZWFzLWZyb20tdGhyaWZ0LXN0b3Jlcy8_dXRtX21lZGl1bT1wcGMmdXRtX3NvdXJjZT1nb29nbGVfYWR3b3JkcyZ1dG1fdGVybT0mdXRtX2NhbXBhaWduPSZjb3Vwb249YmxvZzMwZGF5c2ZyZWUmZ2NsaWQ9Q2p3S0NBanc2OW1vQmhCZ0Vpd0FVRkN4MkRmVGItQS02MWpXbGo2U1U1NlpsS1R0MkpWVlJVaW1yeVlXNXVEVGludTFxRzFJbllfUm54b0NiSUlRQXZEX0J3RSIsImNvbnRlbnRVdWlkIjoiNjhlYjg3MTgtNWFlYi0zNmNjLWE2ZjUtYjIyZTgyNWQzNTEyIiwib3JpZ2luYWxVcmwiOiJodHRwczovL3d3dy5za2lsbHNoYXJlLmNvbS9lbi9ibG9nLzYtdXBjeWNsaW5nLWlkZWFzLWZyb20tdGhyaWZ0LXN0b3Jlcy8_dXRtX21lZGl1bT1wcGMmdXRtX3NvdXJjZT1nb29nbGVfYWR3b3JkcyZ1dG1fdGVybT0mdXRtX2NhbXBhaWduPSZjb3Vwb249YmxvZzMwZGF5c2ZyZWUmZ2NsaWQ9Q2p3S0NBanc2OW1vQmhCZ0Vpd0FVRkN4MkRmVGItQS02MWpXbGo2U1U1NlpsS1R0MkpWVlJVaW1yeVlXNXVEVGludTFxRzFJbllfUm54b0NiSUlRQXZEX0J3RSJ9&amp;amp;signature=AQAAAX3jJcI_YF_nLLVGGztG-zk2XPfssRk9Q9BMscBRQcj4&amp;amp;gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.skillshare.com%2Fen%2Fblog%2F6-upcycling-ideas-from-thrift-stores%2F%3Futm_medium%3Dppc%26utm_source%3Dgoogle_adwords%26utm_term%3D%26utm_campaign%3D%26coupon%3Dblog30daysfree%26gclid%3DCjwKCAjw69moBhBgEiwAUFCx2DfTb-A-61jWlj6SU56ZlKTt2JVVRUimryYW5uDTinu1qG1InY_RnxoCbIIQAvD_BwE&amp;amp;spaceId=980751755" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;sellerN:Skillshare;elmt:" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:new life;elm:affiliate_link;sellerN:Skillshare;elmt:;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt; new life&lt;/a&gt; into secondhand finds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Shopping secondhand at flea markets, yard sales, and thrift stores is a great way to save money and discover hidden treasures while also helping the planet. As one Redditor aptly&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ThriftStoreHauls/comments/16cp9qy/comment/jzm8vc3/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:noted;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; noted&lt;/a&gt;, "Siftin' for gold ain't easy," but it can be incredibly rewarding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Unreal find! This is gearing me up for next time at the bins!" &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ThriftStoreHauls/comments/16cp9qy/comment/jzmkzmk/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:added;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;added&lt;/a&gt; another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;With patience and luck, thrifters have found&lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/daniellaemanuel/best-thrift-store-finds" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:ama;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; ama&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/daniellaemanuel/best-thrift-store-finds" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:z;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;z&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/daniellaemanuel/best-thrift-store-finds" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:ing deals;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;ing deals&lt;/a&gt; on specialty and designer items while saving them from finding their way to the landfill.&lt;a href="https://www.bu.edu/sph/news/articles/2022/the-aftermath-of-fast-fashion-how-discarded-clothes-impact-public-health-and-the-environment/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Textile waste;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; Textile waste&lt;/a&gt; is a growing problem in the U.S., as more than 34 billion pounds of textiles are thrown out each year — two-thirds of which is sent to landfills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A significant amount of textile waste gets shipped abroad, causing damage to the environment and human health by polluting the soil and groundwater as they decompose, clogging up gutters and waterways, and damaging people's lungs from the air pollution that results from burning unwanted clothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;With &lt;a href="https://www.cleanup.org.au/top-10-ways-to-reuse-reduce-and-recycle-your-clothes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:actions;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;actions&lt;/a&gt; like shopping secondhand, repairing or upcycling clothes, and swapping wardrobes with a friend, we can help reduce textile waste. Patient and eagle-eyed thrifters might even come across unbelievable finds like the Redditor's designer backpack while browsing the secondhand racks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxNanhRNjVPTERUV011QjJ6T1htQUFVTHBLLUxlRzlubmRjU0Zzb0kxbkNyLV9VangtR3l4cXVvUlVFXzhneGZuNldsQTVMQ01PMGZmNTZvclZ6X2gtbzhab3VUODM2d1hHaDc3SHhmMTNPVFM1bWhCOTFxSEtHd1FCZTl1TDdlTGtHTDJvVTZ2ZDBzZw</guid></item><item><title>髋关节屈肌无力导致我腰痛-这是我用来加强它们的三个练习- Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://www.fitandwell.com/exercise/bodyweight-exercises/weak-hip-flexors-were-causing-me-backache-these-are-the-three-exercises-i-used-to-strengthen-them</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p id="c77ee928-a87f-4265-92c0-e5794a1d67d3"&gt;While being a journalist who specializes in fitness allows me more opportunities to work out than other professions would, I still spend most of time at my desk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is the reality for most office workers. Hours upon hours hunched over at a desk and only ever small windows of opportunity to undo the damage with exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="c77ee928-a87f-4265-92c0-e5794a1d67d3-2"&gt;Over time, this inactivity, coupled with a gradual shortening and weakening of my &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.physio-pedia.com/Hip_Flexors" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.physio-pedia.com/Hip_Flexors" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;hip flexors&lt;/a&gt;, has led to backache that’s been hard to shake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I returned to three simple exercises an osteopath recommended that I used previously to strengthen these muscles and offset the effects of long stints of sitting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-how-to-tell-if-your-hip-flexors-are-weak" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-how-to-tell-if-your-hip-flexors-are-weak"&gt;&lt;span&gt;How to tell if your hip flexors are weak&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="f0f4f203-0132-4767-8b80-2bcd6e0a8c2e"&gt;The &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.physio-pedia.com/Iliopsoas" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.physio-pedia.com/Iliopsoas" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;iliopsoas&lt;/a&gt; muscles that make up the hip flexors play a pivotal role in raising your knee toward your chest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every time you take a step forward, that's your hip flexor muscles kicking in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People often confuse pain around the front of the hips as a sign of hip flexor tightness, but more often than not these muscles are undertrained and weakness is the issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-FHcm4Y8JbxaSyeeUXThsrL" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-FHcm4Y8JbxaSyeeUXThsrL slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DPOoFf0EQRj/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.instagram.com/p/DPOoFf0EQRj/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;weak hip flexor explainer video&lt;/a&gt;, trainer Jason Pak demonstrates a quick test you can try to work out if your hip flexors need a bit of TLC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you can’t lift your knee toward your chest while standing or you struggle to get it high without leaning back, that’s a sign that your hip flexors might need a little care and attention,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weak hip flexors, he goes on to explain, can mean the back has to work harder to compensate, leading to pain or discomfort around the hip joint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His solution—and mine—is to use exercises to strengthen the hip flexors and take the strain off your lower back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-three-exercises-i-used-to-strengthen-my-weak-hip-flexors" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-three-exercises-i-used-to-strengthen-my-weak-hip-flexors"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Three exercises I used to strengthen my weak hip flexors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;a id="elk-8aa6c1ce-c3b9-4c35-b542-869c4c212c25" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="1-supine-hip-flexor-raise-3"&gt;1. Supine hip flexor raise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="54dcc232-93e1-499a-bb3b-626a80b04fb9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sets:&lt;/strong&gt; 1-2 &lt;strong&gt;Reps:&lt;/strong&gt; 10 each side&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="b26988bc-7dc5-4421-93dd-567c3132d761"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lie on your back, pressing your lower back into the floor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly lift and bend your right knee until it’s bent to 90° and directly above your right hip, focusing on the deep muscles around your hips to control the move.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly return to the starting position.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do all your reps on one side, then swap sides.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="e7c13f4b-db91-40f0-9f31-c4ca23e8353d"&gt;As you build strength, you can add a resistance band and to work against the resistance to increase the challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-96cc2b37-5b1a-4672-b712-f5cab6f97f2c" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="2-seated-hip-flexor-isometric-hold-3"&gt;2. Seated hip flexor isometric hold&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="6d94fca5-5a0d-42c8-94cf-47d6b36c7ca3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sets:&lt;/strong&gt; 1-2 &lt;strong&gt;Reps:&lt;/strong&gt; 5 each side&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="2ee2065e-ad3e-45ae-bd81-361fcce5a302"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sit upright on a bench or chair with your feet on the floor and your knees bent to 90°.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keeping your hips and torso stable, lift your right knee as high as possible.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hold for five seconds, then lower with control.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do all your reps on one side, then swap sides.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="30842262-ed3c-4b96-8aa0-e7daae8144cf"&gt;You can also perform these standing (I like to do them while brushing my teeth), or apply extra resistance by pressing down on your knee with your hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-e392a638-99e9-41c1-acce-d35829c607ce" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="3-kneeling-hip-flexor-raise-3"&gt;3. Kneeling hip flexor raise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="31bdd94f-d231-4749-97bc-e3f74b831f9b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sets:&lt;/strong&gt; 1-2 &lt;strong&gt;Reps:&lt;/strong&gt; 5 each side&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="c46674ce-39de-4a18-bc6a-a86a972e3171"&gt;&lt;li&gt;From kneeling, place your right foot on the floor in front of you on a weight plate or other similar, sturdy platform.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Concentrating on using just your hip flexors, lift your right foot off the elevated platform as high as you can.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hold for three seconds, then lower with control.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do all your reps on one side, then swap sides.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6gFBVV95cUxQZTMtTDIwbnhCWjFQUllzelJiOVp3Zl9INGN5empnc2JQcm9adEdzTHJBWUVaUlpMNjlfZEtYb0lIaEF6ZnZRTXUtMzc2YjlyWHI1VEZxcHdxbEE1MmpWYU9UVlVIODZSR0FMb0laZzlpQlRicXVuaUNSdlBQNnlVUGdHOUtZX19rUF91QW92Qlpqd2toa050RlBHUHo1TlhBaW1yd2MwekJBOS1teW56elowTUNUT042QlZYUmJjdWxoY2JieGhHQTdubkw0MG8xcnE5djk4Vl8xS2M3VmkyMGQ2SEFuSENzUnc</guid></item><item><title>排名前10位的高纤维坚果和种子- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/top-high-fiber-nuts-and-seeds-ranked-11842186</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fiber supports digestion, heart health and blood sugar control, yet most Americans fall short of daily goals.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chia seeds, flaxseeds and almonds are top sources, delivering 3–10g of fiber per serving.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nuts and seeds also offer plenty of protein, minerals and antioxidants to support overall health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Maybe you've been feeling sluggish lately, or your digestion isn't quite right. At your checkup, your healthcare provider brings up fiber—so you do what any health-conscious person would do: start choking down bowls of high-fiber cereal and forcing yourself to eat &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-happens-when-you-eat-brussels-sprouts-11801582" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Brussels sprouts with every meal&lt;/a&gt;. A few days in, you're already dreading breakfast and wondering how long you can keep this up.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; But what if getting more fiber didn't have to feel like such a chore? The truth is, some of the most satisfying, portable and versatile fiber sources might already be &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/37009/how-to-stock-your-pantry/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;sitting in your pantry&lt;/a&gt;. Nuts and seeds pack a surprising amount of fiber—along with healthy fats, plant-based protein and an array of vitamins and minerals that support overall health. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "They're overlooked because people think of them as 'fats,' not 'fiber foods.' But they're stealthy fiber ninjas," says &lt;a href="https://www.nutritionbybess.com/old-about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Bess Berger, RDN, CDN, CLT&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Considering over 90% of people fall short of their &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-much-fiber-should-you-be-eating-11752876" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;daily fiber needs&lt;/a&gt;—25 grams for women and 34 for men—it’s time to rethink how we get our fiber.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This starts with adding more nuts and seeds to the mix. Take a look at our list of 10 nuts and seeds ranked by their fiber content, from highest to lowest.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-chia-seeds"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 1. Chia Seeds &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fiber: 10 grams per 1 ounce (28 grams), per the USDA.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When it comes to fiber, chia seeds take the crown. These tiny seeds deliver an impressive 10 grams of fiber in just a 1-ounce serving. “In addition to being packed with fiber, chia seeds are a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/healthy-snacks-that-have-more-calcium-than-a-cup-of-yogurt-11803455" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;surprising source of calcium&lt;/a&gt;, with 14% of the daily value for this nutrient,” says &lt;a href="https://samanthacassetty.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Samantha Cassetty, RD&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Chia seeds are especially high in &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7962360/what-is-the-difference-between-insoluble-and-soluble-fiber-according-to-a-dietitian/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;soluble fiber&lt;/a&gt;, which absorbs water to form a gel-like substance that picks up excess sugar and cholesterol in the gut, supporting blood sugar control and heart health.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Their ability to absorb liquid also makes them &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/8029350/basic-overnight-oats/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;perfect for overnight oats&lt;/a&gt;, smoothies or chia pudding.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-flaxseeds"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 2. Flaxseeds &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fiber: 8 grams per 1 ounce (28 grams), per the USDA.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Coming in second place, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/are-flaxseeds-good-for-you-11733695" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;flaxseeds are true fiber heavyweights&lt;/a&gt;, packing about 8 grams per ounce. But what really sets flaxseeds apart goes beyond their fiber content. Cassetty notes that flaxseeds are high in lignans, a plant compound with strong anti-inflammatory properties.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For better nutrient absorption, choose ground flaxseeds over whole ones—your body can better digest them when they’re ground.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3-almonds"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 3. Almonds &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fiber: 3 grams per 1 ounce (28 grams), per the USDA.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Almonds are popular for a reason—and it’s not just their great taste. Each ounce serving provides 3 grams of fiber along with a wealth of other nutrients. “Almonds stand out for providing &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-happens-when-you-consume-vitamin-e-regularly-8685814" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;almost 50% of your daily value for vitamin E&lt;/a&gt;,” says Cassetty. They also contain phytosterols that help to lower LDL (“bad”) cholesterol, she adds.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Whether you snack on them raw, toss slivered almonds onto salads or use almond butter in recipes, these versatile nuts make it easy to boost your fiber intake.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-4-pistachios"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 4. Pistachios &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fiber: 3 grams per 1 ounce (28 grams), per the USDA.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These vibrant green nuts pack 3 grams of fiber per ounce, but their benefits don't stop there. Cassetty points out that pistachios have 6 grams of protein—the same amount as a hard-boiled egg.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; With their satisfying crunch and naturally portioned shells, pistachios make an easy, fiber-rich snack you can enjoy on their own or sprinkled over salads and grain bowls.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-5-sunflower-seeds"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 5. Sunflower Seeds &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fiber: 3 grams per 1 ounce (28 grams), per the USDA.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Don't underestimate these small but mighty seeds. Sunflower seeds deliver about 3 grams of fiber per ounce, and they're nutritional powerhouses in other ways too. Cassetty highlights that these seeds are abundant in vitamin E, providing 49% of your daily value.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; They also supply 40% of your daily value of selenium, a mineral that plays a key role in DNA repair and antioxidant defense.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Sprinkle them on salads, blend them into smoothies or enjoy them as a standalone snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-6-pecans"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 6. Pecans &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fiber: 3 grams per 1 ounce (28 grams), per the USDA.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Pecans deliver just under 3 grams of fiber per ounce and provide notable heart health benefits. In one study, adults with metabolic syndrome who replaced their usual daily snacks with two ounces of pecans experienced reductions in triglycerides as well as total and LDL (“bad”) cholesterol.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; With their buttery flavor and satisfying crunch, pecans work beautifully in both sweet and savory dishes, from salads to baked goods.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-7-pumpkin-seeds"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 7. Pumpkin Seeds &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fiber: 2 grams per 1 ounce (28 grams), per the USDA.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Pumpkin seeds may offer slightly less fiber—about 2 grams per ounce—but they make up for it with an impressive lineup of immune-supporting nutrients. Cassetty notes that pumpkin seeds are an excellent source of key minerals, providing 40% of the daily value (DV) for magnesium, 20% DV for zinc and 14% DV for iron.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; These minerals play essential roles in immune function, energy production and muscle health.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Pumpkin seeds can be enjoyed on their own, sprinkled on top of yogurt or incorporated into baked goods.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-8-walnuts"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_63-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 8. Walnuts &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_64-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fiber: 2 grams per 1 ounce (28 grams), per the USDA.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Walnuts provide 2 grams of fiber per ounce, but they truly shine for their unique nutritional profile. Cassetty points out that walnuts are the only nut that is high in the &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-nutrient-to-lower-inflammation-8783795" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;alpha-linolenic acid&lt;/a&gt; (ALA), a type of plant-based omega-3. They’re also rich in polyphenols and vitamin E, both of which have antioxidant properties. Together, these compounds may reduce the risk of chronic diseases, including heart disease, diabetes and certain cancers.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_67-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_68-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Add walnuts to your morning oatmeal or evening yogurt for a fiber boost that supports both your gut and your sleep.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_69-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-9-peanuts"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_70-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 9. Peanuts &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_71-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fiber: 2 grams per 1 ounce (28 grams), per the USDA.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_72-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_73-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While technically a legume rather than a true nut, peanuts earn their spot on this list with about 2 grams of fiber per ounce. Unlike other nuts, peanuts are high in protein, with 7 grams per ounce. They’re also rich in anti-inflammatory nutrients—such as magnesium, selenium, vitamin E, monounsaturated fats and polyphenols—that have been linked with a lower risk of heart disease.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_74-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_75-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Whether you enjoy them roasted, as peanut butter or tossed in a stir-fry, peanuts are an affordable, accessible way to add fiber to your diet.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_76-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-10-hemp-seeds"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_77-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 10. Hemp Seeds &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_78-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fiber: 1 gram per 1 ounce (28 grams), per the USDA.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_79-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_80-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Hemp seeds come in last on our fiber ranking, with about 1 gram per ounce, but they still deserve recognition for their overall nutritional value. Cassetty points out that the real reason these seeds stand out is their protein and mineral content—a single serving provides 10 grams of plant protein and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-magnesium-rich-foods-11772823" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;50% of your daily value for magnesium&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_81-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_82-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Their mild, nutty flavor makes them an &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7832841/smoothie-formula/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;easy addition to smoothies&lt;/a&gt;, yogurt bowls and salads without overpowering other ingredients.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_83-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-ways-to-enjoy-nuts-and-seeds"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_84-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Ways to Enjoy Nuts and Seeds &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_85-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Incorporating nuts and seeds into your daily routine is easier than you might think. Here are some simple ways to add them to your meals and snacks:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_86-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_87-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Sprinkle chia or flaxseeds into smoothies, oatmeal or yogurt for a fiber boost&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Top salads with almonds, walnuts or pumpkin seeds for added crunch and nutrition&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spread nut butter on whole-grain toast or apple slices for a satisfying snack&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use crushed almonds or pecans as a coating for chicken, fish or tofu&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Blend cashews into creamy sauces or soups for richness without dairy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use nut or seed butters as a dip for fruit and vegetables&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Add sunflower or pumpkin seeds to baked goods for texture and nutrients&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bake with almond flour and nut butters for added fiber and protein&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use chopped nuts or seeds instead of breadcrumbs to coat chicken or fish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_88-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_89-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; However, keep in mind that while nuts and seeds are nutritious, they're also calorie-dense. Berger recommends sticking with about 1 ounce of nuts or 1–2 tablespoons of seeds, which offers roughly 160–200 calories for a snack. Even that modest serving packs fiber, protein and healthy fats that keep hunger away longer.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_90-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_92-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_93-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_94-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Nuts and seeds are nutritional superheroes. Berger explains they're packed with heart-healthy fats, plant-based protein, antioxidants and key minerals like magnesium, zinc and selenium. They're the total package: fiber for your gut, fats for your heart and protein for staying power. With so many varieties to choose from and endless ways to enjoy them, nuts and seeds make it easy—and delicious—to increase your fiber intake every day.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTFAwVloyTnYzYmpqQk1CSDZTZE0zb1M3ZTdfUGNHdVMtVm9lUXhOM0dtdnUtMThsejlxa2dCeE1RX09pT0s5WWFmZTRqaENQOTNWZFB1WWd2aFFuMkZ3RWR1YTMxc0VJZHN5Y3BrdVotT2FDRU9hMUtJMmZNTXc</guid></item><item><title>医生解释了您必须依靠能量饮料度过一天的真正原因： “它们的工作原理是阻塞……” |《印度斯坦时报》-《印度斯坦时报》</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/physician-explains-the-real-reason-you-have-to-depend-on-energy-drinks-to-get-through-the-day-101762317502445.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/physician-explains-the-real-reason-you-have-to-depend-on-energy-drinks-to-get-through-the-day-101762317502445.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;It’s 2 pm, your energy is crashing, and you’re reaching for yet another can of your go-to &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/world-news/energy-drinks-are-now-offering-a-bit-of-value-along-with-that-caffeine-boost-101755859305773.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="energy drink"&gt;energy drink&lt;/a&gt; to push through the rest of the day. Sounds familiar? While it may seem like a harmless pick-me-up, depending on multiple cans just to stay awake or focused isn’t just harmful for your health - it could be your body’s way of signalling that something deeper is wrong.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/05/550x309/energy_drink_1762318795429_1762318795601.jpeg" alt="Dr. Mezher reveals that energy drinks don't provide true energy but mask tiredness by blocking adenosine." title="Dr. Mezher reveals that energy drinks don't provide true energy but mask tiredness by blocking adenosine."&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/05/550x309/energy_drink_1762318795429_1762318795601.jpeg" alt="Dr. Mezher reveals that energy drinks don't provide true energy but mask tiredness by blocking adenosine." title="Dr. Mezher reveals that energy drinks don't provide true energy but mask tiredness by blocking adenosine."&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Dr. Mezher reveals that energy drinks don't provide true energy but mask tiredness by blocking adenosine.&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/relying-on-energy-drinks-for-focus-doctor-reveals-how-they-affect-your-health-effects-on-the-heart-sleep-101762169258032.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Relying on energy drinks for focus? Doctor reveals how they affect your health: ‘Effects on the heart, sleep…’"&gt;Relying on energy drinks for focus? Doctor reveals how they affect your health: ‘Effects on the heart, sleep…’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Sermed Mezher, a family medicine physician and health content creator based in England, has explained how energy drinks can trap people in a vicious cycle of dependence - where they’re used to mask deeper issues that actually need attention. In an Instagram video posted on October 4, the physician breaks down the mechanism of these beverages, explaining the real reason people become reliant on them, and warns about the dangers of overuse.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How do energy drinks work?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Mezher, energy drinks don’t actually give you energy. He explains, “They work by either blocking you from feeling tired or potentially regulating &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/health/can-a-dopamine-detox-reset-your-brain-101762146790734.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="dopamine"&gt;dopamine &lt;/a&gt;levels. You do that by blocking a hormone called adenosine which makes you feel sleepy but also acts like a break on dopamine which we know is affected in some conditions.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Why do you need energy drinks?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Energy drinks are used by many people for a quick boost in alertness, focus or stamina, especially when struggling with fatigue, poor concentration, or low motivation. However, according to Dr Mezher, “In some cases, this pattern can become a form of self-medication, where individuals use &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/more-caffeine-less-control-how-drinking-too-much-coffee-before-driving-can-slow-your-reflexes-and-cloud-judgment-101762232167996.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="caffeine"&gt;caffeine &lt;/a&gt;and stimulants in energy drinks to temporarily mask deeper issues such as insomnia, chronic stress, anxiety, or undiagnosed ADHD.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The physician explains, “Dopamine levels can be low in the areas of the frontal lobe responsible for planning and organisation in people with ADHD. So we commonly see people self-medicating with caffeine before they even know they have a diagnosis.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;People with insomnia or poor sleep hygiene tend to rely more on energy drinks to deal with tiredness, instead of addressing the real problem. Dr Mezher also highlights, “Excessive tiredness can also be caused by a slew of other things like vitamin &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/aiims-trained-gastroenterologist-reveals-early-warning-signs-of-5-key-nutrient-deficiencies-brain-fog-fatigue-and-more-101762241206334.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="deficiencies"&gt;deficiencies &lt;/a&gt;such as D and B12 or potentially myalgic encephalomyelitis or depression.” He stresses that needing chemical reinforcements like energy drinks to get through the day is not normal and recommends getting checked for underlying issues.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Dangers of overuse&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The physician emphasises that the short term effects of energy drinks - increased energy, sharper focus and enhanced productivity - might seem helpful but they come at a hidden cost. He explains, “Relying on energy drinks can lead to tolerance, dependence, and side effects such as palpitations, elevated &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/neurosurgeon-with-26-years-of-experience-warns-your-high-blood-pressure-is-silent-killer-you-get-less-blood-flow-101762139496234.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="blood pressure"&gt;blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;, irritability, and disrupted sleep. Over time, this can worsen the very problems people are trying to manage, creating a cycle of fatigue and overstimulation.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. It is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:03:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6wFBVV95cUxNTFpCMlBNZzRNTklYbmxPbzdvdjYtZS03aDlJQmhKQ0gtWDlwNHhPNTRFaXFzbVhncGFQZWFfYnhON1JENndrSGlHaV9BekFRdFVhVjM2NlhLSjJIdlcxb3RHZnkyT2tqTzZEMVNpY0lPNTFNNV9zWkNzVFNWVmpvb2RSbFNuQUFZMUUzclA2X0gtX0xfVmVVOEZ3QjFGdllHTDJvQjZ5U1lmZXhoOHBZdW9hMTVQVm9jNFEwUFRhSEItdGFscWRaakJOZmFIU3ZadHA3YmFCa003MHFXZmloc1RLcHJRQ3hlVEpN0gHwAUFVX3lxTE9vTzk5UVVNMGpMYk9YYzc1ZGIxVnJjQzVoS0lOOUxTWEhOZ0JNSjQtY3Z5MElSNDRmN2hWLW5KRkR2SUctSHJ6MjA0REVzd3ZQRmhwcTN4Y2hUTTRSd0syNEFOaG5IY040ZlVkMVhKUWxqcjFzN2o1aEs3MjlWbHNBNWZzakhKWlczdWtYXzkzSEV0V21Xdk9wMHp3bHBwZWg3UmdRRjRBYnp5RG1aRHJoZ0laNEtWYjA3U3RXaHlBY1NpYmhrQzRJbGlmMHo3VjExSUg0aGV4ajJPMnIxWVhlc3E3dG9UQ1ByVmNZV3I2VA</guid></item><item><title>新冠肺炎比疫苗接种更能增加儿童罕见心脏病的风险-英国《金融时报》</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/231d6787-a431-44e3-a8e7-bdc246882232</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="o-grid-row details-section o3-type-body-base css-pmzbjb"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Complete digital access to quality FT journalism with expert analysis from industry leaders. Pay a year upfront and save 20%.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Financial Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:00:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE9uVTQyS1I2a2gxYnk4Rm5HN1JNOWlvOS1JUkp0YjZ0d0VBVlI3Vm9HWlJMZFZBNF8ySG1uVWlMbWVvdS0wdjJqZnJ4MFJsMzFjZGpTOHl0MkJQbmZVQkJfa1dfc2VYWG1CNzVmalVxdUs</guid></item><item><title>5种适合糖尿病的蔬菜，可以帮助控制血糖-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/5-vegetables-that-are-great-for-diabetes-and-can-help-keep-blood-sugar-in-control/photostory/124735985.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A diabetic friendly vegetable that is incredibly low in carbs, with just about one gram per cup of raw leaves, it is packed with fiber, magnesium, and potassium, three nutrients that play a great role in blood sugar control. Spinach, which contains alpha-lipoic acid, plays a great role in blood sugar management. The best is that spinach is quite versatile, throw in a handful into a smoothie, saute it with garlic and herbs, for a quick side dish, use it as a base for salads, since it is so low in calories, but high in volume. A study in the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://fathomjournal.org/bfsp8eic-0tam-avsugarn9s-s1lv-ds9i"&gt;Fathom Journa&lt;/a&gt;l, found that one key compound found in nitrate, found in spinach, has been shown to have positive effects on insulin sensitivity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 04:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_AFBVV95cUxPOFM0WXd0Vm9RYTNsZG8yeWt3c2lZUlVOQWw1VUFRZHpDVk9TU1l6Qlh6RmNxd0QyN0g0bU1mVHZaTXhVSHVnOW04VVI4X19nVGtLVnlQamI4YjU5Sk5HRWR1YUt3NDdIVHZMUmZUSjE1aEhYSGQ1T01xTXZMQXp1TmlTRVNoSFd1UmJDdkk2Uk00YVc0Qlp2by1iOXBWVXVBS00wZE40V0pWRjRGTFFpLWJKSmNfdFlVOFBtVXM4dzRsbVduSldFaklKT2tJcko4MVJZcnZFQ0lDejlXbXAxSE9PVWRxcC1rOUM1a1BJTlp2WkYxS3JmUEp5VVHSAYQCQVVfeXFMTzViZm1LR2pVaUZzLWxwMjc4UXFybnUyTGhJSDhpYUJZQWxqVE5SdEl4NXN3WTdmbFY4cVBPdS1rdTlXQ3RsNmdlczNBY1B3WjBCNHFad2x5SGdMX3dWTDNidzZHeUlUSDFjNV9qRnJIUDRsUW12S0VNZXFpYTBnT1l1UlZRRl8yb1FpdzRBcG00UnZfdjd2bTJYV19UU0gtOU9rY0lsVS1BSkZrRTRpaUFMa1ZlV2xLa180YzJnY1JzMVRuNDdPamR5ZGZCU0REaGI3WndjdzNiTWhHblJyV3g5amMtaUU3dlZJQ2NWaVBBczhiYUs2V3hzUVFfLXFKR2Z2bC0</guid></item><item><title>美国最胖的州……和四分之三肥胖的地区--《每日邮报》</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15254345/obese-states-map.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="/news/west-virginia/index.html" id="mol-5dc1a5d0-b8ec-11f0-b3e8-452d1ad5c980" class=""&gt;West Virginia&lt;/a&gt; has been named the most obese state in the US for the fifth year in a row, according to an analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a report ranking all 50 states and Washington, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/washington-dc/index.html" id="mol-5dbe9890-b8ec-11f0-b3e8-452d1ad5c980"&gt;DC&lt;/a&gt;, the Mountain State took the top spot, with 73 percent of adults considered either overweight or obese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It also ranked number one for obesity rates among children between the ages of 10 and 17, and landed among the top 10 worst states for access to healthy food, with only 41 percent of residents living near a healthy food retailer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Overall, nine of the 10 fattest US states were in the South, an area long plagued by obesity and chronic conditions like &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-575a7db0-b8f2-11f0-b3e8-452d1ad5c980"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="/news/mississippi/index.html" id="mol-3db43480-b8ef-11f0-b3e8-452d1ad5c980" class=""&gt;Mississippi&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/arkansas/index.html" id="mol-3db32310-b8ef-11f0-b3e8-452d1ad5c980"&gt;Arkansas&lt;/a&gt; came in second and third place, respectively, with up to 71.5 percent of adult residents classified as overweight or obese. &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/louisiana/index.html" id="mol-3db40d70-b8ef-11f0-b3e8-452d1ad5c980"&gt;Louisiana&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/alabama/index.html" id="mol-3db2fc00-b8ef-11f0-b3e8-452d1ad5c980" class=""&gt;Alabama&lt;/a&gt; rounded out the top five. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="/news/delaware/index.html" id="mol-5dbf0dc0-b8ec-11f0-b3e8-452d1ad5c980" class=""&gt;Delaware&lt;/a&gt; was the only state in the top 10 that was &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14908049/obese-europe-overweight-americans-measurement-study.html"&gt;not in the South&lt;/a&gt;. The state has one of the largest senior populations in the nation, which tends to be less active than younger age groups. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts at personal finance website WalletHub revealed the rankings for this year based on an analysis of CDC data and other official figures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It marked the fifth consecutive year - and sixth year in total - that West Virginia landed at the top of the ranking since the report was first published in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
     &lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox floatLHS health" data-version="2" id="mol-33d4f640-b8ed-11f0-b3e8-452d1ad5c980" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15254345/obese-states-map.html"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;TOP 10 MOST OBESE STATES &lt;/h3&gt; &lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt; &lt;ol class="mol-bullets-with-font"&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;West Virginia&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Mississippi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Arkansas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Louisiana&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Alabama&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Tennessee&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Kentucky&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Texas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Delaware&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Oklahoma &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;According to a report from personal finance website WalletHub based on CDC data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox floatLHS health" data-version="2" id="mol-33d54460-b8ed-11f0-b3e8-452d1ad5c980" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15254345/obese-states-map.html"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;TEN LEAST OBESE STATES&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt; &lt;ol class="mol-bullets-with-font"&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Colorado&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Utah&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Massachusetts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;California&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Hawaii&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Minnesota&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Montana&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;D.C.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Washington&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Vermont &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;According to a report from personal finance website WalletHub based on CDC data. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; 
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Though, WalletHub experts said their methodology changes annually, and this year's data is not exactly comparable to that of any previous year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In addition to limited access to healthy foods and high levels of sugary drink consumption, the state also has lower levels of physical activity and the second-lowest number of gyms and fitness centers nationwide, the researchers said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;West Virginia has the second lowest average salary in the US, at $55,900 per year. And the study found that lower salaries are linked to worse diets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It does, however, have the fourth highest rate in the nation for prescriptions of Ozempic and other GLP-1 drugs, according to a &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.realchemistry.com/article/states-with-highest-rates-of-glp-1-use"&gt;2024 report&lt;/a&gt; from Real Chemistry, in a sign that its obesity rates may soon start to fall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For WalletHub's report, the researchers ranked states based on three categories: overweight and obesity rates, health consequences (such as the proportion of adults with weight-related complications like type 2 diabetes, high cholesterol and heart disease), and food and fitness (the number of fast food restaurants per area and the proportion of adults consuming sugar-sweetened beverages or at least one fruit or vegetable per day).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To come up with the rankings, they analyzed official data on 31 factors - including the share of adults with obesity and high cholesterol, and the state's projected obesity rate in 2030.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above graph, based on estimates from pollster Gallup, suggests that obesity rates in the US are now starting to decline after peaking at 39.9 percent in 2022&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A separate report published in October showed that the proportion of America's states with very high levels of obesity had now started to fall&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team did not calculate an overall obesity rate for the US, although recent statistics have suggested that, amid the advent of weight loss drugs, this has started to drop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://news.gallup.com/poll/696599/obesity-rate-declining.aspx"&gt;survey by Gallup&lt;/a&gt; released last week suggested that 37 percent of adults in the US are now considered to be obese, down from 37.4 percent last year and the peak of 39.9 percent in 2022. Gallup did not break down its data by state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another report from Trust for America's Health, a nonprofit focused on health policy, also suggested that obesity rates have declined. It found the number of states with an obesity rate above 35 percent fell to 19 last year, compared to 23 the year before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Trust for America's Health report also found West Virginia was among the 16 states to record a drop in the proportion of adults considered to be obese by at least five percent over the one-year period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Figures from the CDC published in 2024 also suggest that America's obesity rate is falling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In its latest report, the agency found that, between 2021 and 2023, a total of 40.3 percent of US adults were obese, a drop from the 41.9 percent over the previous three-year period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers have repeatedly suggested that weight loss drugs such as Ozempic are behind the downturn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;According to estimates, at least one in eight Americans use these drugs, which help someone lose weight with little more than a weekly injection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://s3.amazonaws.com/media2.fairhealth.org/whitepaper/asset/Obesity%20and%20GLP-1%20Drugs%20-%20A%20FAIR%20Health%20White%20Paper.pdf"&gt;report from nonprofit Fair Health&lt;/a&gt; suggests that about 5 million adults in the US were taking the drugs in May this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Researchers have previously suggested that the decline may be down to weight loss drugs, which can help people to lose weight with little more than a weekly injection (Stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At the other end of the scale, the WalletHub report found that the state with the lowest obesity rate was Colorado, where 11.6 percent of adults are considered obese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Reports have previously suggested that this is linked to the state's culture, which is said to promote outdoor activities, boosting health and fitness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Colorado is also home to the&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14069617/inside-america-skinny-city-fat-secret-boulder-colorado.html"&gt; nation's least-fat city&lt;/a&gt;, Boulder, where only 12 percent of residents are obese - nearly four times lower than the national average.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;YouTuber Will Tennyson spoke with locals in Boulder late last year and found many felt a stronger social pressure to stay healthy than those in other cities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rounding out the bottom five for the fattest cities list were Utah, Massachusetts, California and Hawaii, generally wealthier states with increased access to fresh produce and gyms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'While losing weight largely hinges on whether an individual chooses to eat healthy foods, limit their calorie intake and exercise consistently, certain states make shedding the pounds easier than others,' said Chip Lupo, a WalletHub analyst behind the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'For example, some states are much better at regulating school lunches to make sure they are healthy, and have more opportunities for adults to buy fresh, nutritious ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'In addition, while anyone can exercise at home, some states provide far more locations for people to go to work out or play sports.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 02:59:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE80eEY5alRsa3ZrOXdMM05xUWdUa0ZEa2VZM0VMc1lTZVN0aVZ3X1VuQTh4aGtUN3k2SjU4eXBveDFsbEs4X2kwZGxlLWhwcUxDV2NiMERZLWY0eE5maVdTdFVKRVRpTlRpaVFPeUlqdXpEZVl4TnR2dl96Z2NvZw</guid></item><item><title>40岁以下成年人的记忆问题激增，美国大型研究发现- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/memory-problems-are-surging-in-adults-under-40-large-us-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The latest study on America's state of mind is in, and it reveals a concerning rise in the share of adults who say they have &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clearing-brain-waste-dramatically-improves-memory-in-aging-mice"&gt;problems with memory&lt;/a&gt;, decision-making, or concentration – known collectively as cognitive disability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A US team led by University of Utah neurology researcher Ka-Ho Wong found that those aged 18–39 experienced the biggest uptick in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/shockingly-common-injury-linked-with-increased-dementia-risk"&gt;cognitive disability&lt;/a&gt; in the past decade, after analyzing survey data from more than 4.5 million people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, the proportion of US adults reporting serious cognitive difficulties rose from 5.3 percent to 7.4 percent between 2013 and 2023. For those under 40, the rate nearly doubled, jumping from 5.1 percent to 9.7 percent across the same period. People who &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/worldwide-review-finds-most-people-with-depression-aren-t-getting-treatment"&gt;reported depression&lt;/a&gt; were excluded from the figures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-eye-movements-could-be-hiding-signs-of-a-failing-memory"&gt;Your Eye Movements Could Be Hiding Signs of a Failing Memory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Challenges with memory and thinking have emerged as a leading health issue reported by US adults," &lt;a href="https://www.aan.com/PressRoom/home/PressRelease/5286"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; vascular neurologist Adam de Havenon, from Yale University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_179988" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-179988" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/CognitiveNumbers.jpg" alt="Cognitive disability" class="wp-image-179988 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/CognitiveNumbers.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/CognitiveNumbers-600x323.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-179988" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Self-reported cognitive disability rates rose in all age groups except those aged 70 and over. (Wong et al., &lt;em&gt;Neurol.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Self-reported cognitive disability rose across most age groups; however, an upward trend was not observed in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/aging-isn-t-all-bad-some-key-mental-abilities-improve-as-we-get-older"&gt;senior citizens&lt;/a&gt;. Rates in those aged 70 and older actually declined slightly, the researchers found, from 7.3 percent in 2013 to 6.6 percent in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our study shows that these difficulties may be becoming more widespread, especially among younger adults, and that social and structural factors likely play a key role," de Havenon &lt;a href="https://www.aan.com/PressRoom/home/PressRelease/5286"&gt;explains&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those factors include &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/having-rich-friends-when-you-re-young-increases-your-income-later-in-life"&gt;socioeconomic status&lt;/a&gt;. Groups with annual incomes under US$35,000 and those with lower educational attainment saw increases in cognitive disability that were larger than the general trend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;American Indian and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/these-indigenous-alaskan-groups-are-linked-to-the-first-humans-to-settle-in-northwest-america"&gt;Alaska Native&lt;/a&gt; adults reported the highest rates of cognitive disability, despite a rise in reported prevalence across all racial and ethnic groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These findings suggest we're seeing the steepest increases in memory and thinking problems among people who already face structural disadvantages," &lt;a href="https://www.aan.com/PressRoom/home/PressRelease/5286"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; de Havenon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of 2022, cognitive disability affects 13.9 percent of adults in the US, according to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/brfss/about/brfss_faq.htm"&gt;annual surveys by the CDC&lt;/a&gt; – making it the most commonly reported disability in those surveys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_180148" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-180148" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/US-Disability-Infographic.jpg" alt="Infographic showing rates of multiple types of disability" class="size-full wp-image-180148" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/US-Disability-Infographic.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/US-Disability-Infographic-433x675.jpg 433w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/US-Disability-Infographic-600x935.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-180148" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;13.9 percent of U.S. adults have a cognitive disability. (&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/disability-and-health/articles-documents/disability-impacts-all-of-us-infographic.html"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study doesn't pin down specific causes, but there's growing evidence that our minds aren't &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/millions-of-americans-have-cognitive-impairment-and-dont-know-it"&gt;in great shape&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People's increased willingness to report mental health issues or the lingering effects of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/human-brains-rapidly-aged-in-the-pandemic-and-it-wasnt-just-the-virus"&gt;the coronavirus pandemic&lt;/a&gt; could partially explain the rise, the team thinks, thought it's almost certain that multiple factors are combining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There may be a growing openness to talk about mental health in younger people in particular. The researchers also suggest that increased &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/working-long-hours-is-killing-hundreds-of-thousands-of-people-who-study-finds"&gt;uncertainty about work&lt;/a&gt; among younger adults and greater reliance &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/chatgpt-5-surprising-truths-about-how-ai-chatbots-actually-work"&gt;on digital tools&lt;/a&gt; might be contributing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some limitations here, primarily that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/heres-why-multitasking-gets-trickier-and-even-dangerous-as-we-age"&gt;cognitive problems&lt;/a&gt; were self-reported by phone rather than clinically assessed. Even without specific diagnoses, the numbers are enough to point to a public-health concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to better understand and address the underlying social and economic factors that may be driving this trend," &lt;a href="https://www.aan.com/PressRoom/home/PressRelease/5286"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; de Havenon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"More research is also needed to understand what's driving the large increase in rates among younger adults, given the potential long-term implications for health, workforce productivity and health care systems."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1212/WNL.0000000000214226"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Neurology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 02:40:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPZlpBbHJOTHM3V2E5MndCLTQ5TDBVTzI5RlpFN1dKRU9JSF9zdjdwYjhkMTRYM1NhWjFSZW0yOTJBRWxiNDI2XzlqOW5wdzZsUzZpZEkzeDhlOWJCV01yYk5tYUsxR1c2RFI4UFIxRFlRQ2ZMRjlqenNnUXE0ODg2MlBUYzk0bzJ6akFOazF3VVVBYUgwOVg2WTRScUg</guid></item><item><title>“我是一名营养师-这4种食物可以快速燃烧50岁以上女性的腹部脂肪（我每天都吃它们！) ’- Woman's World</title><link>https://www.womansworld.com/weight-loss/nutrition/the-best-foods-that-burn-belly-fat-for-women-over-50</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body class="post-template-default single single-post postid-589326 single-format-standard post-the-best-foods-that-burn-belly-fat-for-women-over-50 theme-womans-world has-custom-search article-format-posts" id="readabilityBody"&gt;
				
			&lt;noscript&gt;
				
			&lt;/noscript&gt;		
				

	
		
	

	




	
			&lt;p class="screen-reader-only"&gt;
							&lt;span id="ac-describe-top-level-help"&gt;
					Use left and right arrow keys to navigate between menu items.				&lt;/span&gt;
							
							&lt;span id="ac-describe-esc-help"&gt;
					Use escape to exit the menu.				&lt;/span&gt;
							
							
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
	
	
&lt;span id="recommended-posts-config" data-config='{"appName":"womansworld_non_commerce_oyml","ab_percentage":50,"tracking_event":"recommended-item-clicked-v2","post_type":"non_commerce","api_key":"AIzaSyARaAm8QMYecpd36kg0Jg7H1TwKE7_DofY","post_id":589326,"blacklist":""}'&gt; &lt;/span&gt;



	







&lt;p class="feedback-wrapper" id="feedback-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="login-body sso-ww" id="login-body"&gt;
	
	
	
	

&lt;div class="login-request" id="login"&gt;
			&lt;svg class="login-logo logo-ww" aria-label="Woman's World" focusable="false" aria-hidden="true" viewbox="0 0 148 20" role="presentation"&gt;
			&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d="m91.8888889 19.3333333h-2.0277778l-1.2222222-13.36111108c-.1111111-1.19444444-.5277778-1.30555555-2.1388889-1.30555555l.2777778-.94444445h8.5555555l-.2777777.94444445c-1.5555556 0-2.1388889.19444444-2.1388889.88888889.0011281.82599168.0474938 1.6513017.1388889 2.47222222l.6111111 6.30555552h.0555555l4.1666667-6.49999997-.2222222-2.5c-.0555556-.47222222-.2222223-.69444444-1.6666667-.69444444l.2777778-.94444445h8.5555552l-.277777.94444445c-1.916667 0-2.416667.13888889-2.416667 1.11111111 0 .55555556.111111 1.25.138889 1.69444444l.555555 7.11111116h.055556l4.638889-7.27777782c.666666-1.13888889 1.055555-1.66666667 1.055555-2.02777778 0-.44444444-.222222-.61111111-2.305555-.61111111l.277778-.94444445h6.361111l-.277778.94444445c-1.805556 0-2.111111.25-2.722222 1.16666667l-8.833334 13.52777774h-2.083333l-.8611111-9.5833333h-.0555556z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m113.777778 8.38888889c2.605007-.02319741 4.739683 2.06183461 4.777778 4.66666671 0 3.5555555-3.194445 6.5555555-6.861112 6.5555555-2.605007.0231974-4.739683-2.0618346-4.777777-4.6666667 0-3.5833333 3.555555-6.55555551 6.861111-6.55555551zm1.5 2.61111111c0-1.27777778-.444445-1.77777778-1.444445-1.77777778-2.194444 0-3.638889 5.44444448-3.638889 7.72222218 0 1.2777778.444445 1.7777778 1.444445 1.7777778 2.111111.0277778 3.638889-4.8888889 3.638889-7.7222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m118.472222 19.3333333 1.944445-7.8333333c.116623-.3974592.181967-.8081944.194444-1.2222222 0-.5277778-.333333-.69444447-1.277778-.75000002l.222223-.80555556 4.5-.08333333-.555556 2.80555551.055556.0555556c.861111-1.91666667 2.361111-3.08333333 3.75-3.08333333.480391-.0127098.945638.16869666 1.290632.50323645.344994.33453978.540627.79398588.542701 1.27454128.015623.4761137-.166656.9374326-.503501 1.2742771-.336844.3368444-.798163.5191237-1.274277.5035007-.916667 0-1.305555-.5-1.305555-1.2777778.000887-.3187878.077026-.6328625.222222-.91666662l-.055556-.05555556c-1.222222.44444448-2.833333 3.27777778-3.833333 6.69444448l-.861111 2.9444444h-3.055556z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m132.416667 15.3055556c-.416667 1.5277777-.694445 2.5-.694445 2.8055555 0 .1944445.138889.3055556.361111.3055556.527778 0 1.277778-1.0833334 2.055556-2.3333334l.638889.4444445c-.722222 1.4444444-1.944445 3.0833333-3.75 3.0833333-1.527778 0-2.277778-1-2.277778-2.3055555 0-1.5277778.388889-2.5833334.944444-4.6666667l1.694445-6.16666668c.088503-.30004703.153514-.60652843.194444-.91666666 0-.52777778-.333333-.69444445-1.583333-.75l.222222-.80555556 5.305556-.08333333z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m142.444444 4.02777778 5.166667-.08333334-3.222222 12.58333336c-.222222.9444444-.305556 1.2222222-.305556 1.5555555 0 .1944445.055556.4444445.333334.4444445.805555 0 1.916666-2.2777778 2.166666-2.8055556l.75.4722222c-.694444 1.6388889-1.805555 3.4166667-3.805555 3.4166667-1.222222 0-2.111111-.8055555-2.333334-2.4166667h-.055555c-.527778 1.3055556-1.694445 2.4166667-3.25 2.4166667-2.25 0-3.972222-1.6388889-3.972222-4.4444444 0-3.9444445 3.416666-6.77777781 6.166666-6.77777781 1.305556 0 2.055556.61111111 2.444445 1.63888891h.055555c.416667-1.72222224 1.083334-3.91666669 1.083334-4.25000002 0-.55555556-.333334-.88888889-1.5-.94444445zm-.5 7.30555552c0-1.44444441-.555555-1.86111108-1.305555-1.86111108-1.555556 0-3.444445 4.49999998-3.444445 7.58333338 0 .9444444.472223 1.4444444 1.138889 1.4444444 1.472223 0 3.611111-3.5 3.611111-7.1666667z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m33.7222222 5.11111111c-2.25 0-1.5277778-1.83333333-4.7222222-2.16666667-2.8888889-.30555555-5.6944444 3.05555556-5.6944444 3.05555556l-8.75 13.25h-2.0833334l-.8611111-9.58333333h-.0555555l-6.16666671 9.58333333h-2.02777778l-1.22222222-13.36111111c-.11111111-1.19444445-.52777778-1.30555556-2.13888889-1.30555556l.27777778-.97222222h8.55555555l-.27777777.94444445c-1.55555556 0-2.13888889.19444444-2.13888889.88888888.00112815.82599169.04749388 1.65130171.13888889 2.47222223l.61111111 6.30555553h.05555555l4.16666668-6.49999998-.2222222-2.5c-.0555556-.47222222-.2222223-.69444444-1.6666667-.69444444l.27777778-.94444445h8.55555552l-.2777777.94444445c-1.9166667 0-2.4166667.13888889-2.4166667 1.11111111 0 .55555555.1111111 1.25.1388889 1.69444444l.5555555 7.11111107h.0555556l4.6388889-7.27777773s4.0833333-6.86111111 10.2777778-6.91666667c5.0833333.02777778 4.6666666 4.86111111 2.4166666 4.86111111z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m26.6944444 8.27777778c2.6144808-.02004059 4.7518163 2.08001582 4.7777778 4.69444442 0 3.5555556-3.1944444 6.5555556-6.8611111 6.5555556-2.6144807.0200406-4.7518162-2.0800158-4.7777778-4.6944445 0-3.5833333 3.5555556-6.55555552 6.8611111-6.55555552zm1.5 2.63888892c0-1.27777781-.4444444-1.77777781-1.4444444-1.77777781-2.1944444 0-3.6388889 5.44444441-3.6388889 7.72222221 0 1.2777778.4444445 1.7777778 1.4444445 1.7777778 2.1111111 0 3.6388888-4.8888889 3.6388888-7.7222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m31.2777778 19.25 1.8611111-7.0555556c.3888889-1.4444444.4444444-1.8611111.4444444-2.1111111 0-.41666663-.1944444-.5833333-1.2777777-.63888886l.2222222-.80555555 4.4444444-.08333333c-.1388889.5-.2777778 1.41666666-.5555555 2.41666664l.0555555.0555556c1.0833334-1.72222224 2.0833334-2.69444447 3.7222222-2.69444447 1.6944445 0 2.3611112 1.08333334 2.3888889 2.72222227h.0555556c1.0555555-1.69444449 2.1944444-2.72222227 3.8055555-2.72222227 1.3611112 0 2.5833334 1.27777778 2.5833334 3.05555557 0 1.7777778-1.8055556 4.9722222-1.8055556 6.2777778 0 .3055555.1111111.4444444.3333334.4444444.6111111 0 1.75-1.8055555 1.9444444-2.2777778l.7222222.4444445c-.8055555 1.5-2.0277778 3.2777778-3.9444444 3.2777778-1 0-2.0833334-.6944445-2.0833334-2.4166667 0-2.0277778 1.9166667-5.3055556 1.9166667-6.6666667.0227162-.2100288-.0469496-.4195642-.1909018-.57417953s-.3479839-.23905139-.5590982-.231376c-1.3055555 0-3.1111111 3.33333333-4.3611111 8.08333333l-.4166667 1.5555556h-3.1388889l1.8611112-6.9444445c.2086249-.6724026.3664759-1.3595186.4722222-2.0555555.0194795-.1723714-.0426735-.34394811-.1680291-.46385348s-.299524-.17437514-.4708598-.14725768c-1.3055556 0-3.2777778 3.19444446-4.8055556 9.63888886h-3.0555555z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m62 8.5-2 8.1111111c-.1036623.4296284-.1779085.8658253-.2222222 1.3055556 0 .1944444.0555555.4166666.3055555.4166666.8611111 0 1.9722223-2.0833333 2.8333334-2.4444444l.75.4166667c-1.3611111 1.3333333-2.4166667 3.2222222-4.5 3.2222222-1.2777778 0-2.0555556-.8611111-2.2777778-2.4166667h-.0555556c-.9166666 1.4166667-1.8055555 2.4166667-3.4444444 2.4166667-1.9444445 0-4.0555556-1.2222222-4.0555556-4.3888889 0-3.4722222 3.2222223-6.83333334 6.4166667-6.83333334 1.4166667 0 2.0833333.75 2.4444444 1.80555554h.0555556l.3611111-1.58333332h3.3888889zm-5.7222222.97222222c-2.0833334 0-3.4166667 5.05555558-3.4166667 7.22222218 0 1.1388889.3611111 1.6388889 1.1388889 1.6388889 2.0277778 0 3.6944444-4.5 3.6944444-6.8888889 0-1.3333333-.5-1.97222218-1.4166666-1.97222218z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m74.2222222 8.88888889c.8888889-.47222222 2.0277778-1 2.0833334-2.16666667-.1526535.04739195-.312738.06622543-.4722223.05555556-.6944444 0-1.1111111-.52777778-1.1111111-1.19444445-.0097931-.3664445.1295472-.72117485.3861237-.98298767.2565766-.26181281.6084199-.40829022.9749874-.40592999 1.0555556 0 1.6111111.77780655 1.6111111 1.77780655 0 1.77777778-1.6944444 2.94444445-3.1944444 3.52777778-.6111111-.05555556-.2777778-.61111111-.2777778-.61111111z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m73.5555556 18.3333333c-.6944445.6944445-1.5 1.1666667-2.5277778 1.1666667s-2.1944445-.6388889-2.1944445-2.3333333c0-1.8055556 2-5.1666667 2-6.6944445.0280553-.2358712-.0536058-.4715817-.2215676-.63954351-.1679617-.16796178-.4036723-.24962286-.6395435-.22156758-1.3611111 0-3.2222222 2.94444449-4.3611111 7.33333329l-.5833333 2.3055556h-3.2222222l1.8888888-6.8611111c.25-.9444445.6111112-2 .6111112-2.3055556 0-.41666663-.1666667-.5833333-1.3055556-.63888886l.2222222-.80555555 4.5833334-.08333333c-.1388889.55555555-.3055556 1.41666666-.5 2.22222224l.0555555.0555555c.9722222-1.30555552 1.9722222-2.49999997 3.7222222-2.49999997s2.8055556 1.41666667 2.8055556 3.05555557c0 1.8055555-1.9166667 5.1944444-1.9166667 6.2777778 0 .2222222.0833334.4444444.4166667.4444444-.0277778-.0555555 1.6111111-.9166667 1.1666667.2222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m80.1111111 8.27777778c3.2777778 0 4.2222222 1.41666666 4.2222222 2.30555552 0 1.0277778-.5277777 1.5555556-1.6388889 1.5555556-.9166666 0-1.5555555-.5277778-1.5555555-1.3055556 0-1.0833333.9722222-1.13888886.9722222-1.22222219s-.6666667-.41666667-1.8333333-.41666667c-1.1666667 0-2.3055556.69444445-2.3055556 1.66666666 0 2.0277778 5.7222222 1.6666667 5.7222222 5.1944445 0 2.1111111-2.3055555 3.8611111-6.25 3.8611111-2.1666666 0-4.3055555-.9722223-4.3055555-2.9444445 0-.9722222.6944444-1.6111111 1.8333333-1.6111111.8160985-.025586 1.5049253.6017385 1.5555556 1.4166667 0 1.2777778-1.1666667 1.4444444-1.1666667 1.5277778 0 .3611111.8055556.7222222 2.25.7222222 1.9166667 0 2.9166667-.8888889 2.9166667-1.5833334 0-2.4444444-5.6388889-1.8333333-5.6388889-5.4444444.0277778-2.22222222 2.3888889-3.72222222 5.2222222-3.72222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;
		&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;p class="login-body__title"&gt;Sign In&lt;/p&gt;
	
	&lt;div class="login-form__wrapper"&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="social-login"&gt;
	&lt;p class="social-login__title"&gt;Sign &lt;b class="title--sign-in"&gt;In&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b class="title--sign-up"&gt;Up&lt;/b&gt; with your social account&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;button name="googleSignUpButton" class="btn google-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;
		&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 256 262" preserveaspectratio="xMidYMid"&gt;
			&lt;path d="M255.878 133.451c0-10.734-.871-18.567-2.756-26.69H130.55v48.448h71.947c-1.45 12.04-9.283 30.172-26.69 42.356l-.244 1.622 38.755 30.023 2.685.268c24.659-22.774 38.875-56.282 38.875-96.027" fill="#4285F4"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M130.55 261.1c35.248 0 64.839-11.605 86.453-31.622l-41.196-31.913c-11.024 7.688-25.82 13.055-45.257 13.055-34.523 0-63.824-22.773-74.269-54.25l-1.531.13-40.298 31.187-.527 1.465C35.393 231.798 79.49 261.1 130.55 261.1" fill="#34A853"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M56.281 156.37c-2.756-8.123-4.351-16.827-4.351-25.82 0-8.994 1.595-17.697 4.206-25.82l-.073-1.73L15.26 71.312l-1.335.635C5.077 89.644 0 109.517 0 130.55s5.077 40.905 13.925 58.602l42.356-32.782" fill="#FBBC05"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M130.55 50.479c24.514 0 41.05 10.589 50.479 19.438l36.844-35.974C195.245 12.91 165.798 0 130.55 0 79.49 0 35.393 29.301 13.925 71.947l42.211 32.783c10.59-31.477 39.891-54.251 74.414-54.251" fill="#EA4335"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
		&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Google&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;














	&lt;button name="amazonSignUpButton" class="btn amazon-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;
		&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 175 181" version="1.1" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;
			&lt;defs&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;
			&lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;
				&lt;g fill="#000"&gt;
					&lt;path d="M153.507609,149.082589 C154.515676,148.678569 155.38932,148.577566 156.128569,148.779576 C156.867818,148.981586 157.237437,149.570773 157.237437,150.547154 C157.237437,151.523535 156.733411,152.651407 155.725344,153.930804 C154.851687,155.00819 153.373211,156.47274 151.289874,158.324498 C149.206536,160.176256 145.997572,162.465667 141.662886,165.192801 C137.3282,167.919936 132.590358,170.411354 127.449219,172.667132 C122.308079,174.922909 115.990957,176.875643 108.497662,178.525391 C101.004367,180.175138 93.2927738,181 85.3626502,181 C77.3653221,181 69.368114,179.956298 61.370786,177.868862 C53.3734579,175.781426 46.3506996,173.205837 40.3023002,170.14202 C34.2539008,167.078203 28.457605,163.57675 22.913239,159.637556 C17.3688729,155.698362 12.9166457,152.163241 9.5564238,149.032087 C6.19620193,145.900933 3.3736579,142.954999 1.08870702,140.194196 C0.551071524,139.588167 0.215054377,139.032648 0.0806455023,138.527623 C-0.0537633725,138.022598 -0.0201616578,137.618584 0.181451654,137.315569 C0.383064967,137.012554 0.651878684,136.77688 0.987900871,136.608538 C1.32392306,136.440196 1.71034278,136.372861 2.14717162,136.406529 C2.58400046,136.440197 2.97042018,136.591703 3.30644237,136.861049 C16.2096944,144.739437 26.2902088,150.328295 33.548288,153.62779 C59.6908142,165.47904 86.5385842,168.509144 114.092404,162.718192 C126.861247,160.024726 139.999517,155.479571 153.507609,149.082589 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
					&lt;path d="M174.374483,137.467076 C175.113731,138.544462 175.197736,140.884376 174.626498,144.486886 C174.05526,148.089397 173.097611,151.540348 171.753523,154.839844 C169.468572,160.428785 166.612426,164.603595 163.185,167.364397 C162.042524,168.30711 161.16888,168.610121 160.56404,168.273437 C159.9592,167.936754 159.9592,167.128727 160.56404,165.84933 C161.975333,162.819181 163.470609,158.728541 165.049913,153.577288 C166.629218,148.426035 166.847629,145.109754 165.705153,143.628348 C165.369131,143.156992 164.848305,142.769812 164.142658,142.466797 C163.437011,142.163782 162.529765,141.961775 161.420892,141.86077 C160.312019,141.759765 159.320768,141.675596 158.44711,141.608259 C157.573453,141.540922 156.397393,141.540922 154.918895,141.608259 C153.440398,141.675596 152.381944,141.742931 151.743501,141.810268 C151.105059,141.877605 150.063406,141.978608 148.618511,142.113281 C147.173615,142.247955 146.417577,142.31529 146.350372,142.31529 C145.947146,142.382627 145.510323,142.433129 145.039892,142.466797 C144.569461,142.500465 144.199842,142.534133 143.931025,142.567801 C143.662207,142.60147 143.376592,142.635137 143.074172,142.668806 C142.771752,142.702474 142.53654,142.719308 142.368529,142.719308 L141.360468,142.719308 C141.259661,142.719308 141.158856,142.702474 141.058049,142.668806 C140.957243,142.635137 140.890039,142.584636 140.856437,142.517299 L140.705228,142.214286 C140.302001,141.136899 141.881282,139.790187 145.443117,138.174107 C149.004952,136.558028 152.465929,135.547993 155.826151,135.143973 C158.917555,134.672617 162.54654,134.638949 166.713215,135.042969 C170.87989,135.446989 173.43362,136.255016 174.374483,137.467076 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
					&lt;path d="M134.656859,92.7220982 C134.656859,94.8095342 135.110482,96.9642746 136.017742,99.1863839 C136.925002,101.408493 138.000256,103.361227 139.243539,105.044643 C140.486821,106.728059 141.746885,108.276779 143.023769,109.690848 C144.300654,111.104918 145.40951,112.182288 146.350372,112.922991 L147.660852,114.03404 L124.777856,136.65904 C122.089678,134.167584 119.435143,131.625664 116.81417,129.033203 C114.193197,126.440742 112.244297,124.471175 110.967413,123.124442 L109.052096,121.104353 C108.312847,120.36365 107.472804,119.252612 106.531942,117.771205 C103.978174,121.744067 100.702006,125.195019 96.7033423,128.124163 C92.7046783,131.053307 88.4204597,133.191214 83.8505579,134.537946 C79.2806562,135.884679 74.5764161,136.659039 69.7376966,136.861049 C64.8989771,137.063059 60.2787414,136.356035 55.8768507,134.739955 C51.4749601,133.123876 47.5267586,130.918634 44.0321278,128.124163 C40.5374971,125.329692 37.7485548,121.525229 35.6652172,116.710658 C33.5818796,111.896088 32.5402265,106.425068 32.5402265,100.297433 C32.5402265,94.6411548 33.4810745,89.4563108 35.3627987,84.7427455 C37.244523,80.0291803 39.6638465,76.1068795 42.6208417,72.9757254 C45.5778369,69.8445714 49.1564196,67.0501425 53.3566969,64.5923549 C57.5569742,62.1345673 61.6731843,60.2155017 65.7054505,58.8351004 C69.7377168,57.4546992 74.1059397,56.2931595 78.8102503,55.3504464 C83.5145609,54.4077334 87.5299658,53.7848787 90.8565855,53.4818638 C94.1832051,53.1788489 97.5265758,52.9600081 100.886798,52.8253348 L100.886798,39.9977679 C100.886798,35.6208859 100.181162,32.3551075 98.7698684,30.2003348 C96.4849176,26.6314926 92.4191101,24.8470982 86.572324,24.8470982 C86.1690974,24.8470982 85.6146691,24.880766 84.9090225,24.9481027 C84.2033759,25.0154393 82.8425065,25.4194531 80.8263734,26.1601562 C78.8102402,26.9008594 76.9285442,27.89406 75.1812288,29.1397879 C73.4339135,30.3855159 71.5522174,32.3887511 69.5360843,35.1495536 C67.5199512,37.9103561 65.9070689,41.1424666 64.697389,44.8459821 L35.0603803,42.1188616 C35.0603803,38.0786628 35.799618,34.0721925 37.2781156,30.0993304 C38.7566133,26.1264682 41.0079281,22.3220048 44.0321278,18.6858259 C47.0563275,15.049647 50.6853127,11.8512043 54.9191923,9.09040179 C59.1530718,6.32959929 64.2437316,4.12435721 70.1913243,2.47460938 C76.138917,0.824861543 82.5400437,0 89.3948963,0 C96.11534,0 102.19725,0.841695452 107.64081,2.52511161 C113.084369,4.20852776 117.435791,6.27909857 120.695207,8.73688616 C123.954622,11.1946737 126.676361,13.9891026 128.860505,17.1202567 C131.044649,20.2514107 132.556726,23.1468431 133.396782,25.8066406 C134.236837,28.4664382 134.656859,30.9410228 134.656859,33.2304688 L134.656859,92.7220982 Z M66.9151244,94.843192 C66.9151244,100.634144 69.2672444,105.111963 73.971555,108.276786 C78.4070479,111.239598 83.0776862,111.98029 87.9836102,110.498884 C93.6287829,108.815468 97.4593784,104.674326 99.4755115,98.0753348 C100.416374,95.0451857 100.886798,91.6447361 100.886798,87.8738839 L100.886798,71.5111607 C96.9217358,71.645834 93.1919455,72.0498478 89.6973147,72.7232143 C86.202684,73.3965807 82.6241014,74.5244527 78.9614595,76.1068638 C75.2988177,77.689275 72.3754685,80.0796901 70.1913243,83.2781808 C68.0071801,86.4766715 66.9151244,90.3316367 66.9151244,94.843192 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
				&lt;/g&gt;
			&lt;/g&gt;
		&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Amazon&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;

	&lt;button name="appleSignUpButton" class="btn apple-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;

                &lt;span&gt;&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 170 170" version="1.1"&gt;
    &lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;
        &lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;
            &lt;path d="m150.37 130.25c-2.45 5.66-5.35 10.87-8.71 15.66-4.58 6.53-8.33 11.05-11.22 13.56-4.48 4.12-9.28 6.23-14.42 6.35-3.69 0-8.14-1.05-13.32-3.18-5.197-2.12-9.973-3.17-14.34-3.17-4.58 0-9.492 1.05-14.746 3.17-5.262 2.13-9.501 3.24-12.742 3.35-4.929 0.21-9.842-1.96-14.746-6.52-3.13-2.73-7.045-7.41-11.735-14.04-5.032-7.08-9.169-15.29-12.41-24.65-3.471-10.11-5.211-19.9-5.211-29.378 0-10.857 2.346-20.221 7.045-28.068 3.693-6.303 8.606-11.275 14.755-14.925s12.793-5.51 19.948-5.629c3.915 0 9.049 1.211 15.429 3.591 6.362 2.388 10.447 3.599 12.238 3.599 1.339 0 5.877-1.416 13.57-4.239 7.275-2.618 13.415-3.702 18.445-3.275 13.63 1.1 23.87 6.473 30.68 16.153-12.19 7.386-18.22 17.731-18.1 31.002 0.11 10.337 3.86 18.939 11.23 25.769 3.34 3.17 7.07 5.62 11.22 7.36-0.9 2.61-1.85 5.11-2.86 7.51zm-31.26-123.01c0 8.1021-2.96 15.667-8.86 22.669-7.12 8.324-15.732 13.134-25.071 12.375-0.119-0.972-0.188-1.995-0.188-3.07 0-7.778 3.386-16.102 9.399-22.908 3.002-3.446 6.82-6.3113 11.45-8.597 4.62-2.2516 8.99-3.4968 13.1-3.71 0.12 1.0831 0.17 2.1663 0.17 3.2409z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
        &lt;/g&gt;
    &lt;/g&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Apple&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;

	&lt;p class="social-login__legal"&gt;We won't post to any of your accounts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

	
	&lt;div class="login-register" id="register"&gt;
					&lt;svg class="login-logo logo-ww" aria-label="Woman's World" focusable="false" aria-hidden="true" viewbox="0 0 148 20" role="presentation"&gt;
				&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d="m91.8888889 19.3333333h-2.0277778l-1.2222222-13.36111108c-.1111111-1.19444444-.5277778-1.30555555-2.1388889-1.30555555l.2777778-.94444445h8.5555555l-.2777777.94444445c-1.5555556 0-2.1388889.19444444-2.1388889.88888889.0011281.82599168.0474938 1.6513017.1388889 2.47222222l.6111111 6.30555552h.0555555l4.1666667-6.49999997-.2222222-2.5c-.0555556-.47222222-.2222223-.69444444-1.6666667-.69444444l.2777778-.94444445h8.5555552l-.277777.94444445c-1.916667 0-2.416667.13888889-2.416667 1.11111111 0 .55555556.111111 1.25.138889 1.69444444l.555555 7.11111116h.055556l4.638889-7.27777782c.666666-1.13888889 1.055555-1.66666667 1.055555-2.02777778 0-.44444444-.222222-.61111111-2.305555-.61111111l.277778-.94444445h6.361111l-.277778.94444445c-1.805556 0-2.111111.25-2.722222 1.16666667l-8.833334 13.52777774h-2.083333l-.8611111-9.5833333h-.0555556z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m113.777778 8.38888889c2.605007-.02319741 4.739683 2.06183461 4.777778 4.66666671 0 3.5555555-3.194445 6.5555555-6.861112 6.5555555-2.605007.0231974-4.739683-2.0618346-4.777777-4.6666667 0-3.5833333 3.555555-6.55555551 6.861111-6.55555551zm1.5 2.61111111c0-1.27777778-.444445-1.77777778-1.444445-1.77777778-2.194444 0-3.638889 5.44444448-3.638889 7.72222218 0 1.2777778.444445 1.7777778 1.444445 1.7777778 2.111111.0277778 3.638889-4.8888889 3.638889-7.7222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m118.472222 19.3333333 1.944445-7.8333333c.116623-.3974592.181967-.8081944.194444-1.2222222 0-.5277778-.333333-.69444447-1.277778-.75000002l.222223-.80555556 4.5-.08333333-.555556 2.80555551.055556.0555556c.861111-1.91666667 2.361111-3.08333333 3.75-3.08333333.480391-.0127098.945638.16869666 1.290632.50323645.344994.33453978.540627.79398588.542701 1.27454128.015623.4761137-.166656.9374326-.503501 1.2742771-.336844.3368444-.798163.5191237-1.274277.5035007-.916667 0-1.305555-.5-1.305555-1.2777778.000887-.3187878.077026-.6328625.222222-.91666662l-.055556-.05555556c-1.222222.44444448-2.833333 3.27777778-3.833333 6.69444448l-.861111 2.9444444h-3.055556z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m132.416667 15.3055556c-.416667 1.5277777-.694445 2.5-.694445 2.8055555 0 .1944445.138889.3055556.361111.3055556.527778 0 1.277778-1.0833334 2.055556-2.3333334l.638889.4444445c-.722222 1.4444444-1.944445 3.0833333-3.75 3.0833333-1.527778 0-2.277778-1-2.277778-2.3055555 0-1.5277778.388889-2.5833334.944444-4.6666667l1.694445-6.16666668c.088503-.30004703.153514-.60652843.194444-.91666666 0-.52777778-.333333-.69444445-1.583333-.75l.222222-.80555556 5.305556-.08333333z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m142.444444 4.02777778 5.166667-.08333334-3.222222 12.58333336c-.222222.9444444-.305556 1.2222222-.305556 1.5555555 0 .1944445.055556.4444445.333334.4444445.805555 0 1.916666-2.2777778 2.166666-2.8055556l.75.4722222c-.694444 1.6388889-1.805555 3.4166667-3.805555 3.4166667-1.222222 0-2.111111-.8055555-2.333334-2.4166667h-.055555c-.527778 1.3055556-1.694445 2.4166667-3.25 2.4166667-2.25 0-3.972222-1.6388889-3.972222-4.4444444 0-3.9444445 3.416666-6.77777781 6.166666-6.77777781 1.305556 0 2.055556.61111111 2.444445 1.63888891h.055555c.416667-1.72222224 1.083334-3.91666669 1.083334-4.25000002 0-.55555556-.333334-.88888889-1.5-.94444445zm-.5 7.30555552c0-1.44444441-.555555-1.86111108-1.305555-1.86111108-1.555556 0-3.444445 4.49999998-3.444445 7.58333338 0 .9444444.472223 1.4444444 1.138889 1.4444444 1.472223 0 3.611111-3.5 3.611111-7.1666667z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m33.7222222 5.11111111c-2.25 0-1.5277778-1.83333333-4.7222222-2.16666667-2.8888889-.30555555-5.6944444 3.05555556-5.6944444 3.05555556l-8.75 13.25h-2.0833334l-.8611111-9.58333333h-.0555555l-6.16666671 9.58333333h-2.02777778l-1.22222222-13.36111111c-.11111111-1.19444445-.52777778-1.30555556-2.13888889-1.30555556l.27777778-.97222222h8.55555555l-.27777777.94444445c-1.55555556 0-2.13888889.19444444-2.13888889.88888888.00112815.82599169.04749388 1.65130171.13888889 2.47222223l.61111111 6.30555553h.05555555l4.16666668-6.49999998-.2222222-2.5c-.0555556-.47222222-.2222223-.69444444-1.6666667-.69444444l.27777778-.94444445h8.55555552l-.2777777.94444445c-1.9166667 0-2.4166667.13888889-2.4166667 1.11111111 0 .55555555.1111111 1.25.1388889 1.69444444l.5555555 7.11111107h.0555556l4.6388889-7.27777773s4.0833333-6.86111111 10.2777778-6.91666667c5.0833333.02777778 4.6666666 4.86111111 2.4166666 4.86111111z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m26.6944444 8.27777778c2.6144808-.02004059 4.7518163 2.08001582 4.7777778 4.69444442 0 3.5555556-3.1944444 6.5555556-6.8611111 6.5555556-2.6144807.0200406-4.7518162-2.0800158-4.7777778-4.6944445 0-3.5833333 3.5555556-6.55555552 6.8611111-6.55555552zm1.5 2.63888892c0-1.27777781-.4444444-1.77777781-1.4444444-1.77777781-2.1944444 0-3.6388889 5.44444441-3.6388889 7.72222221 0 1.2777778.4444445 1.7777778 1.4444445 1.7777778 2.1111111 0 3.6388888-4.8888889 3.6388888-7.7222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m31.2777778 19.25 1.8611111-7.0555556c.3888889-1.4444444.4444444-1.8611111.4444444-2.1111111 0-.41666663-.1944444-.5833333-1.2777777-.63888886l.2222222-.80555555 4.4444444-.08333333c-.1388889.5-.2777778 1.41666666-.5555555 2.41666664l.0555555.0555556c1.0833334-1.72222224 2.0833334-2.69444447 3.7222222-2.69444447 1.6944445 0 2.3611112 1.08333334 2.3888889 2.72222227h.0555556c1.0555555-1.69444449 2.1944444-2.72222227 3.8055555-2.72222227 1.3611112 0 2.5833334 1.27777778 2.5833334 3.05555557 0 1.7777778-1.8055556 4.9722222-1.8055556 6.2777778 0 .3055555.1111111.4444444.3333334.4444444.6111111 0 1.75-1.8055555 1.9444444-2.2777778l.7222222.4444445c-.8055555 1.5-2.0277778 3.2777778-3.9444444 3.2777778-1 0-2.0833334-.6944445-2.0833334-2.4166667 0-2.0277778 1.9166667-5.3055556 1.9166667-6.6666667.0227162-.2100288-.0469496-.4195642-.1909018-.57417953s-.3479839-.23905139-.5590982-.231376c-1.3055555 0-3.1111111 3.33333333-4.3611111 8.08333333l-.4166667 1.5555556h-3.1388889l1.8611112-6.9444445c.2086249-.6724026.3664759-1.3595186.4722222-2.0555555.0194795-.1723714-.0426735-.34394811-.1680291-.46385348s-.299524-.17437514-.4708598-.14725768c-1.3055556 0-3.2777778 3.19444446-4.8055556 9.63888886h-3.0555555z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m62 8.5-2 8.1111111c-.1036623.4296284-.1779085.8658253-.2222222 1.3055556 0 .1944444.0555555.4166666.3055555.4166666.8611111 0 1.9722223-2.0833333 2.8333334-2.4444444l.75.4166667c-1.3611111 1.3333333-2.4166667 3.2222222-4.5 3.2222222-1.2777778 0-2.0555556-.8611111-2.2777778-2.4166667h-.0555556c-.9166666 1.4166667-1.8055555 2.4166667-3.4444444 2.4166667-1.9444445 0-4.0555556-1.2222222-4.0555556-4.3888889 0-3.4722222 3.2222223-6.83333334 6.4166667-6.83333334 1.4166667 0 2.0833333.75 2.4444444 1.80555554h.0555556l.3611111-1.58333332h3.3888889zm-5.7222222.97222222c-2.0833334 0-3.4166667 5.05555558-3.4166667 7.22222218 0 1.1388889.3611111 1.6388889 1.1388889 1.6388889 2.0277778 0 3.6944444-4.5 3.6944444-6.8888889 0-1.3333333-.5-1.97222218-1.4166666-1.97222218z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m74.2222222 8.88888889c.8888889-.47222222 2.0277778-1 2.0833334-2.16666667-.1526535.04739195-.312738.06622543-.4722223.05555556-.6944444 0-1.1111111-.52777778-1.1111111-1.19444445-.0097931-.3664445.1295472-.72117485.3861237-.98298767.2565766-.26181281.6084199-.40829022.9749874-.40592999 1.0555556 0 1.6111111.77780655 1.6111111 1.77780655 0 1.77777778-1.6944444 2.94444445-3.1944444 3.52777778-.6111111-.05555556-.2777778-.61111111-.2777778-.61111111z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m73.5555556 18.3333333c-.6944445.6944445-1.5 1.1666667-2.5277778 1.1666667s-2.1944445-.6388889-2.1944445-2.3333333c0-1.8055556 2-5.1666667 2-6.6944445.0280553-.2358712-.0536058-.4715817-.2215676-.63954351-.1679617-.16796178-.4036723-.24962286-.6395435-.22156758-1.3611111 0-3.2222222 2.94444449-4.3611111 7.33333329l-.5833333 2.3055556h-3.2222222l1.8888888-6.8611111c.25-.9444445.6111112-2 .6111112-2.3055556 0-.41666663-.1666667-.5833333-1.3055556-.63888886l.2222222-.80555555 4.5833334-.08333333c-.1388889.55555555-.3055556 1.41666666-.5 2.22222224l.0555555.0555555c.9722222-1.30555552 1.9722222-2.49999997 3.7222222-2.49999997s2.8055556 1.41666667 2.8055556 3.05555557c0 1.8055555-1.9166667 5.1944444-1.9166667 6.2777778 0 .2222222.0833334.4444444.4166667.4444444-.0277778-.0555555 1.6111111-.9166667 1.1666667.2222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m80.1111111 8.27777778c3.2777778 0 4.2222222 1.41666666 4.2222222 2.30555552 0 1.0277778-.5277777 1.5555556-1.6388889 1.5555556-.9166666 0-1.5555555-.5277778-1.5555555-1.3055556 0-1.0833333.9722222-1.13888886.9722222-1.22222219s-.6666667-.41666667-1.8333333-.41666667c-1.1666667 0-2.3055556.69444445-2.3055556 1.66666666 0 2.0277778 5.7222222 1.6666667 5.7222222 5.1944445 0 2.1111111-2.3055555 3.8611111-6.25 3.8611111-2.1666666 0-4.3055555-.9722223-4.3055555-2.9444445 0-.9722222.6944444-1.6111111 1.8333333-1.6111111.8160985-.025586 1.5049253.6017385 1.5555556 1.4166667 0 1.2777778-1.1666667 1.4444444-1.1666667 1.5277778 0 .3611111.8055556.7222222 2.25.7222222 1.9166667 0 2.9166667-.8888889 2.9166667-1.5833334 0-2.4444444-5.6388889-1.8333333-5.6388889-5.4444444.0277778-2.22222222 2.3888889-3.72222222 5.2222222-3.72222222z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;
			&lt;/svg&gt;
				&lt;p class="login-body__title" id="titleheader"&gt;Sign Up&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;span class="login-registration-cta"&gt;Create a free account to access exclusive content, play games, solve puzzles, test your pop-culture knowledge and receive special offers.&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;span class="already-have-acc"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a id="signin-already-have-account" class="signin-already-have-account" role="button" name="Login" tabindex="0"&gt;Login&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
		
		
		&lt;div class="social-login"&gt;
	&lt;p class="social-login__title"&gt;Sign &lt;b class="title--sign-in"&gt;In&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b class="title--sign-up"&gt;Up&lt;/b&gt; with your social account&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;button name="googleSignUpButton" class="btn google-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;
		&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 256 262" preserveaspectratio="xMidYMid"&gt;
			&lt;path d="M255.878 133.451c0-10.734-.871-18.567-2.756-26.69H130.55v48.448h71.947c-1.45 12.04-9.283 30.172-26.69 42.356l-.244 1.622 38.755 30.023 2.685.268c24.659-22.774 38.875-56.282 38.875-96.027" fill="#4285F4"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M130.55 261.1c35.248 0 64.839-11.605 86.453-31.622l-41.196-31.913c-11.024 7.688-25.82 13.055-45.257 13.055-34.523 0-63.824-22.773-74.269-54.25l-1.531.13-40.298 31.187-.527 1.465C35.393 231.798 79.49 261.1 130.55 261.1" fill="#34A853"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M56.281 156.37c-2.756-8.123-4.351-16.827-4.351-25.82 0-8.994 1.595-17.697 4.206-25.82l-.073-1.73L15.26 71.312l-1.335.635C5.077 89.644 0 109.517 0 130.55s5.077 40.905 13.925 58.602l42.356-32.782" fill="#FBBC05"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M130.55 50.479c24.514 0 41.05 10.589 50.479 19.438l36.844-35.974C195.245 12.91 165.798 0 130.55 0 79.49 0 35.393 29.301 13.925 71.947l42.211 32.783c10.59-31.477 39.891-54.251 74.414-54.251" fill="#EA4335"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
		&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Google&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;














	&lt;button name="amazonSignUpButton" class="btn amazon-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;
		&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 175 181" version="1.1" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;
			&lt;defs&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;
			&lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;
				&lt;g fill="#000"&gt;
					&lt;path d="M153.507609,149.082589 C154.515676,148.678569 155.38932,148.577566 156.128569,148.779576 C156.867818,148.981586 157.237437,149.570773 157.237437,150.547154 C157.237437,151.523535 156.733411,152.651407 155.725344,153.930804 C154.851687,155.00819 153.373211,156.47274 151.289874,158.324498 C149.206536,160.176256 145.997572,162.465667 141.662886,165.192801 C137.3282,167.919936 132.590358,170.411354 127.449219,172.667132 C122.308079,174.922909 115.990957,176.875643 108.497662,178.525391 C101.004367,180.175138 93.2927738,181 85.3626502,181 C77.3653221,181 69.368114,179.956298 61.370786,177.868862 C53.3734579,175.781426 46.3506996,173.205837 40.3023002,170.14202 C34.2539008,167.078203 28.457605,163.57675 22.913239,159.637556 C17.3688729,155.698362 12.9166457,152.163241 9.5564238,149.032087 C6.19620193,145.900933 3.3736579,142.954999 1.08870702,140.194196 C0.551071524,139.588167 0.215054377,139.032648 0.0806455023,138.527623 C-0.0537633725,138.022598 -0.0201616578,137.618584 0.181451654,137.315569 C0.383064967,137.012554 0.651878684,136.77688 0.987900871,136.608538 C1.32392306,136.440196 1.71034278,136.372861 2.14717162,136.406529 C2.58400046,136.440197 2.97042018,136.591703 3.30644237,136.861049 C16.2096944,144.739437 26.2902088,150.328295 33.548288,153.62779 C59.6908142,165.47904 86.5385842,168.509144 114.092404,162.718192 C126.861247,160.024726 139.999517,155.479571 153.507609,149.082589 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
					&lt;path d="M174.374483,137.467076 C175.113731,138.544462 175.197736,140.884376 174.626498,144.486886 C174.05526,148.089397 173.097611,151.540348 171.753523,154.839844 C169.468572,160.428785 166.612426,164.603595 163.185,167.364397 C162.042524,168.30711 161.16888,168.610121 160.56404,168.273437 C159.9592,167.936754 159.9592,167.128727 160.56404,165.84933 C161.975333,162.819181 163.470609,158.728541 165.049913,153.577288 C166.629218,148.426035 166.847629,145.109754 165.705153,143.628348 C165.369131,143.156992 164.848305,142.769812 164.142658,142.466797 C163.437011,142.163782 162.529765,141.961775 161.420892,141.86077 C160.312019,141.759765 159.320768,141.675596 158.44711,141.608259 C157.573453,141.540922 156.397393,141.540922 154.918895,141.608259 C153.440398,141.675596 152.381944,141.742931 151.743501,141.810268 C151.105059,141.877605 150.063406,141.978608 148.618511,142.113281 C147.173615,142.247955 146.417577,142.31529 146.350372,142.31529 C145.947146,142.382627 145.510323,142.433129 145.039892,142.466797 C144.569461,142.500465 144.199842,142.534133 143.931025,142.567801 C143.662207,142.60147 143.376592,142.635137 143.074172,142.668806 C142.771752,142.702474 142.53654,142.719308 142.368529,142.719308 L141.360468,142.719308 C141.259661,142.719308 141.158856,142.702474 141.058049,142.668806 C140.957243,142.635137 140.890039,142.584636 140.856437,142.517299 L140.705228,142.214286 C140.302001,141.136899 141.881282,139.790187 145.443117,138.174107 C149.004952,136.558028 152.465929,135.547993 155.826151,135.143973 C158.917555,134.672617 162.54654,134.638949 166.713215,135.042969 C170.87989,135.446989 173.43362,136.255016 174.374483,137.467076 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
					&lt;path d="M134.656859,92.7220982 C134.656859,94.8095342 135.110482,96.9642746 136.017742,99.1863839 C136.925002,101.408493 138.000256,103.361227 139.243539,105.044643 C140.486821,106.728059 141.746885,108.276779 143.023769,109.690848 C144.300654,111.104918 145.40951,112.182288 146.350372,112.922991 L147.660852,114.03404 L124.777856,136.65904 C122.089678,134.167584 119.435143,131.625664 116.81417,129.033203 C114.193197,126.440742 112.244297,124.471175 110.967413,123.124442 L109.052096,121.104353 C108.312847,120.36365 107.472804,119.252612 106.531942,117.771205 C103.978174,121.744067 100.702006,125.195019 96.7033423,128.124163 C92.7046783,131.053307 88.4204597,133.191214 83.8505579,134.537946 C79.2806562,135.884679 74.5764161,136.659039 69.7376966,136.861049 C64.8989771,137.063059 60.2787414,136.356035 55.8768507,134.739955 C51.4749601,133.123876 47.5267586,130.918634 44.0321278,128.124163 C40.5374971,125.329692 37.7485548,121.525229 35.6652172,116.710658 C33.5818796,111.896088 32.5402265,106.425068 32.5402265,100.297433 C32.5402265,94.6411548 33.4810745,89.4563108 35.3627987,84.7427455 C37.244523,80.0291803 39.6638465,76.1068795 42.6208417,72.9757254 C45.5778369,69.8445714 49.1564196,67.0501425 53.3566969,64.5923549 C57.5569742,62.1345673 61.6731843,60.2155017 65.7054505,58.8351004 C69.7377168,57.4546992 74.1059397,56.2931595 78.8102503,55.3504464 C83.5145609,54.4077334 87.5299658,53.7848787 90.8565855,53.4818638 C94.1832051,53.1788489 97.5265758,52.9600081 100.886798,52.8253348 L100.886798,39.9977679 C100.886798,35.6208859 100.181162,32.3551075 98.7698684,30.2003348 C96.4849176,26.6314926 92.4191101,24.8470982 86.572324,24.8470982 C86.1690974,24.8470982 85.6146691,24.880766 84.9090225,24.9481027 C84.2033759,25.0154393 82.8425065,25.4194531 80.8263734,26.1601562 C78.8102402,26.9008594 76.9285442,27.89406 75.1812288,29.1397879 C73.4339135,30.3855159 71.5522174,32.3887511 69.5360843,35.1495536 C67.5199512,37.9103561 65.9070689,41.1424666 64.697389,44.8459821 L35.0603803,42.1188616 C35.0603803,38.0786628 35.799618,34.0721925 37.2781156,30.0993304 C38.7566133,26.1264682 41.0079281,22.3220048 44.0321278,18.6858259 C47.0563275,15.049647 50.6853127,11.8512043 54.9191923,9.09040179 C59.1530718,6.32959929 64.2437316,4.12435721 70.1913243,2.47460938 C76.138917,0.824861543 82.5400437,0 89.3948963,0 C96.11534,0 102.19725,0.841695452 107.64081,2.52511161 C113.084369,4.20852776 117.435791,6.27909857 120.695207,8.73688616 C123.954622,11.1946737 126.676361,13.9891026 128.860505,17.1202567 C131.044649,20.2514107 132.556726,23.1468431 133.396782,25.8066406 C134.236837,28.4664382 134.656859,30.9410228 134.656859,33.2304688 L134.656859,92.7220982 Z M66.9151244,94.843192 C66.9151244,100.634144 69.2672444,105.111963 73.971555,108.276786 C78.4070479,111.239598 83.0776862,111.98029 87.9836102,110.498884 C93.6287829,108.815468 97.4593784,104.674326 99.4755115,98.0753348 C100.416374,95.0451857 100.886798,91.6447361 100.886798,87.8738839 L100.886798,71.5111607 C96.9217358,71.645834 93.1919455,72.0498478 89.6973147,72.7232143 C86.202684,73.3965807 82.6241014,74.5244527 78.9614595,76.1068638 C75.2988177,77.689275 72.3754685,80.0796901 70.1913243,83.2781808 C68.0071801,86.4766715 66.9151244,90.3316367 66.9151244,94.843192 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
				&lt;/g&gt;
			&lt;/g&gt;
		&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Amazon&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;

	&lt;button name="appleSignUpButton" class="btn apple-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;

                &lt;span&gt;&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 170 170" version="1.1"&gt;
    &lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;
        &lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;
            &lt;path d="m150.37 130.25c-2.45 5.66-5.35 10.87-8.71 15.66-4.58 6.53-8.33 11.05-11.22 13.56-4.48 4.12-9.28 6.23-14.42 6.35-3.69 0-8.14-1.05-13.32-3.18-5.197-2.12-9.973-3.17-14.34-3.17-4.58 0-9.492 1.05-14.746 3.17-5.262 2.13-9.501 3.24-12.742 3.35-4.929 0.21-9.842-1.96-14.746-6.52-3.13-2.73-7.045-7.41-11.735-14.04-5.032-7.08-9.169-15.29-12.41-24.65-3.471-10.11-5.211-19.9-5.211-29.378 0-10.857 2.346-20.221 7.045-28.068 3.693-6.303 8.606-11.275 14.755-14.925s12.793-5.51 19.948-5.629c3.915 0 9.049 1.211 15.429 3.591 6.362 2.388 10.447 3.599 12.238 3.599 1.339 0 5.877-1.416 13.57-4.239 7.275-2.618 13.415-3.702 18.445-3.275 13.63 1.1 23.87 6.473 30.68 16.153-12.19 7.386-18.22 17.731-18.1 31.002 0.11 10.337 3.86 18.939 11.23 25.769 3.34 3.17 7.07 5.62 11.22 7.36-0.9 2.61-1.85 5.11-2.86 7.51zm-31.26-123.01c0 8.1021-2.96 15.667-8.86 22.669-7.12 8.324-15.732 13.134-25.071 12.375-0.119-0.972-0.188-1.995-0.188-3.07 0-7.778 3.386-16.102 9.399-22.908 3.002-3.446 6.82-6.3113 11.45-8.597 4.62-2.2516 8.99-3.4968 13.1-3.71 0.12 1.0831 0.17 2.1663 0.17 3.2409z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
        &lt;/g&gt;
    &lt;/g&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Apple&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;

	&lt;p class="social-login__legal"&gt;We won't post to any of your accounts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	

&lt;/div&gt;

		
			
	














		

				

		&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Woman's World</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 02:30:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxNOFhrbHk3UklINDJNaUM4N0FWLXI0NnhRbTJfcnRRZ0pCSHVRTzZnRHp5MzJ2em5KXzRHdWJJRHgyTXlSNXczN1ZRWERPVVRxYnV6X043Qm5XTU5hWjNpWjRyTnZyU0xfd051TVlfMjhYMlVoREI3QlQ0OEZGYzZxRHdIdm41Szh1cG5ZX29FVUZvMzNXU0VZR2k4Mkt5SEFNaWE5bg</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现另一个在完全黑暗中睡觉的原因- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-uncover-yet-another-reason-to-sleep-in-total-darkness-2000681512</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl prose-science dark:prose-science"&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;It turns out that your annoying friend who insists on closing all of the window blinds and covering all of the glowing electronics in a bedroom in order to sleep in total darkness is onto something. New research bolsters the &lt;a href="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/news/2022/study-sleeping-even-small-amount-light-could-harm-heart-health"&gt;well-established&lt;/a&gt; theory linking nighttime light to adverse health impacts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A preliminary analysis set to be presented at the American Heart Association’s Scientific Sessions 2025, starting Friday, suggests that the state of darkness while we sleep plays a crucial role in our overall health. The results link more artificial light at night, also known as artificial nighttime light pollution, with higher brain stress signals, inflamed blood vessels, and greater risk of &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/heartdiseases.html"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;—a broad term for different heart problems.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“We know that environmental factors, such as air and noise pollution, can lead to heart disease by affecting our nerves and blood vessels through stress. Light pollution is very common; however, we don’t know much about how it affects the heart,” Shady Abohashem, head of cardiac PET/CT imaging trials at Massachusetts General Hospital and senior author of the yet-unpublished study, said in a &lt;a href="https://newsroom.heart.org/news/exposure-to-more-artificial-light-at-night-may-raise-heart-disease-risk?preview=d465&amp;amp;preview_mode=True"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; by the American Heart Association.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;Artificial nighttime brightness at home&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;In the observational study, Abohashem and his colleagues reviewed the health data of 466 adults who had undergone the same combined Positron Emission Tomography/Computed Tomography (PET/CT) scan at Massachusetts General Hospital in Boston between 2005 and 2008 to identify stress signals in the brain and evidence of artery inflammation. They also investigated the adults’ exposure to artificial nighttime brightness at their homes via the 2016 New World Atlas of Artificial Night Sky Brightness.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The researchers found that people who experienced greater amounts of nighttime artificial light had higher brain stress activity, blood vessel inflammation, and a greater chance of developing heart disease. Unsurprisingly, the risk of heart issues was increased among participants who lived in areas with additional stress factors like significant traffic noise or lower neighborhood income. By the end of 2018, 17% of the adults had experienced significant heart problems.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“We found a nearly linear relationship between nighttime light and heart disease: the more night-light exposure, the higher the risk. Even modest increases in night-time light were linked with higher brain and artery stress,” Abohashem explained. The correlation remained even after researchers adjusted for known heart risk factors and other socio-environmental stresses.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“When the brain perceives stress, it activates signals that can trigger an immune response and inflame the blood vessels,” he added. “Over time, this process can contribute to hardening of the arteries and increase the risk of heart attack and stroke.”&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;Put the phone down&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;So what can we do about it? Cities could diminish unnecessary external lighting, and individuals could lessen indoor nighttime light before going to bed, according to Abohashem. That includes screens, which means no more scrolling on TikTok before snoozing.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“We know too much exposure to artificial light at night can harm your health, particularly increasing the risk of heart disease. However, we did not know how this harm happened,” said Julio Fernandez-Mendoza, who is director of behavioral sleep medicine at Pennsylvania State University College of Medicine and was not involved in the study. “This study has investigated one of several possible causes, which is how our brains respond to stress. This response seems to play a big role in linking artificial light at night to heart disease.”&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;However, the study has some limitations, according to the statement. For example, the participants were drawn from a single hospital system, so the group may lack diversity, and the results might not reflect the broader population. Furthermore, because of the nature of an observational study, it can’t prove that the associations are causal.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“We want to expand this work in larger, more diverse populations, test interventions that reduce nighttime light, and explore how reducing light exposure might improve heart health,” Abohashem concluded.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxQaEhQbXBybDI3elQxY05VNjBCUUxabkJSa3NTUDgzMlB5cEpKYzRhMUliS3ZYaUY3RFlKWHVjNmI2ek4yUGxkRTYxTHpEQmlnR1dUaC1qdjR0eTdiU0pLeXFVWFRNYkVaYWlLbk1aVTdUSXZRZ0FOVnJIY1JTZ0V1SThCaW90MllQY2w1alplODdpd2ZkZ3hxZmRVVQ</guid></item><item><title>猫也可能患上痴呆症–以下是需要注意的八个迹象- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/cats-can-get-dementia-too-here-are-the-eight-signs-to-look-out-for/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many cat owners don’t realise that just like humans, cats can suffer from dementia. A recent paper has even found many similarities between &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/ejn.70180"&gt;feline and human dementia&lt;/a&gt;, finding that cognitive impairment may &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0197458004002337?via%3Dihub"&gt;develop in similar ways&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the symptoms of dementia in cats are even similar to what we might see in humans – though not all of them, of course. Knowing what signs to look out for is important so you can provide your cat with the best care during this phase of its life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Feline cognitive dysfunction syndrome (also known as feline dementia) is an age-related decline in a cat’s cognitive abilities. It’s generally characterised by behavioural changes that cannot be attributed to other medical conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Feline dementia is thought to be very common in older cats. One study found that by 15 years of age, more than &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/j.1748-5827.2007.00386.x"&gt;half of cats&lt;/a&gt; showed signs of dementia. However, some behaviour associated with the condition has also been identified in cats &lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/342728023_Prevalence_of_Disease_and_Age-Related_Behavioural_Changes_in_Cats_Past_and_Present"&gt;as young as seven&lt;/a&gt;. A separate survey of cat owners also found that &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/j.1748-5827.2007.00386.x"&gt;around 28% of cats&lt;/a&gt; aged between 11 and 14 exhibited at least one behavioural change associated with dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0195561611000428?via%3Dihub"&gt;Behavioural changes&lt;/a&gt; are often the first indication that there may be something wrong. There are eight signs to look out for that might indicate &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1111/j.1748-5827.2007.00386.x?saml_referrer"&gt;your cat has dementia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Unusual vocalisation:&lt;/strong&gt; Your cat might start to vocalise excessively, or in new situations. A common example of this is &lt;a href="https://bvajournals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/vetr.3"&gt;meowing loudly at night&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Altered interactions:&lt;/strong&gt; Cats with dementia sometimes &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/full/10.1016/j.jfms.2010.09.004"&gt;seek attention more&lt;/a&gt; often or become “clingy”. Equally, cats with dementia might interact less than previously, appear irritable or seem not to recognise familiar people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Sleep changes:&lt;/strong&gt; You may notice changes in your cat’s &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0195561611000428?via%3Dihub"&gt;sleeping habits&lt;/a&gt; – often becoming restless at night and sleeping more during the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. House soiling:&lt;/strong&gt; Changes in toilet habits can be a sign of several different conditions, but &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1938973611000079"&gt;toileting outside the litter tray&lt;/a&gt; can be a common sign of dementia in cats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Disorientation:&lt;/strong&gt; Just like people with dementia, cats may show &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1938973611000079"&gt;signs of confusion&lt;/a&gt; or wandering behaviour. This might appear as losing their bearings, staring blankly at walls, getting stuck behind objects or going to the wrong side of the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Changes in activity levels:&lt;/strong&gt; A cat with dementia may be &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0195561612000678?via%3Dihub"&gt;more or less active than usual&lt;/a&gt;. They may play less often or be less inclined to explore. You might also notice them spending less time taking care of themselves, for example grooming or washing themselves less.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. Appearing anxious:&lt;/strong&gt; A cat with dementia might show &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0195561611000428?via%3Dihub"&gt;signs of anxiety&lt;/a&gt; in situations that they were previously confident with – such as around familiar people, places or sounds. An anxious cat might hide more often, going under the bed or on top of cupboards to escape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8. Learning problems:&lt;/strong&gt; Cats with dementia may be less unable to perform &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0195561612000678"&gt;previously learned tasks&lt;/a&gt;, such as finding their food bowl, and may have difficulty learning new tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Caring for your cat&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s significant overlap between symptoms of feline dementia and other common conditions, such as &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/1098612x13511446"&gt;arthritis&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/gps.4226"&gt;kidney disease &lt;/a&gt;. So if you see any of these behavioural changes in your cat, you should speak to your vet to rule out these other conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research into feline dementia is limited. Much of what we know about prevention and treatment is extrapolated from research into humans and dogs. And, as with these other species, there’s no cure for dementia in cats. But there are ways of limiting the impact of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain environmental modifications can help stimulate cats, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/vetr.3"&gt;activating their brains and causing nerves to grow&lt;/a&gt;. But the severity of your cat’s dementia must be considered before making any of these changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In healthy or mildly affected cats, promoting play or simulating hunting with interactive toys and encouraging exploration using hide and seek games is thought to &lt;a href="https://bvajournals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/vetr.3"&gt;delay the progression&lt;/a&gt; of cognitive dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in cats with severe cognitive impairment, changing their environment could lead to confusion and anxiety – &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cvsm.2011.03.017"&gt;worsening behavioural symptoms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cvsm.2003.09.007"&gt;Diet changes&lt;/a&gt; – specifically the addition of supplements containing antioxidants (vitamin E and C) and essential fatty acids – may also help to reduce inflammation in the brain, slowing the disease’s progression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, only dog-specific supplements have been tested in scientific research and proven to enhance cognition in dogs. But if you do want to try giving these supplements to your cat, be sure you only give them supplements approved for felines. Dog supplements should not be given to cats as they may include substances that are toxic to cats – such as &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/vec.13142"&gt;alpha lipoic acid&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Feline dementia is a condition both highly prevalent and challenging to manage. Knowing what symptoms to look out for can ensure your cat gets diagnosed earlier on. This will also ensure you’re able to make the necessary changes to its environment or diet that will ultimately improve its quality of life.&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/263148/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img class="lazyload" decoding="async" src="" data-src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/263148/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/cats-can-get-dementia-too-here-are-the-eight-signs-to-look-out-for-263148"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 01:08:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPNmU3Q1M3RkRicktFaTNGZnRROXl3LUQyaGx3UDg3R2Y3Qkx3YXc0QURTSk1HNEJoSWZTanBBa2pGWXdldUtvUHBaaEFadURwb3owU1N2d0p6Vk9vdFh0Q0dLT2tfaW9jRjV1SlNhQ2RMdVlzSnNwS3hwZUJrNnc2enJiNXNBMlNuaGhpM3ZvTDVhRG85MlE</guid></item><item><title>运动“训练”免疫系统，新研究揭示- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/exercise-trains-the-immune-system-new-research-reveals/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:46:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNcE5QTnp2M2N1Vkp0TWRLU01rTWswcndMRFY0SnV2czdQWWRNallNOF8yVTNBQlV6YnBxbHEzYnJFZFlDd2VvZ2Q2WWlRNURfNzB5SkZoMkFucnRfQ2RKNmZsSXI2T0JUVXhVREp2VTZ2ZTh1MW16dTZoWkN3VW9wUDJhVk9EZ3c</guid></item><item><title>与未来死亡风险密切相关的选举投票行为- Phys.org</title><link>https://phys.org/news/2025-11-voting-behavior-elections-strongly-linked.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
										
&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2019/election.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2019/election.jpg" data-sub-html="Credit: CC0 Public Domain"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2019/election.jpg" alt="election" title="Credit: CC0 Public Domain"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-darken text-low-up text-truncate-js text-truncate mt-3"&gt;
                Credit: CC0 Public Domain
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voting behavior in elections is strongly linked to the future risk of death, and is likely a stronger determinant of health than education—considered a key influence on health—suggests research published online in the &lt;i&gt;Journal of Epidemiology &amp;amp; Community Health&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;


										  

										
																																	&lt;p&gt;Over the past several years, voting in national and local elections has increasingly been seen as a potential social determinant of health—the non-medical factors that influence health and well-being—explain the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And previously published research suggests that voters generally have better health than non-voters, but it's not clear if electoral participation might also be a predictor of future &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/death/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;death&lt;/a&gt; risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To explore this further, the researchers drew on electoral participation information in the 1999 &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/parliamentary+elections/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;parliamentary elections&lt;/a&gt; for the entire electorate of Finnish citizens living in mainland Finland and aged at least 30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turnout among this age group was 71.5% for men and 72.5% for women. In all, 3,185,572 people (1,508,824 men; 1,676,748 women) were included in the study and their survival was tracked from 21 March 1999 (election day) to death or the end of 2020, whichever came first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Between 1999 and 2020, 1,053,483 people died: 95,350 from external causes (accidents, violence and alcohol-attributable causes); 955,723 from other underlying causes; 2,410 people whose cause of death wasn't known were excluded from the final analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not voting was consistently associated with a 73% heightened risk of death from any cause among men and a 63% heightened risk of death among women.&lt;/p&gt;

																																						&lt;p class="w-100 mb-4 ads"&gt;
    
     
&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="8188791252"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
																																			&lt;p&gt;After adjusting for education level (basic or unknown; secondary; or tertiary), this reduced to a 64% heightened risk among men and a 59% heightened risk among women.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The difference in the risk of death between voters and non-voters was larger than it was between those with basic and tertiary level education.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The association between voting participation and death was stronger for external causes of death than for other causes. And when adjusted for age, this risk was twice as high among both men and women who didn't vote than it was among those who did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The difference in the relative risk of death between voters and non-voters was strongest among men under 50. Among 75 to 94-year-olds, women who didn't vote had a higher risk of death than men who voted, whereas the reverse was true for younger age groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And among men in the lowest 25% of &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/household+income/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;household income&lt;/a&gt;, the risk of death associated with not voting was 9–12% higher than it was for other income groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an observational study, and as such, can't establish cause and effect. And the researchers acknowledge various limitations to their findings, including that some people might have wanted to vote, but were unable to do so, or simply chose not to vote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, the fact that voting was more strongly associated with the risk of death than educational level "suggests a strong association between voting and mortality, given that a substantial education gradient in mortality is among the most robustly established sociodemographic mortality patterns," they suggest.&lt;/p&gt;

																									&lt;div class="ads w-100 my-4 article-main__more bg-light p-3 border" aria-hidden="true"&gt;
    &lt;p class="mb-3"&gt;
        Discover the latest in science, tech, and space with over &lt;strong&gt;100,000 subscribers&lt;/strong&gt; who rely on Phys.org for daily insights.
        Sign up for our &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/help/newsletter/" target="_blank"&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; and get updates on breakthroughs,
        innovations, and research that matter—&lt;strong&gt;daily or weekly&lt;/strong&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;/div&gt;
																																			&lt;p&gt;"Voting, as a form of participation, is a type of social capital, which is linked to &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/health+benefits/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;health benefits&lt;/a&gt;. In addition, voting may increase other forms of civic participation," they explain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Health problems and related difficulties in functioning may also negatively affect many important prerequisites of participation, including enhancing resources, motivation to &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/vote/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;vote&lt;/a&gt;, and political mobilization," they add.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They conclude, "Information on voting may be useful in &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/clinical+settings/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;clinical settings&lt;/a&gt;—for example, abandonment of voting habits may be an early signal of significant health decline—and in monitoring population well-being, health, and health disparities. Additionally, a strong association between voting and mortality raises concerns about equal political representation."&lt;/p&gt;

																																	
																														
																				&lt;div class="article-main__more p-4"&gt;
																						&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information:&lt;/strong&gt;
												Voting is a stronger determinant of mortality than education: a full- electorate survival analysis with 21-year follow-up, &lt;i&gt;Journal of Epidemiology and Community Health&lt;/i&gt; (2025). &lt;a data-doi="1" href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1136/jech-2025-224663" target="_blank"&gt;DOI: 10.1136/jech-2025-224663&lt;/a&gt;
																						
																						&lt;/p&gt;
																					&lt;/div&gt;
                               														
																					
                              													                                        
										
										&lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
											 &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
												&lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
												Voting behavior in elections strongly linked to future risk of death (2025, November 4)
												retrieved 5 November 2025
												from https://phys.org/news/2025-11-voting-behavior-elections-strongly-linked.html
											 &lt;/p&gt;
											 &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
											 This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
											 part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
											 &lt;/p&gt;
										&lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:30:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxOdXBHaEFKRE9nTENlWFl5dmt3S2hON0lIOFp2dXFRVnhSQ3g0VjBicmFSTEE2YklsVFUtMzNhUnU5TzVZV3ZIMXZXTWN0ZDgxSUZLc2VGTDhfS2FWSjU1czMwaHJPTFhKUFhRVkNpa3hsWHg2NDBSbFFwaWJHMnJZcmp3</guid></item><item><title>由头发制成的牙膏可以再生牙釉质- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/toothpaste-made-from-hair-could-regrow-tooth-enamel/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:31:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNUVVlUm1JUzhrSWdBRmdfRDUzNEpkeWNfb1c3YVJ0SnVoZzVseG5lMkU4LXFhREhLVmpuRjFTQUtpLVNsTHFOYWlCOXVuZ3FGRnVzNWtNVGZUY3FibkFfMmlVTE5Fbl84M3ZFNW1rUGVKQWd3MHJEdU5zYUJsTDhGX2pZaw</guid></item><item><title>一些常见病毒可能会急剧增加心血管疾病的风险- CIDRAP</title><link>https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/influenza-general/some-common-viruses-may-steeply-raise-risk-cardiovascular-disease</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-field-body field--type-text-long field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/JAHA.125.042670"&gt;&lt;span&gt;meta-analysis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of 155 observational studies ties influenza, COVID-19, hepatitis C, and herpes zoster (shingles) to a dramatically higher risk of major cardiovascular events such as heart attack and stroke in the weeks after infection, and viruses that linger in the body (eg, HIV) can raise long-term risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A University of California Los Angeles (UCLA) researcher led the study, a systematic review of literature on the link between any viral infection and the odds of heart attack and stroke. The findings were published last week in the &lt;em&gt;Journal of the American Heart Association&lt;/em&gt; (AHA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is well recognized that human papillomavirus (HPV), hepatitis B virus, and other viruses can cause cancer; however, the link between viral infections and other non-communicable diseases, such as cardiovascular disease, is less well understood," lead author Kosuke Kawai, ScD, of UCLA, said in an AHA &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1103173"&gt;&lt;span&gt;news release&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Stroke 5 times more likely after flu&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 155 studies, published from 1997 to July 2024, were primarily conducted in North America, Europe, and East Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Self‐controlled case series studies tied flu to a fourfold elevated risk of heart attack (pooled incidence rate ratio [IRR], 4.01) and a fivefold higher risk of stroke during the first 1 month (IRR, 5.01), and cohort studies suggested a higher risk of coronary heart disease (CHD) with hepatitis C infection (RR, 1.27) and stroke (RR, 1.23). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HIV was consistently linked to a higher risk of CHD (pooled adjusted risk ratio [RR], 1.60) and stroke (RR, 1.45), as was SARS‐CoV‐2 (CHD RR, 1.74; stroke RR, 1.69). Likewise, shingles was associated with a greater risk of CHD (RR, 1.12) and stroke (RR, 1.18). Evidence of an effect of cytomegalovirus, which can cause birth defects, on cardiovascular disease was insufficient. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study authors noted that viral infections trigger the immune system to release substances that lead to inflammation and increase the risk of blood clots, processes that may persist long after initial infection and raise the risk of heart attack and stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The elevated risks for cardiovascular disease risks are lower for HIV, hepatitis C and herpes zoster than the heightened short-term risk following influenza and COVID," Kawai said. "However, the risks associated with those three viruses are still clinically relevant, especially because they persist for a long period of time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And when it comes to shingles, which affects roughly one in three people in their lifetime, "the elevated risk associated with that virus translates into a large number of excess cases of cardiovascular disease at the population level," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Vaccines' role in preventing heart, vascular disease&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our study highlights the importance of integrated preventive measures, especially for adults with traditional risk factors for CVD [cardiovascular disease]," the researchers concluded. "Vaccines may play an important role in preventing the risk of CVD."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CIDRAP</author><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:38:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxQaEo0bHE2Rm5yUWQ5dlFibDVNUHhzd3F4STZjQ0hZSXpja0Z1MTRwRzhyQkRSRjlzaXNZWFpkbUd4TW5ZUGRjS24wczEwVVJscjV1SDg5RDBhVlo1aFBYM2l3cU1nVE5iZmg3cUVxc2ZHdGR0QUdPOUFzSXNleTdJbU9rcGNTemtTdDcyTndQSUNxLV9oem0xSzdMS0EzQXJWcUdfdm94aW83YkUzUUU0</guid></item><item><title>越来越多的美国年轻人被警告肠道扭曲“老人病” -美国太阳报</title><link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/15442442/health-warning-early-onset-diverticulitis/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom article__content"&gt;
							










&lt;p&gt;RESEARCHERS have discovered a concerning new trend regarding the gut health of young people. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/health/"&gt;A new study&lt;/a&gt; found that the number of young people suffering from severe gut complications has risen by over 50 percent. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="single__inline-module inline-module inline-module--newsletter aligncenter inline-module--thesun wp-block-nypost-editor-newsletter" data-source-unit="Inline Newsletter Module "&gt;
	&lt;div class="inline-module__inner"&gt;
		&lt;div class="inline-module__title-wrapper"&gt;
			
							&lt;p class="inline-module__unsubmitted-title-wrapper"&gt;
											&lt;h3 class="inline-module__title headline headline--combo-sm-md"&gt;
							Sign up for &lt;span class="newsletter-name theme-main"&gt;The US Sun&lt;/span&gt; newsletter						&lt;/h3&gt;
					
									&lt;/p&gt;
			
							&lt;p class="inline-module__success-title-wrapper"&gt;
					&lt;h3 class="inline-module__title headline headline--combo-sm-md"&gt;
						Thank you!					&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;

		

	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;figure id="attachment_15442471" class="wp-caption alignnone aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-modal-image="15442471" src="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?w=960" alt="Ulcerative colitis, illustration" class="alignnone size-thesun-article-image wp-image-15442471" srcset="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 5580w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=300,169&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 300w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=768,432&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=1024,576&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=1536,864&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 1536w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=2048,1152&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 2048w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=600,338&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 600w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=878,494&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 878w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=744,419&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 744w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=576,324&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 576w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=440,248&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 440w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=424,239&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 424w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=180,101&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 180w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=107,60&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 107w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=130,73&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 130w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=71,40&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 71w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=124,70&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 124w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=96,54&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 96w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=200,113&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 200w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=231,130&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 231w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=322,181&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 322w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=664,374&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 664w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=142,80&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 142w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=960,540&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 960w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=140,79&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 140w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=1920,1080&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 1920w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=742,417&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 742w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/ulcerative-colitis-illustration-1036138301.jpg?resize=50,28&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 50w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Younger people are experiencing colon issues (stock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Credit: Getty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure id="attachment_15442472" class="wp-caption alignnone aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-modal-image="15442472" src="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?w=960" alt="The Young Woman Treats Bowel Polyps" class="alignnone size-thesun-article-image wp-image-15442472" srcset="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 6354w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=300,158&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 300w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=768,405&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=1024,540&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=1536,810&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 1536w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=2048,1080&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 2048w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=600,316&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 600w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=878,463&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 878w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=744,392&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 744w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=576,304&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 576w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=440,232&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 440w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=424,224&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 424w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=180,95&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 180w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=107,56&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 107w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=76,40&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 76w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=133,70&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 133w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=102,54&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 102w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=200,105&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 200w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=231,122&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 231w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=322,170&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 322w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=664,350&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 664w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=114,60&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 114w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=152,80&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 152w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=960,506&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 960w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/11/young-woman-treats-bowel-polyps-1036138278.jpg?resize=50,26&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 50w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Those under the age of 50 are reporting higher cases of early-onset diverticulitis (stock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Credit: Getty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Between 2005 and 2020, &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/dcrjournal/abstract/2025/05000/national_trends_in_hospital_admissions,.13.aspx" target="_blank" aria-label=" (opens in a new tab)" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" data-nyp-affiliate="true"&gt;the study&lt;/a&gt; conducted by researchers from UCLA and Vanderbilt University reviewed hospital admissions, interventions, and outcomes for early-onset diverticulitis. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Diverticulitis is commonly found in those over 50 years old and is caused by the inflammation or infection of pouches called diverticula. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The pouches form in the wall of the colon.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;When irritated, people may experience abdominal pain, fever, and changes in bowel movements. &lt;/p&gt;
		
		&lt;p class="article-readmore__content-clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

		&lt;p id="outstream" class="nuk-ad-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Extreme cases could lead to perforation or bowel obstruction, which would require surgery. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;People with diverticulitis tend to be diagnosed between the ages of 52 and 64; however, studies show that this age range is changing.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;After reviewing 5.2 million hospitalizations in the National Inpatient Sample, researchers found that the proportion of patients under the age of 50 being admitted with diverticulitis complications increased form 18.5 percent to 28.2 percent. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers noted that the reason for the drastic increase still remains unclear, however, &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/health/10531604/dangers-favourite-foods-cancer-lung-issue-death/"&gt;lifestyle changes&lt;/a&gt; in younger people have a massive impact on diverticulitis. &lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;In 2012, a study estimated that about 40 to 53 percent of cases were inheritable, according to &lt;a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15253749/young-people-increased-disease-colon-diverticulitis.html" target="_blank" aria-label=" (opens in a new tab)" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" data-nyp-affiliate="true"&gt;The Daily Mail&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;However, a 2025 study found that those who may be genetically predisposed to the complication &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/health/13195259/magic-numbers-reveal-just-how-healthy-you-are/"&gt;but had a low BMI&lt;/a&gt;, didn’t smoke, and ate nutritious foods were less likely to have the condition.&lt;/p&gt;



		
						
						
		



&lt;p&gt;Younger patients with early-onset diverticulitis were found to have lower mortality rates and shorter hospital stays.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Conversely, younger patients were more likely to need invasive interventions.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Early-onset patients are 29 percent more likely to need a colectomy, which removes part or all of the colon. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;They are also 58 percent more likely to need the area to be drained. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“While younger patients generally have better survival outcomes and shorter hospitalizations, they’re paradoxically more likely to need invasive interventions,” Lead author and fourth-year medical student at UCLA Shineui Kim wrote in the study. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“This suggests their disease may be more aggressive or that treatment approaches differ based on patient age and overall health status.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Kim noted that more research needs to urgently be conducted to investigate the cause of the rise in early-onset diverticulitis. &lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
						
													&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The US Sun</author><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:34:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQdFhqZUlHWHkzbXRYeHBvVnNCeDQxNWNjcUE3RExnWThxR0VVeHh0N3RqcEhsanMtVHFKTERuRUd6M1pPNHJNWlFhU0xWcXZHNkFZT0U4SjNyWWwyZlhLNTAwQ3dRNlpHU1ZaM19naWEyNEdia2t4QnhlTV9Oc3hBaktKakdIMy1XaXc</guid></item><item><title>“我是一名急诊室医生-这种常见的感冒疗法每年都会送人去医院” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/m-er-doctor-common-cold-212500231.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Oh, it's just a cold!" Indeed, colds are often billed as a "mild" upper respiratory virus. You can generally manage them at home, whereas the &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/experts-warn-look-flu-symptoms-145000937.html" data-ylk="slk:flu;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt;, RSV and &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/4-most-common-covid-symptoms-182500971.html" data-ylk="slk:COVID;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;COVID&lt;/a&gt; send more people to the hospital, especially older adults, young kids and people with compromised &lt;a href="https://health.yahoo.com/conditions/immune-system/articles/immunologists-people-over-50-adopt-182500882.html" data-ylk="slk:immune systems;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;immune systems&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yet, colds don't feel all that mild when you're in the throes of one. The coughing, sneezing and stuffy nose can prevent you from sleeping at a time when you need rest more than ever. You may hate to call out of work, cancel plans or not see relatives over the winter holidays.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Understandably, you want to nix a cold the second you feel one coming on. While there's no cure for a common cold, there are over-the-counter remedies that can soothe symptoms and provide relief. However, one common cold remedy sends people to the hospital each year when it's used incorrectly. Here's what to know about it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🩺&lt;a href="https://parade.com/newsletters/healthy-now-2" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SIGN UP for Parade’s health newsletter with expert-approved tips, healthy eats, exercises, news &amp;amp; more to help you stay healthy &amp;amp; feel your best self;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;SIGN UP for Parade’s health newsletter with expert-approved tips, healthy eats, exercises, news &amp;amp; more to help you stay healthy &amp;amp; feel your best self&lt;/a&gt;💊&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;The Common Cold Remedy That Sends People to the Hospital, ER Doctor Warns&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;An ER doctor reveals that using decongestants for cold symptoms carries risks that land people in the hospital each year. "Two big reasons decongestants send people to the hospital each year include misuse and interactions," states &lt;a href="https://som.cuanschutz.edu/Profiles/Faculty/Profile/22968" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Matthew Zuckerman, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Matthew Zuckerman, MD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a practicing ER physician and associate professor at the University of Colorado Anschutz.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He understands why people use decongestants—they want to breathe more easily and sleep better when they have a cold. Some people also notice that their ear and sinus symptoms worsen on flights and may take decongestants for relief.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Decongestants shrink swollen blood vessels in the nose, which can temporarily decrease drainage and swelling, reducing sinus pressure," Dr. Zuckerman explains. While their over-the-counter status can give decongestants a "safe" halo, he notes that every drug carries risks, including decongestants.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://health.yahoo.com/conditions/respiratory-illness/articles/healthy-activity-avoid-sick-according-182500178.html" data-ylk="slk:The One Activity an Infectious Disease Expert Is Begging You To Avoid When You Start Feeling Sick;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;The One Activity an Infectious Disease Expert Is Begging You To Avoid When You Start Feeling Sick&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;The Risks of Decongestants&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Dr. Zuckerman says the two biggest risks of decongestant use for colds are misuse and drug interactions. It's essential to understand these risks and how to avoid them, as the side effects can lead to a need for emergency care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Is it safe to take decongestants daily?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Taking decongestants daily for long periods is dangerous and a flag for misuse. Unfortunately, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10142332/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:misuse of decongestants is common;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;misuse of decongestants is common&lt;/a&gt;, and sometimes unintentional. Dr. Zuckerman says misuse includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Taking too much (accidentally or purposefully)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Using nasal sprays for more than three days&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Stacking cold products that contain a decongestant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;To be fair, self-treating colds with decongestants can get tricky if you don't have a medical degree. "Many cold remedies combine several drugs, and the labels can be confusing, so it’s easy to double-dose the same ingredient without realizing it," he notes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Zuckerman adds that decongestants, like pseudoephedrine (Sudafed) or phenylephrine, can:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;He adds that antihistamines (especially first-generation ones, like Benadryl), which mainly treat allergy symptoms, also have side effects, including:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Finally, Dr. Zuckerman reports that using decongestants for more than three days can cause rebound congestion, which is often worse than the original stuffy nose. &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/14656566.2024.2411009" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Data also shows;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Data also shows&lt;/a&gt; that prolonged use or taking higher-than-recommended doses of decongestants can have this effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What medications interact with decongestants?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Dr. Zuckerman notes that decongestants, commonly used to relieve cold symptoms, can also interact with other medications, especially ones for conditions like:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;High blood pressure, abnormal heart rhythms and other cardiovascular issues&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;ADHD and other conditions treated with stimulants&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"The result can be severe headache, chest pain, very high blood pressure or dangerous heart rhythms," Dr. Zuckerman warns. "Additionally, many of these medications contain acetaminophen, increasing the risk of accidental overdose when patients also take other acetaminophen‑containing products for pain."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://health.yahoo.com/conditions/respiratory-illness/cold-and-flu/articles/doctors-warn-against-common-cold-145000837.html" data-ylk="slk:Doctors Warn Against This Common Cold Remedy Mistake That Actually Makes Symptoms Worse;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;Doctors Warn Against This Common Cold Remedy Mistake That Actually Makes Symptoms Worse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Signs You Need To Go to the ER After Using Decongestants&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Understanding when to seek immediate care after using a decongestant can help ensure you or your loved one stays safe. Dr. Zuckerman advises people to call 9-1-1 or go to the ER if they experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Chest pain, chest pressure or a pounding/irregular heartbeat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A very high home blood pressure reading or a fast heart rate that you can’t slow down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Severe headache, confusion, vision changes or fainting&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Shortness of breath, severe anxiety/agitation or tremors/seizures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Severe allergic reaction, including swelling of lips and tongue, trouble breathing or widespread hives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://health.yahoo.com/conditions/respiratory-illness/cold-and-flu/articles/one-food-nutritionists-help-shorten-145000250.html" data-ylk="slk:The One Food Nutritionists Say Can Help Shorten a Cold;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;The One Food Nutritionists Say Can Help Shorten a Cold&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Alternatives to Decongestants&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Decongestants are often touted as the be-all and end-all of cold management. However, they can carry unwanted side effects that actually make you sicker, especially when misused or if they interact with medications you take for conditions like high blood pressure. Dr. Zuckerman says there are alternatives to decongestants that can help you safely tame cold symptoms, including:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saline nasal spray/irrigation&lt;/strong&gt;. These tools help rinse out mucus and allergens, and are generally safe for frequent use, Dr. Zuckerman explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Humidified air/steam and fluids&lt;/strong&gt;. Dr. Zuckerman reports that humidifiers can help thin mucus, allowing it to drain more easily. As a result, you'll hopefully soothe your throat and nasal irritation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nasal strips&lt;/strong&gt;. These handy strips, available at your local pharmacy, open the nasal passages from the outside, Dr. Zuckerman shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If your decongestion is actually allergy-related, Dr. Zuckerman says second-generation antihistamines (such as cetirizine or loratadine) can help relieve congestion without causing drowsiness. He adds that an Intranasal steroid spray (like fluticasone) can reduce allergy-driven nasal inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As always, though, it's best to talk to your doctor to ensure you're taking medications that are safe and effective based on your personal health needs. The goal is to get you on the mend &lt;em&gt;stat&lt;/em&gt;, not make things worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Up Next:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/articles/one-habit-doctors-begging-break-232500318.html" data-ylk="slk:Related: The One Habit Doctors Are Begging You To Break ASAP if You Don't Want To Get Sick This Fall;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;Related: The One Habit Doctors Are Begging You To Break ASAP if You Don't Want To Get Sick This Fall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Sources:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally reported by &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/common-cold-remedy-that-sends-people-to-hospital-according-to-er-doctor" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Parade&lt;/a&gt; on Nov 4, 2025, where it first appeared in the &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Health &amp;amp; Wellness;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Health &amp;amp; Wellness&lt;/a&gt; section. Add Parade as a &lt;a href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=parade.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Preferred Source by clicking here.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Preferred Source by clicking here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:25:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE93NVNjVHBUc2t6b0tKdE8xNHNrZmdiM3VrUTBxRkVBTlUxSU84el9DSldZa0NCeU9yY1RZRjZ0OFdNN3NlbWdVa3VvNl9XbHZnR1RkdkJ3OTY1OHYyZHJWODV2bUVSeFFoMVpNeXZCR19MeTRnYVZ4NmZqZF9wWjQ</guid></item><item><title>人工智能绘制大脑的隐藏桥梁，揭示与心理健康的遗传联系-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://neurosciencenews.com/ai-genetics-mental-health-29893/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;For the first time, scientists have mapped the genetic architecture of the brain’s communication bridge—the corpus callosum—using AI and MRI data from over 50,000 people. The study uncovered dozens of genes that shape this vital structure’s size and thickness, many active during prenatal development when the brain’s wiring is established.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Differences in these genes may explain why changes in the corpus callosum are associated with mental and neurological disorders. The team’s open-source AI tool now enables global researchers to analyze brain structure faster and with unprecedented precision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First Genetic Blueprint:&lt;/strong&gt; Identified genetic regions that shape the brain’s left-right communication bridge.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI-Driven Discovery:&lt;/strong&gt; Used artificial intelligence to map brain structure across 50,000 MRI scans in record time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mental Health Connection:&lt;/strong&gt; Found genetic overlap between the corpus callosum, cerebral cortex, ADHD, and bipolar disorder.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;USC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For the first time, a research team led by the Mark and Mary Stevens Neuroimaging and Informatics Institute (Stevens INI) at the Keck School of Medicine of USC has mapped the genetic architecture of a crucial part of the human brain known as the corpus callosum—the thick band of nerve fibers that connects the brain’s left and right hemispheres. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings open new pathways for discoveries about mental illness, neurological disorders and other diseases related to defects in this part of the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The corpus callosum is critical for nearly everything the brain does, from coordinating the movement of our limbs in sync to integrating sights and sounds, to higher-order thinking and decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abnormalities in its shape and size have long been linked to disorders such as ADHD, bipolar disorder, and Parkinson’s disease. Until now, the genetic underpinnings of this vital structure remained largely unknown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the new study, published in&lt;em&gt; Nature Communications,&lt;/em&gt; the team analyzed brain scans and genetic data from over 50,000 people, ranging from childhood to late adulthood, with the help of a new tool the team created that leverages artificial intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; “We developed an AI tool that finds the corpus callosum in different types of brain MRI scans and automatically takes its measurements,” said Shruti P. Gadewar, co-first author of the study and research specialist at the Stevens INI. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using this tool, the researchers identified dozens of genetic regions that influence the size and thickness of the corpus callosum and its subregions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These findings provide a genetic blueprint for one of the brain’s most essential communication pathways,” said Ravi R. Bhatt, PhD, co-first author of the study and a post-doctoral scholar at the Stevens INI’s&lt;a href="https://igc.ini.usc.edu/"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;Imaging Genetics Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“By uncovering how specific genes shape the corpus callosum and its subregions, we can start to understand why differences in this structure are linked to various mental health and neurological conditions at a molecular level.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study revealed that different sets of genes govern the area versus the thickness of the corpus callosum—two features that change across the lifespan and play distinct roles in brain function. Several of the implicated genes are active during prenatal brain development, particularly in processes like cell growth, programmed cell death, and the wiring of nerve fibers across hemispheres.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This work demonstrates the power of using AI and large-scale databases to uncover the genetic factors driving brain development,” said&lt;a href="https://keck.usc.edu/faculty-search/neda-jahanshad/"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;Neda Jahanshad, PhD, associate professor of neurology and senior author.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“By linking genetics to brain structure, we gain critical insight into the biological pathways that may underlie psychiatric and neurological diseases.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notably, the study found genetic overlap between the corpus callosum and the cerebral cortex—the outer layer of the brain responsible for memory, attention, and language—as well as with conditions such as ADHD and bipolar disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These connections underscore that the same genetic factors shaping the brain’s communication bridge may also contribute to vulnerabilities for certain disorders,” Jahanshad added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arthur W. Toga, PhD, director of the Stevens INI, emphasized the broader implications of this research. “This study is a landmark in understanding how our brains are built. It not only sheds light on normal brain development but also helps us identify new avenues for diagnosing and potentially treating disorders that affect millions worldwide.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers have made their new AI-based tool publicly available to accelerate future discoveries. The software, developed at the Stevens INI, uses advanced machine learning to identify and measure the corpus callosum from MRI scans automatically. This approach allows scientists to analyze brain structure at an unprecedented scale and level of precision, reducing years of manual work to just hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Stevens INI has become a global leader in applying artificial intelligence to neuroscience, developing tools that are freely shared with the research community. By combining massive datasets with cutting-edge computational methods, the institute is transforming how scientists study brain health and disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Artificial intelligence is revolutionizing brain research, and Stevens INI is at the forefront of that revolution,” said Toga. “By pioneering AI tools and making them widely available, we’re empowering scientists around the world to unlock new discoveries about the brain far faster than ever before.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the study&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to Bhatt, Gadewar and Jahanshad, the study’s other authors include Ankush Shetty, Iyad Ba Gari, Elizabeth Haddad,Shayan Javid, Abhinaav Ramesh, Elnaz Nourollahimoghadam, Alyssa H. Zhu, Christiaan de Leeuw,&lt;sup&gt; &lt;/sup&gt;Paul M. Thompson,&lt;sup&gt; &lt;/sup&gt;and Sarah E. Medland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding: &lt;/strong&gt;This work was supported by the National Institutes of Health (Grant Nos. R01 MH134004 and R01 AG059874 [NJ], National Science Foundation Graduate Research Fellowship Program (Grant No. 2020290241 [RRB], R01 MH126213, R01NS105746, the Adolescent Brain Cognitive Development (ABCD) Study (https://abcdstudy.org), and UK Biobank (Resource Application No. 11559). SEM was supported by NHMRC grants APP1172917 and APP1158127. Research reported in this publication was supported by the Office of the Director, National Institutes of Health under Award Number S10OD032285.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Key Questions Answered:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq wp-block-yoast-faq-block"&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1762289110090"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: What did scientists map in this new study?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: Researchers created the first large-scale genetic map of the corpus callosum—the thick bundle of nerve fibers that connects the left and right hemispheres of the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1762289111633"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Why is the corpus callosum important?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: It’s essential for coordination, communication, and higher-order thinking, and abnormalities in its structure are linked to conditions such as ADHD, bipolar disorder, and Parkinson’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1762289111506"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: How was artificial intelligence used?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: An AI tool analyzed MRI scans from more than 50,000 people, identifying dozens of genetic regions that influence the size and thickness of the corpus callosum and how these traits relate to brain function and disease risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this AI, genetics, and mental health research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#7e121f0b0c1f50121b1c121f101d3e131b1a500b0d1d501b1a0b" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Laura LeBlanc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://med.usc.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;USC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Laura LeBlanc – USC&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1038/s41467-025-64791-3" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;The Genetic Architecture of the Human Corpus Callosum and its Subregions&lt;/a&gt;” by Ravi R. Bhatt et al. &lt;em&gt;Nature Communications&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Genetic Architecture of the Human Corpus Callosum and its Subregions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The corpus callosum (CC) is the largest set of white matter fibers connecting the two hemispheres of the brain. In humans, it is essential for coordinating sensorimotor responses and performing associative or executive functions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identifying which genetic variants underpin CC morphometry can provide molecular insights into the CC’s role in mediating cognitive processes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We developed and used an artificial intelligence based tool to extract the midsagittal CC’s total and regional area and thickness in two large public datasets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We performed a genome-wide association study (GWAS) meta-analysis of European participants (combined &lt;em&gt;N&lt;/em&gt; = 46,685) with generalization to the non-European participants (combined &lt;em&gt;N&lt;/em&gt; = 7040). Post-GWAS analyses implicated prenatal intracellular organization and cell growth patterns, and high heritability in regions of open chromatin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Results suggest programmed cell death mediated by the immune system drives the thinning of the posterior body and isthmus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genetic overlap, and causal genetic liability, between the CC, cerebral cortex features, and neuropsychiatric disorders such as attention-deficit/hyperactivity, bipolar disorders, and Parkinson’s disease were identified.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:49:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibkFVX3lxTE5Kakx4OEhvS1lwUHBUVXhFOEpwaXJJS25lTm5NYzk4S0lpa3dMZGIzNEhiTDFDSzNOOHk1RW1ZcXhBUmFGam9zcVBpWXVhTlplODNMdjN6VDVwc2NlSExkbTNIcXBTZl9RVXJVZ0tB</guid></item><item><title>新研究发现，这种类型的咖啡“显着增加”永久性失明的风险- WKRC</title><link>https://local12.com/news/nation-world/coffee-significantly-increases-risk-permanent-blindness-new-study-finds-effects-additives-factors-vision-loss-harmful-substances-instant-central-vision</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText_storyText__C3hWI StoryText_storyText__C3hWI"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;UNDATED (WKRC) - A new study suggests that instant coffee “significantly increases” a person’s risk of developing permanent blindness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research, published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12166192/#fsn370439-sec-0016" target="_blank"&gt;Food Science &amp;amp; Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; and reported by &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://people.com/eye-disease-risk-significantly-increases-with-this-go-to-beverage-11843359" target="_blank"&gt;PEOPLE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, found that instant coffee “significantly increases” the risk of age-related macular degeneration, or AMD — a common eye disease that can cause permanent vision loss in people over 50.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the Cleveland Clinic, AMD affects the center of the retina, which controls central vision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers said “different effects of various types of coffee on AMD may be related to manufacturing processes, additives and other factors,” &lt;em&gt;PEOPLE&lt;/em&gt; reported. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They also cited studies indicating that the "production of instant coffee may lead to the formation of potentially harmful substances.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WKRC</author><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:48:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAJBVV95cUxQd0NfNHRxMVFkZm1PQnRGcGozN19fVzA2eHNSSm4weGxDRy1vaFFob0lGamNSM29mYk9OU0puMTVEWEZHRS1maFBwLUx6REpaSTJSOGc1MER5dDM4bllTYm5jUV9BMmxMaWg0eVdtTTNfS0F2WS1yRXV4Z0dLQUl6UDM1T3hFQXY2dGNJbEYzRTMzWmVtekl6d1EwcC1Kdl84Q1UtTXdzeVkxUzJtbmhLWWYxaU9NS3ZwTWlMdkFmZnYzYVYyeVAyY2dFWUcyY2dIVjF6a3YxVWo1dGgzblRWLUpmRjZtdXhhY2VQY3Z0VkxHMXl3cUdYbW1LeVBGRWpZSlRDUnlfMndmTXJtR2xZVl9zTTNsN3Ru</guid></item><item><title>更新出生时患有“泡泡男孩病”的婴儿的长期随访似乎仍然可以治愈-好消息网络</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/update-long-term-follow-up-in-babies-born-with-bubble-boy-disease-still-seem-cured/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_224979" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-224979" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-224979" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/download-1024x683.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/download-1024x683.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/download-326x217.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/download-768x512.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/download-696x464.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/download-1068x712.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/download-630x420.jpg 630w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/download-530x353.jpg 530w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/download.jpg 1125w" sizes="(max-width: 696px) 100vw, 696px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-224979" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;6 of the children treated for SCID living their best lives – credit, UCLA, supplied by the parents&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Between 2012 and 2017, 62 babies and toddlers were treated with a genetic therapy for severe combined immunodeficiency, known colloquially as the “Bubble Boy disease.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2021, GNN &lt;a href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/ucla-gene-therapy-breakthrough-children-no-immune-system/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; on the results of the trial—that by 2019, 95%, or all but two of the young patients, showed complete immune system reconstruction. Now, the long-term follow-up results are in—still 95% effective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_224977" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-224977" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-224977" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Screenshot-2025-11-04-125140-1024x613.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Screenshot-2025-11-04-125140-1024x613.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Screenshot-2025-11-04-125140-326x195.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Screenshot-2025-11-04-125140-768x460.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Screenshot-2025-11-04-125140-696x417.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Screenshot-2025-11-04-125140-1068x640.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Screenshot-2025-11-04-125140-701x420.jpg 701w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Screenshot-2025-11-04-125140-530x317.jpg 530w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Screenshot-2025-11-04-125140.jpg 1252w" sizes="(max-width: 696px) 100vw, 696px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-224977" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Screenshot, GNN&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The durability of immune function, the consistency over time and the continued safety profile are all incredibly encouraging,” &lt;a href="https://newsroom.ucla.edu/releases/gene-therapy-delivers-lasting-immune-protection-children-rare-disorder" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; the study’s senior author, Donald Kohn, MD, a pediatric transplant physician at Univ. of California LA, where the trial was conducted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Severe combined immunodeficiency due to adenosine deaminase deficiency, or ADA-SCID, is caused by mutations in the ADA gene, which creates an enzyme essential for immune function. For children with the condition, day-to-day activities like going to school or playing with friends can lead to dangerous, life-threatening infections. If untreated, ADA-SCID can be fatal within the first two years of life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 1984, SCID become suddenly well-known in America because of “the boy in the bubble,” David Vetter, who received a special spacesuit from NASA to allow him to leave his total medical isolation. Despite this, Vetter passed away from an infection at age 12.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gene therapy method involves first collecting some of the child’s blood-forming stem cells in their bone marrow, which have the potential to create all types of blood and immune cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, using an approach developed by the research team at UCLA with help from the UK’s Great Ormond Street Hospital and University College London, a new copy of the ADA gene is delivered into the stem cells by a modified lentivirus, or “viral vector.” The corrected cells are then returned to the child’s body, where they are intended to produce a continual supply of healthy immune cells capable of fighting infection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Between all three clinical trials, 50 patients were treated, and the overall results were very encouraging,” said Kohn back in 2021. “All the patients are alive and well, and in more than 95% of them, the therapy appears to have corrected their underlying immune system problems.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This brand new study, also &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2502754" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;published in the New England Journal of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, represents the largest and longest follow-up of a gene therapy of this kind to date, with 474 total patient-years of follow-up data—including five patients who received the therapy a decade ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the 59 patients successfully treated, immune function has remained stable beyond the initial recovery period, with no treatment-limiting complications reported.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With support from the California Institute for Regenerative Medicine, the UCLA team is now working to complete the steps necessary to apply for FDA approval.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MORE INFANTILE DISEASES CURED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a title="CRISPR Used to Remove Extra Chromosomes in Lab Model of Down Syndrome and Restore Cell Function" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/crispr-used-to-remove-extra-chromosomes-in-lab-model-of-down-syndrome-and-restore-cell-function/" rel="bookmark"&gt;CRISPR Used to Remove Extra Chromosomes in Lab Model of Down Syndrome and Restore Cell Function&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Our goal is to have this therapy FDA-approved within two to three years,” Kohn said. “The clinical data strongly supports approval—now we need to demonstrate that we can manufacture the treatment under commercial pharmaceutical standards.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_224978" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-224978" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-224978" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Eliana2-1024x683.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Eliana2-1024x683.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Eliana2-326x217.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Eliana2-768x512.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Eliana2-696x464.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Eliana2-1068x712.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Eliana2-630x420.jpg 630w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Eliana2-530x353.jpg 530w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Eliana2.jpg 1125w" sizes="(max-width: 696px) 100vw, 696px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-224978" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Eliana Nachem received gene therapy at 10 months (left) and is 11 now (right), free from living in medical isolation – credit, supplied by Caroline and Jeff Nachem&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When GNN originally reported on the 2021 study, a slide of photos was released of 6 of the children treated, taken at various times between 2012 and 2017. Accompanying the new study are slides of the same children, not necessarily &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; grown up, but grown up, and living their best healthy lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11-year-old Eliana Nachem of Fredericksburg, Virginia, is starting sixth grade with dreams of becoming an artist. It’s a remarkably ordinary life that once seemed impossible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LIFE BEYOND TREATMENT: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a title="New Base Editing Gene Therapy Cures its First Patient: A Sickle-Cell Sufferer Now in the ‘Gym Every Day’" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/new-base-editing-gene-therapy-cures-its-first-patient-a-sickle-cell-sufferer-now-in-the-gym-every-day/" rel="bookmark"&gt;New Base Editing Gene Therapy Cures its First Patient: A Sickle-Cell Sufferer Now in the ‘Gym Every Day’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Eliana was diagnosed with ADA-SCID at 3 months old in 2014, she lived in complete medical isolation. No pets, no contact with the outside world, with HEPA air filters running constantly and all food and toys sterilized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We had to get rid of our dog and cat, she couldn’t go outside, and I had to stop breastfeeding,” her mother, Caroline, recalled. “Formula had to be consumed within an hour or thrown out. Everything that might harbor germs was dangerous to her.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In September 2014, at 10 months old, Eliana received her corrected cells at UCLA. Caroline and Jeff described watching the infusion as their daughter’s “rebirth”—her own genetically modified cells carrying the promise of a normal life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CHILDREN BEING CURED:  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a title="Infant With Incurable Disease is First to Successfully Receive Personalized Gene Therapy Treatment" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/infant-with-incurable-disease-is-first-to-successfully-receive-personalized-gene-therapy-treatment/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Infant With Incurable Disease is First to Successfully Receive Personalized Gene Therapy Treatment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A decade later, that promise has been fulfilled. Despite some early complications during her immune system’s recovery, Eliana has thrived, attending public school, playing basketball and living the unrestricted childhood her parents once could only dream of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Now the biggest thing I have to worry about is her entering middle school and bossing me around,” Caroline said with a laugh. “I am eternally grateful to every single scientist, doctor, lab worker, nurse, hospital security guard—all the people who had anything to do with this gene therapy coming into existence and saving her.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SHARE This Incredible Cure Ready For FDA Approval To Save Infants Around The Country…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:30:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxNXzhHLUpoSEhjT294X0dNQTc1VjNxTVR5VkwzQlFLTk96U1JGSWo2SEgzOFJMbUk5SnJvcmtiY2s4Z2VrbU1SdFFWM0V0bVdadTNtTUYtUW8zV3ZkUXFGTlpPckFXOGlvSmRxdThBb3MxZHhfYnNXUm9kbWs3akhSNk5adHhrWlZrWmxVMUpEZTlvNm9OcU90OGltS0hIdmxwQmJ2YUpRbkEyLURaUVo4U1pWVTNwdw</guid></item></channel></rss>