<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>科学家发现，狗可以提醒人类注意这种快速传播的疾病- Earth.com | Scientists discover that dogs can alert humans to this quickly-spreading disease - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinwFBVV95cUxONFBEWVdFMndNT3YyN0VVRWFFbTVkOGlsNDNVRHl3Nk1STnplcUtMRmI2VzVRcDctWDBqWTdENkk2Q2E0Q1cxcVRybDRpaDdZOE5EXy12cU9iajYtWWVIeVlvVWdBbXF6MGRzOEdIWlQ3bHB6S1NFQjJHSGxBT0hqSWxGLXU0eWdXVDlsbDh6b3l6Y2F3WVdrWWJUS3FsSVk?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dogs aren’t just companions who brighten our daily routines. They may also be key players in monitoring how Valley fever moves through certain regions in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This disease, also called coccidioidomycosis, involves inhaling fungal spores found in dry soil conditions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://vetmed.ucdavis.edu/faculty/jane-sykes" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Jane Sykes&lt;/a&gt;, lead author of a recent &lt;a href="https://www.vetmed.ucdavis.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;UC Davis&lt;/a&gt; study, worked with her team to see how information from dog infections could apply to humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-understanding-valley-fever"&gt;Understanding Valley fever&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When disturbed by wind, construction, or agricultural activity, the spores of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/immunology-and-microbiology/coccidioides-immitis" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Coccidioides immitis&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/agricultural-and-biological-sciences/coccidioides-posadasii" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Coccidioides posadasii&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; can ride on dust particles and travel into the lungs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some pets like to dig into dirt, creating an ideal chance to breathe in fungal particles. These Valley fever spores thrive in the Western parts of the country, often in places with specific soil moisture levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though many people who are exposed may not experience symptoms, those who do often report flu-like illness, including fatigue, cough, fever, chest pain, and muscle aches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some cases, especially in individuals with weakened immune systems, Valley fever can become severe, spreading from the lungs to other parts of the body such as the skin, bones, joints, or even the brain, where it may cause &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/harmful-microbes-persist-on-hospital-surfaces-after-disinfection/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;meningitis&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diagnosis is typically confirmed through blood tests or imaging, and while mild cases often resolve without treatment, antifungal medications like fluconazole are prescribed for moderate to severe infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-unusual-canine-clues"&gt;Unusual canine clues&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers discovered patterns by checking large collections of &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/lost-in-translation-how-we-misread-our-dogs-emotions/"&gt;dog&lt;/a&gt; blood tests. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They found that most positive results are linked to certain states with known contamination zones, but they also noticed smaller clusters appearing in locations not typically flagged for this infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Dogs are sentinels for human infections,” said Jane Sykes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her team collected blood test data in different areas to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/valley-fever/about/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;identify rising trends&lt;/a&gt; and potential health concerns for people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-puts-dogs-at-risk"&gt;What puts dogs at risk&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some vets &lt;a href="https://vfce.arizona.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;note&lt;/a&gt; that certain breeds may be more prone to lung ailments, but any fungus exposure can be an issue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This might involve dusty backyards, fields, or construction sites, where spores in the soil can become airborne.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In regions with droughts or strong winds, soil dryness allows fungal particles to swirl into the air. Intense rainfall can also boost &lt;a href="https://today.ucsd.edu/story/dangerous-airborne-fungus-boosted-by-california-droughts" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;fungal growth&lt;/a&gt;, which further contributes to sporadic spikes in infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers see these canine cases as indicators for possible spread in the broader population. Common symptoms in people include fatigue, cough, and sometimes sore joints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health agencies note that valley fever can become serious for those with weakened immune systems. Because dogs are tested more readily in certain regions, their results may warn us before human cases spike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-mapping-valley-fever-in-new-zones"&gt;Mapping valley fever in new zones&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists have spotted positive &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/uncovering-the-truth-the-reality-behind-canine-dna-testing/"&gt;canine&lt;/a&gt; cases outside historically recognized areas. Jane Sykes explained that pockets of infection can appear in nearby states that might be overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We should be closely watching those states because there could be under-recognition,” she said. This under-recognition means some doctors in these regions may not be aware of the disease and could miss early signs in humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Decades of shifting &lt;a href="https://www.noaa.gov/education/resource-collections/climate/climate-change-impacts" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;climate patterns&lt;/a&gt; have altered soil conditions. Over 130 places in the United States have recorded heavier bursts of rain in recent years, raising concerns about potential fungal growth when storms finally soak the land.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As new weather extremes develop, the fungus might have more opportunities to spread. Researchers keep emphasizing how environmental changes can shift the boundaries of diseases, leading to surprises in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/covid-virus-can-remain-in-sperm-months-after-infection/"&gt;infection&lt;/a&gt; data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-protecting-yourself-and-your-pet"&gt;Protecting yourself and your pet&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many dog owners wonder if this infection is preventable. Avoiding areas with visible dust clouds is one measure, though it can be tough when your pet loves running outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30690600/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;vets&lt;/a&gt; provide guidance on ways to limit exposure if your area is known for this fungus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though these spores are hard to avoid entirely, regular checkups and early tests may help pets and owners stay aware of new health risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Veterinarians who live in spots with many valley fever cases watch for respiratory problems in dogs. A sudden cough or limp can signal hidden issues, prompting tests that reveal infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If caught early, there are antifungal treatments that can relieve symptoms. The goal is to manage lung damage and reduce further spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-dogs-valley-fever-and-the-future"&gt;Dogs, valley fever, and the future&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers who track these &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/covid-infection-equips-the-body-to-fight-off-the-flu/"&gt;infections&lt;/a&gt; see a bigger picture beyond local hotspots. They hope more states will gather accurate data so public health teams can warn residents who may be at risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Better knowledge about where the spores hide allows for timely alerts. Clear communication between veterinarians and medical professionals could help limit the toll on both animals and people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trends linked to heavy rain, population growth, and soil changes highlight the complexity of valley fever. Officials suggest that improved teaching for doctors could keep illness from going unnoticed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dogs may help identify emerging dangers because their health data can fill the gaps where human data are patchy. Scientists remain hopeful that continued studies will keep the public informed about this evolving fungal risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/jid/article/231/5/e986/8108831?login=false" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Journal of Infectious Diseases&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 18:13:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxONFBEWVdFMndNT3YyN0VVRWFFbTVkOGlsNDNVRHl3Nk1STnplcUtMRmI2VzVRcDctWDBqWTdENkk2Q2E0Q1cxcVRybDRpaDdZOE5EXy12cU9iajYtWWVIeVlvVWdBbXF6MGRzOEdIWlQ3bHB6S1NFQjJHSGxBT0hqSWxGLXU0eWdXVDlsbDh6b3l6Y2F3WVdrWWJUS3FsSVk</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，有问题的色情使用随着时间的推移保持稳定，并与精神痛苦密切相关- PsyPost | Problematic porn use remains stable over time and is strongly linked to mental distress, study finds - PsyPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPSnJheFl5dTdHTkRHZ1dGb0M2dTludGJFWjh2V0g4MjZPajBaWDNOd1V6d01yN1dqRmFNbnFXbkZZWHg1SnBfQVB5TVJJWHhBZE1EVGlmUmdPb0FLVDlTZ2hsR2xfV3gxUjlqUFhZMG5ULWJtekdNOWNVTUZFMWx6Qm1fQ3UwMFl6cjJwMWRTTjNjbkVqeldHRG45R1AzclNvd1RuQlpKNklrQ2t4d3l3NFRrS0l4cHhWbGdfOHVkWmJIUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new longitudinal study has found that problematic pornography use tends to remain stable over time and is strongly associated with psychological distress such as anxiety and depression. The findings, published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Addictive Behaviors&lt;/em&gt;, suggest that while some people may experience short-term relief from distress through pornography use, long-term patterns of dysregulation are tied to more persistent psychological difficulties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pornography is widely used in the United States and globally, but for some individuals, it can become problematic. People who experience problematic pornography use often report difficulty controlling their use and suffer negative consequences in their personal, professional, or emotional lives. The condition has recently gained clinical recognition under the diagnostic label of Compulsive Sexual Behavior Disorder in the World Health Organization’s latest classification system. Despite this recognition, little research has explored how problematic pornography use develops and changes over time, especially in relation to mental health symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robin Engelhardt of Bundeswehr University, the lead author, was motivated by “the necessity to scientifically catch up in this field. Previous studies depicted comparatively high prevalence rates of problematic pornography use and associations with psychological distress.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers conducted a one-year, three-wave longitudinal study of over 4,300 U.S. adults. They wanted to examine how problematic pornography use and psychological distress influence each other over time and whether these patterns are stable or fluctuate. Their work builds on previous research that identified a link between pornography dysregulation and psychological distress but could not determine whether one causes the other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants were recruited through a national polling company and included a combination of a general population sample and an oversample of sports bettors to increase statistical power. The final sample included 4,363 individuals between the ages of 18 and 96, with an average age of 50 and a gender distribution of roughly equal numbers of men and women. The study took place over three timepoints: March-April 2022, September-October 2022, and March-April 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To assess problematic pornography use, the researchers used the Brief Pornography Screen, a five-item questionnaire designed to measure symptoms of dysregulation, such as difficulty resisting urges or using pornography in ways that cause distress. A score of 4 or higher on this measure was considered a potential indicator of problematic use. Psychological distress was measured through widely used tools for assessing anxiety and depression: the Generalized Anxiety Disorder-2 and the Patient Health Questionnaire-9. The researchers combined responses from both scales into a single composite reflecting overall distress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study found that problematic pornography use was highly consistent across time. Correlations between timepoints were strong, and most participants remained in the same clinical category—either below or above the threshold for potential problematic use—throughout the year. About 67% of participants consistently scored below the clinical threshold, while 14% consistently scored above it. Only a small proportion moved between categories, indicating either recovery or the development of problematic use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Psychological distress was also stable across timepoints, and the researchers found a strong positive association between pornography dysregulation and distress at the level of individuals. That is, people who tended to score higher on pornography problems also tended to report more distress, and vice versa. This suggests a stable, trait-like relationship between the two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, when the researchers examined how changes in one variable might predict changes in the other over time, the results were more nuanced. They found small, negative within-person effects: when an individual experienced an increase in pornography dysregulation at one time point, they were slightly less likely to report increased psychological distress six months later. The reverse was also true. This pattern was unexpected, as many theories in psychology predict that distress and problematic behaviors reinforce one another over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers offered a few potential explanations for this finding. One possibility is that pornography use may provide temporary relief from emotional distress, functioning as a short-term coping strategy. People experiencing anxiety or depression may turn to pornography for distraction or mood regulation, which could lead to a slight reduction in distress in the short run. However, over time, this pattern may backfire, leading to a worsening of dysregulation and deepening of psychological problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another interpretation centers on the effects of depression itself. Depression can dampen a person’s general motivation and reduce interest in activities, including sexual ones. This might result in lower pornography use during depressive episodes, even among people with a history of dysregulation. In this way, depression could inhibit some of the behavioral patterns associated with problematic pornography use, at least temporarily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these small short-term effects, the dominant pattern was one of a strong and consistent link between problematic use and psychological distress across individuals. This means that, in general, people who have more difficulty regulating their pornography use are also more likely to struggle with anxiety and depression. These findings echo previous research and align with the idea that both problematic pornography use and psychological distress can reinforce each other in the long term, even if their moment-to-moment dynamics are more complex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings provide evidence of “a trait-like connection between problematic pornography use and psychological distress,” Engelhardt told PsyPost. “They appear to be the same construct — problematic pornography use appears a part of psychological distress and psychological distress a part of problematic pornography use. However, cross-sectional studies may not depict this underlying strong time-consistent association due to small time-dependent inhibition effects that let the association appear smaller.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study has several important strengths, including its large sample size, use of validated measurement tools, and robust statistical modeling techniques that distinguish between stable traits and temporary fluctuations. However, the authors caution that the findings are based on self-report data, which can be influenced by social desirability or memory biases. Additionally, the study focused on dysregulation rather than the frequency of pornography use, which could be an important factor in understanding how and why pornography affects mental health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research, the authors suggest, should investigate these dynamics in clinical populations and over longer periods. They also recommend using more fine-grained, daily tracking methods to examine short-term interactions between distress and pornography use in real-world settings. Experimental studies could also help clarify whether reducing pornography use leads to improved mental health outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “Problematic pornography use and psychological distress: A longitudinal study in a large US sample,” Robin Engelhardt, Rahel Geppert, Joshua B. Grubbs, Timo von Oertzen, Dominik Trommer, Jürgen Maes, and Shane W. Kraus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 18:03:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPSnJheFl5dTdHTkRHZ1dGb0M2dTludGJFWjh2V0g4MjZPajBaWDNOd1V6d01yN1dqRmFNbnFXbkZZWHg1SnBfQVB5TVJJWHhBZE1EVGlmUmdPb0FLVDlTZ2hsR2xfV3gxUjlqUFhZMG5ULWJtekdNOWNVTUZFMWx6Qm1fQ3UwMFl6cjJwMWRTTjNjbkVqeldHRG45R1AzclNvd1RuQlpKNklrQ2t4d3l3NFRrS0l4cHhWbGdfOHVkWmJIUQ</guid></item><item><title>我曾经害怕服用肌酸-然后我发现了这些软糖-每日野兽 | I Used to Dread Taking Creatine—Then I Found These Gummies - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMic0FVX3lxTE5SUkViREh5R2ZpcDR2dU56V1RjQTVDVUxHLXlOTm9lNklVQmU3Q1NDNHNQRjZWMl9oUzhlWXN4UEtnMmNKSGFXWFBVQVNTSTVZSzJ3U0lpTXVyR2lKTmFIa3hkR2JfUEdneGJ5LXprdmQtRTA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/category/scouted/"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Scouted&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt; selects products independently. If you purchase something from our posts, we may earn a small commission.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Creatine is finally garnering the recognition it deserves. After years of being regarded as a bulking supplement used exclusively by gym bros and bodybuilders (my mom, one of the latter, has been taking it daily for years), those focused on muscle mass are finally incorporating the naturally occurring substance into their everyday supplement regimen. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;â€œWhile itâ€™s true that historically, creatineâ€™s primary use was as an athletic or bodybuilding supplement, research is now showing that it can profoundly impact the brain and neurological health,â€� says &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/myersdetox/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.instagram.com/myersdetox/?hl=en"&gt;Dr. Wendy Myers, MD&lt;/a&gt;. â€œStudies show that creatine improves energy metabolism in the brain, which can have several positive downstream effects, including &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38297476/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38297476/"&gt;protecting against neurodegeneration&lt;/a&gt;, improving focus, enhancing memory, and supporting overall mental stamina.â€� &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Muscle is having a momentâ€”thanks to its ties to longevity and metabolismâ€”but creatineâ€™s rep hasnâ€™t fully caught up. While its muscle-building benefits still lead the charge, skepticism lingers, especially among women who equate it with bulking. But, according to experts, creatine may even be more important for women than for men. â€œCreatine has a long-standing reputation as a supplement for bodybuilders, but &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33800439/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33800439/"&gt;new research &lt;/a&gt;shows it could be one of the most important tools for women navigating perimenopause, menopause, and postpartum recovery,â€� Dr. Meyers says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="conversion-card conversion-card-extended"&gt;&lt;p class="conversion-card__description"&gt;In addition to five grams of creatine monohydrate, Arraeâ€™s Tone Gummies also contain the brandâ€™s proprietary Slimbiotics blend and ginger extract, which helps support the gut while combatting bloat, aiding digestion, and further supporting your body composition goals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Sadly, most creatine supplements on the market come in the form of chalky, bitter powders you have to chug to get down, which is kind of a dealbreakerâ€”especially if youâ€™re already on the fence about incorporating it into your ever-expanding supplement lineup (I get it). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Before I discovered &lt;a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=999&amp;amp;u=1701660&amp;amp;m=120420&amp;amp;urllink=www.arrae.com%2Fpages%2Ftry-tone-gummies" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=999&amp;amp;u=1701660&amp;amp;m=120420&amp;amp;urllink=www.arrae.com%2Fpages%2Ftry-tone-gummies"&gt;Arraeâ€™s Tone Gummies&lt;/a&gt;, I was adding my creatine powder to water and taking it down like a shot. Iâ€™ve been a fan of Arrae for years (especially of its weight-management, GLP-1-like &lt;a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=999&amp;amp;u=1701660&amp;amp;m=120420&amp;amp;urllink=www.arrae.com%2Fpages%2Fmb-1" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=999&amp;amp;u=1701660&amp;amp;m=120420&amp;amp;urllink=www.arrae.com%2Fpages%2Fmb-1"&gt;MB-1 metabolic supplement&lt;/a&gt;), so itâ€™s not a shock that I have the Tone Gummies on an automatically recurring subscription plan now. Each serving contains five milligrams of creatine monohydrate (based on my research, the gold standard creatine type and dose) and has a berry-like flavor. It almost tastes like a berry-flavored powdered sugar gummy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;&lt;a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=999&amp;amp;u=1701660&amp;amp;m=120420&amp;amp;urllink=www.arrae.com%2Fpages%2Ftry-tone-gummies" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=999&amp;amp;u=1701660&amp;amp;m=120420&amp;amp;urllink=www.arrae.com%2Fpages%2Ftry-tone-gummies"&gt;Arraeâ€™s Tone Gummies&lt;/a&gt; are formulated specifically for women to promote lean muscle mass, enhance post-workout recovery, and aid digestion. Along with five milligrams of creatine monohydrate, these gummies also contain gut-nourishing ginger and a postbiotic to combat bloating, foster regularity, and prevent any unwanted â€œbulking.â€�&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt; I used to dread my daily creatine dose, and now I actually look forward to it. Plus, as someone who travels at least once a month, the fact that Iâ€™m not transporting suspicious white powder in a random vessel or plastic bag through the TSA is a major selling point for these gummies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;If youâ€™re looking for a clean protein supplement that doesnâ€™t require consuming excess sugar, meat, and calories, Arraeâ€™s new &lt;a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=999&amp;amp;u=1701660&amp;amp;m=120420&amp;amp;urllink=www.arrae.com%2Fpages%2Fclear-protein" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=999&amp;amp;u=1701660&amp;amp;m=120420&amp;amp;urllink=www.arrae.com%2Fpages%2Fclear-protein"&gt;Clear Protein+&lt;/a&gt; is worth adding to cart as well. Each packet is formulated with 15 grams of grass-fed whey and collagen protein, as well as electrolytes, and for just 70 calories per serving. Think your standard electrolyte packet, but without the excess sugar, chemicals, and saccharine taste. Add these two muscle-supporting supplements to my ride-or-die &lt;a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=999&amp;amp;u=1701660&amp;amp;m=120420&amp;amp;urllink=www.arrae.com%2Fpages%2Fmb-1" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=999&amp;amp;u=1701660&amp;amp;m=120420&amp;amp;urllink=www.arrae.com%2Fpages%2Fmb-1"&gt;â€œfaux-zempicâ€� MB1&lt;/a&gt; and youâ€™ve got the ultimate body-composition-boosting trio. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="b-article-body__h2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;MORE FROM SCOUTED:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Daily Beast</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE5SUkViREh5R2ZpcDR2dU56V1RjQTVDVUxHLXlOTm9lNklVQmU3Q1NDNHNQRjZWMl9oUzhlWXN4UEtnMmNKSGFXWFBVQVNTSTVZSzJ3U0lpTXVyR2lKTmFIa3hkR2JfUEdneGJ5LXprdmQtRTA</guid></item><item><title>如果您想在60天内看起来和感觉更年轻，请告别这7个习惯- VegOut | If you want to look and feel younger in 60 days, say goodbye to these 7 habits - VegOut</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitAFBVV95cUxPZER2SFpzY0VRRDVqNXd1d2hBOFl0TVlRSmFmQ2o1NUpINXZzMGlrMkJoT2tUaVFpdlRpN0lsN1ktWGl5RmFOc2Vwd3UxdlY3eTY5Z2tTYWQ3M09PRXFrN0wtM3dVRFhzbXBzN1dTZi16T3JUb052LVFxTDZFY2JwNjItUVA3djZtQm80V1VVOUVScVNYb2NoeE55ci1WUUhyOThLNzdXM1FXdFpxMjIxUV80LUU?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p data-start="429" data-end="1135"&gt;Sixty days ago, I hit what I call a “high-definition moment.” I’d just climbed three flights of office stairs, latte in hand, and caught my reflection: puffy eyes, sallow skin, shoulders slumped like a crooked coat hanger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="429" data-end="1135"&gt;My spreadsheet brain kicked in—if the numbers don’t add up, change the inputs. That afternoon I drafted a personal experiment: for two months I would prune the daily habits scientists link to accelerated aging and replace them with low-friction alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="429" data-end="1135"&gt;The payoff was remarkable: deeper sleep, steadier mood, a brighter complexion, and enough energy to skip the 3 p.m. coffee. Here’s the seven-item checklist that made the difference—and how each swap works under the hood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="1142" data-end="1167"&gt;1. Skimping on sleep&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1169" data-end="1601"&gt;We treat sleep like an optional software update, clicking “remind me tomorrow” until the system crashes. Trouble is, the hard drive (your DNA) keeps score.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1169" data-end="1601"&gt;A 2024 &lt;em data-start="1332" data-end="1340"&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt; study showed that chronic insomnia speeds up the &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-024-84957-1?.com"&gt;GrimAge epigenetic clock&lt;/a&gt;, a blood-based marker that predicts mortality risk; put simply, six-hour nights can make your cells behave years older than the calendar says. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1603" data-end="2176"&gt;To nudge my bedtime earlier, I scheduled “lights-out meetings” in my calendar at 10 p.m.—no agenda, just a recurring commitment. The ritual felt silly for a week, but the visual block stiff-armed late-night emails and streaming rabbit holes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1603" data-end="2176"&gt;Within three weeks my resting heart rate dropped, and the gray half-moons under my eyes looked like they’d been erased with concealer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1603" data-end="2176"&gt;For anyone skeptical, do the math: banking 56–60 hours of shut-eye per week equals eight full nights of cellular repair every 30 days. That’s compound interest you can literally see in the mirror.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="2183" data-end="2218"&gt;2. Living the chair-bound life&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2220" data-end="2629"&gt;Most of us sit longer than our phones charge. A systematic review of 48 studies found that regular exercise preserves &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8879766/?.com"&gt;telomere length&lt;/a&gt;—the protective caps on DNA that fray with age—while inactivity lets them shrink faster. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2220" data-end="2629"&gt;Telomeres are like the plastic tips on shoelaces; once they wear down, the lace unravels. Daily movement, even short bouts, slows that fraying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2631" data-end="3170"&gt;In practice, I turned every conference call into a roaming meeting. Headset on, I paced a looping circuit from desk to kitchen, adding roughly 4,000 steps without reshuffling my schedule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2631" data-end="3170"&gt;Bonus: walking activated my “idea engine”—the best line items in my quarterly budget presentation were drafted mid-stride.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2631" data-end="3170"&gt;If treadmills bore you, pair routines: brew morning coffee while doing calf raises, stream your favorite show only if you stretch through the first act, or meet a friend for a brisk “walk-and-talk” instead of sitting over fries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="3177" data-end="3212"&gt;3. Sipping sugar by the bottle&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3214" data-end="3684"&gt;Yes, that “innocent” craft cola counts. Harvard researchers tracking 15,000 adults with type 2 diabetes found that each additional sugar-sweetened beverage raised the &lt;a href="https://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2023/04/sugary-drinks-raise-risk-of-premature-death-in-people-with-type-2-diabetes/?.com"&gt;risk of cardiovascular death by 8 percent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3214" data-end="3684"&gt;Internally, fructose also binds to skin collagen, forming advanced glycation end-products (appropriately nicknamed “AGEs”) that stiffen tissue and deepen wrinkles. Think of it as shrink-wrapping your face in plastic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3686" data-end="4212"&gt;During the 60-day trial, I swapped my 3 p.m. soda for sparkling water spiked with frozen raspberries. The first week felt like quitting a sitcom mid-season—flat, anticlimactic—but by week two my palate recalibrated and afternoon brain fog vanished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3686" data-end="4212"&gt;Track your own liquid intake for seven days; you might be shocked to find 200–400 stealth calories sliding through a straw. Replace half with flavored seltzer or unsweetened tea and watch your energy curve flatten in a good way—no more syrupy spikes followed by sleepy troughs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="4219" data-end="4262"&gt;4. Chasing that “always-on” adrenaline&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4264" data-end="4522"&gt;When inbox pings trigger a cortisol surge, your body thinks it’s sprinting from a lion even while seated. Chronic stress shortens telomeres, spikes systemic inflammation, and sabotages collagen repair—effectively paying triple interest on a lifestyle loan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4524" data-end="5142"&gt;My antidote borrowed from the trading floor: the 5-5-5 pause. Before replying to any tense email, I took five slow breaths, held for five seconds, and exhaled for five. The micro-ritual lasted under a minute but recalibrated my nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4524" data-end="5142"&gt;By week four the smartwatch data told its own story: fewer jaw-clench headaches, steadier heart-rate variability, and—surprise—more thoughtful email replies that required fewer follow-ups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4524" data-end="5142"&gt;If breathing apps feel woo-woo, rebrand them in financial terms: each deep inhale is a deposit in your cellular savings account; the momentary pause banks years of health dividends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="5149" data-end="5183"&gt;5. Soaking up unprotected sun&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5185" data-end="5532"&gt;A little daylight sets your circadian clock, but ultraviolet rays punch holes in collagen faster than you can say “serum.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5185" data-end="5532"&gt;Dermatology research estimates up to &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3790843/?.com"&gt;80 percent of visible facial aging&lt;/a&gt; stems from cumulative UV exposure. Translation: sunscreen is still the cheapest anti-aging product on Earth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5534" data-end="6108"&gt;To ingrain the habit, I parked the sunscreen pump beside my toothbrush. Brushing equals SPF—no willpower required. Gel formulas with a barely-there finish replaced the heavy, beach-day lotions I loathed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5534" data-end="6108"&gt;Two months later, my freckles stopped multiplying and friends asked if I’d “done something” to my skin. The answer was less glamorous than a laser treatment: I’d simply put a cap on daily sun damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5534" data-end="6108"&gt;For outdoor enthusiasts the rule of thumb is SPF 30 every two hours, wide-brim hat, and sunglasses that block UVA and UVB. Think of those shades as collagen’s bodyguards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="6115" data-end="6147"&gt;6. Feeding the inner critic&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6149" data-end="6522"&gt;Negative self-talk elevates cortisol and dampens dopamine, the double punch that drains motivation and accelerates biological wear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6149" data-end="6522"&gt;Self-compassion researcher Kristin Neff points out that replacing harsh judgment with supportive inner dialogue flips the nervous system from threat to care and&lt;a href="https://self-compassion.org/wp-content/uploads/publications/SC-Germer-Chapter.pdf?.com"&gt; generates a cascade of calming oxytocin&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6524" data-end="7140"&gt;During the experiment I noticed how often my mental narrator sneered, “You’re behind,” or “You look exhausted.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6524" data-end="7140"&gt;Instead of shutting it down, I responded aloud, “We’re learning.” Sounds corny, but the verbal reframing turned sneers into neutral status reports—“Current position: improving; next step: tweak the process.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6524" data-end="7140"&gt;Over 60 days my posture subtly straightened, and I found myself volunteering for camera-on calls rather than hiding behind profile photos. Replace your critic with a coach: state the observation, then propose one constructive action. You’ll feel the emotional temperature drop almost immediately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="7147" data-end="7184"&gt;7. Doom-scrolling into isolation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7186" data-end="7492"&gt;Scrolling a highlight reel while sitting alone convinces your brain everyone else is sprinting ahead, eroding self-worth and inviting &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/sites/default/files/surgeon-general-social-connection-advisory.pdf?.com"&gt;low-grade loneliness&lt;/a&gt;—a health risk comparable to smoking 15 cigarettes a day, according to the U.S. Surgeon General’s 2023 advisory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7494" data-end="8166"&gt;My workaround was embarrassingly simple: after 8 p.m. my phone flips to grayscale. The washed-out palette turns vibrant feeds into dull spreadsheets—the temptation drops by half. The reclaimed minutes went toward ten-minute calls with friends, which spiked oxytocin and finished the day on an upward social note.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7494" data-end="8166"&gt;You don’t need to delete social media; you need to corral it. Cap your social apps at 45 minutes daily, and pair each scroll session with a commitment to one real-time interaction—coffee chat, voice message, quick walk with your neighbor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7494" data-end="8166"&gt;The goal isn’t digital detox; it’s restoring balance so online life amplifies, rather than replaces, genuine connection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="8173" data-end="8240"&gt;Younger is a daily ledger, not a distant lottery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8242" data-end="8711"&gt;Feeling youthful isn’t cosmetic; it’s compound interest on tiny choices. Over 60 days, trimming these seven habits recalibrated my energy, skin tone, and mood more reliably than any pricey potion or high-tech gadget.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8242" data-end="8711"&gt;Pick one habit and run a two-week A/B test—compare your sleep score, afternoon alertness, or mirror check-in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8242" data-end="8711"&gt;Aging may be inevitable, but accelerated aging is often optional, and the levers sit in your calendar, pantry, inbox, and thought loops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8713" data-end="8856"&gt;Your own 60-day clock starts whenever you decide to hit “optimize.” Here’s to budgeting for a younger tomorrow—one smarter line item at a time.&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 16:33:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxPZER2SFpzY0VRRDVqNXd1d2hBOFl0TVlRSmFmQ2o1NUpINXZzMGlrMkJoT2tUaVFpdlRpN0lsN1ktWGl5RmFOc2Vwd3UxdlY3eTY5Z2tTYWQ3M09PRXFrN0wtM3dVRFhzbXBzN1dTZi16T3JUb052LVFxTDZFY2JwNjItUVA3djZtQm80V1VVOUVScVNYb2NoeE55ci1WUUhyOThLNzdXM1FXdFpxMjIxUV80LUU</guid></item><item><title>科学家揭示了如何在不哭的情况下切洋葱，他们的方法非常简单。- Farmingdale Observer | Scientists reveal how to cut onions without crying, and their method is incredibly simple. - Farmingdale Observer</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizgFBVV95cUxQZWJoblpqaU8wVjFUcWVSZUJCUWIxcmIxdE15Ml82T2FudVpTVDVvSTExRVVUbjdkLXJqNklGTUhPSTNlb3BEcUlvSVZ0OTdqb2o1aWZxRGtGbzB1akhhcFJ2YWdpZWUtWGFCNnFrZjBuOHdmdE5UREVnOThyTXRMWWp6VG83Tk5WNGduQzkzbHg2RlNVRjloT252cDhxTzdzbVI5RGx2R1JiNU45RUN0bGdhdEx0dFN3SXBkRlhWWmh0ZmJRLWYxeFc2WjBJZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content" itemprop="text"&gt;
			
&lt;p&gt;Cutting onions ranks among the most dreaded kitchen tasks for many &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/tag/home/" class="st_tag internal_tag " rel="tag" title="Posts tagged with home"&gt;home&lt;/a&gt; cooks. The inevitable tears and burning sensation can turn a simple &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/tag/cooking/" class="st_tag internal_tag " rel="tag" title="Posts tagged with cooking"&gt;cooking&lt;/a&gt; preparation into an uncomfortable experience. However, recent scientific research has uncovered a surprisingly straightforward method to chop onions without the waterworks. This technique could revolutionize how we approach this essential culinary ingredient that features in countless dishes worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Scientific insights into why onions make us cry&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Understanding why onions trigger tears helps explain the scientific solution. When you cut into an onion, you damage its cells, releasing enzymes that convert sulfur compounds into syn-propanethial-S-oxide. This volatile chemical rises through the air and irritates the sensitive membranes in your eyes, prompting them to produce tears as a protective response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="farmi-in-text-1" id="farmi-1297554083"&gt;

&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-7994036760405448" data-ad-slot="3843226833" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This chemical reaction occurs naturally as a defense mechanism for the onion plant. Research conducted at Cornell University has delved deeper into this process, examining exactly how these irritating compounds become airborne during cutting. Their findings reveal that the method of cutting significantly impacts how much of this tear-inducing substance reaches your eyes.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Traditional remedies like chilling onions or cutting them underwater offer limited effectiveness against this chemical reaction. However, the Cornell research team discovered that the primary factors affecting tear production relate to knife technique rather than external interventions. This revelation provides a practical solution that doesn’t require special equipment or preparation steps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="farmi-display-adsense-3" id="farmi-2526234600"&gt;

&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-7994036760405448" data-ad-slot="9294255259" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="farmi-display-adsense" id="farmi-1037479000"&gt;

&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-7994036760405448" data-ad-slot="4875636047" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Just as &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/2025/02/14/french-pastry-chefs-know-it-this-type-of-butter-makes-the-best-pie-crusts/"&gt;French pastry chefs know which butter creates superior pie crusts&lt;/a&gt;, professional chefs have long understood that proper knife skills make a difference when cutting onions – now &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/tag/science/" class="st_tag internal_tag " rel="tag" title="Posts tagged with science"&gt;science&lt;/a&gt; confirms why.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The simple technique for tear-free onion cutting&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The groundbreaking research from Cornell University reveals that two key factors determine how much eye-irritating spray gets released when cutting onions: knife sharpness and cutting speed. Contrary to what many might assume, the solution doesn’t involve fancy gadgets or unusual preparation methods.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Scientists created a specialized guillotine apparatus that allowed them to test different blade types and cutting speeds while filming the resulting spray patterns. Their experiments conclusively demonstrated that using a sharp knife and cutting slowly dramatically reduces the amount of irritating compounds released into the air.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;When using dull knives, the researchers observed that the blade pushed down on the onion layers, causing them to bend inward before springing back and forcefully ejecting juice into the air. Sharp knives, by contrast, cleanly slice through the onion cells without compressing them, minimizing juice spray.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The cutting speed proved equally important. Fast chopping motions, while seemingly efficient, actually generated more airborne mist. The researchers found that slowing down your cutting motion allows for more precise slicing and significantly less tear-inducing spray. This patient approach yields better results than rushing through the task.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This technique also carries additional benefits beyond preventing tears. The same approach that prevents &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/2025/02/16/italians-add-this-ingredient-to-their-cakes-making-them-incredibly-moist-and-soft/"&gt;moisture loss when adding secret ingredients to cakes&lt;/a&gt; helps preserve the onion’s flavor compounds when cut properly.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Practical applications beyond kitchen comfort&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The implications of this research extend beyond simply making onion preparation more comfortable. The scientists noted that minimizing airborne food particles has broader hygiene benefits in the kitchen. Reducing the spray from cutting vegetables with tough outer layers helps limit the spread of potential pathogens during food preparation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This finding proves particularly relevant for professional kitchens where large quantities of onions are processed daily. The cumulative effect of reducing airborne particles creates a healthier environment for food preparation. Commercial kitchens can benefit from implementing these techniques as standard practice.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For home cooks, adopting this method eliminates the need for quirky workarounds that many have tried over the years. No more swimming goggles, bread in the mouth, or freezing onions before cutting. The solution lies simply in using proper equipment and technique – a sharp knife and a patient cutting motion.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Maintaining sharp kitchen knives represents a wise investment for any &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/tag/cook/" class="st_tag internal_tag " rel="tag" title="Posts tagged with cook"&gt;cook&lt;/a&gt;. While many focus on &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/2025/02/21/this-is-the-household-appliance-that-consumes-the-most-electricity-after-heating/"&gt;reducing energy consumption of major kitchen appliances&lt;/a&gt;, proper knife maintenance requires minimal resources while delivering significant benefits.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This discovery reminds us that sometimes the most effective solutions come from understanding the science behind everyday problems. Just as &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/2025/03/14/more-and-more-gardeners-are-burying-bananas-in-their-gardens-and-once-you-know-why-it-makes-perfect-sense/"&gt;gardeners apply scientific principles when using natural fertilizers&lt;/a&gt;, home cooks can apply these findings to improve their culinary experience through better understanding of the chemistry happening in their kitchens&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="farmi-display-adsense-end" id="farmi-1619915483"&gt;

&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-7994036760405448" data-ad-slot="4701254182" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;		&lt;/div&gt;

				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Farmingdale Observer</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 15:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizgFBVV95cUxQZWJoblpqaU8wVjFUcWVSZUJCUWIxcmIxdE15Ml82T2FudVpTVDVvSTExRVVUbjdkLXJqNklGTUhPSTNlb3BEcUlvSVZ0OTdqb2o1aWZxRGtGbzB1akhhcFJ2YWdpZWUtWGFCNnFrZjBuOHdmdE5UREVnOThyTXRMWWp6VG83Tk5WNGduQzkzbHg2RlNVRjloT252cDhxTzdzbVI5RGx2R1JiNU45RUN0bGdhdEx0dFN3SXBkRlhWWmh0ZmJRLWYxeFc2WjBJZw</guid></item><item><title>新的研究表明，身体外的体验可能是应对机制，而不是病理学-汇报 | Out-of-Body Experiences Could Be Coping Mechanisms Instead of Pathology, New Research Suggests - The Debrief</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuAFBVV95cUxPSlJkaThVSUJIeExNdjlvMHV0dXJPbzVKUDlseGl5eTE3TW4yNENBMVdnM0R1TkpwRzFOYk9Ra3ZFRFVjaldYbWhIVG55M09JR3VBdm9haXNWOVpnWXZ0U0tlUTFYdjN6U3MxYmpqLVVheFRGa2lwVG9SQXlJSEVDcmdmVmVVSTVnTk5tbkNXXzRTT2I4WERvUUFxenlCdVlvYUxmMlQtMVk4QjFzbDh2dHh6WFgwVnNG?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;
																										&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/out-of-body-experiences-can-lead-to-profound-and-lasting-psychological-transformations-new-research-reports/"&gt;Out-of-body experiences&lt;/a&gt; (OBEs), where experiencers feel like their mind and/or spirit is detached from their body, may be symptoms of &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/scientists-may-have-just-gotten-closer-to-being-able-to-alter-memories-new-research-says/"&gt;traumatic experiences&lt;/a&gt; or high stress situations, new research has shown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new findings point to traumatic events, which often occur during childhood, as a likely cause of OBEs as opposed to poor mental wellness, as past research has suggested. The scientists behind the discovery suggest that viewing OBEs as symptoms rather than causes could improve treatment options for experiencers who have been diagnosed with a &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/playing-video-games-can-boost-satisfaction-and-improve-mental-wellness-new-research-shows/"&gt;mental health condition&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If OBEs are understood not as symptoms of pathology but as coping mechanisms – especially in response to trauma – this reframing can lead to several important shifts in clinical practice, research and public understanding,” &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1087170" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;explained&lt;/a&gt; Marina Weiler, PhD from the University of Virginia’s (UVA) School of Medicine and the lead author of a &lt;a href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.paid.2025.113292"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; detailing the findings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Connection Between Out-of-Body Experiences and Mental Health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Previous efforts to study out-of-body experiences found a statistical correlation to&lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/social-media-is-impacting-young-peoples-mental-health-new-research-shows/"&gt; poor mental health&lt;/a&gt;. The authors of the new study say these findings, and the general attitudes of medical professionals tasked with understanding and treating experiencers suffering from both OBEs and &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/being-read-on-reddit-how-an-ai-model-can-predict-a-users-mental-health/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;mental health conditions&lt;/a&gt;, have resulted in experiencers avoiding seeking out treatment due to stigma.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Many people believe that having OBEs means there’s something wrong with them, so they often keep it to themselves out of fear of being judged or seen as mentally ill,” Weiler, who is also a neuroscientist with UVA’s Division of Perceptual Studies, explained. “Unfortunately, many mental health professionals still view these experiences in the same way.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Surprisingly, the researchers said that an examination of prior research into the potential causes and effects of OBEs revealed a much more nuanced picture where many people don’t consider the experiences themselves as negative. For example, many experiencers say they are more open to new ideas about the nature of existence, experience greater inner peace, and often report they are less afraid of dying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Weiler and colleagues, one previous study found that 55% of experiencers felt the experience permanently changed their lives. 71% of the same study participants said they experienced lasting benefits of their OBE. And nearly half (40%) said the out-of-body experience was the single “greatest thing” that had ever happened to them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hoping to determine why something many consider beneficial was still treated as a cause of poor mental health and not a symptom of something else, the researchers collected online questionnaire data from OBE experiencers. Along with establishing whether the person was confident that they had undergone an authentic out-of-body experience, this questionnaire asked about the experiencer’s medical and mental health history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Survey Results Show OBEs May Be a Symptom and Not a Cause&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After reviewing the online survey responses, the team found several interesting trends. Four out of five respondents reported between one and four out-of-body experiences, while the remaining one out of five reported five or more OBEs. 74% of the experiencers described the event as “spontaneous,” 9% reported the use of &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/study-says-spiritual-psychedelics-may-aid-mental-health/"&gt;psychoactive compounds&lt;/a&gt; in conjunction with the experience, and 8.2% described the OBEs as self-induced through &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/study-finds-mindfulness-training-may-induce-altered-states-of-consciousness/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;meditation&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/study-finds-mindfulness-training-may-induce-altered-states-of-consciousness/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;visualization&lt;/a&gt;, or other &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/a-new-study-reveals-surprising-results-on-the-mind-altering-power-of-binaural-beats/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;non-pharmacological techniques&lt;/a&gt;. Only 0.7% reported &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/hypnosis-radically-alters-how-the-brain-processes-information-new-study-finds/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;hypnosis&lt;/a&gt; as the cause.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On average, Weiler said experiencers “tend to report poorer mental health” compared to non-experiencers, supporting the findings of previous studies. The results also showed that the younger the experiencer was during their first OBE, the more likely the experiencer was also diagnosed with a concurrent mental health condition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notably, the team found that the average first-reported OBE occurred at a young age, often during childhood, and experiencers also reported significantly higher levels of childhood trauma than non-experiencers. These correlations led the team to propose that OBEs may not be a cause, but rather a “dissociative response to overwhelming stress or emotional pain.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Our findings also suggest that OBEs may function as a coping mechanism in response to past trauma, rather than serving as a cause of mental illness,” Weiler said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers said this view of OBEs “shifts the focus from causation” to the possibility that OBEs “may also emerge as a consequence, a coping strategy for navigating difficult or traumatic experiences.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Building ‘Community and Resilience’ Among OBE Experiencers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the study’s conclusion, the authors reaffirm the idea that out-of-body experiences may be a reaction to events and that the correlation to poor mental health may, in some part, be attached to the unwillingness of experiencers to seek treatment. As a result, Weiller says she and her colleagues “encourage mental health practitioners to reconsider the way they interpret these experiences and to approach them with greater openness and sensitivity.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research team also suggested further research exploring the mental health care that OBE experiencers receive could further the goal of better treatment and reduced stigma.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ultimately, we hope to reduce the stigma around this topic, encourage help-seeking, and build community and resilience among experiencers,” Weiler said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Christopher Plain is a Science Fiction and Fantasy novelist and Head Science Writer at The Debrief. Follow and connect with him on &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/plain_fiction"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;X&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;u&gt;,&lt;/u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; learn about his books at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://plainfiction.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;plainfiction.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;, or email him directly at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:christopher@thedebrief.org"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;christopher@thedebrief.org&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Debrief</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 13:17:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxPSlJkaThVSUJIeExNdjlvMHV0dXJPbzVKUDlseGl5eTE3TW4yNENBMVdnM0R1TkpwRzFOYk9Ra3ZFRFVjaldYbWhIVG55M09JR3VBdm9haXNWOVpnWXZ0U0tlUTFYdjN6U3MxYmpqLVVheFRGa2lwVG9SQXlJSEVDcmdmVmVVSTVnTk5tbkNXXzRTT2I4WERvUUFxenlCdVlvYUxmMlQtMVk4QjFzbDh2dHh6WFgwVnNG</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，多走路可以将慢性腰痛的风险降低23% - KSL新闻 | Walking more may lower your risk for chronic low back pain by 23%, study suggests - KSL News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitwFBVV95cUxONHZBWEVRc1RjMDZaLWtBd1d1S2VzaWd2X3o4eDVDSG8tVnIxakxIUW80eElRR0ExbjBQa3ZGNVZ3NjhoN1FURDhpUzlOODJVbmlOUjhFTFdLMTRxTTZzTWc0TzZZeUlKQXNnbGx3SzktMkJ0Si1lV3JPU1VlWWJVNmJhMUlCc0RVVmZOcmNIUGNfNlR2QjF4eGpQbmh3dG82RU9SaHhYaUVrUXU4akhBUUV4OHMzTEU?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;ATLANTA — Getting your steps in is good for your health, but it may also help keep you from being affected by disability later, new research has found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walking 100 minutes a day was associated with a 23% reduced risk of chronic low back pain, according to a study published Friday in the journal &lt;a href="http://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/10.1001/jamanetworkopen.2025.15592?utm_source=For_The_Media&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=ftm_links&amp;amp;utm_term=061325" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;JAMA Network Open&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is an important finding because walking is a simple, low cost, and accessible activity that can be promoted widely to reduce the burden of low back pain," said lead study author Rayane Haddadj, a doctoral candidate in the department of public health and nursing at the Norwegian University of Science and Technology, in an email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An estimated 600 million people worldwide experience low back pain, which is considered the leading cause of disability, said physiotherapist Dr. Natasha Pocovi, a postdoctoral research fellow in health sciences at Macquarie University in Sydney. She was not involved in the research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By 2050, the number of people with chronic low back pain is expected to grow to 843 million, according to the World Health Organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And yet prevention of low back pain is often overlooked in research and clinical practice, Pocovi added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results from this latest study show there is the possibility of using physical activity as prevention. Pocovi said the research also "suggests that we don't need to complicate our exercise routines to protect ourselves against chronic low back pain."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;More steps, less pain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To investigate the connection between walking and back pain prevention, the research team analyzed data from more than 11,000 participants age 20 and older from the Trøndelag Health, or HUNT, Study in Norway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between 2017 and 2019, HUNT researchers asked study participants to wear accelerometers for seven days to track their walking patterns. The HUNT team then followed up from 2021 and 2023 and asked if participants experienced back pain, according to the new study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People were divided into four groups: those who walked less than 78 minutes in a day, 78 to 100 minutes, 101 to 124 minutes, and more than 125 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings showed that as the amount of daily walking increased, the risk of chronic low back pain decreased, and preliminary evidence revealed moderate or brisk walking was more protective than a slow pace, Pocovi said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are reasons to have confidence in the study results, including the large sample size and the use of accelerometers instead of people reporting their own levels of physical activity, she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the walking data was only captured over one week, which might not be reflective of people's patterns over a month or year, Pocovi said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is also observational, which means that while it can show associations, researchers can't say for sure that the walking caused reduced risk of low back pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Getting more walking in&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not only is low back pain a leading cause of disability –– it's also expensive. On average, people spend more than $30,000 on back pain-related costs over the five years after first diagnosis, according to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1529943023035428" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;an April 2024 study&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Easy, inexpensive changes that prevent chronic low back pain can make a big difference, Haddadj said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study wasn't able to address if walking 100 minutes straight had more, less or the same impact as accumulating that same amount of time in short bursts, Pocovi said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in most cases, unless there is an underlying medical condition, any amount of walking is better than none, Pocovi said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Start with short walking sessions, either by planning specific walks or finding small ways to integrate a brief stroll into your daily routine," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She likes to take stairs instead of the elevator or walk to a coffee shop a little farther from her home, Pocovi said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The key is to gradually increase your walking in a sustainable and enjoyable way," she said in an email. "Additionally, it can be helpful to have a friend, partner, or colleague join you for walks to keep yourself motivated and accountable."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL News</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 13:15:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxONHZBWEVRc1RjMDZaLWtBd1d1S2VzaWd2X3o4eDVDSG8tVnIxakxIUW80eElRR0ExbjBQa3ZGNVZ3NjhoN1FURDhpUzlOODJVbmlOUjhFTFdLMTRxTTZzTWc0TzZZeUlKQXNnbGx3SzktMkJ0Si1lV3JPU1VlWWJVNmJhMUlCc0RVVmZOcmNIUGNfNlR2QjF4eGpQbmh3dG82RU9SaHhYaUVrUXU4akhBUUV4OHMzTEU</guid></item><item><title>科学家绘制酒精如何改变身体感觉的地图- PsyPost | Scientists map how alcohol changes bodily sensations - PsyPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigwFBVV95cUxQNTg3OUlxT2hYUXphY2o1b21BbzhPcklnY295YXlYazNwa3RBUnoxd2g1cUp4RE54OGZpQXNpVmhlTUpXbURaVGN6LXBTUXpsR044LWIxV0hXOUYzLUU3RjBJeGdtR1BFaFNqOWtJUFJVSHBPMWJsQ0gwbjZ2TmxCXzlzaw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/02698811251338223" target="_blank"&gt;Journal of Psychopharmacology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; offers insight into how alcohol changes our internal bodily experience — and why that might matter for understanding addiction. People who felt less bodily sensation tended to report greater stimulation and less sedation from alcohol — patterns associated with elevated risk for alcohol use disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study aimed to explore how alcohol affects interoception, the ability to sense internal bodily signals like heartbeats or feelings of warmth. Prior research has shown that alcohol alters heart rate and other physiological functions, and that people’s sensitivity to these changes may play a role in how alcohol feels and whether they continue drinking. However, most research has focused on cognitive effects or retrospective reports, not on the actual lived, bodily experience of intoxication as it unfolds in real time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We have known for a long time that people differ in the way they respond to alcohol effects, and that this differential responsiveness can be a risk marker for future addiction problems,” said study author &lt;a href="https://www.adapt-lab.nl/team/mateo-leganes-fonteneau" target="_blank"&gt;Mateo Leganes-Fonteneau&lt;/a&gt;, an FNRS Chargé de Recherche at &lt;a href="https://www.uclep.be/labs/ARL/mateo_leganes_fonteneau" target="_blank"&gt;UCLouvain&lt;/a&gt; and Marie Curie Research Fellow at the University of Amsterdam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This has usually been studied by looking at subjective cognitive responses, using questionnaires, or observing basic physiological processes. However, we now know that our sensitivity to bodily states and the way we perceive our bodies plays a key role in shaping our behavior and motivation — but that part of the addiction puzzle is still understudied. With this research I wanted to show that we can measure the subjective bodily sensations associated with alcohol intoxication.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To investigate this, the researchers recruited 37 adult social drinkers with no history of psychiatric disorders or substance use treatment. Participants completed two lab sessions in a double-blind, placebo-controlled design. On one occasion, they were given a moderate dose of alcohol (0.4 grams per kilogram of body weight, mixed with tonic water and bitters). On the other, they received a placebo beverage with identical taste and smell cues. The order of sessions was randomized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Throughout each session, participants were repeatedly asked to map where they felt bodily sensations using a digital tool called emBODY. This interactive tool allowed them to indicate, on a digital human figure, where they felt activation (such as tingling or warmth) and deactivation (such as numbness or heaviness). These maps were collected at several time points corresponding to the rising and falling phases of their blood alcohol levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition, participants filled out questionnaires assessing how sedated or stimulated they felt and completed a task designed to assess cardiac interoception. This task involved listening to their heartbeat and deciding whether a series of tones matched it in speed. Participants also rated their confidence in their decisions, which allowed researchers to assess both accuracy and metacognitive insight into their own interoceptive abilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bodily maps revealed clear differences between the alcohol and placebo conditions. During the ascending phase of intoxication, when blood alcohol levels were rising, participants in the alcohol condition reported intense activation in the chest and head, as well as in the arms. As intoxication wore off during the descending phase, those sensations became more diffuse, with some deactivation (numbness) appearing in the limbs. These patterns were not observed in the placebo condition, which showed weaker and less widespread bodily sensations overall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, the researchers found that the strength of bodily sensations was linked to actual physiological changes. During the ascending phase, increases in heart rate predicted greater reported bodily sensation in the alcohol condition, but not in the placebo group. During the descending phase, breath alcohol levels were similarly associated with stronger bodily sensations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The way people felt their bodies during intoxication also predicted how they reported feeling mentally. Participants who experienced more bodily sensation tended to report greater sedation and less stimulation. This was especially true during the rising phase of intoxication, when alcohol typically produces its most energizing effects. People who reported fewer bodily sensations, on the other hand, reported feeling more stimulated and less sedated — suggesting a disconnect between their body’s response and their subjective awareness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This pattern is noteworthy because earlier studies have shown that people who experience more stimulation and less sedation from alcohol tend to be at higher risk for problematic drinking. These individuals may find alcohol more rewarding and are more likely to seek out its stimulating effects, even as tolerance develops. The new findings suggest that reduced bodily sensation during intoxication may be another factor contributing to this risk, by making alcohol feel more pleasurable and less impairing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also found that bodily sensations were related to how well participants could judge their heartbeats. During the descending limb of intoxication, those who reported more bodily sensation showed greater metacognitive sensitivity — meaning they had better insight into how accurate their heartbeat judgments were. This suggests that bodily sensations and interoceptive awareness are not separate systems but may be tightly linked during intoxication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People experience a range of bodily sensations when they are intoxicated, and there is inter-individual variability in the intensity of these sensations,” Leganes-Fonteneau told PsyPost. “Depending on how strong those sensations are, they will feel more or less intoxicated. We use our bodily sensations to build the conscious experience of intoxication. These bodily sensations partly reflect the effects of alcohol on physiological states, such as heart rate or breath alcohol content. Bodily sensations act as a window to the conscious perception of internal changes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the placebo condition also produced bodily sensations, especially during the early stages of the session. Participants reported some activation in the chest and head even when they had not consumed alcohol, and these sensations were associated with feelings of sedation. The researchers believe this reflects the power of expectancy and conditioning: repeated experiences of drinking alcohol may train the brain to anticipate bodily changes, even when the beverage contains no alcohol. These effects faded over time as the absence of real alcohol became more apparent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People experience bodily sensations when we give them a placebo, and these sensations are similar to those of alcohol,” Leganes-Fonteneau said. “This is important for understanding placebo effects, as they not only generate subjective mental states but also bodily sensations that have no underlying physiological change.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By combining bodily mapping with physiological and psychological measures, the study provides a comprehensive picture of how alcohol affects the body from the inside out. It also supports the idea that bodily sensation is not just a passive side effect of intoxication but an active part of how people experience — and perhaps become vulnerable to — alcohol’s effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But as with all research, there are limitations to consider. First, it was based on a relatively small sample, which limited the ability to detect more nuanced effects, such as sex differences in bodily sensation. Another limitation is that the bodily mapping data were averaged across participants and time points, which may mask individual differences in how intoxication is felt. For example, some people may feel stimulation in their head while others feel sedation in their chest or limbs. A larger study could explore these differences more precisely and link them to personality traits, drinking history, or risk for addiction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We link these bodily sensations to subjective feelings of intoxication in a way that appears to map onto risk markers for alcohol misuse: those experiencing less bodily sensations would be at higher risk,” Leganes-Fonteneau said. “However, we still do not have cross-sectional (between groups) or longitudinal evidence that (in)sensitivity to bodily sensations of intoxication can predict alcohol misuse.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is a study conducted in the laboratory, where participants sit by themselves and don’t have much to do, so they end up being able to reflect more directly on their bodily sensations. It is not clear how these bodily sensations would emerge in a real-world setting, where more exteroceptive and social information can distract them. At the same time, this insensitivity to bodily signals might be even more critical when there’s competing information, explaining why some people end up drinking too much without even realizing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these caveats, the research marks an important step forward in understanding how bodily sensations contribute to the experience of alcohol intoxication. It suggests that people who are less tuned into their internal states may be more vulnerable to alcohol misuse — not because they lack self-control, but because they do not fully register the body’s warning signals. The researchers are currently working on follow-up studies exploring how bodily sensations relate to craving and hangovers, and how these signals can be tracked in everyday life using smartphone-based assessments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This work is more than anything a blueprint for how bodily sensations can be measured in applied addiction research and other mental disorders,” Leganes-Fonteneau explained. “We have produced additional work on the bodily sensations of alcohol craving and hangover and are working on integrating bodily sensations within ecological momentary assessment. This can in the future help us target bodily sensations in therapeutic settings.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/02698811251338223" target="_blank"&gt;Mapping acute alcohol effects on bodily sensations: A cross-dimensional interoceptive approach&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Mateo Leganes-Fonteneau, Olivier Desmedt, Micah G. Allen, Reinout W. Wiers, and Pierre Maurage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 12:11:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQNTg3OUlxT2hYUXphY2o1b21BbzhPcklnY295YXlYazNwa3RBUnoxd2g1cUp4RE54OGZpQXNpVmhlTUpXbURaVGN6LXBTUXpsR044LWIxV0hXOUYzLUU3RjBJeGdtR1BFaFNqOWtJUFJVSHBPMWJsQ0gwbjZ2TmxCXzlzaw</guid></item><item><title>3个孩子的父亲感觉很健康。然后，常规筛查发现了一种罕见的致命疾病。-哥伦比亚广播公司新闻 | A father of 3 felt healthy. Then a routine screening found a rare, deadly illness. - CBS News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxPZncxZGNQNWtFUzEzUHo2dTNlUUZXa1hPOHB4Tk5VZXdfODNLYTdWUUVXTFhGc1VmQndzYzNzem0tNkpiYklmZVRBRVNuZW55amswYWlpeGJGem9EQ3lRckZ0SHNXYmpLSGk4UUlzeFQ5Yl8wMWZOSno1NmxmdkZKTTRaZ2RsY211U0o0MUt1Z2tuVURZSC1aOGJFUXYydmVESnBGeVFXZTNJdkJZZHfSAbMBQVVfeXFMUGpoNGZvR2RVQjhLWHc0TzZhejl3SEpFM0dVdEc0Qm5QRGdIdTllWkZocUc3Vm5jdGo0ZnhpZ21NVlJOQnhtR25oalZxTjY5NDlNaTVLMTdtSmIyMEtHM0FrU1N5cHZXY1RyWUV3MHpTSW1WcDItc1RpUW90YVZwRFFQdXBLeHNDdUlGWk1OZ2hjYmdrYVo4bXdGRWw5NUxyM1kzZlAyem9CT0xuUGhka0FmS0E?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Curtis Jackson was feeling fit and healthy in late 2020 when he decided to update his life insurance policy: He was in better shape than he'd been in a while, but he wanted to make sure his wife and three kids were taken care of if anything happened to him. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jackson, now 46, underwent an intensive physical, and everything seemed to be going well until he received a strange phone call. The call was focused on a questionnaire he had filled out. Jackson had truthfully marked that he did not drink alcohol. But his liver numbers were those of "a functioning alcoholic," he was told. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It set off alarm bells. Jackson went to his primary care physician for another round of bloodwork. That doctor thought he had a problem with his gallbladder. Jackson went to have his gallbladder removed. During that operation, doctors found he had an unusual condition called primary sclerosing cholangitis, or PSC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chronic, progressive disease affects the liver and inflames the bile ducts, causing liver damage. Patients eventually need a liver transplant. There's also a small but real chance of a deadly diagnosis: a dangerous cancer called cholangiocarcinoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early treatment and diagnosis can make a difference, so Jackson started undergoing two MRIs a year at the Mayo Clinic in Arizona to make sure he was cancer-free. He also had a regular test to check the progress of his PSC. In October 2024, Jackson had a nerve-wracking appointment where the technician scoping him seemed "very concerned." He felt healthy, but was worried by the appointment. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"She didn't say that it was cancer, but she was hinting towards it," Jackson said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/aac23374-cd38-4e62-96b9-dd69f28874c5/thumbnail/620x827/0b26fe16954a1c41fe2b54729f82acb7/curtis-jackson-4-7-25-1-mos-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698#" alt="curtis-jackson-4-7-25-1-mos-post-op.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/aac23374-cd38-4e62-96b9-dd69f28874c5/thumbnail/620x827/0b26fe16954a1c41fe2b54729f82acb7/curtis-jackson-4-7-25-1-mos-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/aac23374-cd38-4e62-96b9-dd69f28874c5/thumbnail/1240x1654/0148cd4d734935cedb4235eb53c91753/curtis-jackson-4-7-25-1-mos-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Curtis Jackson at home in April 2025.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Mayo Clinic

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Three weeks later, Jackson and his wife received the news he had been dreading: The tests had diagnosed him with the deadly cancer. He would need to undergo intensive treatment to try to fight the illness. It felt like a repeat of when he had had the initial PSC diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was feeling fine ... and both times netted a result of something pretty serious," Jackson said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is cholangiocarcinoma? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cholangiocarcinoma, or bile duct cancer, is considered a silent killer, according to Dr. Tanios Bekaii-Saab, the chairman of the division of hematology and medical oncology at the Mayo Clinic in Phoenix, Arizona. Bekaii-Saab was Jackson's oncologist. It tends to spread to other organs before symptoms appear, so most patients are diagnosed "too late to cure," Bekaii-Saab said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="leader-plus-inc3" data-ad="leader-plus-inc" class="ad-leader-plus-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["leader-plus-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About 20% of people with PSC are diagnosed with cholangiocarcinoma, said Dr. Aqel Bashar, the director of the Mayo Clinic's Transplant Center in Phoenix, Arizona, who also treated Jackson. It's a rare disease, affecting about 1 in 100,000 people in the U.S., Bashar said. Not all cases are associated with PCS. Like many other cancers, it is on the rise, Bekaii-Saab said, with diagnoses of cholangiocarcinoma increasing more than 50% in the past decade. Fewer than 10% of the people diagnosed with cholangiocarcinoma live more than five years, Bashar said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best way to treat cholangiocarcinoma is with a liver transplant, Bekaii-Saab said. But it can only be done if the disease is caught early, before the cancer spreads. Many cholangiocarcinoma patients are not eligible for a liver transplant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, Jackson's case was caught early. He underwent three weeks of chemotherapy and radiation to kill as many cancer cells as possible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Basically, I lived at Mayo Clinic. I would literally do work out of the parking lot, and then go and do radiation," Jackson said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During treatment, he lost about 30 pounds. But despite the odds, he remained optimistic that everything would work out. He even encouraged his wife to start a long-anticipated kitchen renovation. In the middle of the process, the family was told a liver was available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On March 6, he was wheeled into surgery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/b748edc0-b06e-4210-bee1-421bb1c5e0c6/thumbnail/620x465g2/28690e52890a37fb3e572ac3410c5fc5/curtis-jackson-family-4-7-25-aprox-1-mo-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698#" alt="curtis-jackson-family-4-7-25-aprox-1-mo-post-op.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/b748edc0-b06e-4210-bee1-421bb1c5e0c6/thumbnail/620x465g2/28690e52890a37fb3e572ac3410c5fc5/curtis-jackson-family-4-7-25-aprox-1-mo-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/b748edc0-b06e-4210-bee1-421bb1c5e0c6/thumbnail/1240x930g2/108ac8e727377944edd4b49c12544429/curtis-jackson-family-4-7-25-aprox-1-mo-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;The Jackson family and their dog Lucy at home in April 2025. From left: Stetson Jackson, Gwyn Jackson, Rooney Jackson, Curtis Jackson and Kim Jackson. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Mayo Clinic

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Surgery and recovery &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The surgery took about four hours. Six days later, Jackson was released from the hospital. Testing showed that he was cancer-free. For the next year, he will undergo weekly blood tests and have monthly check-ups. He will need close monitoring for the rest of his life, Bashar said, since his transplant needs to be monitored and doctors need to make sure his cholangiocarcinoma does not return.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="leader-plus-inc4" data-ad="leader-plus-inc" class="ad-leader-plus-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["leader-plus-inc",4]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For now, Jackson is trying to focus on his home and family, he said. His routine is "pretty close to normal," though he still can't lift more than 10 pounds, and climbing stairs can be draining. He gained back much of the weight he lost in treatment, and his energy levels are close to where they were before the cancer diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Things are definitely getting back to normal, which is really exciting. I wasn't expecting that so fast," Jackson said. "We might call it either lucky, or blessed, or whatever. I am just so thankful that I was able to bounce back so quickly." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/e098f644-b5ae-46fd-b2b6-c2c658a73b0d/thumbnail/620x827/24b7575afb49284ea5b5f62d60fee9d1/curtis-jackson-stetson-rooney-gwyn-3-6-25-6-hrs-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698#" alt="curtis-jackson-stetson-rooney-gwyn-3-6-25-6-hrs-post-op.jpg " srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/e098f644-b5ae-46fd-b2b6-c2c658a73b0d/thumbnail/620x827/24b7575afb49284ea5b5f62d60fee9d1/curtis-jackson-stetson-rooney-gwyn-3-6-25-6-hrs-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/e098f644-b5ae-46fd-b2b6-c2c658a73b0d/thumbnail/1240x1654/902cc53388ff4d0c638157f3b3168635/curtis-jackson-stetson-rooney-gwyn-3-6-25-6-hrs-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Curtis Jackson and his children hours after his transplant surgery. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Jackson family

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Jacksons are putting the finishing touches on the kitchen renovation, and planning to travel to North Carolina for vacation this summer. He also wants to plan family trips outside the country once he needs less frequent check-ups. His other priority is turning his story into something that can help others, and advocating for organ transplant and donation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have a new passion now," Jackson said. "I'm here because of these things. I would like to help this going forward and make sure people are learning the importance of donation." &lt;/p&gt;

      

                    
        
      
                  
    

    


    
      
    
  

          
  
        
      &lt;div class="content-author"&gt;
      &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/team/kerry-breen/" class="content-author__name" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Kerry  Breen&lt;/a&gt;

      &lt;div class="content-author__bio"&gt;
        &lt;div class="content-author__full-information"&gt;
          &lt;p class="content-author__text"&gt;Kerry Breen is a news editor at CBSNews.com. A graduate of New York University's Arthur L. Carter School of Journalism, she previously worked at NBC News' TODAY Digital. She covers current events, breaking news and issues including substance use.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/section&gt;

  
  

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPZncxZGNQNWtFUzEzUHo2dTNlUUZXa1hPOHB4Tk5VZXdfODNLYTdWUUVXTFhGc1VmQndzYzNzem0tNkpiYklmZVRBRVNuZW55amswYWlpeGJGem9EQ3lRckZ0SHNXYmpLSGk4UUlzeFQ5Yl8wMWZOSno1NmxmdkZKTTRaZ2RsY211U0o0MUt1Z2tuVURZSC1aOGJFUXYydmVESnBGeVFXZTNJdkJZZHfSAbMBQVVfeXFMUGpoNGZvR2RVQjhLWHc0TzZhejl3SEpFM0dVdEc0Qm5QRGdIdTllWkZocUc3Vm5jdGo0ZnhpZ21NVlJOQnhtR25oalZxTjY5NDlNaTVLMTdtSmIyMEtHM0FrU1N5cHZXY1RyWUV3MHpTSW1WcDItc1RpUW90YVZwRFFQdXBLeHNDdUlGWk1OZ2hjYmdrYVo4bXdGRWw5NUxyM1kzZlAyem9CT0xuUGhka0FmS0E</guid></item><item><title>许多老年人接种疫苗。研究证明了他们是对的。-《纽约时报》 | Many Older People Embrace Vaccines. Research Is Proving Them Right. - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifEFVX3lxTE1kSldSWVJWbEpPaWh5Z3VKc3NrVnQ4cTdnbjFYcVpjeWNLNDE1cUktd1BGU0ZwWXEzdG55X3duOC1ZRDZJN3hyU3BPZkpOWkRIMjVnZ0ZUX1BuRngtMXBRd01iLTBHekE5V0dnSWZUN1RvblFIN0lfc1ZJcHY?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 11:21:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE1kSldSWVJWbEpPaWh5Z3VKc3NrVnQ4cTdnbjFYcVpjeWNLNDE1cUktd1BGU0ZwWXEzdG55X3duOC1ZRDZJN3hyU3BPZkpOWkRIMjVnZ0ZUX1BuRngtMXBRd01iLTBHekE5V0dnSWZUN1RvblFIN0lfc1ZJcHY</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，每天花五分钟来做这件事可以提高幸福感-旧金山纪事报 | Taking five minutes a day to do this can improve happiness, study finds - San Francisco Chronicle</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV95cUxOXzI1WGFuWjhrZW03UWo0cXYzNzh5bVNNVGRNa2U5YWQwaHlwNTMtUmhVb2RVNlYtZUc4ejFvVnFFTEpUVEZXaDBEUmJ3WXpicVRBTkhBMUh2M3N4Rmg5bE5YMU5xdlZZMEVzNVpuemZJR3RHWnFGTmh1bzNwckpQTzVn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>San Francisco Chronicle</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 11:11:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxOXzI1WGFuWjhrZW03UWo0cXYzNzh5bVNNVGRNa2U5YWQwaHlwNTMtUmhVb2RVNlYtZUc4ejFvVnFFTEpUVEZXaDBEUmJ3WXpicVRBTkhBMUh2M3N4Rmg5bE5YMU5xdlZZMEVzNVpuemZJR3RHWnFGTmh1bzNwckpQTzVn</guid></item><item><title>在吃袋装生菜之前，您可能需要三思而后行- HuffPost | You May Want To Think Twice Before You Eat Bagged Lettuce - HuffPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivAFBVV95cUxPb3lfcUU5Y3gxdHQtWlZwaWRZb2xxTlVJNF9zQ2lzc0tNQjAtOGljcW5RdHI3OVpNd0dfYnJJSzVVTE5LS1lJQXBINDI1dWxuZ2JuenN2b2pLWXVCTXBUaWtaT2VvSmk0RXo4bTBobDIxYmt0RnM2aGgySGNYVkFHTkczWjJIUTF5cExkeEhtU1QyOHNNNDZweDZKMk1ZcVNPdFhWWTB4WmVIOVFTeXZBUnhXTFZRLThQUkVYQdIBwgFBVV95cUxPMU9kQmd1NmhZSTVscndiUThWWl9Sa0VMRktjN1BUQUQyVlNZaFYzcy1kVVp0OFY2eWw1eVgwUDdsVjF5Snk5bVh4Zk53MzVXMk4tZkk4ZDNaTUREcVJ5OGFRSVl6S1VQYktRYW5pVENNV2dHNEFVcEIteVNldlVtRlNRYzdiT3JCYVJ2TFBzMlZTWjBMSzNqa3poTEN0LUZRZnU0Tlo0cmhLRi1sR1MzM1VjeU5RMkI1OHVNRjZhQjl0UQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;You likely buy some &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/topic/grocery-shopping" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="grocery" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/topic/grocery-shopping" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;grocery&lt;/a&gt; items for convenience, to save a couple of steps when it’s time to prepare a meal. Prewashed bagged greens, such as lettuce or spinach, seem like a no-brainer if you’re trying to eat nutritiously. But not so fast ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to food safety experts, prewashed bagged greens aren’t the safest choice. Bacteria and contamination are more common than you may suspect in this particular grocery item.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“While consumers expect convenience and safety, the reality is that prewashed bagged greens remain one of the riskiest items in the grocery store due to contamination risks throughout the supply chain,” says &lt;a href="https://cps.northeastern.edu/faculty/darin-detwiler/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Darin Detwiler" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://cps.northeastern.edu/faculty/darin-detwiler/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;Darin Detwiler&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of food policy at Northeastern University and author of “&lt;a href="https://r.bttn.io?btn_ref=org-677cb81987ed72f9&amp;amp;btn_url=https://r.bttn.io/?tag=thehuffingtop-20%26ascsubtag%3D68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0%252C-1%252C-1%252Cd%252C0%252C0%252Chp-fil-am%253D0%252C0%253A0%252C0%252C0%252C0" role="link" data-amazon-link="true" data-aps-asin="null" data-aps-asc-tag="null" data-aps-asc-subtag="null" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Food Safety: Past, Present, and Predictions" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://r.bttn.io?btn_ref=org-677cb81987ed72f9&amp;amp;btn_url=https://r.bttn.io/?tag=thehuffingtop-20%26ascsubtag%3D68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0%252C-1%252C-1%252Cd%252C0%252C0%252Chp-fil-am%253D0%252C0%253A0%252C0%252C0%252C0" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;Food Safety: Past, Present, and Predictions&lt;/a&gt;.” He avoids buying bagged greens because of the risk of deadly E. coli contamination. “When you look at past outbreaks, bagged salads have been a leading cause of foodborne illness, with some outbreaks resulting in hospitalizations, kidney failure (hemolytic uremic syndrome), and even death,” Detwiler said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’re not imagining it — there are a lot of outbreaks.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many factors in the supply chain can contaminate the greens with pathogens — such as E. coli, listeria or salmonella — that can leave people sick, hospitalized or worse. “Bagged greens are washed and processed in large batches, which is an effective way to spread pathogens,” said &lt;a href="https://www.ice.edu/about/faculty-profiles/olivia-roszkowski" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Olivia Roszkowski" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ice.edu/about/faculty-profiles/olivia-roszkowski" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Olivia Roszkowski&lt;/a&gt;, chef-instructor of plant-based culinary arts and food safety certification at the Institute of Culinary Education’s New York City campus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leafy green outbreaks happen more than you’d expect, and the FDA created a &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/food/foodborne-pathogens/leafy-greens-stec-action-plan" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Leafy Greens STEC Action Plan" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.fda.gov/food/foodborne-pathogens/leafy-greens-stec-action-plan" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;Leafy Greens STEC Action Plan&lt;/a&gt; in 2020 to reduce different strains of E. coli in leafy greens and updated the plan in 2023. (For example, shiga toxin-producing Escherichia coli O157:H7 is the pathogenic strain that is often associated with &lt;a href="https://www.ars.usda.gov/oc/utm/keeping-bagged-leafy-greens-safe-and-nutritious-for-human-consumption/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="lettuce and leafy green outbreaks" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ars.usda.gov/oc/utm/keeping-bagged-leafy-greens-safe-and-nutritious-for-human-consumption/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;lettuce and leafy green outbreaks&lt;/a&gt;, and Detwiler says it “is particularly dangerous because it takes a very small amount to cause severe illness. ... The risk isn’t theoretical — it’s been repeatedly proven in outbreak after outbreak.” )&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Stefano Oppo via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Stefano Oppo via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;The greens that end up in a bag can come from multiple different farms and locations.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;And despite the efforts to reduce leafy green-related outbreaks, they continue to occur. Leafy greens are attributed to “up to 9.2% of known pathogen-caused foodborne illnesses” in the U.S., according to a report in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0362028X24000590" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Journal of Foodborne Illness" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0362028X24000590" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Journal of Foodborne Illness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; published in April 2024. The report estimates over 2.3 million illnesses every year are related to contaminated leafy greens. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How the food supply chain becomes contaminated&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On the farm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Contamination can occur at different stages before bagged salad greens reach the refrigerated produce section and eventually your plate. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“In the field, produce can become contaminated with pathogens from sources such as contaminated irrigation water, wild or domesticated animals, soil, or air,” said &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.clemson.edu/cafls/faculty_staff/profiles/kabaker" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Kimberly Baker," data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.clemson.edu/cafls/faculty_staff/profiles/kabaker" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kimberly Baker,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;a food systems and safety program team director at Clemson University. It’s more common to have contaminated greens “when the field is in close proximity to livestock farms or feedlots where animals are being held in densely populated conditions,” Roszkowski explained. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Arizona and California are big producers of leafy greens in the United States and are often near large cattle operations, according to Detwiler. E. coli, salmonella, or listeria can be introduced to the crops through contaminated irrigation water from nearby cattle farms, he said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Runoff from manure lagoons can seep into irrigation canals and contaminate fields with deadly bacteria like E. coli O157:H7,” Detwiler continued. Manure lagoons are large pits where livestock waste is stored, per &lt;a href="https://environmentamerica.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/AccidentsFactsheet-ManureLagoons-1.pdf" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Environmental" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://environmentamerica.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/AccidentsFactsheet-ManureLagoons-1.pdf" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;Environmental&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://environmentamerica.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/AccidentsFactsheet-ManureLagoons-1.pdf" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name=" America" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://environmentamerica.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/AccidentsFactsheet-ManureLagoons-1.pdf" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;&lt;span&gt; America&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. And it’s not only contaminated water that can be a problem. Some farms use unregulated water sources to irrigate the fields. “Some farms use untreated or minimally treated surface water from rivers, lakes or canals, increasing the risk of contamination,” Detwiler said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When it’s time to harvest, there are added risks for pathogens and bacteria to come in contact with lettuce. “Contamination can occur through human handling, contaminated equipment or water used in post-harvest processes to transport, produce or remove soil,” Baker said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In the processing plant&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are opportunities for pathogens to come in contact with leafy greens once they reach a processing plant. The greens you get in a bag don’t typically come from one field but from multiple farms, complicating traceability and increasing contamination. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Greens are processed in a centralized area and distributed — which is convenient for all the companies involved in the process— but not ideal from a food safety standpoint. “Greens from different farms are mixed, washed and packaged together, so one contaminated leaf can impact thousands of bags across multiple states,” Detwiler explained. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lettuce is washed in large vats, added &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://drexel.edu/cnhp/faculty/profiles/TroutRosemary/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Rosemary Trout," data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://drexel.edu/cnhp/faculty/profiles/TroutRosemary/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rosemary Trout,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; associate professor and program director of Culinary Arts &amp;amp; Food Science at Drexel University. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;What you may not suspect, according to Trout, is that “plant foods are usually more often associated with foodborne illness than animal products.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On the journey to store shelves&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Keeping the greens cold is necessary to prevent any pathogens from growing and spreading. According to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Roszkowski&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;, “Not keeping the greens consistently cold throughout the process of harvesting, processing and transporting can cause bacterial growth to occur.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;However, refrigeration doesn’t eliminate the chance of pathogens; it can help slow them down. “Refrigeration slows bacterial growth but does not kill bacteria, meaning contaminated greens can still cause illness, even if stored properly,” Detwiler said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Will washing prewashed salad greens help?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you’re thinking, “W&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;ell, I’ll wash my prewashed greens for extra safety measures&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;,” don’t. Washing greens at home doesn’t make them safer because water won’t remove the pathogens, Detwiler said. Rinsing prewashed greens can introduce pathogens that may be lurking on your counter or sink. “Prewashed greens should not be rewashed at home, as doing so can introduce contamination if the sink, utensils, equipment or hands of the preparer are not properly cleaned or sanitized,” Baker said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Westend61 via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Westend61 via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Washing greens can remove pesticides, but it's not been proven to be effective in removing pathogens.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bacteria or pathogens aren’t obvious and can’t be seen. “If greens are contaminated with pathogens, they cannot be detected by sight, smell or taste … and can’t be removed by washing,” Baker explained. According to Detwiler, “Bacteria like &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;E. coli&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;salmonella&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; can form biofilms that help them stick to the surface of the leaves [and] once attached, these bacteria do not simply rinse off.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Harmful pathogens need to be cooked to be eliminated, as heat kills them, said Detwiler. A big issue with lettuce is it’s usually eaten raw, not cooked, “making it challenging to reduce the risk of foodborne illness,” Baker said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommendations for buying bagged greens&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you still prefer buying bagged greens for the convenience, there are several precautions to take. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check for recalls &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Before you purchase any salad greens, check if there are any recalls, advised &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Detwiler and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Roszkowski&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;. “Stay updated on recalls via the FDA and CDC websites,” Detwiler said. “If your greens are part of an outbreak, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;throw them away immediately.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check expiration dates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experts say you should look at the expiration dates before purchasing. Trout advises to only buy what you will eat within a day or two. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look for freshness&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Avoid bags with excess moisture that look wet, as damp environments are a haven for bacteria to thrive, Detwiler said. “Inspect the package to ensure the lettuce looks fresh, without wilting or discoloration, as these signs may indicate improper storage or reduced freshness,” Baker said. You also want to stay away from any bags that have slimy leaves, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Roszkowski added&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimize temperature changes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Once you’ve purchased greens, don’t let them sit in a hot car or garage or out on the counter. “Avoid drastic changes in temperature when transporting them from the store and when preparing a meal,” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Roszkowski said&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;. “This leads to condensation and creates a moist and warm environment that can encourage both spoilage and bacterial growth.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ice.edu/about/faculty-profiles/olivia-roszkowski" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ice.edu/about/faculty-profiles/olivia-roszkowski" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Store properly&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Greens should be kept refrigerated at or below 40 degrees Fahrenheit, say Detwiler and Trout. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Buy heads of lettuce &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Purchasing a head of lettuce or a bunch of spinach may have the extra step of rinsing and drying before tossing in a salad bowl or stir-frying, but you could be minimizing the risk of lurking pathogens. “Whole heads of lettuce or spinach have less surface area for contamination compared to pre-cut, mixed bagged greens,” Detwiler said. He suggests rinsing them under cold water — not soaking — to remove dirt, debris, any insects and surface-level bacteria. “Wash them at home before eating.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 11:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxPb3lfcUU5Y3gxdHQtWlZwaWRZb2xxTlVJNF9zQ2lzc0tNQjAtOGljcW5RdHI3OVpNd0dfYnJJSzVVTE5LS1lJQXBINDI1dWxuZ2JuenN2b2pLWXVCTXBUaWtaT2VvSmk0RXo4bTBobDIxYmt0RnM2aGgySGNYVkFHTkczWjJIUTF5cExkeEhtU1QyOHNNNDZweDZKMk1ZcVNPdFhWWTB4WmVIOVFTeXZBUnhXTFZRLThQUkVYQdIBwgFBVV95cUxPMU9kQmd1NmhZSTVscndiUThWWl9Sa0VMRktjN1BUQUQyVlNZaFYzcy1kVVp0OFY2eWw1eVgwUDdsVjF5Snk5bVh4Zk53MzVXMk4tZkk4ZDNaTUREcVJ5OGFRSVl6S1VQYktRYW5pVENNV2dHNEFVcEIteVNldlVtRlNRYzdiT3JCYVJ2TFBzMlZTWjBMSzNqa3poTEN0LUZRZnU0Tlo0cmhLRi1sR1MzM1VjeU5RMkI1OHVNRjZhQjl0UQ</guid></item><item><title>汉堡包多少才算太多？以下是健康专家的建议。- HuffPost | How Many Burgers Are Too Many Burgers? Here's What Health Experts Advise. - HuffPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizgFBVV95cUxQYll2QTRWUElTNHVBV1RrSDVBVHlYOHRtbVd3OGhwSWRIUU1VLVVNY0lZbHBhb1dXLWE4S3VIbFNnVDJKSjFDYWNrX01VRmg0N19RekF3MXQ5X2kzVFVjeDQ0Tmd6WnBhX2hQbDNqX2IwTDBhb1loT2h6QklIbE13aEpHcjhRZ2tZZGdMcVBYZmZOUEdHNUhZem90SktjVFZZNHBJRElUQmV2WkcwTFRWcndYQndQUnVuY1dXTndKSEVJZW9ZTVNmaVlIbVhvQdIB0wFBVV95cUxNU2hDVjVhWGZxQWJ3U3l4dUNBQ2VsalRiVHNiYmtiRW92VHR0UlR2YjBQMVlranFUTVRyWEhRbzFQLVItUG95cEFCZWM3aFV2b24yeUlqV2NDS3Z3dDhhUTcySGVTT0F5djh2VmlTdExma3VmelNDNExHZmhtSURqX2FuS21lVTVHWVFfSjdkaVlRNDRHUUhIM1dHMDFrUE1fOGlvLTE5LTBXZTdsbmE3QTJOMnk3M0FoMndiLVBWdGh6UzJhUk42V1dJZ0xuWHQzY2Jr?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/homemade-burger-recipe-no-grill_l_62853ee2e4b0c2dce6583821" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="hamburgers and cheeseburgers " data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="684b1b93e4b03a16ecb33efb" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="62853ee2e4b0c2dce6583821" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;hamburgers and cheeseburgers &lt;/a&gt;are your go-to food during grilling season (or, let’s be honest, at your local fast-food joint all year long), you may need to stop and think about just how many you’re eating. They can pile up fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though burgers are delicious and a quintessential warm-weather food, they’re also linked to health issues including heart disease and even &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4698595/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="cancer" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="684b1b93e4b03a16ecb33efb" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4698595/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because of red meat’s connection to serious health concerns, many people, including some doctors, don’t eat it or &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/cancer-doctors-food_l_64357018e4b0c2da1508a4a9" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="severely limit it in their diets" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="684b1b93e4b03a16ecb33efb" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="64357018e4b0c2da1508a4a9" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;severely limit it in their diets&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s the best way to go about a summer of grilling and eating burgers? How many is too many? And should certain people avoid burgers altogether? Here’s what experts say:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Red meat does have health benefits.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The news about red meat isn’t all bad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Red meat is a good source of protein, iron, zinc and B12, which are nutrients needed for daily bodily functions, cell growth, tissue repair, red blood cell development, etc.,” &lt;a href="https://wexnermedical.osu.edu/mediaroom/expertslisting/stacey-pence" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Stacey Pence" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="684b1b93e4b03a16ecb33efb" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://wexnermedical.osu.edu/mediaroom/expertslisting/stacey-pence" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Stacey Pence&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian at Ohio State University’s Wexner Medical Center, told HuffPost.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While this is a plus for red meat, Pence pointed out that other animal products and plant-based sources can also provide you with the same benefits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Red meat doesn’t have a monopoly on those nutrients,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samantha McKinney, a registered dietitian for &lt;a href="https://www.lifetime.life/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Life Time" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="684b1b93e4b03a16ecb33efb" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.lifetime.life/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;Life Time&lt;/a&gt; fitness centers, told HuffPost that healthy sources of protein can include a variety of options, including fish, poultry, eggs, plain dairy (with no added sugar), shellfish and red meat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Most people will want to include a variety of these protein sources in their routine (as tolerated) to maximize variety and nutrient intake,” McKinney stated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;But red meat also has risks.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There’s a lot of saturated fat that comes as part of ground beef and red meat in general,” said &lt;a href="https://www.pccmn.com/copy-of-dr-klodas" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Elizabeth Klodas" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="684b1b93e4b03a16ecb33efb" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.pccmn.com/copy-of-dr-klodas" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;Dr. Elizabeth Klodas&lt;/a&gt;, a cardiologist and chief medical officer of &lt;a href="https://go.skimresources.com/?id=38395X987171&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;xcust=6406486fe4b0586db70f4ef4&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.steponefoods.com%2Fpages%2Foverview-2%2F" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Step One Foods" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="684b1b93e4b03a16ecb33efb" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://go.skimresources.com/?id=38395X987171&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;xcust=6406486fe4b0586db70f4ef4&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.steponefoods.com%2Fpages%2Foverview-2%2F" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;Step One Foods&lt;/a&gt;. “Saturated fat ... causes elevated LDL cholesterol, bad cholesterol, and LDL cholesterol is linearly linked to heart disease risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, Klodas said, &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6664935/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="saturated fat is pro-inflammatory" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="684b1b93e4b03a16ecb33efb" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6664935/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;saturated fat is pro-inflammatory&lt;/a&gt;, which is not a good thing.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We know that all of the three major diseases we’re all trying to avoid, whether it’s &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/life/topic/heart-disease" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="heart disease" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="684b1b93e4b03a16ecb33efb" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/life/topic/heart-disease" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;, cancer or &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/signs-dementia-symptoms_l_6494849ee4b08f753c2a90f0" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="dementia" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="684b1b93e4b03a16ecb33efb" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="6494849ee4b08f753c2a90f0" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt;, these are all driven in part by inflammation,” Klodas said. And we don’t want to be adding inflammation to our bodies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;For most health concerns, how much red meat you should eat varies by person.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just like other aspects of your life, what is right for you is not the same as what is right for your neighbor. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There are no hard and fast guidelines,” McKinney said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;She added that for some people — like those with iron deficiency anemia — eating red meat three times a week is suggested, but for some, that much red meat would be a major health risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Others may have hemochromatosis (a relatively common iron storage disorder) or other health condition that warrants them avoiding it completely,” McKinney said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;And people with heart disease risk factors, such as high cholesterol or high blood pressure, may want to eat less red meat than folks who don’t have those underlying conditions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“I know people like to have a hard and fast number, but it does not exist,” McKinney said. “W&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;e do not all respond to specific diet patterns in the same way, and different approaches work for different people based on a variety of factors.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you need additional guidance about red meat intake, it’s a good idea to talk to your doctor or nutritionist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“It’s appropriate for most people to include [red meat] in their weekly rotation, assuming they’re eating various foods at baseline,” McKinney noted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it’s important to limit just how much you’re eating to aid your longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In general, if you look at the dietary patterns of people who live long well ... their diets are relatively low in ... animal flesh and animal-product-derived calories,” Klodas said. “So probably a good thing to say is the less the better.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;But she noted that she doesn’t think you have to avoid hamburgers, or any red meat, altogether. “We are omnivores. We have canine teeth for a reason, right?” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Klodas said even though it varies from person to person, overall, red meat once a week at most is a good benchmark for most people. And one serving of meat is 3 ounces, according to &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/caregiver-support/what-is-a-serving" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="the American Heart Association" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="684b1b93e4b03a16ecb33efb" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/caregiver-support/what-is-a-serving" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;the American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting that &lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2021-03/Dietary_Guidelines_for_Americans-2020-2025.pdf" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="the Dietary Guidelines for Americans" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="684b1b93e4b03a16ecb33efb" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2021-03/Dietary_Guidelines_for_Americans-2020-2025.pdf" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;the Dietary Guidelines for Americans&lt;/a&gt; do not have specific red meat consumption limits but say you should choose lean meats over fatty meats and limit yourself to 26 ounces of meat, poultry and eggs each week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the guidelines say you should limit your saturated fat consumption to less than 10% of your daily calories. “The main sources of saturated fat in the U.S. diet include sandwiches, including burgers, tacos, and burritos,” the guidelines say and suggest that folks, once again, select lean meats because of their lower levels of saturated fats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Westend61 via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Westend61 via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;“It’s appropriate for most people to include [red meat] in their weekly rotation," registered dietitian Samantha McKinney said, assuming they’re eating a variety of other foods as well.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;But to reduce your cancer risk, there is a suggested red meat limit.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“According to [the] American Institute for Cancer Research (AICR), eating red meat in excess of 12 to 18 ounces per week increases the risk of colorectal cancer,” Pence stated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Keep portion sizes to about 4 to 6 ounces cooked or about the size of one or two decks of cards, and stay within that 12 to 18 ounce per week red meat limit.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;She said you can also consider other proteins for a healthier meal. &lt;span&gt;If you’re craving a burger, you can grill a portobello mushroom or a black bean burger instead of the traditional red-meat option.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, McKinney said, how you cook your red meat can affect your cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Anytime there is charring, burning or high-temperature cooking, it can form heterocyclic amines and polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons ... which are compounds that have been implicated in cancer risk,” McKinney said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are both known carcinogens, &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/profiles/details/otis-brawley" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Otis Brawley" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="684b1b93e4b03a16ecb33efb" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/profiles/details/otis-brawley" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="12"&gt;Dr. Otis Brawley&lt;/a&gt;, the associate director of community outreach and engagement at the Sidney Kimmel Comprehensive Cancer Center at Johns Hopkins Medicine, &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/cancer-doctors-food_l_64357018e4b0c2da1508a4a9" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="previously told HuffPost" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="684b1b93e4b03a16ecb33efb" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="64357018e4b0c2da1508a4a9" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="13"&gt;previously told HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Development of these compounds &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;can&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt; be mitigated and reduced ― but not eliminated,” McKinney said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;You can reduce your risk by shortening the cooking time and avoiding direct exposure of the meat to a flame or smoke, she noted. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;McKinney added that these compounds are also created when you grill and char other foods, too, like chicken and fish. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;You should think about what you eat with your burger, too.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There’s also other parts to this ... which is, OK, how are we presenting this, this burger or this meat, right?” Klodas said. “It’s also what it comes with.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, if you’re eating a 4-once lean ground beef patty over a bed of lettuce, you can eat that more frequently than a bacon double cheeseburger with fries, she noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bacon double cheeseburger with fries “should be a really rare indulgence, right? Maybe once a year. It’s kind of thinking about the entirety of what you’re eating and what you’re surrounding it with,” Klodas said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which is hard, she added. You’re probably used to eating and shopping a certain way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But you typically serve some vegetables at dinner and meat, and people talk about having meat with vegetables. And I say, OK, well, just have vegetables with meat ... just change the proportions of what’s landing on your plate,” Klodas said. “That’s a significant change because that can have a marked health impact.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“According to AICR’s New American Plate recommendations,” Pence added, “we should limit animal proteins to a third of our plate or less and make meat the side dish.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;So if you are going to have that burger at a cookout, be sure to load your plate with fresh fruit and veggies, too, and allow those items to be the stars of your plate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 11:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizgFBVV95cUxQYll2QTRWUElTNHVBV1RrSDVBVHlYOHRtbVd3OGhwSWRIUU1VLVVNY0lZbHBhb1dXLWE4S3VIbFNnVDJKSjFDYWNrX01VRmg0N19RekF3MXQ5X2kzVFVjeDQ0Tmd6WnBhX2hQbDNqX2IwTDBhb1loT2h6QklIbE13aEpHcjhRZ2tZZGdMcVBYZmZOUEdHNUhZem90SktjVFZZNHBJRElUQmV2WkcwTFRWcndYQndQUnVuY1dXTndKSEVJZW9ZTVNmaVlIbVhvQdIB0wFBVV95cUxNU2hDVjVhWGZxQWJ3U3l4dUNBQ2VsalRiVHNiYmtiRW92VHR0UlR2YjBQMVlranFUTVRyWEhRbzFQLVItUG95cEFCZWM3aFV2b24yeUlqV2NDS3Z3dDhhUTcySGVTT0F5djh2VmlTdExma3VmelNDNExHZmhtSURqX2FuS21lVTVHWVFfSjdkaVlRNDRHUUhIM1dHMDFrUE1fOGlvLTE5LTBXZTdsbmE3QTJOMnk3M0FoMndiLVBWdGh6UzJhUk42V1dJZ0xuWHQzY2Jr</guid></item><item><title>Ossett前列腺癌患者敦促男性进行检查- BBC | Ossett prostate cancer patient urges men to have checks - BBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5rb1hRWFJLbW5DNjh3bml6bV9zOTF1NV9SaUhBWEJiNmR3NVNhUWhyaGQzNHhPUF9yN2pTQ3FqTmd0NUNrY01SdjZyNksxRktkanBBSEtLZTc3QdIBX0FVX3lxTE5ULWtYOGVsZjVjQXJuYzRCNDdpN01EOXpMV1hKbHN0dzZaWXRNZE52dmJ6STI2eTRjb25IVVMwYm1URUxuQVFDYWQxajRUdE5WYmtkTi1Nd1d2LWVaMkI4?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 dfvxux"&gt;'Prostate cancer diagnosis felt like a black hole'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gyQxwn"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250611-093910-fc500e843d-web-2.23.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="PCUK A man in a black polo shirt sits in a white armchair. He has grey hair and wears a Prostate Cancer UK badge." class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;PCUK&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Danny Burkey was diagnosed with prostate cancer in 2021&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A man diagnosed with incurable prostate cancer said the news felt like falling into a "black hole", as he urged others to check for signs of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Danny Burkey, from Ossett, was diagnosed in 2021, and was told his condition was incurable after a bone scan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The 59-year-old spoke as Prostate Cancer UK launched a campaign urging men to visit their GP with prostate concerns, in the hope of an early diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Mr Burkey told BBC Radio Leeds: "You think it is always going to happen to somebody else; you just cannot believe it is you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Mr Burkey sought a diagnosis after experiencing symptoms related to prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;According to the NHS, symptoms can include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 fusmZA"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 huNRXw"&gt;Having a sudden urge to urinate &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 huNRXw"&gt;Getting up often in the night to urinate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 huNRXw"&gt;Blood in your urine&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 huNRXw"&gt;Erectile dysfunction.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"I had a blood test, an MRI and a biopsy," Mr Burkey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Recalling being told his illness was incurable, he said: "You are almost standing next to yourself thinking, I do not know what to do with this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"You just cannot process it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250611-093910-fc500e843d-web-2.23.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="PA Media A medic looks through a microscope at prostate cancer testing measures." class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;PA Media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Prostate cancer is now England's most common cancer, affecting one in eight men&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;According to Prostate Cancer UK, one in eight men will get prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;It is now England's most common cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Despite the prevalence, the charity's research suggests six in 10 men are concerned about having a Digital Rectal Exam (DRE).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Of those, over a third would not speak to a GP about prostate worries because they feared the DRE exam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Mr Burkey urged men to seek a diagnosis despite barriers, saying: "You do not need to have a DRE now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"You can ask your GP for a simple blood test and that gets the ball rolling, it is as simple as that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250611-093910-fc500e843d-web-2.23.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt='PCUK A man with grey hair and a beard stands in a garden. He wears a black polo shirt and a Prostate Cancer UK badge. He holds a card which reads: "The first test is a simple blood test you can ask your GP for."' class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;PCUK&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Doctors determined Danny Burkey's prostate cancer was incurable after a bone scan&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Earlier this week, the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.baus.org.uk/professionals/baus_business/news/289/rectal_exam_a_poor_test_for_prostate_cancer_surgeons_and_charity_agree" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;British Association of Urological Surgeons&lt;/a&gt; urged GPs to stop using the "outdated" and "inaccurate" DRE as a standard test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;They labelled it a "poor test" that deterred men from coming forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Men are encouraged to use Prostate Cancer UK's 30-second online risk checker and to talk to their GP about the prostate-specific antigen (PSA) blood test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A high level of PSA in the blood can indicate prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Research led by Prostate Cancer UK shows that the way prostate cancer is diagnosed - with a PSA blood test followed by an MRI scan - reduces potential harms to men by 79%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Among those to catch the disease early was actor Colin McFarlane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;McFarlane, who has appeared in The Dark Knight and Doctor Who, announced he had prostate cancer on the BBC Breakfast sofa in June 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He said: "I'm really lucky I caught it early, so I thought if I'm lucky and I know so much about this, I need to try and share this knowledge."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Actor Colin McFarlane announced he had prostate cancer on the BBC Breakfast sofa in June 2023&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;McFarlane's friend, theatre director Femi Elufowoju Jr said hearing his story encouraged him to get checked, which led him to also being diagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cqxenrxy3n7o" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;thanked McFarlane&lt;/a&gt; for saving his life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Despite treatment, including chemotherapy and radiotherapy, Mr Burkey's body has stopped responding to advanced hormone therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He said: "Inevitably your body becomes resistant, the cancer becomes resistant to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"You are constantly having your PSA levels monitored to see how treatments are working.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"You are constantly sort of on your toes thinking where am I up to now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"What have I still got left that can be used?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"It is a very anxious time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"I do not want another man to be in the position I am in."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dHQIrb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 10:12:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5rb1hRWFJLbW5DNjh3bml6bV9zOTF1NV9SaUhBWEJiNmR3NVNhUWhyaGQzNHhPUF9yN2pTQ3FqTmd0NUNrY01SdjZyNksxRktkanBBSEtLZTc3QdIBX0FVX3lxTE5ULWtYOGVsZjVjQXJuYzRCNDdpN01EOXpMV1hKbHN0dzZaWXRNZE52dmJ6STI2eTRjb25IVVMwYm1URUxuQVFDYWQxajRUdE5WYmtkTi1Nd1d2LWVaMkI4</guid></item><item><title>“我们不了解大量精子” ：为什么精子仍然如此神秘-英国广播公司 | 'There's a huge amount that we don't understand': Why sperm is still so mysterious - BBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxPektuVkZrZTRMWnRMSHF0UGdvNGRrUXF6OWpjeXRtNHZwUHdBMTlwVk0wY3ZfZGNDRFFZQ2RpeWlLRk1POVQtZXl0ZTdLODc5clVfWHg4N0lzcmpLRVJuZVVwbjVYbXpFME1WQzYwczd3VXJOc29SeXVKWklNUjFSQjNndldoV1pfZnhTWGhpNUpIeEw5NG5vcWduWDdTLVBfZVBz?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 dfvxux"&gt;'There's a huge amount that we don't understand': Why sperm is still so mysterious&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;&lt;b id="how-do-sperm-swim?-how-do-they-navigate?-what-is-sperm-made-of?-what-does-a-world-war-two-codebreaker-have-to-do-with-it-all?-the-bbc-untangles-why-we-know-so-little-about-this-mysterious-cell." class="sc-d16436d-0 jpoiOL"&gt;How do sperm swim? How do they navigate? What is sperm made of? What does a World War Two codebreaker have to do with it all? The BBC untangles why we know so little about this mysterious cell.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;But much about this epic journey – and the microscopic explorers themselves – remains a mystery to science. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Using newly developed methods, scientists are now following sperm on their migration – from their genesis in the testes all the way to the fertilisation of the egg in the female body. The results are leading to groundbreaking new discoveries, from how sperm really swim to the surprisingly big changes that occur to them when they reach the female body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="quote-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-2b8ea91d-0 bgzaEJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-2b8ea91d-2 dYxeIv"&gt;No other cell within the body changes its structure, its shape, in such a unique way – Adam Watkins&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"Sperm – or spermatozoa – are 'very, very different' from all other cells on Earth," says Martins da Silva. "They don't &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35680646/%2525252523:~:text=The%252525252520two%252525252520main%252525252520ATP-producing,-called%252525252520sperm%252525252520energy%252525252520debate)." class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;handle energy&lt;/a&gt; in the same way. They don't have the same sort of cellular metabolism and mechanisms that we would expect to find in all other cells."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Sperm are also the only human cells which can survive outside the body, Martins da Silva adds. "For that reason, they are extraordinarily specialised." However, due to their size these tiny cells are very difficult to study, she says. "There's a lot we know about reproduction – but there's a huge amount that we don't understand."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250611-093910-fc500e843d-web-2.23.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/160xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 160w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/240xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/320xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/640xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/800xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1024xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1376xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 1376w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1920xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 1920w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Alamy Despite being the smallest cell in the human body, sperm are extraordinarily specialised (Credit: Alamy)" class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Alamy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Despite being the smallest cell in the human body, sperm are extraordinarily specialised (Credit: Alamy)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;One fundamental question that remained unanswered over almost 350 years of research: what exactly are sperm?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"The sperm is incredibly well-packaged," says Adam Watkins, associate professor in reproductive and developmental physiology at Nottingham University in the UK. "We typically thought of the sperm as a bag of DNA on a tail. But as we've started to realise, it's quite a complex cell – there's a lot of &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3015006/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;[other] genetic information in there&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Almost 200 years later, in 1869, Johannes Friedrich Miescher, a Swiss physician and biologist, was studying human white blood cells collected from pus left on soiled hospital bandages when he &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7268995/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;discovered what he called "nuclein"&lt;/a&gt; inside the nuclei. The term "nuclein" was later changed to "nucleic acid" and eventually became "deoxyribonucleic acid" – or "DNA". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Since then, our understanding of sperm has moved on leaps and bounds. But &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.3000953" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;much still remains a mystery&lt;/a&gt;, says Watkins. As scientists have started to better understand early embryonic development, he adds, they are realising that sperm doesn't just pass the father's chromosomes on, but also &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://clinicalepigeneticsjournal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s13148-025-01815-1" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;epigenetic information&lt;/a&gt;, an extra layer of information that affects how and when the genes should be used. "It can really influence how the embryo develops and potentially the lifelong trajectory of the offspring that those sperm generate," says Watkins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="quote-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-2b8ea91d-0 bgzaEJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-2b8ea91d-2 dYxeIv"&gt;It turns out that what's driving the system is female evolution – and males are just trying to keep up – Scott Pitnick&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Sperm cells begin to form from puberty onwards, made in vessels within the testicles called seminiferous tubules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"If you look inside the testes where the sperm are made, it starts as just a round cell that looks pretty much like anything else," says Watkins. "Then it undergoes this dramatic change where it becomes a sperm head with a tail. No other cell within the body changes its structure, its shape, in such a unique way."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;After ejaculation, each of these tiny cells must propel themselves forward (alongside their 50 million competitors) using their tail-like appendages to swim for the egg. And while you may have seen plenty of videos of tadpole-like sperm swimming around, in fact scientists are only just beginning to understand how sperm really swim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250611-093910-fc500e843d-web-2.23.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/160xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 160w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/240xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/320xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/640xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/800xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1024xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1376xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 1376w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1920xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 1920w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Alamy 17th-Century Dutch microbiologist Antoni van Leeuwenhoek believed a tiny but complete human existed within spermatozoa (Credit: Alamy)" class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Alamy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;17th-Century Dutch microbiologist Antoni van Leeuwenhoek believed a tiny but complete human existed within spermatozoa (Credit: Alamy)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="quote-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-2b8ea91d-0 bgzaEJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-2b8ea91d-2 dYxeIv"&gt;Some fruit fly species produce sperm cells 20 times their own body length. That would be like a man producing sperm the length of a 40m (130ft) python&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Spermatozoa which are healthy and take the right route are rare. &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.open.edu/openlearn/nature-environment/natural-history/sperm-counts" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;Many take a wrong turn&lt;/a&gt; in the maze that is the female body – and never even make it near the goal line. For the ones that do find their way to the fallopian tubes, scientists think that they may be &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/16272225/%2525252523:~:text=A%252525252520few%252525252520thousand%252525252520sperm%252525252520swim,with%252525252520endosalpingeal%252525252520(oviductal)%252525252520epithelium." class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;guided by chemical signals&lt;/a&gt; emitted by the egg. One recent theory is that sperm may use taste receptors to "&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://mdpi.com/1422-0067/20/4/967" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;taste&lt;/a&gt;" their way to the egg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Once the sperm find the egg, the challenge is not over. The egg is surrounded by a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/16272225/%2525252523:~:text=A%252525252520few%252525252520thousand%252525252520sperm%252525252520swim,with%252525252520endosalpingeal%252525252520(oviductal)%252525252520epithelium." class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;triplicate coat of armour&lt;/a&gt;: the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.britannica.com/science/fertilization-reproduction%23ref606596" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;corona radiata&lt;/a&gt;, an array of cells; the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8789258/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;zona pellucida&lt;/a&gt;, a jelly-like cushion made of protein; and finally the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s13669-013-0059-2%23:~:text=When%2520the%2520first%2520sperm%2520enters%2520the%2520egg,,has%2520not%2520been%2520well%2520studied%2520in%2520humans." class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;egg plasma membrane&lt;/a&gt;. The sperm cells have to fight their way through all the layers, using chemicals contained in their &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3271650/%2525252523:~:text=The%252525252520acrosome%252525252520is%252525252520a%252525252520unique,sperm%252525252520penetrate%252525252520the%252525252520egg's%252525252520coats." class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;acrosome&lt;/a&gt;, a cap-like structure on the head of a sperm cell containing enzymes that digest the egg cell coating. However, what prompts the release of these enzymes &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/endocrinology/articles/10.3389/fendo.2023.1273878/epub" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;remains a mystery&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.genome.gov/genetics-glossary/Diploid" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;Human cells are diploid&lt;/a&gt;. This means they contain two complete sets of chromosomes, one from each parent. If more than one sperm were to fuse with the egg, a condition called &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK26843/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;polyspermy&lt;/a&gt; would arise. Nondiploid cells – ones with the incorrect number of chromosomes – would develop, a condition lethal to a growing embryo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;To prevent this from happening, once a sperm cell has made contact with it, the egg quickly employs two mechanisms. First, its plasma membrane rapidly depolarises – meaning it creates &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.carlsonscience.com/fast-block" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;an electrical barrier&lt;/a&gt; that further sperm cannot cross. However, this only lasts a short time before returning to normal. This is where the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK26843/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;cortical reaction&lt;/a&gt; comes in. A sudden release of calcium causes the zona pellucida – the egg's "&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2528931/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;extracellular coat&lt;/a&gt;" – to become hardened, creating an impenetrable barrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;What external factors affect male fertility and why.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;One way researchers are hoping to shed light on sperm is by &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nature18005" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;studying species other than our own&lt;/a&gt;, says Scott Pitnick, a professor of biology at Syracuse University in New York. Human sperm cells are microscopic, so we can't see them with the naked eye. But some fruit fly species produce sperm cells &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nature18005" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;20 times their own body length&lt;/a&gt;. That would be like a man producing sperm the length of a 40m (130ft) python.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"Why do males in some species make a few giant sperm?" asks Pitnick. "The answer, it turns out, is because females have evolved reproductive tracts that favour them." That's "not really much of an answer", he adds, because it's just the redirects the question: why have females evolved this way? "We still don't understand that at all."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="quote-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-2b8ea91d-0 bgzaEJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-2b8ea91d-2 dYxeIv"&gt;Research suggests sperm counts are tumbling globally and the decline appears to be accelerating&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;But it does teach us that sperm as they exist in the male body is only half the story, says Pitnick. "There's a massive sex bias historically in science. There's been this obscenely biased male focus on male traits. But it turns out that what's driving the system is female evolution – and males are just trying to keep up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"It turns out the female reproductive tract is this incredibly, rapidly evolving environment," says Pitnick, "and we don't know much about what sperm do inside the female. That is the big, hidden world. I think the female reproductive tract is the greatest unexplored frontier for sexual selection, theory and speciation [the process by which &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nature.com/scitable/knowledge/library/speciation-the-origin-of-new-species-26230527/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;new species are formed&lt;/a&gt;]."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The fruit fly's long-tailed sperm, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41559-024-02587-2" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;suggests Pitnick&lt;/a&gt;, could be considered an ornament – much like a deer's antlers or a peacock's tail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Ornaments are a "sort of a weapon in evolution", explains Pitnick. More than just a defence from predators, ornaments like antlers and horns often have two roles to play. "A lot of these weapons are about sex, and usually male-male competition. The [fruit fly's] long sperm flagellum really meets the definitional criteria of an ornament. We think the female tract has traits that bias fertilisation in favour of some sperm phenotypes over others."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;We know a lot about pre-mating sexual selection, Pitnick says. "Say, it's &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/future/article/20240902-how-controlled-burns-can-help-wildlife" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;prairie chickens dancing&lt;/a&gt; out on a grassland, or a &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p023wbh0" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;bird of paradise displaying&lt;/a&gt; in a rainforest. It's motion, it's colour, it's smells?" Processing this sensory input, explains Pitnick, leads to decision making – whether the pair mate or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;But, Pitnick says, the sexual selection that goes on inside the female after mating – and how this drives the evolution of sperm – largely remains a mystery. "We still understand very little about the genetics of ornaments and preferences," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250611-093910-fc500e843d-web-2.23.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/160xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 160w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/240xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/320xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/640xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/800xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1024xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1376xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 1376w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1920xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 1920w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Alamy Sperm are so tiny that they can be difficult to study. Samples can be stained to make them easier to see under a microscope (Credit: Alamy)" class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Alamy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Sperm are so tiny that they can be difficult to study. Samples can be stained to make them easier to see under a microscope (Credit: Alamy)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;To fully understand sperm, we need to think about how the entire lifecycle of the sperm – and the female body, explains Pitnick, plays a huge role in the sperm's development. "Sperm are not mature when they finish developing in the testes, they're not done developing." Complex – and critical – interactions occur between the sperm and the female reproductive tract, he says. "We're now spending a lot of time studying what we call &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://experts.syr.edu/en/publications/post-ejaculatory-modifications-to-sperm-pems" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;post-ejaculatory modifications to sperm&lt;/a&gt; across the whole animal kingdom." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;According to a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/978920068315" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;2023 report&lt;/a&gt; published by the World Health Organisation (WHO), around one in six adults worldwide experience infertility – and male infertility contributes to roughly &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/future/article/20230327-how-pollution-is-causing-a-male-fertility-crisis" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;half of all cases&lt;/a&gt;. (It's also worth noting that many people around the world are not having as many children as they want for other reasons too, such as the prohibitive cost of parenthood, as a &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/clynq459wxgo" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;recent United Nation population Fund report highlighted&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"With all those moving parts, there are so many things that could go wrong," says Hannah Morgan, a post-doctoral research associate in maternal and fetal health at the University of Manchester, UK. "It could be a mechanism: it doesn't swim very well, so it can't get to the egg. Or it could be something more intricate within the head of the sperm, or other regions of the sperm. It's so specialised in so many different ways, that lots of little things can go wrong."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;One way to see if a man may be infertile is to look inside the sperm, says Morgan. "How does the DNA look? How is it packaged? How fragmented is it? To break open the sperm, there's a whole range of stuff you could look at. But what is a good or bad measurement? We don't actually know." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Perhaps by unravelling the mystery of sperm and how they function, Morgan says, we might begin to understand male infertility too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;&lt;i id="for-more-science,-technology,-environment-and-health-stories-from-the-bbc,-follow-us-on" class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt;For more science, technology, environment and health stories from the BBC, follow us on &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/BBCFuture/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;&lt;i id="facebook" class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt;Facebook&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="," class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt;, &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://x.com/BBC_Future" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;&lt;i id="x" class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt;X&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="and" class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt; and &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.instagram.com/bbcfuture_official/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;&lt;i id="instagram" class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt;Instagram&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="." class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt;&lt;b id="." class="sc-d16436d-0 jpoiOL"&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i id="" class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:01:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPektuVkZrZTRMWnRMSHF0UGdvNGRrUXF6OWpjeXRtNHZwUHdBMTlwVk0wY3ZfZGNDRFFZQ2RpeWlLRk1POVQtZXl0ZTdLODc5clVfWHg4N0lzcmpLRVJuZVVwbjVYbXpFME1WQzYwczd3VXJOc29SeXVKWklNUjFSQjNndldoV1pfZnhTWGhpNUpIeEw5NG5vcWduWDdTLVBfZVBz</guid></item><item><title>处理背部痤疮的8个护肤技巧-印度时报 | 8 skincare hacks to deal with back acne - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiygFBVV95cUxPUk12MnYyN0w3SGZ5RlJYeVVhM0RCMm5lYVhtakpyZlp2SmFLWUdGUEdlblRkS1p6bmZRS0hyOHc2QXA5TEltNnExQl9hS2ZnSE5lSjZUZkJ2WWJScmVKQWN3ZXUyNlE4RmhMTzY4aWRjNVdadWxUbUlpYjk1S1A0Sjl0RlhzZ1pzcFdEcEppb3BBNnRBRFpwRDM5bUdtZTJnWlVXZjdwQzRFcG9UZnFGUHB3VnhkemdyWGhXMHpRaFNTTUtyRDB5YW1R0gHKAUFVX3lxTE9STXYydjI3TDdIZnlGUlh5VWEzREIybmVhWG1qSnJmWnZKYUtZR0ZQR2VuVGRLWnpuZlFLSHI4dzZBcDlMSW02cTFCX2FLZmdITmVKNlRmQnZZYlJyZUpBY3dldTI2UThGaExPNjhpZGM1V1p1bFRtSWliOTVLUDRKOXRGWHNnWnNwV0RwSmlvcEE2dEFEWnBEMzltR21lMmdaVVdmN3BDNEVwb1RmcUZQcHdWeGR6Z3JYaFcwelFoU1NNS3JEMHlhbVE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;amp-story-grid-layer class="recircular" id="rcontent" template="vertical"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt;&lt;p class="mid-heading"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;You may also like&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc3 pa"&gt;Deepika Padukone to Shraddha Kapoor: Ski...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc5 pa"&gt;Celebrity-approved makeup looks to try t...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiygFBVV95cUxPUk12MnYyN0w3SGZ5RlJYeVVhM0RCMm5lYVhtakpyZlp2SmFLWUdGUEdlblRkS1p6bmZRS0hyOHc2QXA5TEltNnExQl9hS2ZnSE5lSjZUZkJ2WWJScmVKQWN3ZXUyNlE4RmhMTzY4aWRjNVdadWxUbUlpYjk1S1A0Sjl0RlhzZ1pzcFdEcEppb3BBNnRBRFpwRDM5bUdtZTJnWlVXZjdwQzRFcG9UZnFGUHB3VnhkemdyWGhXMHpRaFNTTUtyRDB5YW1R0gHKAUFVX3lxTE9STXYydjI3TDdIZnlGUlh5VWEzREIybmVhWG1qSnJmWnZKYUtZR0ZQR2VuVGRLWnpuZlFLSHI4dzZBcDlMSW02cTFCX2FLZmdITmVKNlRmQnZZYlJyZUpBY3dldTI2UThGaExPNjhpZGM1V1p1bFRtSWliOTVLUDRKOXRGWHNnWnNwV0RwSmlvcEE2dEFEWnBEMzltR21lMmdaVVdmN3BDNEVwb1RmcUZQcHdWeGR6Z3JYaFcwelFoU1NNS3JEMHlhbVE</guid></item><item><title>肠道问题、糖尿病或高血压？抛弃这些水果-印度时报 | Gut issues, Diabetes or High BP? Ditch these fruits - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi4wFBVV95cUxONDhfVHc1a3dwZ0M5amFUbTkwdDRuZ25ic3hpWmVBbG1xc2ZYMVNDNUUzWFRYUEdxYnRZdFJuTGRpS1JTTUlzc1FuZ3VFa2FFSHdoNEFobnZJVjZUMDVKelhZbUZoUXFSczZmTEVTdm14Zjdpdm8zOWh5cTVtLU9FNVplY2VDZEVyTjZpeXB6SFBVSy1xMW5tbG9vaTM1NWN3Mng3QThrc3UxcTdybFBXWTZheUlWWk1ydDRiak5TN3NHd01OeF9RQ2lEc2NyWDRKeXZLR3Z5UmUyblc2NUl1eWFESQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fruits are sometimes regarded as the ultimate health food, full of vitamins, fiber, and natural sugars, and our dearest friends. Most of the times, that is largely the case, but some fruits can actually increase certain medical conditions because of their sugar content, acidity, or nutrient burden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowing what to steer clear of can assist you in controlling symptoms better and with more informed decisions. Below is a guide to which fruits may not be your friend if you have any of the following conditions. (source: Healthline)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Diabetes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have diabetes, blood glucose control is paramount. Fruits such as bananas and grapes can be harmful; they contain a high glycemic wallop. Their natural sugars are rapidly absorbed and will give your glucose levels a boost. You don't have to eliminate all fruits, but it's advisable to stick to lower-sugar choices such as berries and steer clear of overly ripe types altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Kidney issues&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those with compromised kidney function, potassium can build up to dangerous levels. Bananas and oranges are particularly high in potassium, which can strain the kidneys. It’s best to limit or avoid these fruits if your doctor has warned you about high potassium intake. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alternatives like apples or grapes are typically better tolerated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Joint Pain or inflammatory conditions&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have arthritis or chronic joint inflammation, some of the fruits in the nightshade category, such as tomatoes and eggplants, trigger inflammation. While technically fruits, these may be included in main courses rather than desserts. Many people experience flare-ups if they eat them regularly, so an elimination trial could identify whether they're a trigger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Bloating and gas&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apples, watermelon, and cherries are gut fermenters. If you have issues with bloating or discomfort in the digestive system, these FODMAP-rich fruits may be the offender. Limiting the amount or cooking them lightly might help alleviate symptoms. Watch how your body reacts, particularly if your digestive system is already sensitive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Skin issues&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skin conditions such as acne, eczema, or psoriasis can be exacerbated by some tropical fruits. Mangoes, pineapples, and oranges are high in substances that could possibly cause inflammation or allergic responses in sensitive patients. If your flare-ups occur around fruit-laden meals, try reducing to observe if your skin improves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Heart disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fatty or sugary fruits such as coconut and dried fruits are problematic for individuals with heart ailments. Dried fruits might be a healthy choice for snacks, but they tend to be calorie-rich and sugary. Coconut has been known to have saturated fat that might increase cholesterol levels. Be moderate about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Stomach sensitivity&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have acid reflux or a sensitive stomach lining, pineapples and citrus fruits can irritate your system. Their acidity level is extremely high, causing discomfort or aggravating gastritis. If you suffer from digestive flare-ups, go for less acidic fruits such as bananas or melons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Low immunity&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Individuals with compromised immune systems need to exercise care with overripe or dried fruits. They may contain molds or provide a source of food for toxic gut bacteria, resulting in infections or imbalances. Fresh, well-washed fruits are always the best option, and anything which appears excessively soft or fermented or has been stored for long periods should be avoided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;High cholesterol and migraine&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coconut, dried fruits, and citrus could aggravate both. Coconut's saturated fat and dried fruits' concentrated sugars can lead to increased cholesterol. Citrus, on the other hand, has been reported to induce migraines in others. If you're susceptible to either, staying vigilant about your consumption can spell a difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fruits are usually a foundation of healthy eating, but when you have a chronic illness, it's all about personalization. It's not about vilifying any single fruit it's about making wiser, more individualised decisions for your body. Always speak with your doctor or a registered dietitian before removing foods from your diet, but being aware of these associations can make you feel more in charge of your health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4wFBVV95cUxONDhfVHc1a3dwZ0M5amFUbTkwdDRuZ25ic3hpWmVBbG1xc2ZYMVNDNUUzWFRYUEdxYnRZdFJuTGRpS1JTTUlzc1FuZ3VFa2FFSHdoNEFobnZJVjZUMDVKelhZbUZoUXFSczZmTEVTdm14Zjdpdm8zOWh5cTVtLU9FNVplY2VDZEVyTjZpeXB6SFBVSy1xMW5tbG9vaTM1NWN3Mng3QThrc3UxcTdybFBXWTZheUlWWk1ydDRiak5TN3NHd01OeF9RQ2lEc2NyWDRKeXZLR3Z5UmUyblc2NUl1eWFESQ</guid></item><item><title>甜点中令人惊讶的成分会增加心脏病发作的风险-每日邮报 | Surprising ingredient in dessert favorites that raises your risk of a heart attack - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivgFBVV95cUxNSWNYUzV1cy1yOWpJNF9sc1o4NDZIay1hVHp6d3pYQy0yd2lHTmdIZXhMdC04RlRRZk1zdjJ3YnR6WWJwbHA4SThtaGFBUVF2Z0VIWUE0UHgyUndTWWtBSGxrcFRmMFhYSXc4cGg1ZVRQYVBEMlZFekVybE00WFdjTXVaSmtGQlM5UjY1V254SkQyblZaWlBIaG1tNzZ3VXM1VUplOEc4VU11SUVEVHd1czdiRnRYMWYxcmlDU0VB0gHDAUFVX3lxTE1aTTA3b0hFTXlkWU02Qi1zU2h4aTBzNXlNSzQ0OFJ0Vmw0OTVBM0NheGZYOGRKTExrbXkwR2ZIUzEzVTVmeVpUNmVCSWNLQVRGa0pqdXpJTmFrZE9OblFRTDRlWVZ2b0pmS3V2S1NrWkxtdHB0WjJQM2k0ZG8yUmVMSzdGdTZ5WHdxazR6R0xtRzhDdnFDcDhDd29wanBBZDF0SFBtMy1pdllnZmp2b3lzZWpyTWkxMzdFODFyRVlGbzRDcw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cardiologists are warning of an often overlooked ingredient in desserts that can lead to high blood pressure if consumed in excess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Typically a garnish on cookies, bread and butter, soft pretzels, and caramel treats, coarse sea salt contains more sodium than its less expensive grocery store alternative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;People enjoy the added crunch and marriage of savory and sweet in desserts, but people are inadvertently eating too much salt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Because coarse salt has larger crystals, it may feel less salty per bite, leading some people to use more than they would with fine salt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Excessive sodium intake is linked to high blood pressure, heart disease, stroke, and kidney problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The body &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14603535/Adding-salt-food-increase-risk-depression-anxiety-40-cent-study-finds.html"&gt;only needs a small amount&lt;/a&gt; of sodium to function properly. Sodium is an essential electrolyte that plays several critical roles in the body, including maintaining fluid balance and blood pressure, supporting nerve function, and enabling muscle contractions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Most Americans &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/news/article-2130801/Sodium-content-fast-food-varies-country--And-U-S-saltiest.html"&gt;consume too much sodium&lt;/a&gt;, though – 3,300 mg per day on average, or about 40 percent more than the recommended 2,300mg limit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;People tend to believe that coarse sea salt contains less sodium than standard fine salt, yet both contain about 40 percent sodium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Typically a garnish on cookies, bread and butter, soft pretzels, and caramel treats, coarse sea salt contains more sodium than its less expensive grocery store alternative&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Salt lurks everywhere in the Western diet, not just in processed meats, snack foods, but in unsuspecting foods, including breads, canned soups, frozen meals, cheese, sauces, and marinades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;An estimated 89 percent of adults and around 94 percent of children consume too much sodium, &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/article-11950525/Youve-heard-artificial-sweeteners-ready-artificial-salt.html"&gt;according to the CDC&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Eating too much salt is a major setup for high blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The World Health Organization also estimates that 1.9 million deaths globally each year can be attributed to eating too much salt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As sodium causes the body to retain fluids, blood volume and pressure on artery walls increase. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;High blood pressure is a significant risk factor for heart disease, stroke, kidney disease, and other serious health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Brent Egan, an internist and vice president of cardiovascular health at the American Medical Association, &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.ama-assn.org/delivering-care/public-health/what-doctors-wish-patients-knew-about-sodium-consumption"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;: ‘It would take us about a little over 1,000 milligrams a day to get from where we are to where the recommendation would be for the upper limit.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;“And if we did that, we’d probably see a significant reduction in blood pressure, heart attack and stroke.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Americans consume up to 45 percent more sodium per day than the recommended limit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above graph shows the change in hypertension prevalence among all American adults, as well as among men and women from 1999 to 2023&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Roughly 116 million Americans &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/article-5947119/More-1-3-MILLION-American-teenagers-hypertension-CDC-report-reveals.html"&gt;have high blood pressure.&lt;/a&gt; Approximately 805,000 heart attacks occur each year, as well as 795,000 strokes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘If someone has high blood pressure, heart disease, that type of thing, 1,500 milligrams is probably a better target, but for the general population that’s really interested in limiting the burden of chronic disease, 2,300 milligrams is generally what is recommended,’ Dr Egan said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Too much sodium also causes bloating – the uncomfortable feeling that the stomach is swollen and tight. &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Body parts like hands, feet, and ankles are likely to swell. And feelings of thirst take over due to dehydration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Too much salt before bed can also cause restless sleep. Studies suggest high-salt diets may alter cortisol (stress hormone) levels, which regulate sleep-wake cycles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/article-12737661/Reducing-salt-one-teaspoon-blood-pressure-medication.html" class=""&gt;recent study&lt;/a&gt; by researchers at Vanderbilt University found that reducing daily salt intake by just one teaspoon is as effective as blood pressure medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They tested high and low-salt diets on hundreds of patients, some of whom had high blood pressure, and found that cutting out a can of Heinz soup each day lowered people's blood pressure by six percent within a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This reduction was comparable to that of thiazide diuretic hydrochlorothiazide, a popular blood pressure medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;An estimated 89 percent of adults and around 94 percent of children consume too much sodium, according to the CDC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;“Obviously we need some sodium—it's essential for life,” Dr Egan said. But ‘here we are with an average intake of 3,400 milligrams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Now the body has to make a lot of adjustments, but we can get by with very little sodium,’ he said, noting ‘there's very little danger in this country that most people won't get enough sodium, even if they're eating those fresh foods and not processed foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘They'll still—for the most part—get more than sufficient sodium that the body needs,” said Dr. Egan. “We live in a state of pretty much constant excess.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 05:03:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxNSWNYUzV1cy1yOWpJNF9sc1o4NDZIay1hVHp6d3pYQy0yd2lHTmdIZXhMdC04RlRRZk1zdjJ3YnR6WWJwbHA4SThtaGFBUVF2Z0VIWUE0UHgyUndTWWtBSGxrcFRmMFhYSXc4cGg1ZVRQYVBEMlZFekVybE00WFdjTXVaSmtGQlM5UjY1V254SkQyblZaWlBIaG1tNzZ3VXM1VUplOEc4VU11SUVEVHd1czdiRnRYMWYxcmlDU0VB0gHDAUFVX3lxTE1aTTA3b0hFTXlkWU02Qi1zU2h4aTBzNXlNSzQ0OFJ0Vmw0OTVBM0NheGZYOGRKTExrbXkwR2ZIUzEzVTVmeVpUNmVCSWNLQVRGa0pqdXpJTmFrZE9OblFRTDRlWVZ2b0pmS3V2S1NrWkxtdHB0WjJQM2k0ZG8yUmVMSzdGdTZ5WHdxazR6R0xtRzhDdnFDcDhDd29wanBBZDF0SFBtMy1pdllnZmp2b3lzZWpyTWkxMzdFODFyRVlGbzRDcw</guid></item><item><title>对堆肥中腐烂肺部并导致死亡的隐患发出警告- The Mirror | Warning over hidden danger in compost that rots lungs and kills - The Mirror</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihwFBVV95cUxNTExPOXBwamNMSEJKM1daSG9YeER6dlRyU0lEcWp3R0FQaTczN1dWVk1Hem40SnN1eXhYdFhjcU8zWXQxSnNHaG9GNWtsVTI2ZkVLNTJKR0lySlZqVG90dEFXMDdFczB3bmJtQy1rTkFJeHJ4dmczWFo5Z2tpSmFvYkU3UG5WYU3SAYwBQVVfeXFMTjJxdXAyQ1V2R0NWa0ZXSWlfbUNBNlBqRzY4R2Y1TVJLSFJHcFFlTUpBWVNkOXl4YXdVcjFWMXppOGN6UmFNRnZiazI0cFJZY2twYlpDbkswbDZPcFRrUHhUelp6VzRsRnNRVFVlRVpTekxURXcyYUFGbGdUMl9iVUwwTEdWeG9ZMFZOZTg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="article-body" class="ArticleBody_article__AwrJE" data-testid="body"&gt;&lt;h1 class="HeadingOne_heading-one__mmNWJ  __className_09f1df"&gt;Warning over hidden danger in compost that rots lungs and kills&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 class="LeadText_lead-text__wd_PA __className_d2008b" data-testid="leadtext"&gt;A fungus that thrives in compost is posing an increasing threat to human health because of climate change, experts have warned, and it can rapidly adapt, becoming resistant to drugs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX ImageEmbed_image-lead__Ti3qQ" data-testid="leadimage"&gt;&lt;figure class="Figure_figure__Uce4f"&gt;&lt;img src="https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368841.ece/ALTERNATES/s615/0_Man-showing-compost.jpg" alt="man holding compost" loading="eager" srcset="https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368841.ece/ALTERNATES/s508/0_Man-showing-compost.jpg 508w, https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368841.ece/ALTERNATES/s615/0_Man-showing-compost.jpg 615w,
          https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368841.ece/ALTERNATES/s1023/0_Man-showing-compost.jpg 1023w" sizes="(max-width: 508px) 508px, (max-width: 615px) 615px, 1023px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Prolific fungus that thrives in compost heaps might increasingly be a threat to human health&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;Experts have warned that a commonplace fungus could begin to pose a massive threat to human &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/health/" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; as the &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/climate-change" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;climate crisis&lt;/a&gt; progresses. Aspergillus fumigatus is present in the air and soil, and in damp and warm places like compost heaps absolutely thrives - and it can cause serious and long-lasting health problems in some people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BoxStyles_box-container__Qk3WH BoxStyles_commercial__Wo6Z4" data-testid="commercial-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;This includes chronic lung infections that sometimes must be medicated for a lifetime, and can even be fatal. Currently, around 4000 people each year in the UK suffer from the most severe form of the infection - invasive aspergillosis - which can be deadly. Experts say the mortality rate can be up to 85 percent, even when treated with powerful antifungal medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;Those who have weakened immune systems are currently the most vulnerable to fungal infections like this - but climate change could mean that even healthy people come under threat, as mutations of the fungi make them even more infectious and resistant to medicines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX false" data-testid="imageembed-35368733"&gt;&lt;figure class="Figure_figure__Uce4f"&gt;&lt;img src="https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368733.ece/ALTERNATES/s615b/0_Aspergillus-fumigatus-fungus-illustration.jpg" alt="Aspergillus fumigatus" loading="lazy" srcset="https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368733.ece/ALTERNATES/s458b/0_Aspergillus-fumigatus-fungus-illustration.jpg 458w, https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368733.ece/ALTERNATES/s615b/0_Aspergillus-fumigatus-fungus-illustration.jpg 615w,
          https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368733.ece/ALTERNATES/s1200e/0_Aspergillus-fumigatus-fungus-illustration.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 458px) 458px, (max-width: 615px) 615px, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Aspergillus fumigatus might become a threat to human health due to rising temperatures&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: Getty Images/Science Photo Library RF)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="BoxStyles_box-container__Qk3WH BoxStyles_non-commercial__aiWwo" data-testid="recommended-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;Higher temperatures across Europe caused by the climate emergency are already causing increased spread and growth of aspergillosis. This could create "significant public health concerns," according to a new &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://research.manchester.ac.uk/en/publications/climate-change-shifting-boundaries-of-fungal-disease-in-europe-an" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;study published last month&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;The ability of fungi to adapt easily and quickly is a key component in what makes it such a threat. According to the report, "rising temperatures, changing precipitation patterns, and extreme &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/weather" target="" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;weather&lt;/a&gt; events are thought to be driving the adaptation of fungal pathogens to new climates, expanding their geographical range and posing a growing threat to human health and agriculture."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BoxStyles_box-container__Qk3WH BoxStyles_non-commercial__aiWwo" data-testid="non-commercial-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;Despite the growing concerns from researchers, chronic fungal infections like aspergillus bronchitis are often misdiagnosed, leading to delays in treatment. Viv Goosens, Research Manager at Wellcome Trust, explained to The &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk" target="" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;Mirror&lt;/a&gt;, that this is due to a "combination of factors".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;"Firstly, aspergillus bronchitis can be easily misdiagnosed for more common respiratory diseases or allergic reactions due to the similarity of symptoms. Secondly, fungal infections aren't usually the first thing doctors think of—especially in people with healthy immune systems—so the diagnosis can be delayed. And even when it's suspected, confirming it isn’t straightforward. It requires a specialised test that isn’t always easy to access."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX false" data-testid="imageembed-35368737"&gt;&lt;figure class="Figure_figure__Uce4f"&gt;&lt;img src="https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368737.ece/ALTERNATES/s615b/0_Doctor-examining-elderly-patients-back-with-stethoscope-in-hospital-ward.jpg" alt="man being treated by doctor" loading="lazy" srcset="https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368737.ece/ALTERNATES/s458b/0_Doctor-examining-elderly-patients-back-with-stethoscope-in-hospital-ward.jpg 458w, https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368737.ece/ALTERNATES/s615b/0_Doctor-examining-elderly-patients-back-with-stethoscope-in-hospital-ward.jpg 615w,
          https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368737.ece/ALTERNATES/s1200e/0_Doctor-examining-elderly-patients-back-with-stethoscope-in-hospital-ward.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 458px) 458px, (max-width: 615px) 615px, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Chronic fungal infections in the lung can be hard to diagnose (Stock Image)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;For 14 years, mum-of-two Lisa McNeil, 54, battled chronic chest infections, with her doctors none the wiser about why no treatment was working.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;In 1998, a year after having her first &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/child" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;child&lt;/a&gt; - and suffering a lung injury whilst pregnant - Lisa's &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/health/" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; difficulties began, and after enduring a repeated cycle of being &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/hospitals" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;hospitalised&lt;/a&gt; for chest infections, she was eventually diagnosed with a condition called bronchiectasis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;This occurs when the bronchi in the lungs - the small airways - get too wide, which leads to an excess of mucus and makes someone more susceptible to infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;However, it would be over a decade until her medical team realised that Lisa had in fact not been battling bacterial infections all this time. Instead, her lungs were home to a fungus called aspergillus fumigatus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;Since 2011, Lisa has been taking a series of intense antifungal medications in an attempt to treat her chronic fungal infection - including one that is so poisonous, that she can only take it whilst in a room by herself, that is properly ventilated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;The medications have had varying degrees of success, Lisa explained to the &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-14773177/compost-heap-hide-lethal-superfungus-destroys-lungs-kills-85-percent-infected-Doctors-warn-threat.html" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;Daily Mail.&lt;/a&gt; She was first put on voriconazole, which stops the fungus from growing by attacking the cells, but she experienced intense visual side effects, and it didn't work for her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;Her medical team at the National Aspergillosis Centre in &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/manchester" target="" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;Manchester&lt;/a&gt; then tried her on amphotericin B, which each day she had to use a device to inhale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;"Only one in five patients can tolerate it,' she told the publication. "It gives you a &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/lifestyle/health/how-rid-sore-throat-quickly-9585923" target="" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;sore throat&lt;/a&gt; and nausea for about an hour after taking it. Because of the toxicity, you have to be on your own in a room with an open window, and no one can enter the room for 30 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX false" data-testid="imageembed-35368743"&gt;&lt;figure class="Figure_figure__Uce4f"&gt;&lt;img src="https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368743.ece/ALTERNATES/s615b/0_Medical-Treatment-for-Breathing-Issues-Child-Wearing-Nebulizer-Mask.jpg" alt="child uses nebulizer" loading="lazy" srcset="https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368743.ece/ALTERNATES/s458b/0_Medical-Treatment-for-Breathing-Issues-Child-Wearing-Nebulizer-Mask.jpg 458w, https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368743.ece/ALTERNATES/s615b/0_Medical-Treatment-for-Breathing-Issues-Child-Wearing-Nebulizer-Mask.jpg 615w,
          https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368743.ece/ALTERNATES/s1200e/0_Medical-Treatment-for-Breathing-Issues-Child-Wearing-Nebulizer-Mask.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 458px) 458px, (max-width: 615px) 615px, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;One antifungal medication has to be taken through a nebulizer in an empty room because it is so toxic (Stock Image)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;"Despite all that, it was brilliant. The drug made such a difference for my health and energy levels. Even my constant cough went away."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;However, the drug is too toxic for patients to take for an extended period, so after three years she had to stop to avoid dangerous complications like damage to her kidneys and anaemia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;At the moment, Lisa is taking the antifungal medication itraconazole, and has recently suffered from bouts of ill health after picking up bacterial infections alongside her aspergillus bronchitis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;Experts have warned that due to the &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/climate-change" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;climate crisis&lt;/a&gt;, stories like Lisa's may become even more common because Aspergillus fumigatus is prolific.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;One of the study's authors, Dr Norman Van Rhijn, explained to the Mail that the UK already has higher levels of aspergillosis in places like compost heaps and bags and that when the compost is moved it is able to move easily through the air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;Viv Goosens explains that "Aspergillus spores are everywhere in the environment but typically don't cause infection," adding that this is because "a healthy immune system can fend off infections effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX false" data-testid="imageembed-35368754"&gt;&lt;figure class="Figure_figure__Uce4f"&gt;&lt;img src="https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368754.ece/ALTERNATES/s615b/0_Soil-with-a-garden-trowel.jpg" alt="digging in soil" loading="lazy" srcset="https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368754.ece/ALTERNATES/s458b/0_Soil-with-a-garden-trowel.jpg 458w, https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368754.ece/ALTERNATES/s615b/0_Soil-with-a-garden-trowel.jpg 615w,
          https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368754.ece/ALTERNATES/s1200e/0_Soil-with-a-garden-trowel.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 458px) 458px, (max-width: 615px) 615px, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;If you think you might be high risk, you should seek advice from a doctor, the expert explains&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: Getty Images/iStockphoto)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;"However, there are times when our immune systems are weakened, due to other infections or chronic conditions, where we may be more susceptible to fungal infections. When this is the case, it is advisable to wear a mask and to avoid high risk areas."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;Goosens adds that if you are concerned about your risk level for encountering these spores then you should speak to a healthcare professional.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;Research has predicted that "the spread of Aspergillus fumigatus &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;could increase by 77.5 percent and potentially expose 9 million people in Europe," and Aspergillus flavus - one of the most resistant to antifungal meds, could expose one million to severe and deadly infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;Diagnosing fungal infections of this kind is, as the experts have noted, no mean feat, but they can also be very tricky to treat. There is one major reason why, according to the researchers: "As fungi are more similar to humans than other pathogens, developing anti-fungal treatments without toxic side effects is challenging."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;Not only that, but common agriculture practices mean that the medications that are available are themselves under threat - as the fungus rapidly adapts, becoming resistant to even the most cutting-edge treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;"Their spread is accelerated by globalisation, urbanisation, and the intensifying use of agricultural fungicides, which further increase antifungal resistance," the study explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;Fungicides are used widely in agriculture, and many of them work similarly to the antifungal medications being developed, with a large overlap in their chemical makeup - presenting a massive problem. "A lot of the fungicides used in farming are either identical or really similar to the antifungal drugs that we rely on in medicine," Goosens explains. "That means fungi out in the environment can start building resistance to treatments we use to fight infections in people. "&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;It's much faster and easier for fungicides to be approved compared to antifungal medications, which means that fungi are presented with an opportunity to learn how to adapt to them when they are sprayed on crops at an industrial level. By the time the medications are approved, they can be rendered ineffective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX false" data-testid="imageembed-35368757"&gt;&lt;figure class="Figure_figure__Uce4f"&gt;&lt;img src="https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368757.ece/ALTERNATES/s615b/0_Crop-sprayer.jpg" alt="crops being sprayed by machine" loading="lazy" srcset="https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368757.ece/ALTERNATES/s458b/0_Crop-sprayer.jpg 458w, https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368757.ece/ALTERNATES/s615b/0_Crop-sprayer.jpg 615w,
          https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/article35368757.ece/ALTERNATES/s1200e/0_Crop-sprayer.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 458px) 458px, (max-width: 615px) 615px, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Industrial use of fungicides in agriculture is presenting big problems when it comes to creating antifungal medications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;Two antifungal medications that are currently undergoing clinical trials, olorofim and fosmanogepix, in humans, are poised to be approved in the UK right now - giving the fast-adapting fungi a two-year head start.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;"To tackle this, we need better communication between the agriculture and healthcare sectors," Goosens explains, "and stronger government oversight to make sure we're using these chemicals responsibly."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;One of the major issues, the expert explains, is that so little is known about fungi - and much more research is needed into them. "Fungi are a huge part of life on Earth, but we've barely scratched the surface in understanding them. That really needs to change, especially as the climate shifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;"We need more research into their basic biology, better tools to diagnose fungal infections, and stronger systems to keep an eye on how fungi are spreading or changing. They don’t exist in isolation—they’re part of wider ecosystems, and they’re adapting in ways we’re only just beginning to understand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh "&gt;"Sometimes that means a fungi that’s normally harmless can start causing disease, or it can evolve to survive in new environments. We’ve only identified a tiny fraction—less than 10%—of all fungal species out there. There’s so much potential, not just for treating and preventing infections, but also for discovering new medicines and other breakthroughs. We just need to start paying more attention to them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Mirror</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNTExPOXBwamNMSEJKM1daSG9YeER6dlRyU0lEcWp3R0FQaTczN1dWVk1Hem40SnN1eXhYdFhjcU8zWXQxSnNHaG9GNWtsVTI2ZkVLNTJKR0lySlZqVG90dEFXMDdFczB3bmJtQy1rTkFJeHJ4dmczWFo5Z2tpSmFvYkU3UG5WYU3SAYwBQVVfeXFMTjJxdXAyQ1V2R0NWa0ZXSWlfbUNBNlBqRzY4R2Y1TVJLSFJHcFFlTUpBWVNkOXl4YXdVcjFWMXppOGN6UmFNRnZiazI0cFJZY2twYlpDbkswbDZPcFRrUHhUelp6VzRsRnNRVFVlRVpTekxURXcyYUFGbGdUMl9iVUwwTEdWeG9ZMFZOZTg</guid></item><item><title>在Aldi购买的6种最佳高蛋白零食，由营养师推荐- EatingWell | The 6 Best High-Protein Snacks to Buy at Aldi, Recommended by a Dietitian - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMid0FVX3lxTE12Szk4ZVhwQzRvbkpXaTBoa0Q5TTJnckphbklQRmxXWFpxZ1dsemRqZFlLQTlOMWZZN3VkTVFIZDdRZTdVOXkwWlZGY19SZVRkSG5idVhldW9tN3lyT29JM3FySTJUVnNBd2U4X2FNTU8zVi1BVnJr?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;High-protein snacks help you stay full longer and keep your energy up between meals.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Aldi has many tasty, budget-friendly snacks with 7 grams or more of protein per serving.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Choosing snacks with protein can support strong muscles, a healthy gut and a better mood.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you're anything like me, you hit the 3 p.m. slump and suddenly you're ready to eat the nearest houseplant. I used to reach for whatever was closest—usually something sugary and regrettable—until I realized that a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/dietitians-high-protein-snack-11712761" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;protein-packed snack&lt;/a&gt; could turn my afternoon around. There's a lot of hype about protein, but it's not just nutritionist-speak. When I switched to &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-high-protein-foods-to-eat-as-snacks-8674784" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;high-protein snacks&lt;/a&gt;, it meant the difference between raiding the fridge at 5 p.m. and calmly making dinner like an actual adult. If this resonates with you, keep reading! 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Incorporating protein-packed snacks into your daily routine can be the catalyst for bettering your energy levels and overall well-being. But here's some even better news: You don't have to spend a lot of money or hours scouring specialty stores to find these nutritional gems. As a food writer, Aldi is one of my favorite places to stock up on budget-friendly, convenient and nutrient-rich snacks. Below are six Aldi finds you'll want to toss into your cart the next time you hit up the store.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-friendly-farms-low-fat-cottage-cheese"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 1. Friendly Farms Low Fat Cottage Cheese &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Cottage cheese and I had a complicated relationship for years. But more recently, I've become a convert. At just 80 calories per ½-cup serving, Friendly Farms cottage cheese delivers an impressive 13 grams of protein—making it one of the most &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/291961/10-high-protein-snacks-that-keep-you-feeling-full-longer/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;protein-dense snacks&lt;/a&gt; you can grab.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Casein, the main protein in &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/cottage-cheese-health-benefits-11728968" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;cottage cheese&lt;/a&gt;, digests slowly—meaning it keeps you full longer, says &lt;a href="https://dominationdietitian.com/index.html" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="nofollow"&gt;Lacy Puttuck, M.S., RD&lt;/a&gt;. That’s one of the reasons she recommends it as a snack. “Its slow-digesting quality means you'll stay fuller longer,” she explains. It's also an easy way to get a good amount of calcium. Each serving contains 114 milligrams of the &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-for-bone-health-11745664" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;bone-supporting nutrient&lt;/a&gt;—that's 11% of the recommended daily value (DV).&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Cottage cheese also earns points for being endlessly adaptable in a range of sweet and savory applications. Some afternoons, if I'm in the mood for something sweet, I'll top it with fresh seasonal berries or &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/no-added-sugar-chia-seed-jam-8728331" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="5"&gt;chia jam&lt;/a&gt;. Other days, I’ll mix it with everything bagel seasoning for something more savory. Or I’ll even turn it into a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8039820/high-protein-2-ingredient-cottage-cheese-ice-cream-recipe/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="6"&gt;2-ingredient ice cream&lt;/a&gt; (yes, really!) or use it in &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-high-protein-upgrade-for-your-morning-toast-11681776" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="7"&gt;myriad other ways&lt;/a&gt; on toast. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-millville-peanut-almond-dark-chocolate-protein-chewy-bar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 2. Millville Peanut Almond Dark Chocolate Protein Chewy Bar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These bars are what happens when someone finally gets the assignment right. They taste like a treat but pack 10 g of protein and 6 g of fiber—"a great amount," according to Puttuck, who notes that the fiber "works to increase satiety and feed a healthy gut microbiome."&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The classic combination of nuts and dark chocolate nails the sweet-salty balance while keeping the sugar low at only 6 g. Because they're individually wrapped, I can easily keep them in my purse, backpack or gym bag as a quick energy source in a pinch.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3-friendly-farms-super-zero-nonfat-greek-yogurt"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 3. Friendly Farms Super Zero Nonfat Greek Yogurt &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Greek yogurt lovers, this one's for you. With an incredible 15 g of protein, zero fat and zero added sugar, this yogurt is a nutritional all-star packed into a convenient cup.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The berry flavor is sweet without any added sugar, and the thick, creamy texture rivals much more expensive brands. What makes &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8015607/greek-yogurt-benefits/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Greek yogurt&lt;/a&gt; especially valuable goes beyond just its high-protein content.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "One of the biggest benefits of yogurt is the active probiotics that are in it," says Puttuck, who advises eating a bit of yogurt daily to "improve and maintain optimal gut health." If you're not yet convinced, Puttuck positions yogurt as &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8001367/poor-gut-health-increases-anxiety-depression-risk-what-to-eat/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;mood food&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; stating, "The microbes typically found in yogurt can also improve mood by increasing the production of serotonin."&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Current research backs this and also sees it as a possible antidote to depression.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; To make it even better, top it with fruit or granola, or turn the vanilla version into a frozen, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8053032/high-protein-yogurt-cup-dessert-tastes-like-a-snickers-bar/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;Snickers-like treat&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-4-southern-grove-dry-roasted-peanuts-with-sea-salt"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 4. Southern Grove Dry Roasted Peanuts with Sea Salt &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Sometimes, I need something salty and crunchy, and these peanuts deliver exactly that. One ounce provides 8 g of protein along with a bit of fiber and some &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/surprising-nutrient-for-better-heart-health-8686588" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;heart-healthy fats&lt;/a&gt;, which Puttuck advises "can promote brain and nervous system health."&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; I like the simple sea salt seasoning for flavor (and because it plays into the same snacky vibe as chips). And if you're highly active or outdoors a lot in the summer, Puttuck says, they're a great choice for getting those much-needed electrolytes during hot weather.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-5-country-archer-beef-sticks"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 5. Country Archer Beef Sticks &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These individually-packaged beef sticks have saved me countless times when traveling or needing something ultra-portable. With 8 g of protein per stick, they are perfect for keeping hunger at bay.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Plus, Country Archer is known for using higher-quality ingredients like grass-fed beef, which has higher levels of omega-3s than conventionally grain-fed beef. "Beef contains a good vitamin and mineral profile," says Puttuck, adding that "some of these include vitamin B12 for DNA and energy production and iron to maintain optimal oxygen levels." County Archer's beef sticks contain just 1 mg of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/health-benefits-of-iron-8733430" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;iron&lt;/a&gt; each, but at about 6% of your daily iron needs, that's pretty impressive for such a convenient snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-6-park-street-deli-genoa-salami-provolone-and-breadsticks"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 6. Park Street Deli Genoa Salami, Provolone and Breadsticks &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These pre-portioned trays are like having a mini charcuterie board ready to go. With 18 g of protein per package, they combine the satisfaction of multiple flavors and textures in one convenient serving.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The meat, cheese and breadsticks feel indulgent while still supporting your goals. Puttuck loves these because they're "very satisfying" thanks to the "fats and protein that can carry through the day." It's the kind of snack that never feels restrictive, which is exactly what I need.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-health-benefits-of-protein"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Health Benefits of Protein &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Beyond keeping hunger at bay, high-protein snacks offer some much bigger benefits. Protein plays a crucial role in maintaining muscle mass, supporting immune function and regulating blood sugar.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; By choosing &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/snacks-more-protein-than-egg-11744826" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;protein-rich snacks&lt;/a&gt;, you're setting up your body to function well and feel great.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Research consistently shows that protein has the highest thermic effect of any macronutrient—meaning your body burns more calories digesting it compared to carbs or fats.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This makes high-protein snacking particularly valuable if you have weight management goals. Perhaps most importantly, protein helps stabilize your energy levels throughout the day.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; So instead of experiencing the energy rollercoaster that often comes with high-sugar snacks, protein provides steady, sustained fuel that supports physical &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; mental performance.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Convenient, high-protein snacks are a helpful tool in a balanced diet. When shopping for high-protein snacks at Aldi or any grocery store, Puttuck emphasizes the importance of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/things-i-check-first-on-the-nutrition-label-8548484" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;reading labels carefully&lt;/a&gt;, looking for products with minimal ingredients and trying to avoid ingredients like high fructose corn syrup and artificial colors and flavors, which she says can "have adverse health effects on the body." Choose minimally processed snacks whenever you can—&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8067928/how-to-know-when-boiled-eggs-are-done/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;hard-boiled eggs&lt;/a&gt; and jerky are two of her favorites. Outside of this, look for at least 7 g of protein (Puttuck says 10 to 15 g is even better).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Smart, protein-rich choices like these aren't just great for curbing hunger—they can also help stabilize energy, support muscle health and improve overall well-being. Whether you’re powering through an afternoon work sprint, recovering from a workout, or just trying to avoid hangry spirals, these are the snacks you’ll reach for again and again.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE12Szk4ZVhwQzRvbkpXaTBoa0Q5TTJnckphbklQRmxXWFpxZ1dsemRqZFlLQTlOMWZZN3VkTVFIZDdRZTdVOXkwWlZGY19SZVRkSG5idVhldW9tN3lyT29JM3FySTJUVnNBd2U4X2FNTU8zVi1BVnJr</guid></item><item><title>麻疹患者前往波士顿酒店、博物馆、机场，卫生官员警告- NBC波士顿 | Person with measles visited Boston hotel, museum, airport, health officials warn - NBC Boston</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipAFBVV95cUxNTUFMajRleU1iQzYxX0dmVzNBSXRRWUxMUzZvWTJGTGwwbGlLM3IzRWFUcTdHbGFEQVI3QTBpZWlkaXJsT0JOdDdfNzRrbjM1QUlXVDJnUE40WUdXN1FqSG1kVTMzSTJYd2RjMm1Ed0VhcmVUQkJfU2E3enNVaENST2sybVk4MC1tXzNSNGt4ZG5QTHU5TkZaOGNPTkpsaE5ocVZkZNIBrAFBVV95cUxPc3hEZHlFUVBOMTBtb0lwX1lNYUJ1MS1VZS1oeXhrSXpPalotRURJM29fZFZoQVNFNlYyUEtfU3Nhb3lxaTJpOXFndHZQSVRXXzVsb1Z4d3praXZiV2tsRFM4YjhrLWhWbEN3QWpfdkszR2U1bnc0TkNSLWN4NUdRM2Z4V0NtVS1DSVRPQVI2TkdHM3ZjTXhITGFSbm1GSlQxc2lydFZiWG1UN2Jw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content rich-text"&gt;
									
					
&lt;p&gt;A person with &lt;a href="https://www.nbcboston.com/?s=measles" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.nbcboston.com/?s=measles" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;measles&lt;/a&gt; visited Boston over the weekend, health officials warned Friday, sharing a hotel, museum and airport terminal where other people may have been exposed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Boston Public Health Commission and Massachusetts Department of Public Health said the infected person was in the city June 7-8.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The health agencies are working to identify and alert people who may have been exposed. They specified that people who were at the following locations at the listed times could be affected:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Westin Boston Seaport District hotel, and the restaurants inside, between 5:30 p.m. on Saturday, June 7 and 1:30 p.m. on Sunday, June 8&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;The Museum of Fine Arts Boston between 1 p.m. and 6:30 p.m. on Sunday, June 8&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Logan Airport Terminal C between 5 p.m. and 11:15 p.m. on Sunday, June 8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The person then flew to Miami on JetBlue Flight 639 on Sunday, departing at 9:12 p.m., health officials said, noting that they are working with the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention to notify passengers who are at risk of being exposed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-react-component="VideoPlaylist" data-props='{"accountId":"Yh1nAC","autoplay":false,"placeholder":true,"brand":"nbc","host":"nbcboston.com","twitter":"nbc10boston","callLetters":"WBTS","station":"NBC OTS BOSTON","excludeEndCard":false,"islead":false,"fastSchedule":[],"videos":[{"mediaId":"jsjmtnBvd3gO","poster":"https:\/\/media.nbcboston.com\/2025\/04\/39318077125-1080pnbcstations.jpg?quality=85&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;resize=850%2C478","title":"Health officials warn against misleading measles information","url":"https:\/\/www.nbcboston.com\/news\/national-international\/video-health-officials-warn-against-misleading-measles-information\/3700279\/","videoContentId":"1:5:3700279","videoId":"2424340035622","isLivestream":"","isFast":"","m3uPid":"","mp4Url":"https:\/\/prodamdlim.akamaized.net\/NBCU_LM_VMS\/863\/847\/39318077125-1080pnbcnews6m.mp4","m3u8Url":"","catNames":{"206944":"News","207276":"U.S. &amp;amp;amp; World"},"tagNames":{"665804":"Health"},"contentSource":"NBC","sentiment":"Neutral","topic":"","origination":"NBCU LM VMS","sponsorName":"","datePublished":"2025-04-30T09:53:25","duration":134,"syndicated_id":"1:1:10442642","videoSport":"","videoLeague":"","videoTeam":"","show":"","event":"","genre":"","originCallLetters":"NATIONALNBC","canonicalUrl":"https:\/\/www.nbcchicago.com\/news\/national-international\/video-health-officials-warn-against-misleading-measles-information\/3734168\/","sensitivity":[],"disableEmbed":false}]}'&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="video_caption" data-react-component="NBCTruncate" data-maxlines="2" data-maxlinesmobile="4" data-readmore="Read more" data-text="Health officials are warning about misleading information aimed at preventing measles as the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reports rising case numbers across the United States." data-ellipsis="false"&gt;
								Health officials are warning about misleading information aimed at preventing measles as the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reports rising case numbers across the United States.
							&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who are not vaccinated against measles who have been exposed should contact their health care provider immediately, health officials said, adding that they need to avoid public places and monitor for symptoms for 21 days, or through June 29.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Citing data from the DPH, the BPHC said 94% of children in Suffolk County are fully vaccinated against measles, explaining that it is 93% to 97% effective in preventing infection and protecting against severe disease. Boston Public Health Commissioner Dr. Bisola Ojikutu told reporters Saturday morning that the city's strong vaccination means Boston is "protected from a large measles outbreak."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"We're hopeful that we will not see many cases in this instance," she said, stressing that the Boston Public Health Commission has been preparing for a case to arrive and "hopefully protect us from any additional cases or a large outbreak."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She stressed that Health officials said measles is "a highly contagious virus that begins with flu-like symptoms, including cough, high fever, runny nose, and red, watery eyes, followed by a red, blotchy rash that spreads from the face to the rest of the body." It can be spread through breathing, coughing and sneezing, and it can be contracted if surfaces are touched within two hours of an infected person being in the area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The U.S. has seen &lt;a href="https://www.nbcboston.com/news/national-international/united-states-1001-measles-cases-11-states-active-outbreaks/3710161/" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.nbcboston.com/news/national-international/united-states-1001-measles-cases-11-states-active-outbreaks/3710161/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;an uptick in measles cases this year&lt;/a&gt;, with several states reporting outbreaks. Two unvaccinated children have died in Texas, and an unvaccinated adult died in New Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-react-component="VideoPlaylist" data-props="{&amp;quot;accountId&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Yh1nAC&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;autoplay&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;placeholder&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;brand&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;nbc&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;host&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;nbcboston.com&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;twitter&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;nbc10boston&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;callLetters&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;WBTS&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;station&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;NBC OTS BOSTON&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;excludeEndCard&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;islead&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;fastSchedule&amp;quot;:[],&amp;quot;videos&amp;quot;:[{&amp;quot;mediaId&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;t0X3mwhxmD1B&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;poster&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https:\/\/media.nbcnewyork.com\/2025\/03\/38155623247-1080pnbcstations.jpg?quality=85&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;resize=850%2C478&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;What's the risk of a measles outbreak in Massachusetts?&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;url&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https:\/\/www.nbcboston.com\/on-air\/as-seen-on\/whats-the-risk-of-a-measles-outbreak-in-massachusetts\/3646659\/&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;videoContentId&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;1:5:3646659&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;videoId&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;2412307011701&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;isLivestream&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;isFast&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;m3uPid&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;mp4Url&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https:\/\/prodamdlim.akamaized.net\/NBCU_LM_VMS_WBTS\/652\/247\/38155623247-1080pnbcnews6m.mp4&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;m3u8Url&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;catNames&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;1813&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;On Air&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;1814&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;As Seen On&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;206944&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;News&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;876&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Health&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;705&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Local&amp;quot;},&amp;quot;tagNames&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;665804&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Health&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;124&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Massachusetts&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;196&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Texas&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;666123&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Vaccines&amp;quot;},&amp;quot;contentSource&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;NBC&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sentiment&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;topic&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;origination&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;BOS&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sponsorName&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;datePublished&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;2025-03-03T16:47:14&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;duration&amp;quot;:136,&amp;quot;syndicated_id&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;videoSport&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;videoLeague&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;videoTeam&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;show&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;event&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;genre&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;originCallLetters&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;WBTS&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;canonicalUrl&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https:\/\/www.nbcboston.com\/on-air\/as-seen-on\/whats-the-risk-of-a-measles-outbreak-in-massachusetts\/3646659\/&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sensitivity&amp;quot;:[],&amp;quot;disableEmbed&amp;quot;:false}]}"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="video_caption" data-react-component="NBCTruncate" data-maxlines="2" data-maxlinesmobile="4" data-readmore="Read more" data-text="A child's death in Texas has prompted a nationwide call for children to be vaccinated against the disease. 

Follow NBC10 Boston:
https://instagram.com/nbc10boston
https://tiktok.com/@nbc10boston
https://facebook.com/NBC10Boston
https://twitter.com/NBC10Boston
https://bsky.app/profile/nbcboston.com" data-ellipsis="false"&gt;
								A child's death in Texas has prompted a nationwide call for children to be vaccinated against the disease. 

Follow NBC10 Boston:
https://instagram.com/nbc10boston
https://tiktok.com/@nbc10boston
https://facebook.com/NBC10Boston
https://twitter.com/NBC10Boston
https://bsky.app/profile/nbcboston.com
							&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The person with measles who traveled through Boston didn't arrive at the airport or arrive from abroad, Ojikutu told reporters, but couldn't share more about where they were previously — patient health data is confidential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city typically gets up to two cases of measles per years, a low level she attributed to Boston's vaccination rate. She believed the last uptick in cases was in 2011, amid a statewide bump in cases of about two dozen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ojikutu reported that contract tracing efforts were going well with the Museum of Fine Arts, Westin and the CDC, and that guests of the MFA and hotel who may have been exposed should expect to receive a notification.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"This case of measles highlights the importance of obtaining the MMR vaccine to protect ourselves and our community. The MMR vaccine is highly effective at preventing measles infection and also protects against mumps and rubella," Ojikutu said in an earlier statement. "Children should receive the vaccine at 12-15 months of age and again before kindergarten to ensure strong immunity. Children who are at least 6 months old who are traveling internationally should receive an early dose of vaccine before traveling. It is never too late for children or adults to get the measles vaccine and for the vaccine to be effective, even if they are past the age recommended by doctors."&lt;/p&gt;
			
	
									&lt;/div&gt;
												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC Boston</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 02:43:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxNTUFMajRleU1iQzYxX0dmVzNBSXRRWUxMUzZvWTJGTGwwbGlLM3IzRWFUcTdHbGFEQVI3QTBpZWlkaXJsT0JOdDdfNzRrbjM1QUlXVDJnUE40WUdXN1FqSG1kVTMzSTJYd2RjMm1Ed0VhcmVUQkJfU2E3enNVaENST2sybVk4MC1tXzNSNGt4ZG5QTHU5TkZaOGNPTkpsaE5ocVZkZNIBrAFBVV95cUxPc3hEZHlFUVBOMTBtb0lwX1lNYUJ1MS1VZS1oeXhrSXpPalotRURJM29fZFZoQVNFNlYyUEtfU3Nhb3lxaTJpOXFndHZQSVRXXzVsb1Z4d3praXZiV2tsRFM4YjhrLWhWbEN3QWpfdkszR2U1bnc0TkNSLWN4NUdRM2Z4V0NtVS1DSVRPQVI2TkdHM3ZjTXhITGFSbm1GSlQxc2lydFZiWG1UN2Jw</guid></item><item><title>大多数女性忽视这种症状是心脏病发作的微妙迹象，但它可能是生死攸关的问题- BuzzFeed | Most Women Ignore This Symptom As A Subtle Sign Of A Heart Attack, But It Could Be A Matter Of Life And Death - BuzzFeed</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigAFBVV95cUxQMEFTZHJhakxhYWxHVFpncjR2RDdBQXNIZy1heXZFV1VHYzNlSHU4LVNrYktNcXlFSnlMVWYzaDBBUEk1TWplOUVUa29vb0tNUkRJdkdSc09PaE90Tm1uQ09tQTZkdXlpWDFfZmd3ZGJLQTVzNUFEeGZvRW5tLVppbw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-1
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="138786352" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;In a recent segment on &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/disease/nausea-widowmaker-heart-attack-symptom-women-rcna136801" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7888385" data-affiliate="true"&gt;the “Today” show&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://drchantrise.com/about/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7888385" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Chantrise Holliman&lt;/a&gt;, a mother, wife and heart health educator based in Georgia,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;shared the story of her &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/life/topic/heart-attack" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7888385"&gt;heart attack&lt;/a&gt; and what seemed like the fairly benign symptoms that accompanied it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holliman experienced nausea, vomiting and mild chest pressure. The first two symptoms ― which aren’t commonly associated with heart attacks ― led her to believe the sensations had more to do with her dinner the night before than a serious medical concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like Holliman, many people don’t know that stomach symptoms can, indeed, be signs of a heart attack. While not the most common warning sign (chest pain is most reported), nausea is also not uncommon during a cardiac event, according to &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1316106776/sean-p-heffron" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7888385" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Dr. Sean Heffron&lt;/a&gt;, a cardiologist at NYU Langone Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It “tends to depend somewhat on which blood vessel in the heart is affected,” Heffron explained. Additionally, nausea is more commonly seen in women, Heffron said, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/heartdisease/heart_attack.htm" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7888385" data-affiliate="true"&gt;as is vomiting&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other heart attack signs in women include jaw pain, neck pain, a dull feeling of chest discomfort, upper abdomen pain, back pain and excessive tiredness, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s so important to hear stories like this, because many women think it has to be like, ‘I’m clutching my chest and falling to the ground like you see in the movies,’ and it can be much more subtle,” Dr. Tara Narula, a cardiologist and NBC News medical contributor, &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/disease/nausea-widowmaker-heart-attack-symptom-women-rcna136801" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7888385" data-affiliate="true"&gt;told “Today.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart attacks can look very different in women than in men, which means that sufferers and doctors alike sometimes dismiss them. But it’s important to recognize the signs, especially since heart disease “is the leading cause of death for women in this country,” Narula told “Today.” “One woman every 80 seconds dies of cardiovascular disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to tell if your nausea is part of a heart attack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:31:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQMEFTZHJhakxhYWxHVFpncjR2RDdBQXNIZy1heXZFV1VHYzNlSHU4LVNrYktNcXlFSnlMVWYzaDBBUEk1TWplOUVUa29vb0tNUkRJdkdSc09PaE90Tm1uQ09tQTZkdXlpWDFfZmd3ZGJLQTVzNUFEeGZvRW5tLVppbw</guid></item><item><title>Bernalillo、Sandoval和Santa Fe县的潜在麻疹暴露- KOAT | Potential measles exposure in Bernalillo, Sandoval and Santa Fe counties - KOAT</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxNaXV3aVpWWFI1NG9Md0ZNUXNGWVMxTmxHWFpJRkh5bm5tZWQyVzRxRzJ4U05BZF9CamZGODNSVnN1Mkp5cERlc1VtSWo3ZDg0X3RjMXFQRTdiWnh3X1QyZFloMXdpYkFacHFpN3lHMzd0Q1ozUUN4SjIzclY2a2VkWUVpTmoyclRDY0RoMnAyc0NIN2RhOHpneXZ6anZQa2Q3V0F6R1dSN1c1Q1pfc2c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article-content--body-text-raw"&gt;
						The New Mexico Department of Health is warning the public about a possible measles exposure in Bernalillo, Santa Fe and Sandoval counties. According to the NMDOH, two travelers have been diagnosed with measles during their visit to New Mexico, leading to potential exposures at various locations. The two travelers, who were traveling separately, were an adult of unknown vaccination status and an 18-month-old child who was vaccinated. The NMDOH warns that the public could have possibly been exposed to the measles at these locations and during these times: • Rio Rancho Aquatic Center, 745 Loma Colorado NE in Rio Rancho.  o  Monday, June 2: 1-4 p.m.  • Walmart Supercenter, 5701 Herrera Drive in Santa Fe. o Thursday, June 5: 11 a.m.-2 p.m.  • Walmart Supercenter, 2550 Coors Boulevard NW in Albuquerque.  o Friday, June 6: 9 a.m.-1 p.m.• El Super, 4201 Central Ave NW in Albuquerque.o Friday, June 6: 9 a.m.-1 p.m.• University of New Mexico Hospice Adult Urgent Care, 2211 Lomas Boulevard NE in Albuquerque.o Tuesday, June 10: 9:30 a.m.- 1:40 p.m.• Albuquerque International Sunport, 2200 Sunport Boulevard in Albuquerque.o Tuesday, June 10: 3 - 7 p.m. o Main Terminal and TSA Security Checkpointo Terminal A, Gate A-6Action 7 News On The Go: Download our app for free
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;div class="article-content--body-text"&gt;
						&lt;strong class="dateline"&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. —&lt;/strong&gt; 													&lt;p&gt;The New Mexico Department of Health is warning the public about a possible measles exposure in Bernalillo, Santa Fe and Sandoval counties. According to the NMDOH, two travelers have been diagnosed with measles during their visit to New Mexico, leading to potential exposures at various locations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two travelers, who were traveling separately, were an adult of unknown vaccination status and an 18-month-old child who was vaccinated. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The NMDOH warns that the public could have possibly been exposed to the measles at these locations and during these times: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Rio Rancho Aquatic Center&lt;/strong&gt;, 745 Loma Colorado NE in Rio Rancho.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;o  Monday, June 2: 1-4 p.m.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Walmart Supercenter&lt;/strong&gt;, 5701 Herrera Drive in Santa Fe. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;o Thursday, June 5: 11 a.m.-2 p.m.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="cream-inline-rec" class="cream-inline hidden"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Walmart Supercenter&lt;/strong&gt;, 2550 Coors Boulevard NW in Albuquerque.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;o Friday, June 6: 9 a.m.-1 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;El Super&lt;/strong&gt;, 4201 Central Ave NW in Albuquerque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;o Friday, June 6: 9 a.m.-1 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;• University of New Mexico Hospice Adult Urgent Care&lt;/strong&gt;, 2211 Lomas Boulevard NE in Albuquerque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;o Tuesday, June 10: 9:30 a.m.- 1:40 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Albuquerque International Sunport&lt;/strong&gt;, 2200 Sunport Boulevard in Albuquerque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;o Tuesday, June 10: 3 - 7 p.m. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;o Main Terminal and TSA Security Checkpoint&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;o Terminal A, Gate A-6&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Action 7 News On The Go: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.koat.com/apps"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Download our app for free&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

							
											&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
						
						
																			

																				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KOAT</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:09:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxNaXV3aVpWWFI1NG9Md0ZNUXNGWVMxTmxHWFpJRkh5bm5tZWQyVzRxRzJ4U05BZF9CamZGODNSVnN1Mkp5cERlc1VtSWo3ZDg0X3RjMXFQRTdiWnh3X1QyZFloMXdpYkFacHFpN3lHMzd0Q1ozUUN4SjIzclY2a2VkWUVpTmoyclRDY0RoMnAyc0NIN2RhOHpneXZ6anZQa2Q3V0F6R1dSN1c1Q1pfc2c</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法， 60岁以后应该多吃的6种食物- EatingWell | 6 Foods You Should Eat More of After 60, According to Dietitians - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifkFVX3lxTE5KYzNmM3dibHhJTEtPT3dyM2lBUWJZSzYtbDh4b0NNQktXaHQtaXJjaG80dmd3dzM4b3Y2X3NSNk5qSTFoTnJnVThOSmFOY2dhSWNRMjI3WVA2N1VqOUZvV2VKWERDS0xtRWdDTlVmQURBcnFSbXY2dE9vZFRkZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Diet plays an important role in maintaining bone, heart, eye and brain health as you age.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;After age 60, prioritize nuts, legumes, leafy greens, cranberries and prunes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Socializing, consistent sleep and staying physically and mentally active are key for healthy aging.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Reaching your 60s is a milestone worth celebrating. And while this decade can be filled with travel and more time spent with family, you may also experience some unexpected changes that aren’t quite as welcoming. To keep your energy levels up, mood stable and health on track year after year, it’s important to be intentional about &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8067323/7-day-high-protein-meal-plan-for-healthy-aging/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;the food on your plate&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Certain foods can go a long way in supporting your body as it ages, whether it’s by &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/things-doctors-do-every-day-for-better-brain-health-11678638" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;boosting brain health&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-for-bone-health-11745664" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;strengthening bones&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/heart-healthy-foods-to-eat-in-january-8768223" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;protecting your heart&lt;/a&gt;. According to dietitians, adding more of these six nutrient-packed foods to your routine can help you feel your best and stay active and energized throughout your golden years. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-walnuts"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 1. Walnuts &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One of the most powerful foods for longevity is one that you don’t actually need a lot of to see big benefits. “Walnuts provide plant-based omega-3s, antioxidants and polyphenols, all of which play a role in brain and heart health as we age,” says &lt;a href="https://samanthacassetty.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Samantha Cassetty, MS, RD&lt;/a&gt;, partner with California Walnuts. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Using data from the Nurses’ Health Study, researchers found that women who ate at least two servings or walnuts per week in their late 50s and early 60s were more likely to experience healthy aging, which includes being free from chronic disease, memory problems, physical disability and mental health issues after age 65 compared to those who did not eat walnuts regularly.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Aim to enjoy 2 ounces of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8069681/benefits-of-walnuts/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;walnuts&lt;/a&gt; weekly, either on their own or incorporated into recipes. Try adding these crunchy nuts to salads, overnight oats, homemade snack bars and more. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-legumes"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 2. Legumes &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Maintaining bone density is critical for maintaining independence and overall quality of life as we age. Approximately 10 million adults over age 65 have osteoporosis, and while physical activity and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-ways-to-maintain-muscle-mass-to-live-longer-8547770" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;strength training&lt;/a&gt; help, adding legumes to your diet can also support bone health.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “Legumes are an excellent source of plant-based protein and fiber, supporting muscle maintenance, gut health and reduced inflammation,” says &lt;a href="https://erinpalinski.com" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Erin Palinski-Wade, RD, CDCES&lt;/a&gt;.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Legumes include beans, lentils, peas and peanuts. While all legumes can &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-for-bone-health-8737183" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;support strong bones&lt;/a&gt;, chickpeas may be particularly beneficial. The isoflavones and polyphenols in chickpeas may help prevent osteoporosis by supporting bone metabolism and reducing inflammation.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Palinski-Wade explains that these mechanisms are especially helpful and relevant for women post-menopause, who are most at risk for bone loss. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3-pistachios"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 3. Pistachios &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “A handful of pistachios daily can help to improve intake of fiber and key nutrients, including healthy fats, protein and antioxidants, like lutein, which helps &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-nutrient-to-protect-your-vision-8773401" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;protect vision&lt;/a&gt; and supports overall health with age,” says Palinksi-Wade, a consultant for American Pistachio Growers. Additionally, one small study found that eating 2 ounces of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-happens-to-your-body-when-you-eat-pistachios-regularly-8687923" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;pistachios daily&lt;/a&gt; for 4 months reduced oxidative damage and increased the gene expression of specific genes that may support the reversal of certain metabolic conditions that are more common with age, including insulin resistance.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Plus, as a good source of plant-based protein and fiber, pistachios can help to boost satiety with only 160 calories per serving, which can be beneficial when working towards maintaining a healthy body weight,” adds Palinski-Wade.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-4-leafy-greens"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 4. Leafy Greens &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Leafy greens like spinach, kale and collard greens are rich in vitamin K and folate, which help support brain health and may slow age-related cognitive decline,” says &lt;a href="https://alexandria-hardy-rdn.clientsecure.me/#about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Alexandria Hardy RDN LDN&lt;/a&gt;. Diets high in &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/leafy-green-packed-recipes-that-arent-salad-8619158" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;dark leafy greens&lt;/a&gt; have been associated with improved memory and overall cognitive function in older adults and may even help slow cognitive decline.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “These vegetables are rich in brain-supportive nutrients like phylloquinone, beta-carotene and vitamin E, which are thought to support learning and memory,” says Cassetty.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-5-cranberries"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 5. Cranberries &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Over 60% of older adults in the United States do not regularly eat dark leafy vegetables.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Certain medications, like blood thinners, require consistent intake of vitamin K, which is found in greens like spinach and kale. However, this doesn’t mean you need to avoid these vegetables completely. If you take blood thinners, or another medication that interacts with vitamin K, talk with a healthcare professional about how to safely incorporate leafy greens in your diet. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For older adults with difficulties chewing, Hardy recommends steaming, sautéing or pureeing greens rather than enjoying them raw. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/cranberry-health-benefits-8726317" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Cranberries&lt;/a&gt; are rich in anthocyanins and proanthocyanins—antioxiants that support numerous aspects of health, from your brain to your urinary tract. Anthocyanins in cranberries are responsible for their vibrant red color and play a key role in protecting and supporting brain cells.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “Thanks to their antioxidative and anti-inflammatory properties, anthocyanins are being studied for their potential role in reducing the risk of brain disorders like Alzheimer’s disease and Parkinson’s disease,” says &lt;a href="https://www.nutritionnowcounseling.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Lauren Manaker MS, RDN, LD&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Cranberries can also be helpful for preventing &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7962519/uti-bacteria-gut-health-new-research/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;urinary tract infections&lt;/a&gt; (UTIs). While both men and women can experience UTIs, it’s estimated that over 10% of women over age 65 and 30% of women 85 years and older have a UTI at least once a year.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “There are compounds in cranberries called proanthocyanidins (PACs), which have been shown to maintain urinary tract health,” says Manaker. These compounds help prevent bacteria from adhering to the walls of the urinary tract, which can help decrease infection rates.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-6-prunes"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 6. Prunes &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Bone loss is one of the most common and dangerous side effects of aging. Luckily, eating to protect and maintain bone health can be both delicious and simple. “Prunes contain bioactive compounds that may help blunt bone loss, so they're another tool in your toolkit to support healthy aging,” says Cassetty. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In one study, postmenopausal women who ate 50 grams, or approximately 5–6 prunes, per day had reduced rates of total hip bone mineral density loss over 6 to 12 months, whereas women who did not eat prunes experienced increased fracture risk scores at 6 months.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Also noteworthy, this study had a 90% compliance rate, proving just how easy and simple it is to add &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/prunes-benefits-8694943" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;prunes&lt;/a&gt; to your diet. The delicious sweet taste and jelly-like texture make them a welcome addition to salads, toast and smoothies—or just to enjoy by the handful.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Regularly backed up? The high fiber content of prunes can also help &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-breakfast-foods-to-help-you-poop-that-arent-oatmeal-8708873" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;ease constipation&lt;/a&gt; to make bathroom visits smoother (literally).&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Just be sure to drink more water to minimize side effects associated with increased fiber intake, like gas and bloating.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-longevity-tips"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Other Longevity Tips &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; What you put on your plate plays a key role in healthy aging, but it’s far from the only factor. The following strategies can help you feel your best now and support your health in the years to come. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maintain a Regular Sleep Schedule&lt;/strong&gt;: Prioritize a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-happens-if-you-dont-get-enough-sleep-11746534" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;consistent sleep&lt;/a&gt; and wake routine, even on days when you don’t have anywhere to be, encourages Palinski-Wade. Regular sleep may be more important than duration, with some studies showing that people getting consistent sleep have a 20 to 48% lower risk of death from any cause than those with irregular sleep patterns.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stay Active:&lt;/strong&gt; Keep your body moving—and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8026823/what-is-joyful-movement/" class="pseudoStyle" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;make it enjoyable&lt;/a&gt;! “Find something you love, whether it's dancing, walking, gardening or yoga, and make it a regular part of your routine,” says Manaker. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prioritize Connection&lt;/strong&gt;: Research suggests that &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/loneliness-dementia-risk-study-8733921" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;loneliness&lt;/a&gt; and social isolation have a mortality risk similar to smoking cigarettes, drinking alcohol, physical inactivity and obesity.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Make it a priority to stay connected with family and friends and consider joining a club or attending a fitness class once a week. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep Your Mind Active&lt;/strong&gt;: Staying mentally engaged through learning, puzzles, strategic games and other activities can support &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/habit-to-start-to-improve-your-memory-8415078" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;memory&lt;/a&gt; and cognition as you age. Researchers found that people under 75 who regularly participated in cognitively stimulating tasks and activities saw the greatest increases in cognitive function and memory.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Aging well doesn’t have to mean overhauling your entire diet and lifestyle. Focusing on &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7900915/foods-associated-with-living-longer-according-to-research/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nutrient-dense foods&lt;/a&gt;, engaging in joyful movement and maintaining a consistent routine can help you feel your best well into your 60s, 70s and beyond.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE5KYzNmM3dibHhJTEtPT3dyM2lBUWJZSzYtbDh4b0NNQktXaHQtaXJjaG80dmd3dzM4b3Y2X3NSNk5qSTFoTnJnVThOSmFOY2dhSWNRMjI3WVA2N1VqOUZvV2VKWERDS0xtRWdDTlVmQURBcnFSbXY2dE9vZFRkZw</guid></item><item><title>博尔德县居民报告使用公共交通的麻疹病例- 9News | Measles case reported in Boulder County resident who used public transportation - 9News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiswFBVV95cUxPMnAyNjF0OG1fWUx4TUlrMS1IY2tHYmpxd2lINDlGSzVDa1JYd3BvdFEwRWRPdEdNM3c2dVhrN3d1QmdhRlo3S0hhcW1BbkVDakNiV29wNEh0ZFNBaFdlaTZMMVNaT09EeE9DMW1RNHc0V0luREtLSWxTaVpFVkZvOTEzSE9qd0J2bkVjWkxGbnA0RU4xNk02ZFdBZG9Sdmg3WFlONUx3WF9xaEdkcWVjLUx3Zw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Access Denied&lt;/h1&gt;
 
You don't have permission to access "http://www.9news.com/article/news/health/measles-boulder-county-colorado/73-08d6d64c-a5b4-4a9d-958e-57718cf3ea48" on this server.&lt;p&gt;
Reference #18.2c153b17.1749867325.d7334a2
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://errors.edgesuite.net/18.2c153b17.1749867325.d7334a2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>9News</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxPMnAyNjF0OG1fWUx4TUlrMS1IY2tHYmpxd2lINDlGSzVDa1JYd3BvdFEwRWRPdEdNM3c2dVhrN3d1QmdhRlo3S0hhcW1BbkVDakNiV29wNEh0ZFNBaFdlaTZMMVNaT09EeE9DMW1RNHc0V0luREtLSWxTaVpFVkZvOTEzSE9qd0J2bkVjWkxGbnA0RU4xNk02ZFdBZG9Sdmg3WFlONUx3WF9xaEdkcWVjLUx3Zw</guid></item><item><title>华盛顿州和俄勒冈州百日咳病例急剧上升，卫生官员敦促接种疫苗- KGW | Whooping cough cases rise sharply in Washington and Oregon, health officials urge vaccination - KGW</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwwFBVV95cUxNNFZyT1dfaFJCd0xtSDVVRFczVHpHN2QzVEk5VGRjMFdEQ0d0ekhCckFhb3JMTXB3MUxWZmc0Wk1OUEJ6NmtDazNybi1sZ2VUTFd5UVFjOEdaRmcxVUZxSzVWNndSUWVROXVPcE1PZ3pFSWtZdFJaaC1EbVpmc0s4MmtjZll0XzNQc081VnVydEo2Q2RmV3NpcF9Na19sLXp0RlBsOUtGSUNVa1RzZTNlaXRNTkRKUWxUc3NvME9tRXRpTEE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article__summary"&gt;More than 1,300 cases have already been reported this year in Washington. There have been 877 reported cases in Oregon, with the majority in Washington County.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class="article__body"&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. — Health officials in Washington and Oregon are warning the public about a sharp rise in pertussis cases, &lt;a href="/article/news/health/whooping-cough-cases-rising-again/507-b322a88b-1e12-4e48-af99-fec8d9364874" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;also known as whooping cough&lt;/a&gt;, and urging people to stay current on their vaccinations.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Washington, more than 2,200 cases were reported statewide in 2024, a startling increase from just 87 cases in 2023, according to state health officials. As of May 2025, more than 1,300 cases have already been reported.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                        
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doctors said the illness can be particularly dangerous for infants and young children. They recommend that people ensure they and their children are up to date on pertussis vaccinations. Whooping cough is a highly contagious respiratory disease. Early symptoms are often similar to the common cold but can develop into violent coughing fits, difficulty breathing and other serious complications.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Oregon, the state recorded 123 cases of pertussis in May alone, according to the Oregon Health Authority. So far in 2025, there have been 877 reported cases statewide, with the majority in Washington County.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KGW</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxNNFZyT1dfaFJCd0xtSDVVRFczVHpHN2QzVEk5VGRjMFdEQ0d0ekhCckFhb3JMTXB3MUxWZmc0Wk1OUEJ6NmtDazNybi1sZ2VUTFd5UVFjOEdaRmcxVUZxSzVWNndSUWVROXVPcE1PZ3pFSWtZdFJaaC1EbVpmc0s4MmtjZll0XzNQc081VnVydEo2Q2RmV3NpcF9Na19sLXp0RlBsOUtGSUNVa1RzZTNlaXRNTkRKUWxUc3NvME9tRXRpTEE</guid></item></channel></rss>