<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>“科学家只是武器化的食物中毒” ：工程沙门氏菌摧毁癌症肿瘤，而医生害怕活的药物革命-能源记者</title><link>https://www.energy-reporters.com/news/scientists-just-weaponized-food-poisoning-engineered-salmonella-bacteria-destroys-cancer-tumors-while-doctors-fear-the-living-drug-revolution/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Energy Reporters</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 20:46:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAJBVV95cUxNZEpkOFdmUzExMVZad0FrRm42emduRHZ1TVRFbGhja0JFWHhDT1ZaZFRIZ3Y0SGs3b2p0UE1jZF90dEpIdW9NbHI5YUtIZjJjd0Q5UUZJNnBRekRkMzliQmdSREdMLUY4V1dfMlhpWXk4cDh4b2NuaEN1bjZFcVI4R1VqZk94Uk9HQjZIUDY1eHpSZGptTjNKTWgzeEN2ZUptanktVDQ5WE9PeWh4dnNVMTR5ZmNraEVieGdzTUVCazZQUGsyeG1xT25lNTJoMEpXVTdfNU4wT0Ztd2N0Z1U5SktjY0J6UzVZak9Bcmg5WnBXYTJWb0NHMHdTVHBpWmRjbElNNkFiOFB5bjFV</guid></item><item><title>医生测试了一种针对新冠肺炎的常用药物。结果令人惊叹- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250928095616.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A widely available and affordable drug has been shown to be effective in treating seriously ill COVID-19 patients, according to a new international study led by researchers at the Australian National University (ANU) in collaboration with King's College London.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study analyzed data from almost 500 patients hospitalized with COVID-19 across six countries. Patients who inhaled heparin were half as likely to require ventilation and had a significantly lower risk of dying compared with those receiving standard care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heparin, a drug traditionally injected to treat blood clots, was tested in this study in an inhaled form, targeting the lungs directly. As well as acting as an anticoagulant, heparin has anti-inflammatory and pan-antiviral properties. Earlier research results showed breathing and oxygen levels improved in COVID-19 patients after they inhaled a course of heparin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers believe the drug could also be useful in fighting other serious respiratory infections such as pneumonia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professor Clive Page, Emeritus Professor of Pharmacology at King's who co-led the international study with ANU's Professor van Haren, said: "Inhaled heparin is anti-viral, anti-inflammatory and anti-coagulant. There's no other drug that has that unique combination. We know it's only a matter of time until the next pandemic, and there are still COVID-19 patients who get very sick. This is a great weapon to have up our sleeve."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the findings highlight the potential of inhaled heparin, further development is required before the treatment can be routinely adopted. The researchers believe the drug could also be useful in fighting other serious respiratory infections such as pneumonia, which can be caused by a range of viruses and bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Professor van Haren, the drug would also be helpful for those with a compromised immune system, such as cancer patients, when they experience a respiratory infection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professor Frank van Haren, lead author, ANU and Director of the Intensive Care Unit at the St George Hospital in Sydney, said: "It doesn't matter what kind of respiratory infection the patient is dealing with, the drug -- when inhaled -- will stop it from infecting the patient and from damaging the lungs. We're aiming to conduct another trial in Europe to confirm its effectiveness in fighting other common respiratory infections such as influenza and RSV. And because it's inexpensive, it's much more accessible for those from low-income countries"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers are now also developing an improved formulation of heparin, specifically designed to be given by inhalation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research is published in &lt;em&gt;eClinicalMedicine&lt;/em&gt; and simultaneously presented of at the European Respiratory Society (ERS) International Congress in Amsterdam on Sunday, September 28, the leading annual gathering for respiratory research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 20:08:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE83ZlJiSWxZQ2RiclRRcEl1Tzh5dUNaWFRMZUNXN3JjLWE0VW1EbkVqSWZaaVE3dW5la2d2ekw4dlVoTFpWY0k1dWlOU0EyZXdRRXBrNjFwWDJRREd4RU5TUmFfNHNSbUtaTG1YQXB4RQ</guid></item><item><title>您是否患有2型糖尿病？您也可能有可能出现导致器官衰竭的致命疾病的风险-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15115921/type-2-diabetes-deadly-sepsis-organ-failure.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The one in 10 Americans living with type 2 &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-787423d0-958d-11f0-8923-256e77754a14"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; may be at double the risk of deadly sepsis, especially if they're under 60, a study suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers in Australia analyzed data from 157,000 adults to explore the connection between type 2 diabetes and sepsis, an &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-13813249/rise-silent-killer-sepsis-cdc-data.html"&gt;extreme reaction to an infection&lt;/a&gt; that causes the immune system to attack healthy tissues and organs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Using patient medical records, the team found twice as many patients with type 2 diabetes were hospitalized for sepsis than people without type 2 diabetes when they were first enrolled in the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And over the course of 10 years, nearly 2.5 times the participants with type 2 diabetes developed sepsis compared to non-diabetics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The diabetics in their 40s were at a 14-fold increased risk of sepsis compared to non-diabetics in the same age range. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Previous research has suggested diabetics may be at an increased risk because they are more likely to develop wounds that don't heal and can become infected, as high blood sugar damages blood vessels and immune functions needed to close cuts and sores. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;High blood sugar also weakens the immune system, making it harder to fight infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Additionally, the researchers behind the new study found diabetics were more likely to be older, smokers, insulin users and have heart failure, all of which weaken the immune system and vital organs, making the body a target for sepsis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Researchers in Australia found type 2 diabetics were up to 14 times more likely than non-diabetics to suffer sepsis (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Professor Wendy Davis, lead study author and professor at the University of &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/western-australia/index.html" id="mol-787a8c70-958d-11f0-8923-256e77754a14"&gt;Western Australia&lt;/a&gt;, said: 'An association between type 2 diabetes and sepsis has been noted in some earlier studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Our study, in a large community-based sample of adults, confirms a strong relationship even after adjustment for a number of potential risk factors and the competing risk of death from unrelated causes, which may have occurred in people at high risk of sepsis before they developed sepsis, thus leading to overestimation of the incidence of sepsis if ignored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The best way to prevent sepsis is to quit smoking, normalize high blood sugar and prevent the onset of the micro- and macrovascular complications of diabetes. That's why this study is important.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sepsis&lt;a target="_self" href="/health/sepsis/index.html" id="mol-6dee3a50-e854-11ee-9371-b5d203091076" class=""&gt; &lt;/a&gt;is a medical emergency that is caused by the body's extreme reaction to an infection. It occurs when chemicals released in the bloodstream cause the immune system to go haywire. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Instead of sending infection-fighting white blood cells to attack a foreign invader, it targets healthy tissues and organs such as the limbs and the lungs and kidneys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Infections that lead to sepsis most commonly start in the skin, urinary tract, lungs, or gastrointestinal tract, but almost any infection can lead to sepsis - starting in wounds as innocuous as paper cuts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But according to non-profit Sepsis Alliance, half of all cases are from an unknown pathogen. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sepsis kills 350,000 Americans adults every year and 75,000 children. That's done death every 90 seconds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The mortality rate ranges from 10 to 30 percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The latest sepsis data from the CDC has shown a slight uptick in sepsis deaths in the last three months, which experts warn could be due to a lack of cohesive sepsis strategy in the US&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Sepsis symptoms can closely resemble the flu, so look out for a very high or low temperature, sweating, extreme pain, clammy skin, dizziness, nausea, high heart rate, slurred speech, and confusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The new study, which is being presented this week at the Annual Meeting of the European Association for the Study of Diabetes (EASD), looked at the medical records of 157,000 adults between 2008 and 2011 from Australia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Of those, 1,430 had type 2 diabetes. They were matched with 5,720 individuals who were not diabetic based on age, sex and where they lived.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The average participant age was 66, and 52 percent were men. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers tracked their health status until they had a record of sepsis, died, or the study reached its end in 2021. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They found two percent of patients with type 2 diabetes were hospitalized for or with sepsis compared to 0.8 percent of their matched counterparts without diabetes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And during the average 10-year follow-up time, 12 percent of participants with type 2 diabetes suffered sepsis compared to five percent of their matched counterparts, a 2.3-fold increased risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The most notable difference was in diabetics ages 41 to 50, who were at 14.5 times more likely to develop sepsis than non-diabetics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Janice Holloway, 65, from Arizona, suffered an infection from an unknown pathogen, which quickly turned to sepsis - the first signs of which were a rash on the back of her leg and a high fever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Sepsis can affect patients of any age, including three-year-old Beauden Baumkitchner, who had both legs amputated after he scraped his knee and contracted staph bacteria &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers said people with type 2 diabetes were more likely to be older, male, indigenous, smokers, use insulin, have high blood pressure or have heart failure, all of which are independently associated with a greater risk of sepsis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;According to Sepsis Alliance, slow wound healing seen in diabetics also raises the risk, as contaminants that can seep into the wounds and infect the bloodstream, causing sepsis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And as glucose builds up in the blood, it attacks blood vessels, leading to poor blood flow to tissues. This makes it more difficult for blood to deliver oxygen to vital organs that are needed to fight infection. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Professor Davis said: 'Our study identifies several modifiable risk factors, including smoking, high blood sugar, and complications of diabetes, underscoring that there are steps individuals can take to potentially lower their risk of sepsis.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, the researchers cautioned the study is observational and cannot prove direct causation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:29:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxPU2ZZdS1LUXhyMEpWSnM5Uk5HZ1V5Tmg1eVpobmptR2Z3VV9BT3NkQVY2SW5yLUt6QnJzYjU4SV8wNjJqT01pS09zbmJ6MFZlVVZ4dDlSV0wydnVPbmlXZV9MNnFkdEVNZm9RMXpHVXRnenp0R0UwTVdmVlJJd1Etamg2akZBSm9DRUo3YVVlY3A0OGoyWUJPVS1qU19MN2E1ZWfSAacBQVVfeXFMT0dVWnB4WHRtSEVSWUhGdWVBQ2N1UnlhOEEwTTBFZUNHdVNjVjVyWnVTZ3hHZGNuU2dpVmlqWDJiYmNLR0xiTmkyU3hYbm5tOUtqNFZPVmJwQkpkc1JPekYxQm96Ym1FLXQ1NGlvVk1RcERZMmJlbzNkVFZrc3pPZmtWdjFEWGxndEZocHNvMEdDWnhwcXgxZmpEREdPaVdOa1JLTEZXUms</guid></item><item><title>家庭将男性的心理健康状况下降与疫苗接种后的斗争联系起来-特立尼达快报</title><link>https://trinidadexpress.com/newsextra/family-links-man-s-mental-health-decline-to-post-vaccine-struggles/article_920e50ed-f8a5-4dd4-a33f-00837d40cd49.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;• Lifeline has a toll-free number: 800-5588. They can also be contacted at 231-2824 and 220-3636.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 27-year-old man who had reportedly been battling depression and health complications since receiving a COVID-19 vaccine in 2020 was found dead at his family home in Marabella on Saturday, in what police have described as a suspected suicide by hanging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deceased, N’kosi Stephanas Layne, was discovered by relatives around 7 a.m. on Saturday. Officers from the Marabella Police Station were called to the scene shortly after 10:25 a.m., where they met family members and were shown to a small 10x10 bedroom downstairs in the house.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_top" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Layne’s body was found on the floor, with a brown curtain tied around his neck, which relatives had reportedly cut from the ceiling in an attempt to save his life. He was dressed in grey shorts and was bareback. Police noted ligature marks around the neck, discoloration of the lips, and no visible signs of violence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to family members, Layne had suffered a steady mental and physical decline over the past few years, which they believe began after he received a Sinopharm COVID-19 vaccine in late 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His grandparents, Evangeline and Andy Rahim, along with his mother, Joann Cooper, and aunt, Nicole Lamont, told police that following the vaccination, Layne experienced a range of health issues, including chronic insomnia, severe headaches, and a pre-existing heart condition. He also reportedly fell into a deep depression that the family struggled to manage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In search of relief, the family said they turned to alternative medicine and had been consulting with a herbal practitioner based in Tacarigua. However, Layne’s condition reportedly worsened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The grandparents told police that the last conversation they had with him was around 3a.m. on Thursday. Two days later, they found him hanging from the ceiling. Emergency medical personnel were called, but he was already deceased upon their arrival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scene was processed by Crime Scene Investigator WPC Nysus, along with Sgt Lee, Cpl Downes, PC Forbes, and PC Madho.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                &lt;p id="tncms-region-article_bottom_content" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Trinidad Express Newspapers</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:17:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6gFBVV95cUxOSkJiT2FoaV82X2ppTG9PZThEUEpvdTFiX2dyZzItdk5NM0d3RFRYZHBRVkhyRGZsYzZ0OWtCZWxITHZkSGJadWdnWndnak1zRDN2ZUFOUFp0Y2FXOTVFVV9sT2VGWWo1S29QQUlraVo2VVNFVk5NQjdsUVdQOUJMNkRON1hkMEhGdl9Vc3dscUpKM1hYSTlMZVJLbHFvWE1MMEc4WTdBaEtsdENHRVZlREtuYmlibl9sSG9wQllUSE9qV19fLTVEYl9vaExEX3R3RVctMUhZcERtY2YwY3lMWUxNUkFCREdCalHSAe8BQVVfeXFMUDFMajdXN19WOW45NzlNTkt5VjFNTHIzMlItTC1HTVlqdE1XMTlCSk9NSl90X2NnQURwN1JJa2hwdEs1Nmx0LUsyUUpITnpscXpMSUp0aS1IVTBxWDhJc0pmT1JjMGhjNlhycG9jNmxLVW9LSEwzaExzZGt0SUotb29xXy1jYXJWcFg1MzAtT05oRm9JUWpwcmp5dEk0dDBNT0QtaEtlRFdQNFhTVVJKOWdWdWRhU3p0ZHVtcDhrS1RpV1NGM056MWlIa1pyZTJHTlVORk13a2NCUnA3eEs3dmRScHNTQVVIMy1HS1BhQXc</guid></item><item><title>碧姬·马克龙（ Brigitte Macron ）在70岁时进行平腹运动- valleyvanguardonline.com</title><link>https://www.valleyvanguardonline.com/brigitte-macrons-go-to-exercise-for-a-flat-stomach-at-70-ampversion/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>valleyvanguardonline.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:10:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxPaFA5TGVkNmpzVEFTVzVVSVNWbTZPTWY3T3VoUG9LSUQ1dFpPOUNJRl82bHNRazNrbm13YmxTQmRHUGdaWXNjOThlWFdVRGpHNXF0dUItT1ZLVlg5aDd3VXgtVHFVQWI0SElaMW1RVWZBNU1yQzNxemJiMi02M0xIX0JoaWNabUtqN05UOTItMXdvOVFmczM1Y1pKVDhkZ0FjM2ZpdnNLX3M</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法， 8种高纤维谷物可以帮助你排便- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/8-high-fiber-cereals-to-help-you-poop-11816484</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cereals can be a convenient way to load up on fiber in the morning to help you poop.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The best cereals will have at least 4 grams of fiber and ideally are low in sugar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pay attention to serving sizes, which can vary depending on the cereal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If your digestion feels sluggish, you’re not alone. Many people experience constipation or slow bowel movements, and it’s often influenced by diet. One of the most effective fixes? Eating more fiber—yet most people fall short of the recommended 25 to 38 grams of daily fiber recommendations.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re pressed for time and want a quick, fiber-packed meal, cereal can be a surprisingly good choice. While some cereals resemble more of a dessert than a healthy meal, there are plenty of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/new-high-fiber-recipes-you-ll-want-to-make-from-breakfast-to-dinner-8673480" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;high-fiber, nutritious options&lt;/a&gt; out there. To help you navigate the cereal aisle, we’ve asked dietitians to share their top picks and provide useful tips for picking the best cereal to help you “go.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-food-for-life-ezekiel-49-sprouted-crunchy-cereal"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 1. Food for Life Ezekiel 4:9 Sprouted Crunchy Cereal &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_1-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon. Getty Images. EatingWell design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Food for Life’s &lt;a href="https://www.foodforlife.com/product/cereals/ezekiel-49-sprouted-whole-grain-cereal" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Ezekiel 4:9 Sprouted Crunchy Cereal&lt;/a&gt; is packed with fiber and nutrition. Per half-cup, it has 6 grams of fiber, 8 grams of protein and only 1 gram of added sugar, helping you stay full and satisfied. Made with sprouted grains, it may be gentler on digestion. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Nutrition info for ½ cup (57g) without milk:&lt;/strong&gt; 180 calories, 1 g total fat, 0 g saturated fat, 0 mg cholesterol, 35 g carbohydrates, 6 g fiber, 1 g sugar (1 g added sugars), 8 g protein, 160 mg sodium
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-post-shredded-wheat"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 2. Post Shredded Wheat &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_2-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon. Getty Images. EatingWell design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.postconsumerbrands.com/brands/shredded-wheat/products/shredded-wheat-original-big-biscuit-cereal/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Shredded Wheat&lt;/a&gt; has stood the test of time as a fiber-rich classic. A two-biscuit serving provides an impressive 7 grams of fiber, including 6 grams of insoluble fiber that &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/whole-grains-to-help-you-poop-11800440" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;supports healthy bowel movements&lt;/a&gt;. It also offers 15% of the Daily Value for phosphorus and 10% DV of zinc, magnesium and iron. With no added sugars or sodium, it’s a simple and nutritious choice. For extra fiber and flavor, top it with fruit, such as blueberries, strawberries or bananas.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Nutrition info for 2 biscuits (51g) without milk: &lt;/strong&gt;170 calories, 1 g total fat, 0 g saturated fat, 0 mg cholesterol, 41 g carbohydrates, 7 g fiber, 0 g sugar (0 g added sugars), 6 g protein, 0 mg sodium
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3-bobs-red-mill-7-grain-hot-cereal"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 3. Bob’s Red Mill 7-Grain Hot Cereal &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_3-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon. Getty Images. EatingWell design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.bobsredmill.com/product/7-grain-hot-cereal" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Bob’s Red Mill 7-Grain Hot Cereal&lt;/a&gt; is a warm, hearty option to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-much-fiber-should-you-be-eating-11752876" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;boost your fiber intake&lt;/a&gt;. Made with a blend of seven whole grains and seeds—wheat, rye, oats, triticale, brown rice, pearled barley, oat bran—it packs 6 grams of fiber in a ¼-cup serving. Cook it with milk for added protein and top it with fruit for even more fiber and nutrition.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Nutrition info for ¼ cup (40g) without milk:&lt;/strong&gt; 150 calories, 1 g total fat, 0 g saturated fat, 0 mg cholesterol, 30 g carbohydrates, 6 g fiber, 0 g sugar (0 g added sugars), 5 g protein, 0 mg sodium
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-4-grape-nuts"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 4. Grape-Nuts &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_4-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon. Getty Images. EatingWell design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.grapenuts.com/products/the-original/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Grape-Nuts&lt;/a&gt; are made with whole-grain wheat flour and malted barley flour, then twice-baked and ground into their signature crunchy nuggets. “I love a bowl of classic Grape-Nuts in the morning to keep everything moving,” says &lt;a href="https://pennsylvanianutritionservices.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;Alexandria Hardy, RDN, LDN&lt;/a&gt;. She adds that a ½-cup serving provides 7 grams of fiber, including 6 grams from insoluble fiber—the type that helps you poop.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Nutrition info for ½ cup (58g) without milk:&lt;/strong&gt; 200 calories, 1 g total fat, 0 g saturated fat, 0 mg cholesterol, 47 g carbohydrates, 7 g fiber, 5 g sugar (0 grams of added sugars), 6 g protein, 280 mg sodium
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-5-catalina-crunch-cinnamon-toast-cereal"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 5. Catalina Crunch Cinnamon Toast Cereal &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_5-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon. Getty Images. EatingWell design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://us.catalinacrunch.com/products/cinnamon-toast-cereal" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Catalina Crunch Cinnamon Toast&lt;/a&gt; packs both fiber and protein into your bowl, with 9 grams of fiber and 11 grams of protein per ½-cup serving. It’s made with chicory root fiber, pea protein and potato fiber and contains no added sugar. Instead, it uses monk fruit extract, making it a smart choice for people &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/lifestyle-tweaks-healthy-blood-sugar-levels-11792895" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;managing their blood sugar&lt;/a&gt; or following a lower-carb eating pattern.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Nutrition info for ½ cup (36g) without milk: &lt;/strong&gt;110 calories, 5 g total fat, 1 g saturated fat, 0 mg cholesterol, 14 g carbohydrates, 9 g fiber, 0 g sugar (0 g added sugars), 11 g protein, 110 mg sodium
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-6-all-bran-original"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 6. All-Bran Original &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_6-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon. Getty Images. EatingWell design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.wkkellogg.com/products/kellogg-s-all-bran-original-cereal-product" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;All-Bran Original&lt;/a&gt; is a top choice for fiber, delivering an impressive 12 grams of fiber per ⅔-cup serving—nearly half of your daily needs. It also has 25% of your daily iron, 10% of your daily vitamin D and B vitamins. For extra protein, 1 cup of milk adds an extra 8 grams of protein, but you could also add a scoop of peanut butter or mix it with strained (Greek-style) yogurt.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While this option does contain added sugars, this may be a worthwhile compromise for individuals who prefer a sweeter bran cereal.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Nutrition info for ⅔&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;cup (41g) without milk: &lt;/strong&gt;120 calories, 2 g total fat, 0 g saturated fat, 0 mg cholesterol, 32 g carbohydrates, 12 g fiber, 9 g sugar (8 g added sugars), 5 g protein, 95 mg sodium
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-7-kashi-go-protein--fiber-cereal-original"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 7. Kashi Go Protein &amp;amp; Fiber Cereal Original &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_7-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon. Getty Images. EatingWell design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.kashi.com/products/kashi-go-cereal-original" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Kashi Go Protein &amp;amp; Fiber Cereal Original&lt;/a&gt; delivers 12 grams of fiber and 12 grams of protein per serving, thanks to whole grains like oats, hard red wheat and barley. This combination slows digestion, supports steady energy and promotes regular bowel movements. While it contains more added sugars than some other options, the high fiber and protein content makes it a satisfying, gut-friendly choice.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Nutrition info for 1¼ cups (63g) without milk:&lt;/strong&gt; 180 calories, 2 g total fat, 0 g saturated fat, 0 mg cholesterol, 45 g carbohydrates, 12 g fiber, 9 g sugar (9 g added sugars), 12 g protein, 135 mg sodium
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-8-purely-elizabeth-honey-peanut-butter-superfood-cereal"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 8. Purely Elizabeth Honey Peanut Butter Superfood Cereal &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_8-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon. Getty Images. EatingWell design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://purelyelizabeth.com/products/honey-peanut-butter-superfood-cereal-with-vitamin-d" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Purely Elizabeth’s Honey Peanut Butter Superfood Cereal&lt;/a&gt; may be a mouthful to say, but it’s also packed with fiber. This crunchy cereal offers 5 grams of fiber from oats, sorghum, chia seeds and amaranth. These ancient grains and seeds deliver complex carbohydrates for steady energy and gut-friendly benefits. For example, sorghum is rich in dietary fiber and resistant starch, which can help slow digestion and support more regular bowel movements.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To bulk up the fiber content even more, add some fresh or frozen fruit on top.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Nutrition info for ⅔ cup (55g) without milk:&lt;/strong&gt; 240 calories, 8 g total fat, 4 g saturated fat, 0 mg cholesterol, 38 g carbohydrates, 5 g fiber, 7 g sugar (7 g added sugars), 5 g protein, 110 mg sodium.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-to-look-for-in-a-healthy-cereal"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What to Look For in a Healthy Cereal &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_63-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When choosing a cereal that &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7909480/best-foods-for-digestion/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;supports digestion and regularity&lt;/a&gt;, here’s what dietitians recommend checking on the label.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_64-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; High in Fiber &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://myfoodmychoicenutrition.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Tracy Colin, M.S., RD, LDN,&lt;/a&gt; recommends choosing a cereal that has at least 4 grams of fiber per serving to get closer to your daily fiber needs. Look for options that contain &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8031247/healthy-whole-grains-to-eat-more-fiber/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;whole grains like wheat, oats, sorghum or barley&lt;/a&gt;, which provide fiber and other gut-supporting nutrients.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_67-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_68-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; However, she cautions about overdoing it: “Some cereals can have over 15 grams per serving. Too much fiber at once can actually backfire, leaving you bloated or constipated,” says Colin. To support regular bowel movements, choose cereals with a mix of fiber-rich ingredients like whole grains, nuts and seeds.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_69-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_70-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Low in Sugar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_71-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://alissapalladinonutrition.squarespace.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Alissa Palladino, M.S., RDN, LD, CPT&lt;/a&gt;, recommends checking the Nutrition Facts panel and aiming for no more than about 10% of the Daily Value for added sugar, or around 5 grams per serving. That said, for those who don’t like the taste of high-fiber cereals on their own, a small amount of sugar can make it more palatable, which is why some options on this list are slightly higher.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_72-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_73-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Check the Serving Size &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_74-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Hardy points out that cereal serving sizes can vary a lot—from as little as ¼ cup for dense granolas to 1½ cups for lighter, puffed options like Kix. The FDA establishes serving sizes based on a cereal’s density and Reference Amounts Customarily Consumed (RACCs).&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; If you’re watching your fiber, sugar or calorie intake, it’s important to check the serving size so you don’t unintentionally double your portions.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_75-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_77-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_78-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_79-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If your digestion feels sluggish in the morning, a high-fiber cereal can help get things moving. Quick and convenient, cereal is an easy way to start the day with a good serving of fiber. Whether you prefer a childhood classic or a low-sugar option, look for cereals with at least 4 grams of fiber. Don’t forget to check the serving size to keep calories and sugar in check. For a simple, effective way to support regularity, stick with an all-time breakfast favorite: high-fiber cereal.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE4zc1pmM2JGYlZ4UEViYTVxTl9mdlNoWG56ZEZUQzJqeXdFVUVWNjdsQ3BJSlh2WUROVWhSZVo0TkgzdWFydkVXUGNJckhDdEUzdGRQd1hFSXQwVU1seGNLS2FYQ3h2YjJGdjc1d0RDbWZHQ25MeEVfU2JFWV9wQQ</guid></item><item><title>每年14,000例新病例：胰腺衰竭的警告信号- valleyvanguardonline.com</title><link>https://www.valleyvanguardonline.com/14000-new-cases-each-year-the-warning-signs-your-pancreas-is-failing/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>valleyvanguardonline.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:05:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxOYllFZ2ZBdzQyZFloVmxUNGh5RUYyajZTZ0NmZmN3OUtFdlpudVFfRmxxMkQzVFk4UW80cVdibnBxcktpb1p6YnpoaDl5NS04TnJjQW9vZ1RsZ0tqTnRveWlFYnJIMkhhNGQySGFwTlZCdUVFa1hlX2o1Tjg1dkdCalVjSWlwdE1EbmhrM1BZSEVHNHlvT1V2ZWlwQUdvZzJ2aFlxeXZFdjByQQ</guid></item><item><title>最大规模的同类研究揭示了阅读障碍背后的基因- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/largest-study-of-its-kind-reveals-the-genes-behind-dyslexia</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A massive study involving genetic data from over 1.2 million people has identified over a dozen new gene regions associated with dyslexia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We have produced the largest genetic study of dyslexia to date," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41398-025-03514-0"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the study authors, led by University of Edinburgh molecular geneticist Hayley Mountford.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dyslexia is a neurodevelopmental brain difference that can make certain aspects of modern life challenging. In the current study, participants had challenges reading and/or writing, although that is not the case in all people with dyslexia; some find other aspects of verbal processing more challenging than their peers, such as spelling and grammar, or following verbal instructions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/several-psychiatric-disorders-share-the-same-root-cause-study-reveals"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;S&lt;/strong&gt;everal Psychiatric Disorders Share The Same Root Cause, Study Reveals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_175099" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-175099" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/ChildHoldingBookOpen-e1758584257151.jpg" alt="child holding book open" class="wp-image-175099 size-full" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-175099" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;(&lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/person-wearing-blue-long-sleeved-shirt-reading-book-g3O4mCifZEk"&gt;Josh Applegate/Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;As with the other neurodivergences, like  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/autism-spectrum-disorder" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73013" data-postid="175089" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;autism&lt;/a&gt; or  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-adhd" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73112" data-postid="175089" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;ADHD&lt;/a&gt;, dyslexia comes with &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/having-dyslexia-could-mean-your-brain-is-wired-to-make-better-decisions"&gt;advantages as well&lt;/a&gt;, such as &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ridd.2021.104036"&gt;higher non-verbal creativity&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/brainsci12010027"&gt;Past twin studies&lt;/a&gt; have suggested that genes strongly determine dyslexia, so Mountford and colleagues took up the challenge of pinpointing what those genetic associations are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their genome-wide study identified 80 regions associated with dyslexia, including 36 regions not previously reported as significant. Thirteen of these regions were novel to science, with no prior link to dyslexia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of the newly associated genes are involved in early brain development. And, as expected, some of them are &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/09567976241293999"&gt;shared with ADHD&lt;/a&gt;, which can often occur alongside dyslexia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the vast datasets, the researchers also found correlations between dyslexia and measures of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/large-body-map-study-suggests-chronic-pain-comes-in-9-distinct-types"&gt;chronic pain&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The underlying mechanism remains unelucidated, however, the genetic overlap between pain-related phenotypes and neurodevelopmental traits may hint at a shared biological basis," Mountford and team &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41398-025-03514-0"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; in their paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With these newly identified gene associations, researchers might finally start unraveling these connections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41398-025-03514-0"&gt;Translational Psychiatry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:02:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPZ0oyUDE2YXhER21FOEs5YTlKZ3Y1SDBVNzZTYVFCbkpRMHZlOVRQbjJMcG1IME5uNmZpRUp5cmdpYVVoUmQ4bHBOanFzb213cS1GNzk5ZEprRFRycm9ITGNQcXljU1I4NUJCcmI2dHpwamRCb0R0aW94MDBjdGhwanpUaWJ3Z3c0QXgzR2dLc0JsZw</guid></item><item><title>以下是我对重度抑郁症患者养育子女的了解--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/09/28/parenting-with-major-depression/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6FC7YCBN5NEHHPGHZWGIP63PZM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I was just 11 when I had my first experience with &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/12/01/depression-coping-strategies/" target="_blank"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt;. I was feeling alienated at a new school and had body image issues, which were exacerbated by my parents’ divorce. Since then, I have dealt with despondency in cycles. When I experienced heartbreak, a layoff or a &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/10/13/friendship-breakup-healthy-relationship/" target="_blank"&gt;friendship breakup&lt;/a&gt;, it affected me in ways that could interfere with my ability to function in my day-to-day life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:01:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPZm84QUMzb3Y5emwxUWgteGFIeDFQQ2dzcWpFWHFLeTZkSC1tT3NXSDJSZ2xaWG9odHEwcWJtQ3RuU19iWGpxTGtQZFc1dDVwSEZ6MVkwcXUzekZvcjJRWjNiUkVyUnc2RnN6bHRwMFFuY184YXdTYlpLM0FBdllBby1QNjlMOFVPeGpn</guid></item><item><title>自1980年以来，美国城市火灾死亡人数急剧下降- vox.com</title><link>https://www.vox.com/future-perfect/463046/urban-fires-death-united-states-firefighters-accidents-new-york</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="zephr-anchor" class="_1agbrix10"&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;My family lives in a heavily-trafficked part of Brooklyn, and most nights you’ll hear the occasional whine of fire engine sirens through our living room window. But the torrent of sirens early on the morning of September 17 was enough to briefly rouse me from bed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;I found out later that day that a five-alarm fire involving more than 200 firefighters had &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/20/nyregion/red-hook-warehouse-fire.html"&gt;ripped through a 150-year-old artists’ warehouse&lt;/a&gt; in the neighboring area of Red Hook. It was one of the biggest New York has experienced this year, and though no one was killed, the work of more than 500 artists may have been destroyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The Red Hook fire was a tragedy for New York’s already struggling artistic community, but it got me thinking about the state of urban fires in the US today. As long as cities have existed, fires have been a threat. Rome &lt;a href="https://www.thecollector.com/did-emperor-nero-start-the-great-fire-of-rome/"&gt;famously burned to the ground&lt;/a&gt; in 64 CE — though not, as was long assumed, at the hands of the Emperor Nero — while the diarist Samuel Pepys &lt;a href="https://notesfromtheuk.com/2025/08/08/samuel-pepys-the-great-fire-of-london-and-a-wheel-of-parmesan-cheese/#:~:text=%E2%80%9CNobody%2C%20to%20my%20sight%2C,soldiers%20if%20they%20were%20needed."&gt;described&lt;/a&gt; how “even the very stones of churches” burned in London’s Great Fire of 1666.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Here in the US, the Great Chicago Fire of 1871 &lt;a href="https://www.badgeandwallet.com/news/10-most-memorable-fires-us-history#:~:text=October%208%2C%201871%20was%20an,was%20also%20largely%20under%20reported."&gt;consumed&lt;/a&gt; 3.3 square miles of the city, and left 100,000 people homeless. As late as the 1970s, the Bronx in New York was for a time averaging &lt;a href="https://shoeleather.podcasts.library.columbia.edu/podcast/the-bronx-is-burning/"&gt;as many as two fires &lt;em&gt;per hour&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, part of an endless conflagration that ultimately destroyed 80 percent of the borough’s housing over the course of the decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;As the Red Hook disaster shows, fire is still a threat, especially to older buildings. But beneath the sound of those sirens is a story of underappreciated progress toward ever greater safety. Compared with 1980, the per-capita civilian fire death rate &lt;a href="https://www.nxtbook.com/nxtbooks/nfpa/journal_2024winter/index.php"&gt;has fallen&lt;/a&gt; by roughly two-thirds — from about 28.6 deaths per million people to around 11 per million in 2023. Total reported fires are also &lt;a href="https://www.nxtbook.com/nxtbooks/nfpa/journal_2023winter/index.php?startid=58&amp;amp;utm_source=chatgpt.com"&gt;down&lt;/a&gt; by half over that time period, and injuries have fallen by more than half.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;As the terrible Los Angeles fires at the start of the year demonstrated, the &lt;a href="/climate/398719/los-angeles-fire-reconstruction-insurance-housing"&gt;growing risk to urban areas from wildfires&lt;/a&gt; presents a new and dangerous threat to US cities. But even with those rare but spectacular disasters, America’s homes and buildings are far less vulnerable to deadly fires than they once were. And we’ve gotten here through the accumulation of small improvements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smoke alarms that work&lt;/strong&gt;: There may be no single more important fire safety feature than the humble smoke alarm. While the very first automatic smoke fire alarm was invented in 1890, as late as 1977, less than a quarter of all households in the US had smoke alarms, which is one of those facts of the recent past that leaves me gobsmacked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Today alarms are &lt;a href="https://www.nfpa.org/education-and-research/research/nfpa-research/fire-statistical-reports/smoke-alarms-in-us-home-fires?utm_source=chatgpt.com"&gt;now present&lt;/a&gt; in the vast majority of US homes — and when they’re working, the death rate per reported home fire is about 60 percent lower than in homes without a working alarm. Modern building codes also now usually require interconnected systems and alarms in bedrooms. But they have to be checked consistently to make sure they actually work — a large share of fatal fires still occur in homes with no alarm &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt; one that failed to operate. And battery-powered smoke alarms are safer than those that are hardwired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automatic sprinklers: &lt;/strong&gt;If a fire does break out, more buildings have automatic sprinklers to quench them. Sprinklers can make a huge difference: the per-fire civilian death rate is &lt;a href="https://www.nfpa.org/education-and-research/research/nfpa-research/fire-statistical-reports/us-experience-with-sprinklers?utm_source=chatgpt.com"&gt;roughly&lt;/a&gt; 90 percent lower when sprinklers are present than when no automatic extinguishing system is installed. Most new multifamily houses and apartment buildings are required to have them by code, and they’ve become more common in other new construction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Safer furnishings and interior finishes.&lt;/strong&gt; After years of debate, the US &lt;a href="https://www.cpsc.gov/Newsroom/News-Releases/2021/New-Federal-Safety-Standard-for-Upholstered-Furniture-Fires-Goes-into-Effect?utm_source=chatgpt.com"&gt;adopted&lt;/a&gt; a national smolder-resistance standard for upholstered furniture in 2021, which federalized an existing California code. Upholstery that’s less prone to ignite from a dropped cigarette or similar ember means fewer small room fires becoming structure conflagrations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Less smoking — and “fire-safe” cigarettes.&lt;/strong&gt; Cigarettes, man — they can kill you in so many ways, including by accidentally igniting a house fire. In 1980 there were &lt;a href="https://www.maine.gov/future/sites/maine.gov.dps.fmo/files/inline-files/nfpa_home_fires_started_by_smoking.pdf"&gt;an estimated 70,800 smoking-related cigarette home fires&lt;/a&gt; leading to 1,820 deaths. But cigarette smoking in the US has &lt;a href="/public-health/410443/vaping-conundrum-public-health-youth-ecigarettes"&gt;fallen significantly&lt;/a&gt;, meaning fewer cigarettes to trigger fires, and all states now require so-called “fire-safe” cigarettes that are less likely to ignite. By 2016, the number of smoking-related fires had fallen to 16,500, causing 660 deaths, even as both population and the number of buildings had increased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Better electrical and heating safety.&lt;/strong&gt; Modern building codes now &lt;a href="https://www.cpsc.gov/s3fs-public/afci.pdf?utm_source=chatgpt.com"&gt;require&lt;/a&gt; safeguards like arc-fault circuit interrupters (AFCIs) that cut power when wires start arcing behind walls, which can risk sparking sudden fires. While heating equipment is still a major cause of fires, heating–related fires &lt;a href="https://www.usfa.fema.gov/downloads/pdf/statistics/fire-estimate-summary-series.pdf?utm_source=chatgpt.com"&gt;fell&lt;/a&gt; by a third between 2010 and 2019, thanks in part to &lt;a href="https://code-authorities.ul.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/ul_ElectricHeaterTipoverProtection.pdf?utm_source=chatgpt.com"&gt;appliance improvements&lt;/a&gt; like automatic space heater shutoffs and temperature controls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p id="the-boring-important-work-of-making-homes-fire-resistant" class="_7ka5u1 _7ka5u0 duet--article--standard-heading xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;h2 class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup"&gt;The boring, important work of making homes fire-resistant&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;These fire safety improvements didn’t just happen. Each required regulators, often learning from fire disasters of the past, to &lt;a href="https://www.iccsafe.org/building-safety-journal/bsj-dives/fema-highlights-the-life-and-property-savings-of-building-codes/#:~:text=More%20Than%20$1%20Billion%20Saved,Introduction%20of%20fire%20sprinkler%20systems"&gt;institute new building codes and new product safety requirements&lt;/a&gt;. Public service campaigns pushed people to get smoke alarms for their homes and warned them of risky behaviors like smoking in bed. These are the engines of progress that get overlooked, but have directly saved countless lives over the course of decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;We can never know when a fire is prevented. But maybe my life was saved — and maybe yours as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The progress has been uneven. Most US fire deaths still happen where we sleep: homes account for the clear majority of civilian fire fatalities. The risks &lt;a href="https://www.usfa.fema.gov/downloads/pdf/statistics/v21i3.pdf?utm_source=chatgpt.com"&gt;concentrate&lt;/a&gt; among older adults, people with disabilities, and lower-income households living in older buildings, where missing alarms, space-heater misuse, or unsafe extension cords are more common. And we can &lt;a href="https://stories.tamu.edu/news/2025/01/14/los-angeles-fires-demonstrate-rising-threat-of-wildfires-in-urban-areas/#:~:text=WUI%20areas%20are%20often%20(though,especially%20vulnerable%20to%20wildfire%20hazards."&gt;expect the risk of wildfires&lt;/a&gt;, including those that directly threaten cities, will only grow in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;But we shouldn’t miss how far we’ve come from the days when the Bronx — and neighborhoods throughout the country — &lt;a href="http://decadeoffire.com/"&gt;was burning&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;A version of this story originally appeared in the Good News newsletter. &lt;a href="/pages/good-news-newsletter-signup"&gt;Sign up here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>vox.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxNcFlRRlFFbElEUDRzWlpqTkhmTU96MWN3SFZYc1IzN0VSSEhwNDBHeWYzMzhkVTVPWlBNWHRtdlJ2VXFjTEk2QWxYRW1oREdvaTJaZ2NFVVB2Q2lpOTFaXzUySEx4ZUVGZ0lCRlBfU2tqSmNTMXdySERTTFVJR3RQaXZZdUlkclE3YWNNOHBNcHFTeXVIUnJ4QVlqVk9LOUxhYTVndndnblg</guid></item><item><title>“我使用人工智能来发现我的皮肤癌–它挽救了我的生命” -《独立报》</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/ai-skin-cancer-nhs-melanoma-b2835223.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 eWHDRo sc-jbiisr-1" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 dFpFuY"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 iBibVd"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 fXvmgM"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 juUDRT"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 cqPbFA"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 rAFIl sc-hez36s-16 jZSKtc"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 PdmgT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 hJPJVF"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 dDhojf"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 cUJDWn"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 jEZjIj"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 jEZjIj"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 jEZjIj"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 gunhQQ"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 keLMOw sc-aja53j-7 eMEmGu"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 dHXFkr"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 jrwZqm"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 hUgQwJ sc-culv3z-0 eifaJK sc-a5wy94-0 hyKPon"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;When 46-year-old Lynsey Robertson helped launch a new &lt;a href="/topic/ai"&gt;AI &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="/life-style/health-and-families/skin-cancer-symptoms-melanoma-sun-safety-b2813328.html"&gt;skin cancer&lt;/a&gt; screening tool at the &lt;a href="/topic/gp"&gt;GP surgery&lt;/a&gt; where she worked, she knew she would be among the first to try it out – but she never expected to become one of its first patients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just hours after Lynsey used the technology, the system flagged a &lt;a href="/news/health/melanoma-cancer-awareness-symptoms-signs-b2743066.html"&gt;mole&lt;/a&gt; on her skin as high risk, which was soon revealed to be a deadly &lt;a href="/topic/melanoma"&gt;melanoma&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Lynsey, an office manager at Buckshaw Village Surgery in Preston, &lt;a href="/topic/lancashire"&gt;Lancashire&lt;/a&gt;, had been overseeing the rollout of its artificial intelligence &lt;a href="/topic/skin-cancer"&gt;skin cancer&lt;/a&gt; screening service. Curious, she decided to scan a patch of skin that she had largely ignored but that had slowly changed colour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The system flagged the lesion for urgent review under the &lt;a href="/topic/nhs"&gt;NHS’s&lt;/a&gt; two-week suspected cancer pathway. That same day, Lynsey’s referral was sent off to Chorley Hospital. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I couldn’t believe it,” she said. “I just kept thinking, what if I hadn’t said anything?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-left"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 gAZoaM"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/26/14/15/Lynsey-Roberston-ignored-her-mole-for-years.png" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/26/14/15/Lynsey-Roberston-ignored-her-mole-for-years.png?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/26/14/15/Lynsey-Roberston-ignored-her-mole-for-years.png?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Lynsey Robertson ignored her mole for years" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-346242"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 bpFomM hgzWpY"&gt;Lynsey Robertson ignored her mole for years&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 CXMrn"&gt; (Supplied)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mole didn’t hurt and although friends had occasionally asked about it, she had always dismissed it, assuming it wasn’t serious enough to bother a doctor with. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’d had it for years,” she said. “It wasn’t causing me any trouble. I thought I’d be wasting the GP’s time.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was quickly booked in for minor surgery to remove the mole, but was diagnosed days later with malignant &lt;a href="/topic/melanoma"&gt;melanoma&lt;/a&gt;, an aggressive form of skin cancer that can spread rapidly through the body. Lynsey then underwent a second procedure to remove all cancerous cells, which was successful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She is now urging others not to ignore changes in their skin or unusual marks or moles, saying that had she not tested the technology at her office, “who knows what could have happened”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Developed by Skin Analytics, the cancer detection system &lt;a href="/news/uk/home-news/nhs-people-britons-national-institute-for-health-and-care-excellence-b2742713.html"&gt;uses AI to analyse images of lesions&lt;/a&gt; and detect potential signs of skin cancer. The software company claims to have a 99.9 per cent accuracy in ruling out melanoma. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 fIrxWS"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/26/14/31/Skin-Analytics-developed-the-technology-DERM-(Deep-Ensemble-for-Recognition-of-Malignancy).jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/26/14/31/Skin-Analytics-developed-the-technology-DERM-(Deep-Ensemble-for-Recognition-of-Malignancy).jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/26/14/31/Skin-Analytics-developed-the-technology-DERM-(Deep-Ensemble-for-Recognition-of-Malignancy).jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Skin Analytics developed the Deep Ensemble for Recognition of Malignancy technology" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-346243"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 bpFomM hgzWpY"&gt;Skin Analytics developed the Deep Ensemble for Recognition of Malignancy technology&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 CXMrn"&gt; (Skin Analytics)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Healthcare workers can take a photo of suspicious patches of skin on a smartphone with a high-quality magnifying lens attached. The images are then assessed by &lt;a href="/topic/ai"&gt;AI&lt;/a&gt;, and any lesion that is flagged will then be further reviewed by a dermatologist. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The technology, which has been deployed across the country, has been conditionally approved for the next three years and has assessed more than 170,000 &lt;a href="/topic/nhs"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt; patients since 2020. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rapid adoption of &lt;a href="/news/health/ai-depression-mental-illness-research-b2828460.html"&gt;artificial intelligence in healthcare&lt;/a&gt; has sparked debate in the UK as some voice concerns around data security,&lt;a href="/news/health/ai-healthcare-patients-nhs-b2732070.html"&gt; data bias&lt;/a&gt;, and a lack of human empathy. In its 10-year health plan for England, the government said it would “make the NHS the most AI-enabled health system in the world with AI seamlessly integrated into clinical pathways.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 aagrY"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/02/24/14/02/01JMVC5JY0X5KRDZSJK0FBCR8Q.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/02/24/14/02/01JMVC5JY0X5KRDZSJK0FBCR8Q.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/02/24/14/02/01JMVC5JY0X5KRDZSJK0FBCR8Q.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="The NHS employs AI in hospitals and clinics" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-346244"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 bpFomM hgzWpY"&gt;The NHS employs AI in hospitals and clinics&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 CXMrn"&gt; (King’s College London/PA)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this week, health secretary &lt;a href="/topic/wes-streeting"&gt;Wes Streeting&lt;/a&gt; said: “The AI revolution is here, and we are arming staff with the latest ground-breaking technology, so patients get faster and smarter care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This government is reinstating the UK’s position as a technology superpower - driving vital investment and economic growth as we build an NHS fit for the 21st century.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The skin cancer screening technology is the world's first AI legally authorised to detect cancer without a doctor present, according to Skin Analytics. It says that polling of 2,000 people found that 73 per cent believe the NHS has a duty of care to use technology that has proven benefits for patients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-iii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Urgent skin cancer referrals have skyrocketed in the UK in the last decade. According to the NHS, more than 17,000 people are diagnosed with melanoma each year, and around 2,300 people die annually. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A report from Cancer Research this month found that just half of the UK’s cancer patients were being &lt;a href="/news/health/ai-nhs-app-hospital-admissions-waiting-lists-b2827458.html"&gt;diagnosed within NHS England’s target &lt;/a&gt;of 28 days. According to Skin Analytics, 71 per cent of people believe regulated AI could help reduce NHS wait times. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 10:47:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPUkM4THdsSEpidDlYU0pLeXZXb290b24xTm9GZGo0R3ZqREt5NzdJZXkyRjdRMmdHUVFNYXBWQ3JkWEJPOVBTQ3FRRWt0dFR3NTA5STdaeUQxWTktQVVrc01KNjdFQlNVc0pKSENSSkFaZU0wWWdNQU5GWXE0eHZVaXk2UzVCdWp6Vkc0</guid></item><item><title>可以改善血糖和减少体脂肪的热带水果- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/the-tropical-fruit-that-may-improve-blood-sugar-and-cut-body-fat/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content cf entry-content content-spacious"&gt;

		
				
		&lt;figure id="attachment_488482" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-488482" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mango-With-Slices-on-Table.jpg"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-488482 size-large" src="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mango-With-Slices-on-Table-777x518.jpg" alt="Mango With Slices on Table" srcset="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mango-With-Slices-on-Table-777x518.jpg 777w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mango-With-Slices-on-Table-400x267.jpg 400w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mango-With-Slices-on-Table-768x512.jpg 768w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mango-With-Slices-on-Table-1536x1024.jpg 1536w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mango-With-Slices-on-Table-150x100.jpg 150w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mango-With-Slices-on-Table-450x300.jpg 450w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mango-With-Slices-on-Table-1200x800.jpg 1200w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mango-With-Slices-on-Table.jpg 2000w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-488482" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;A new study shows that mangoes, despite their high sugar content, may help prevent diabetes more effectively than low-sugar snacks. Credit: Shutterstock&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A pioneering study by a George Mason University researcher demonstrates the benefits of foods containing natural sugars compared to those with added sugars.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you were offered two snacks, one with seven grams of sugar and another with more than 30 grams, the healthier pick might seem obvious. But the choice is not always so straightforward. Having less sugar does not automatically make a food better for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the nearly 100 million adults in the United States currently living with prediabetes, the idea of a fruit that could help lower the risk of diabetes might sound unlikely. Tropical fruits typically contain between ten and 50 grams of sugar, with mangoes landing near the upper limit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On that basis alone, they might appear to be a poor option. Yet research led by clinical nutrition scientist Raedeh Basiri suggests otherwise. Her work shows that mangoes, even with their higher sugar content compared to many low-sugar snacks, may provide protective benefits for people with prediabetes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It is not just the sugar content that matters, but the overall food context that matters,” said Basiri, assistant professor in George Mason’s Department of Nutrition and Food Studies. This study is the first long-term clinical trial to demonstrate both metabolic and body composition benefits of mangoes in prediabetes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Simply put, it’s more than the sugar in the food; it’s about the whole food. The sugars naturally found in mangoes and other fruits are complemented by fiber and other vitamins and nutrients that offer additional health benefits. Food with added sugar, such as breakfast cereals, and even low-sugar snack options, may not have the same nutritional value and can even increase diabetes risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Whole Fruits in Diabetes Prevention&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The goal is to encourage people to include whole fruits, like mango, as part of healthy eating behaviors and practical dietary strategies for diabetes prevention,” said Basiri. “Individuals at high risk of diabetes should not only focus on the sugar content of foods, but on how sugars are delivered.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basiri and her team split study participants into two groups; one group received a fresh mango daily, while the other group was given a low-sugar granola bar each day. Over six months, researchers measured participants’ blood glucose levels, bodily responses to &lt;span class="glossaryLink" aria-describedby="tt" data-cmtooltip="cmtt_4cb72805779a46424113c0172c95f83d" data-gt-translate-attributes='[{"attribute":"data-cmtooltip", "format":"html"}]' tabindex="0" role="link"&gt;insulin&lt;/span&gt;, and body fat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the conclusion of the study, findings revealed that the high-sugar mango (32 grams of sugar) proved more beneficial than a low-sugar granola bar (11 grams of sugar). The group that consumed the daily mango showed improved blood glucose control, enhanced insulin sensitivity, and reduced body fat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference: “Daily Mango Intake Improves Glycemic and Body Composition Outcomes in Adults with Prediabetes: A Randomized Controlled Study” by Raedeh Basiri, Kallie Dawkins, Saiful Singar, Lauren T. Ormsbee, Neda S. Akhavan, Robert C. Hickner and Bahram H. Arjmandi, 25 August 2025, &lt;i&gt;Foods&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/foods14172971"&gt;DOI: 10.3390/foods14172971&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This study was funded by the National Mango Board. The authors declare no other potential conflicts of interest. The funders had no role in the design of the study, in the collection, analysis, interpretation of data, or the decision to publish results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Never miss a breakthrough: &lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/newsletter/"&gt;Join the SciTechDaily newsletter.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				
		
		
		
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 10:45:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxNMi1mTGc2WnFHeEFXMTc5QmotQURzSXBXdmFsZ2xwTm1CaEZmQWJzMU0tTDRfUUZIQ1dTem51aVRHWlVCeGlTZENRbzZIU0ZmTjJ3WjUwWUxJdkx2NUczS0o2NEdIVmhfLUZvWHptUVdUV3gtazBlVDYyU1I2SE5TVlBjQUN0Ym02eFYzb2xDM0poSGln</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，类风湿性关节炎在疼痛前几年无声无息地开始-今日医学新闻</title><link>https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/rheumatoid-arthritis-silently-starts-years-before-pain-study</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-12va8w7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="css-yhe8zq"&gt;&lt;span class="css-rwmw5v"&gt;&lt;span class="css-mjp0j9"&gt;&lt;picture class="css-16pk1is"&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/09/arthritis-prevention -GettyImages-960937956-Header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 1190px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/09/arthritis-prevention -GettyImages-960937956-Header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 990px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/09/arthritis-prevention -GettyImages-960937956-Header-1024x575.jpg 879w" media="(min-width: 768px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/09/arthritis-prevention%E2%80%AF-GettyImages-960937956-Header-1024x575.jpg" alt="A woman jogging in a field against a backdrop of a clear sky" class="css-1jytyml"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;hl-share-overlay class="css-1mqo1cs"&gt;&lt;a class="icon-hl-pinterest css-11oz8gb" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" data-event="Any Page|Image Pinterest Click|Icon Clicked" data-element-event="OPEN|CONTENTBLOCK|Any Page|Article Body|BUTTON|Image Widget Pinterest Click|" href="https://www.pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicalnewstoday.com%2Farticles%2Frheumatoid-arthritis-silently-starts-years-before-pain-study&amp;amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.post.rvohealth.io%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fsites%2F3%2F2025%2F09%2Farthritis-prevention%E2%80%AF-GettyImages-960937956-Header-1024x575.jpg&amp;amp;description=Rheumatoid%20arthritis%20begins%20years%20before%20symptoms%2C%20study%20finds" title="Share on Pinterest" data-pin-custom="true" data-share-url="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/09/arthritis-prevention -GettyImages-960937956-Header-1024x575.jpg"&gt;&lt;span class="css-z1zfa"&gt;Share on Pinterest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-share-overlay&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;figcaption class="css-13b3g0x"&gt;Scientists have found that rheumatoid arthritis may begin years before symptoms start showing. Cavan Images/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rheumatoid arthritis is a chronic autoimmune condition that cannot be cured but can be treated to prevent its progression.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Individuals at risk of developing rheumatoid arthritis can be identified 3-5 years prior to symptom onset based on autoantibody levels, but only 30-60% of individuals expressing these autoantibodies develop this condition.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A recent study has identified changes in the immune profile or signature of individuals at risk for developing rheumatoid arthritis as they progress in the disease.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;b&gt;These findings could help with detecting rheumatoid arthritis early and &lt;/b&gt;developing more effective preemptive therapies.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;hl-trusted-source source="PubMed Central" rationale="Highly respected database from the National Institutes of Health"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK441999/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Rheumatoid arthritis (RA)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; is an autoimmune condition that currently has no cure; however, researchers are trying to find ways to detect it early in hopes of preventing its progression.&lt;/span&gt; One area scientists have focused on is biomarkers in the blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Individuals with rheumatoid arthritis exhibit elevated levels of autoantibodies several years prior to the onset of the disease and its characteristic symptoms — such as pain and swelling in the joints. While these antibodies are useful in predicting whether a person will develop RA, a significant portion of individuals with these antibodies do not develop this condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A recent study published in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/scitranslmed.adt7214" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Science Translational Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; characterized the changes in individuals’ immune systems as they progressed from being at risk of developing rheumatoid arthritis to actually showing clinical symptoms. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Characterizing this immune profile in at-risk individuals who progress to clinical rheumatoid arthritis could allow the early detection of this condition and the development of preemptive therapies for this at-risk population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study’s author, &lt;a href="https://vchs.ucsd.edu/about/leadership/firestein.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Gary Friestein&lt;/a&gt;, MD, senior associate vice chancellor for health sciences at the University of California, San Diego School of Medicine, said, “Most people who are at-risk for RA never develop the disease. That makes prevention studies difficult because some individuals who do not need therapy will be treated with medicines with potential side effects.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We hope that the findings from this study will directly support new ways to predict RA as well as potentially identify targets for prevention trials,” added the study’s co-author, &lt;a href="https://som.cuanschutz.edu/Profiles/Faculty/Profile/17168" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Kevin Deane,&lt;/a&gt; MD, Professor of Medicine at the University of Colorado Anschutz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rheumatoid arthritis is an autoimmune condition in which the body mistakenly produces an immune response to healthy tissue, specifically the lining that covers the joints. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disease-modifying drugs used for the treatment of RA cannot reverse the damage, but can prevent the progression of the disease and help manage the condition. However, studies suggest that &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/rheumatology/article/64/1/65/7816327" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;5 to 27%&lt;/a&gt; of individuals with rheumatoid arthritis do not respond to these treatments, and relapse is also common after remission in individuals who respond to treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early detection of individuals at risk of developing rheumatoid arthritis can help prevent the condition from progressing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Currently, once someone develops the swollen joints of RA, the disease is usually ‘forever,’ meaning that they will need to be on treatments for life. Furthermore, worldwide, RA affects millions of people’s lives and costs billions of dollars to manage,” said Deane.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If we find ways to prevent the first swollen joints in RA, or even ‘reset’ the immune system in an at-risk stage, this could lead to people never getting full-blown RA — or having a much milder form of disease. That could have huge benefits for individuals’ well-being, as well as for public health.”&lt;br&gt;— Kevin Deane, MD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Individuals with rheumatoid arthritis exhibit elevated levels of anti-citrullinated protein antibodies (ACPA) and rheumatoid factor (RF) 3-5 years prior to the onset of clinical symptoms. Approximately 30-60% of individuals with elevated ACPA and RF levels go on to develop rheumatoid arthritis. In other words, ACPA and RF levels are not accurate predictors of progression to RA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attempts are currently underway to develop preemptive treatments to prevent the development of rheumatoid arthritis in the at-risk population expressing ACPA and RF. For instance, studies have shown that the drug &lt;a href="https://linkinghub.elsevier.com/retrieve/pii/S0140-6736(23)02650-8" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;abatacept&lt;/a&gt; can reduce the risk of rheumatoid arthritis development in this at-risk population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The characterization of the changes in the immune profile of at-risk individuals who develop RA could help understand the mechanism of the disease and more effectively target the subset of at-risk individuals who progress to develop RA symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study’s author, &lt;a href="https://alleninstitute.org/person/mark-gillespie/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Mark Gillespie&lt;/a&gt;, Ph.D., Assistant Investigator at the Allen Institute, explained, “Prior to this study, the field lacked an understanding of the biology of the ‘at-risk’ period and the changes that occur when individuals who are at-risk for RA go on to develop clinical disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the present study, the researchers examined the changes in the immune profiles of at-risk individuals who later developed rheumatoid arthritis, referred to as converters. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The immune profiles of converters were compared with the profiles of at-risk individuals who did not develop RA, referred to as non-converters, and healthy individuals who showed absence or very low levels of ACPA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study consisted of 45 at-risk individuals, with 16 of them developing rheumatoid arthritis during the follow-up period, and a group of 11 individuals with early clinical rheumatoid arthritis. The control group consisted of 38 healthy individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that at-risk individuals exhibited increased levels of inflammatory proteins in their circulation compared with healthy controls at the start of the study. This sign of systemic inflammation was present in at-risk individuals, regardless of whether they developed rheumatoid arthritis during the follow-up duration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Similarly, there was an increase in the number of immune cells, such as &lt;hl-trusted-source source="PubMed Central" rationale="Highly respected database from the National Institutes of Health"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK557618/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;monocytes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt;, that are involved in inflammation in both converters and non-converters. Moreover, these immune cells showed increased expression of inflammatory genes and proteins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers were unable to detect any differences in gene or protein expression in immune cells between converters and non-converters at the start of the study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers then characterized changes within the group of converters from the time of their last visit without clinical symptoms to their next visit when they were first diagnosed with clinical RA. These changes in the immune profile of converters were compared with those in healthy controls over a similar time frame.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Autoimmune conditions are caused by the immune system’s failure to distinguish between the body’s own proteins and foreign proteins or antigens from germs. Autoimmune conditions are characterized by a dysfunction of &lt;hl-trusted-source source="PubMed Central" rationale="Highly respected database from the National Institutes of Health"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK459471/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;T and B lymphocytes,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; which are crucial components of the immune system involved in producing a coordinated response in an antigen-specific manner. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the present study, the researchers found changes in gene expression of B and T cells in converters, suggesting the activation or stimulation of these cells. Naive lymphocytes become activated upon their exposure to antigens, leading to their proliferation and differentiation into effector cells or memory cells. The short-lived effector cells are involved in the immediate immune response, whereas long-lived memory cells facilitate a faster response to future infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naive or memory B cells are activated upon binding to an antigen, leading to their proliferation and differentiation into antibody-producing effector cells. In rheumatoid arthritis, subsets of B cells produce autoantibodies against the lining of joints. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;When cells become pro-inflammatory&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the present study, naive and memory B cells in converters exhibited changes in their gene expression profiles that suggested their activation. In other words, the B cells showed a shift towards a pro-inflammatory state. Moreover, the researchers identified a subset of activated memory B cells in converters with a profile similar to those found in clinical rheumatoid arthritis patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Helper T cells, which express the CD4 protein on their surface, interact with B cells and are essential for the activation of B cells. Consistent with the increase in activated B cells in converters, the researchers also found an increase in the population of effector CD4 T cells in this group of individuals. Moreover, these CD4 T cells showed increased expression of genes that are involved in B cell activation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The activation of B cells and the increase in the number of helper T cells in converters suggest a shift toward increased autoantibody production, which could contribute to disease progression. In addition, naive CD4 T cells also showed changes in gene regulation mechanisms, priming them to differentiate into effector cells capable of promoting B cell activation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking and feeling ‘healthy’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our team discovered that during this ‘at-risk’ period, where individuals look and feel healthy, their immune systems are dramatically different. Individuals at risk for RA exhibit widespread inflammation and signs of immune activity, including in B cells that produce the autoreactive antibodies characteristic of RA, as well as in T cells that interface with and instruct the B cells to produce these antibodies.” &lt;br&gt;— Mark Gillespie, Ph.D.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We also discovered immune changes in ‘naïve’ T cells, which are significant because these cells have not encountered any threats previously and may suggest that immune cells in individuals at-risk for RA are already wired to respond in a determinantal manner,” Gillespie added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical News Today</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 10:34:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxQcVFDQmItTDlEMUhyQjk1dWhyem5MY1h2MmVFb2Y4T1EtS3pnSDNaU0o2b04tTENjY1pWWDFXdWhQV0ZBMXNFbGhXV1JYUnFHb0pzdHlSV3QtYWFfNkxPOE8tQXVKUnRBM0d0eFh5cG5HU3BsVng1N0hoMEJpR1QwZEpTcU1WY0wtRkpQMEJCVHdueE9XZFRGSlg0Umd2ZHpIYVF5Xw</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现肠道-大脑相互作用与心理健康之间的惊人联系- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/scientists-discover-surprising-link-between-gut-brain-interactions-and-mental-health/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study provides evidence that the connection between the brain and the stomach may be linked to mental health in a measurable way. Researchers from Aarhus University in Denmark, publishing their work in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s44220-025-00468-6" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Nature Mental Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, report that a specific pattern of communication between the brain and the stomach reflects how individuals feel emotionally and psychologically. Their findings suggest that these gut-brain interactions can indicate a person’s levels of anxiety, depression, well-being, and overall quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea that emotions are linked to physical sensations in the gut is widely reflected in language. People often talk about having “butterflies in the stomach” when nervous, or feeling “sick to the stomach” when distressed. Yet, despite these common expressions, most scientific attention in the field of brain-body interaction has focused on other organs, such as the heart and lungs. These areas have long been studied for their roles in emotion and mood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers were struck by how little was known about how the stomach, in particular, interacts with the brain. While recent studies have explored the influence of gut bacteria and digestion on mental health, very little work had been done on the electrical rhythms of the stomach and how they may directly communicate with the brain’s networks involved in emotion, attention, and cognition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team behind this new study wanted to explore whether a person’s psychological profile might be reflected in how strongly the stomach and brain are coupled during rest. Their aim was not to link a specific diagnosis like depression to a single brain region, but rather to identify patterns across a broad spectrum of mental health experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our interest grew from the long-standing discussion about the role of the body in shaping emotion, a question that has fascinated philosophers and scientists for centuries,” said study author &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/leah-banellis-phd-b192a6a0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Leah Banellis&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://bsky.app/profile/leahbanellis.bsky.social" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;@leahbanellis&lt;/a&gt;), a postdoctoral fellow in Cognitive Neuroscience at Aarhus University. “Yet, while the heart and lungs have received much attention, the stomach has been largely overlooked. This gap struck us as especially surprising, because the link between the stomach and emotional experience feels so intuitive. It is heavily reflected in everyday language, with phrases like ‘butterflies in the stomach,’ ‘sick to our stomach,’ or ‘trust your gut.'”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was part of the Visceral Mind Project, a large-scale initiative that combines data on brain activity, bodily rhythms, and psychological assessments. The team recorded data from 243 people using a method that captures both electrical signals from the stomach (electrogastrography) and brain activity measured with functional magnetic resonance imaging (fMRI).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The participants represented a wide range of mental health profiles, from those reporting high well-being to others showing signs of distress, including anxiety, depression, fatigue, and insomnia. To capture this diversity, the researchers didn’t exclude people with psychiatric symptoms or diagnoses. Instead, they aimed for variation, which would allow their models to detect patterns across the mental health spectrum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each participant underwent a series of recordings while lying still in the MRI scanner. At the same time, sensors on the abdomen captured the stomach’s slow electrical rhythm, which cycles about three times per minute. This rhythm, which originates from specialized cells in the stomach lining, is typically involved in coordinating digestion. But the researchers suspected it might also be linked to mental state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To analyze the relationship between stomach and brain activity, the team used a method that looks at how well the two rhythms align over time. This measure, known as phase-locking value, essentially captures the degree of synchronization between stomach signals and brain signals across different regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers then combined this data with results from a comprehensive mental health questionnaire. The battery included 37 different scores across a range of domains—such as anxiety, stress, mood, fatigue, attention, sleep quality, and life satisfaction. Using a statistical method known as canonical correlation analysis, they looked for patterns that linked brain-stomach coupling with the participants’ mental health profiles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The analysis revealed a clear and statistically significant pattern. Stronger coupling between the stomach’s rhythm and brain activity was associated with poorer mental health. Individuals who reported more symptoms of anxiety, depression, stress, and fatigue tended to show increased synchronization between their stomach and brain rhythms. In contrast, those with higher levels of well-being and life satisfaction showed weaker coupling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For the first time, we’ve found a scientific link between your ‘gut feelings’ and your mental health, showing a surprising connection between your stomach’s natural rhythm and your brain,” Banellis told PsyPost. “Specifically, our study revealed that stronger communication between the stomach and brain is linked to worse mental health, such as higher symptoms of anxiety, depression, stress, and fatigue, whereas weaker stomach-brain communication aligns with better mental health reflected in higher overall well-being and quality of life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This stomach-brain signature was not random. It was localized in specific brain networks, particularly those involved in attention, cognitive control, and salience detection. Some of the strongest associations were found in regions like the superior angular gyrus and the posterior frontal and parietal areas—regions often implicated in cognitive tasks and mental health disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, the researchers ran multiple control analyses to ensure the robustness of their findings. They ruled out the possibility that the observed effects were simply due to general brain activity patterns, fluctuations in heart rate or breathing, or basic features of stomach physiology. In other words, the association appeared specific to the coupling between the stomach’s electrical rhythm and particular brain networks—not just a general marker of body or brain state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their approach was designed to detect broad psychological dimensions rather than focus on one diagnosis. The strongest psychological pattern they found was a spectrum ranging from negative affective states (like anxiety and depression) to positive traits (like well-being and quality of life). This result suggests that the stomach-brain connection is not tied to any one disorder but instead reflects a general mode of psychological functioning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Anxiety, depression, stress, and fatigue showed the strongest links to stomach-brain communication,” Banellis explained. “While phrases like ‘butterflies in the stomach’ or feeling ‘sick to your stomach’ are common ways we describe emotional distress, it was surprising to find such consistent and clear evidence across these symptoms. Even more unexpected was the direction of the effect: we might have assumed that stronger alignment between the body and brain would be beneficial. Instead, our findings suggest that heightened stomach-brain communication could act more like a warning signal, an internal alarm system reflecting mental strain rather than harmony.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As with all research, there are limitations. The findings are based on resting-state measurements, meaning the participants were not performing any tasks during the brain scans. This leaves open the question of how the stomach-brain relationship behaves during emotional challenges or cognitive demands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another limitation is that the study was cross-sectional—it measured participants at one point in time. This limits the ability to determine cause and effect. Longitudinal studies that follow people over time will be needed to see whether changes in stomach-brain coupling can predict shifts in mental health, or whether interventions that alter this coupling can improve well-being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Despite our study including hundreds of participants, far surpassing the size of previous studies, and using a robust machine learning technique, our study is correlational in nature,” Banellis noted. “Thus, future causal paradigms are needed to understand this mental health associated stomach-brain relationship further.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also note that their measurements relied on surface recordings of stomach activity, which can be affected by noise and variability. Despite extensive quality control, a portion of the data had to be excluded. Future studies using higher-resolution tools or invasive methods in clinical settings might yield even clearer signals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our study raises important questions about causality, whether the stomach is influencing the brain, the brain is influencing the stomach, or both, as well as how stomach-brain communication develops over time and whether it can predict changes in mental health,” Banellis said. “It also opens the door to new treatment approaches targeting the disrupted brain-body connection we identified.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“To build on these findings, we plan to pursue three closely connected next steps: first, case-controlled studies in patients diagnosed with anxiety or depression; second, longitudinal studies to track how stomach-brain communication evolves and whether it predicts mental health trajectories; and third, testing new interventions designed to modulate stomach-brain interactions and evaluate their potential for improving mental health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s44220-025-00468-6" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Stomach–brain coupling indexes a dimensional signature of mental health&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Leah Banellis, Ignacio Rebollo, Niia Nikolova, and Micah Allen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 10:28:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPdVdqTV8zU1p2NDczWEc0SkhmeFFTanVJV2dsMmdXTlI2UTZjNzBFaGtYdDloUGlEcnA2ajduYk9ta1BfemJsclBEVTR6azA2QXVJamlFdnUxcmY1ZnV0c0lXMy1ZSTRaQm1TQjJ5RjNQWlhGaXBlaXRCMkdQVk1VZFVUM0k5dk9Va2VjVE5Dd3NoMHdMRDBpemFsRVZMTTVXcG8wRDZMTi1sRjl6N1E</guid></item><item><title>泰诺很受欢迎，而且很安全。我们将解释这种药物如何在体内发挥作用-今日美国</title><link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/graphics/2025/09/28/how-tylenol-works-nsaids-autism-pain-relivers/86351608007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;On Sept. 22, President &lt;a target="_blank" href="/news/politics/donald-trump/" data-autotag="26f031d1-9924-4f10-b4e6-019d076113d5" rel="noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Donald Trump&lt;/a&gt; pushed an unproven link between Tylenol and an increase in &lt;a href="/story/news/politics/2025/09/22/autism-tylenol-takeaways-trump-rfk-jr/86293921007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;autism in children&lt;/a&gt;, and he issued an urgent warning to expectant mothers not to take the medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;What do we know about the drug? Tylenol is used to treat a several conditions, such as mild to moderate pain, &lt;a href="/story/news/health/2024/11/22/valley-fever-cases-arizona/76476521007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;fever&lt;/a&gt;, headaches, muscle aches, toothaches, backaches and colds. According to medical experts, when taken as directed, traditional &lt;a href="/story/news/2023/02/03/how-often-can-you-take-tylenol-acetaminophen/11039009002/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;over-the-counter pain relievers&lt;/a&gt; like acetaminophen and nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory medicines (NSAIDs) can be safe and effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Tylenol wasn't widely used until 1950, when Tylenol Elixir for Children, a prescription medication at first, was promoted as an aspirin substitute, according to &lt;a href="https://medicine.tufts.edu/news-events/news/how-does-acetaminophen-work" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Tufts University School of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;. Acetaminophen, &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2025/01/06/is-tylenol-an-nsaid/77112041007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;often sold under the brand name Tylenol&lt;/a&gt;, had long been considered the safest option for managing headaches, fever and other pain during pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;How does Tylenol (acetaminophen) work in your body?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Tylenol and NSAIDs lower temperature and relieve pain. They are used for treating various types of pain and are part of different drug classes. One significant distinction is that Tylenol does not relieve inflammation; NSAIDs do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Tylenol falls under the umbrella of two other medication classes: analgesics (pain relievers) and antipyretics (fever reducers), says &lt;a href="https://uihc.org/childrens/providers/anureet-walia" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Anureet Walia&lt;/a&gt;, a pain management specialist with UI Health Care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;To this day, it's still a bit of a mystery how acetaminophen works. What experts do know is acetaminophen works solely on the central nervous system, while NSAIDs work on the brain and the body as a whole. Here's a theory of how acetaminophen works in the body:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Unable to view our graphics? &lt;a href="/story/graphics/2025/09/28/how-tylenol-works-nsaids-autism-pain-relivers/86351608007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Click here to see them.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="gnt_em gnt_em_img"&gt;&lt;img class="gnt_em_img_i" fetchpriority="high" data-g-r="lazy" data-gl-src="/gcdn/authoring/authoring-images/2025/09/23/USAT/86308385007-tylenol.jpg?width=980&amp;amp;height=552&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp" decoding="async" alt="Medical experts are challenging President Donald Trump’s autism claims, defending Tylenol’s safety in pregnancy."&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_em_img_ccw gnt_em_img_ccw__cap gnt_em_img_ccw__crd" data-c-caption="Medical experts are challenging President Donald Trump’s autism claims, defending Tylenol’s safety in pregnancy." data-c-credit="Reuters"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;'Use as directed': Comparing Tylenol and NSAIDs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Tylenol and NSAIDs both help with pain perception and fever, but the medications do have one key difference. Distinctly, Tylenol doesn’t have &lt;a href="/picture-gallery/life/health-wellness/2024/11/20/inflammation-food-causes/75996577007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;anti-inflammatory properties&lt;/a&gt;, meaning it won’t help with swelling or inflammation, says David Mangan, chief pharmacy officer at UMass Memorial Medical Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Like all drugs, the dosage matters. Taking your medication as recommended ensures you will receive its full benefits. Always take your current medical conditions and the sort of pain your body may experiencing into account when choosing between Tylenol and an NSAID.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Here's a comparison on how theses drugs work:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Regardless of the type of pain reliever, it’s important to remember that Tylenol and NSAIDs should &lt;a href="/in-depth/news/health/2022/12/11/pain-america-expensive-complicated-problem-managing-pain/8210733001/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;be taken only for episodic pain&lt;/a&gt;. “If your pain is constant and around the clock, it really should be a discussion with your physician about the source of the pain (and) how to best manage it,” Mangan says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;No casual link between Tylenol and autism&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The American Psychiatric Association issued the following statement on autism in response to President Trump's announcement:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“It is essential that the administration prioritizes evidence-based support for individuals on the autism spectrum and invests in long-term comprehensive research about the disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"Vaccines do not cause autism. Claims of any such association have been repeatedly discredited in peer reviewed studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"Autism is a complex disorder, and it is incorrect to imply that a handful of studies have established causation. A strong base of evidence shows that acetaminophen, when taken as directed, is safe for use during pregnancy. Any decisions around a course of treatment should be determined by a patient and their doctor."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The American Academy of Obstetricians and Gynecologists said in a &lt;a href="https://www.acog.org/news/news-releases/2025/09/acog-affirms-safety-benefits-acetaminophen-pregnancy" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;news release&lt;/a&gt; Sept. 22: “In more than two decades of research on the use of acetaminophen in pregnancy, not a single reputable study has successfully concluded that the use of acetaminophen in any trimester of pregnancy causes neurodevelopmental disorders in children.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;em&gt;CONTIBUTING Caroline C. Boyle, George Petras and Mary Walrath-Holdridge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>USA Today</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 10:21:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxNQnpPd3dIWjFWU1ZJaWZ2anVncE1KSm5rTnRuVEpUZVA0LXA1WlhKc3lwbHpJZzFEVGpBLWZ5RVZ3TXliQnk5MGtDVWs5ZFl6Zmd2bFltWDRFQXhPdHpqWmxEaGxlV0tPVVNvbmRhWTVGMkp3QnVSRHdsc1RBd1g5ZmRyTE1pUVR1QXRqUHIwa2hyQkNBWk5HQU9VeUNobVpHMklqVkU4UXJyNHp6ZEE</guid></item><item><title>无花果真的有死黄蜂吗？ - Live Science</title><link>https://www.livescience.com/planet-earth/plants/do-figs-really-have-dead-wasps-in-them</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto paywall-locker"&gt;
&lt;p id="7d341865-008a-4164-a8cd-960f2950a22f"&gt;If you love figs, you may have heard some unsettling lore about them: that every fig hides a wasp, because these insects need to crawl inside and die in order for the fruit to grow. But are there really wasps in the figs we eat, or is this just a myth?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The answer is somewhere in between. Wasps do play an essential role in the life cycle of many types of fig trees, but most figs from the supermarket are likely bug-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="7d341865-008a-4164-a8cd-960f2950a22f-2" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.botanicgardens.org.au/teachers-and-schools/teacher-resources/primary-learning-resources/garden-safari-invertebrates-0" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.botanicgardens.org.au/teachers-and-schools/teacher-resources/primary-learning-resources/garden-safari-invertebrates-0" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Fig wasps&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are a group of hundreds of species of small insects that spend much of their life inside figs. They're about the size of a fruit fly, and they're not the same type of wasps that sting humans. Figs and fig wasps have &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/planet-earth/evolution" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/planet-earth/evolution"&gt;&lt;u&gt;evolved&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; alongside each other for millions of years, leading to a special relationship called &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.nhm.ac.uk/discover/mutualism-examples-of-species-that-work-together.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.nhm.ac.uk/discover/mutualism-examples-of-species-that-work-together.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;mutualism&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, or a link between two species that benefits both of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="068a1ec1-5f44-4831-bfbf-ba02625da19c"&gt;"Fig trees and fig wasps are a great example of a mutualism," &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.uu.se/en/contact-and-organisation/staff?query=N10-1267" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.uu.se/en/contact-and-organisation/staff?query=N10-1267" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Charlotte Jandér&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a plant ecology and evolution researcher at Uppsala University in Sweden, told Live Science in an email. "Other examples of mutualisms include &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/57831-are-trees-vegetarian.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/57831-are-trees-vegetarian.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;trees and the mycorrhizal fungi&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that help the trees take up nutrients, animals and their gut microbes, and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/animals/insects/how-do-insects-know-which-flowers-have-pollen" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/animals/insects/how-do-insects-know-which-flowers-have-pollen"&gt;&lt;u&gt;flowering plants and pollinators&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in general."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="b3e2dafa-7ed7-4521-bad9-948ed0ca5c65"&gt;In the case of figs and fig wasps, the fruit gets pollinated and the wasp is able to reproduce, leading to a mutualism. But this relationship is rather complex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What we think of as the fig "fruit" is actually a hollow structure called a syconium filled with tiny flowers. Generally, when a female fig wasp crawls inside a synconium from a female fig tree, she spreads pollen, which the plant needs in order to produce seeds and ripen. The hole that the wasp crawls in is very small, and she may lose her wings and antenna in the process and can even die inside the fig.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, it's possible that some types of figs may have dead fig wasps inside them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that doesn't necessarily mean the figs we eat have wasps inside. Not all types of figs require pollination in order to ripen. Humans eat the fig species &lt;em&gt;Ficus carica, &lt;/em&gt;which has several cultivars that are parthenocarpic, meaning they can produce ripe fruit without pollination — and therefore, without fig wasps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Most figs we eat in the US have no wasps inside them," &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://biology.umd.edu/people/carlos-machado" target="_blank" data-url="https://biology.umd.edu/people/carlos-machado" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Carlos Machado&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a biology professor at the University of Maryland, told Live Science in an email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="eee78aa6-647e-43ea-b4d2-f069e5713eea"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;A female wasp entering a fig. Fig wasps can't sting humans, and they're much smaller than the wasps that do. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Danita Delimont via Alamy)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="c8d9cfa5-2d5b-44e1-95f4-3e43394549d6"&gt;Mission figs and Brown Turkey figs are two commonly-sold fig cultivars that don't require wasp pollination to ripen and produce seeds, Jandér said. This doesn't apply to all figs that humans eat, though; Smyrna figs, Calimyrna figs, and wild figs around the Mediterranean all rely on wasps for pollination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Most wild figs do require pollination to produce ripe fruit," Machado explained. That means these types of figs could have a tiny wasp inside them — but it's still not a guarantee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/planet-earth/plants/how-do-plants-with-seedless-fruit-reproduce" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/planet-earth/plants/how-do-plants-with-seedless-fruit-reproduce"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do plants with seedless fruit reproduce?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just because a wasp was once in the fig, doesn't mean it's still in there by the time the fig is eaten. The synconia of &lt;em&gt;Ficus carcia&lt;/em&gt; have a large enough opening that the fig wasp is sometimes able to leave the structure after entering. If the wasp does die inside, her body generally gets squished and decomposes from the process of the fig maturing, Jandér said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Even if there were remnants of the original pollinator there you probably would not see them," Jandér explained. Any crunchy texture is more likely from the plant's seeds, not wasp remains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-a2342a21-12d9-443f-8dc0-543b01059df7" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="the-fig-wasp-life-cycle-3"&gt;The fig wasp life cycle&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="c50a1ca6-b273-44dc-8b65-d4dafd1b56b6"&gt;Although wasps sometimes die inside figs, these fruits are actually an essential part of their reproduction cycle. Just as most types of figs need wasp pollination to make new fruit, fig wasps couldn't reproduce without the help of fig trees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a female wasp crawls into a fig syconium from a female tree — the type of figs we eat — she only pollinates it, because the flowers inside are too long for her to lay her eggs on. But if she ventures into a synconium from a male tree — which are called caprifigs and generally not eaten by humans — she'll start to &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.fs.usda.gov/wildflowers/pollinators/pollinator-of-the-month/fig_wasp.shtml" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.fs.usda.gov/wildflowers/pollinators/pollinator-of-the-month/fig_wasp.shtml" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;lay her eggs&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There, the eggs hatch and develop from larvae into young wasps, which mate while still inside the fruit. Generally, the male wasps die inside the caprifig after mating, though they do help chew a tunnel that allows the female wasps to escape, sometimes even offering themselves as bait for the predatory ants that may be waiting outside. Eventually, the fertilized female wasps burst out in search of a new fig to lay their eggs in, carrying pollen from the old caprifig with them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="08c65b1d-ba48-46e7-8edb-88c362c71881"&gt;There are over &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://news.northwestern.edu/stories/2023/07/unraveling-the-tangled-evolution-of-figs" target="_blank" data-url="https://news.northwestern.edu/stories/2023/07/unraveling-the-tangled-evolution-of-figs" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;850 species of fig trees&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and each one can only be pollinated by a specific species of fig wasp, Jandér said. The relationship between these plants and animals evolved millions of years ago, and both Machado and Jandér pointed to its importance. As a keystone species — an organism that many other plants or animals in the ecosystem rely on to survive — fig trees and their relationship with wasps continue to be of great interest to researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There are other plant-pollinator mutualisms in nature, but the fig-fig wasp mutualism is possibly the most diverse and most consequential of all," Machado said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxNTlowejdDR1VqOW92T2UxTHpDTUJFVG9hX0VBZHBDX0JmaTVmVklnRThHS0tSZlJyUG5PV2JaaFBuZDNUU3BmcVlCNW1lb0FERkN6TTBGZWpZQjdhUjVQejNjQXNRV3FOdXh6OE5ia0t6V1J1X25sbmhLYnBXUnNfQV9SMWI3OVlyaFRlZUdQYw</guid></item><item><title>它被称为“噩梦细菌” ，美国的病例正在上升- ClickOnDetroit</title><link>https://www.clickondetroit.com/health/2025/09/28/its-known-as-nightmare-bacteria-and-cases-are-rising-in-the-united-states/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 fURyTV iQviKm articleBody" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW YORK&lt;/strong&gt; – It’s known as “nightmare bacteria,” and cases are on the rise in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 kNAFkD cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Infection rates from the drug-resistant bacteria rose almost 70% between 2019 and 2023, according to a new &lt;a href="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/ANNALS-25-02404"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; from Centers for Disease Control and Prevention scientists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 kNAFkD cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Bacteria that are difficult to treat due to the so-called NDM gene primarily drove the increase, CDC researchers wrote in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.7326/ANNALS-25-02404"&gt;an article published Monday&lt;/a&gt; in the Annals of Internal Medicine. Only two antibiotics work against those infections, and the drugs are expensive and must be administered through an IV, researchers said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Bacteria with the gene were once considered exotic, linked to a small number of patients who received medical care overseas. Though the numbers are still small, the rate of U.S. cases jumped more than fivefold in recent years, the researchers reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;“The rise of NDMs in the U.S. is a grave danger and very worrisome,” said David Weiss, an Emory University infectious diseases researcher, in an email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;It’s likely many people are unrecognized carriers of the drug-resistant bacteria, which could lead to community spread, the CDC scientists said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;That may play out in doctors’ offices across the country, as infections long considered routine — like urinary tract infections — could become harder to treat, said Dr. Maroya Walters, one of the report’s authors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__FlexBase-sc-1fnzlkn-1 jGlKin adWrapper" aria-label="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Antimicrobial resistance occurs when germs such as bacteria and fungi gain the power to fight off the drugs designed to kill them. The misuse of antibiotics was a big reason for the rise — unfinished or unnecessary prescriptions that didn’t kill the germs made them stronger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 kNAFkD cuqaEv article-text"&gt;In recent years, the CDC has drawn attention to “ &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/afcee30eb24848d38f9b855fbcc9a4ba"&gt;nightmare bacteria&lt;/a&gt; ” resistant to a wide range of antibiotics. That includes carbapenems, a class of antibiotics considered a last resort for treatment of serious infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Researchers drew data from 29 states that do the necessary testing and reporting of carbapenem-resistant bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;They counted 4,341 cases of carbapenem-resistant bacterial infections from those states in 2023, with 1,831 of them the NDM variety. The researchers did not say how many of the infected people died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;The rate of carbapenem-resistant infections rose from just under 2 per 100,000 people in 2019 to more than 3 per 100,000 in 2023 — an increase of 69%. But the rate of NDM cases rose from around 0.25 to about 1.35 — an increase of 460%, the authors said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 kNAFkD cuqaEv article-text"&gt;A researcher not involved in the study said the increase is probably related to the &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/hub/covid-19-pandemic"&gt;COVID-19 pandemic&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;“We know that there was a huge surge in antibiotic use during the pandemic, so this likely is reflected in increasing drug resistance,” said Dr. Jason Burnham, a Washington University researcher, in an email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__FlexBase-sc-1fnzlkn-1 jGlKin adWrapper" aria-label="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;The CDC’s count is only a partial picture. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Many states are not fully testing and reporting cases. Even in states that do, cases tend to be among hospital patients sick enough to warrant special testing. Many hospitals also aren’t able to do the testing needed to detect certain forms of genetic resistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;The CDC researchers did not have data from some of the most populous states, including California, Florida, New York and Texas, which means the absolute number of U.S. infections “is definitely underestimated,” Burnham said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 kNAFkD cuqaEv article-text"&gt;This is not the first study to report a rise. A CDC &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7423a2.htm"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; published in June noted an increase in NDM cases in New York City between 2019 and 2024. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;This story was first published Sept. 23, 2025. It was updated Sept. 24, 2025, to make clear that Walters said routine infections could become harder to treat rather than become a chronic problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 nALdY copyright"&gt;Copyright 2025 The Associated Press. All rights reserved. This material may not be published, broadcast, rewritten or redistributed without permission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ClickOnDetroit</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxNTUctUVFrWEo2TndYNkZmeFVKaVR3X3RaNnpzMVFzLTdFc05faktYZzFaYUw0MHktMVlVd09uLTdJelBqSmZOMEc2V25vdXB6TkxsM2UwNzJsbVVrbzBFRzVPZUtkTEtFT3ZyRGxteUJUQjJSeFVYZlZNQ3RrSS12MVNkcnFuOXV2UmQwTmoxYlFZSmlfRnViSkYxaWo0blVUOXBfaFlLU1dRa1FTMmJrWVQ0M0twdERkbzdZNzZMLXk</guid></item><item><title>“我的眼泪可以帮助人们在脑肿瘤中存活下来” - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cz698z5p84lo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;'My tears could help people survive brain tumours'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-c4820dd1-0 cYDsPh"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-c4820dd1-11 bxdaHR"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;Lynette Horsburgh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;North West&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 kSquvq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Cancer Research UK handout Alex Davies lying in a hospital bed. He has brown stubble with a bandage around his head. He is wearing a black and grey top. Alex is smiling." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Cancer Research UK handout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Alex Davies is taking part in the study that could help people get more timely diagnoses&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A father with an incurable brain tumour has donated his tears to a pioneering study that could revolutionise how brain cancers are detected because he wants to "make a difference".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Alex Davies was initially treated for epilepsy but months later scans revealed he had a brain tumour and was told he may only have 12 to 18 months to live.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The 49-year-old is now taking part in research at the Manchester Cancer Research Centre exploring if tear fluid can identify glioblastoma, the most aggressive form of brain tumour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;He is hoping the study will result in earlier diagnoses and ultimately save lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Mr Davies, from Lostock, Bolton, started suffering seizures in 2023 before later undergoing surgery, chemotherapy and radiotherapy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Follow-up scans initially showed no evidence of cancer but later tests discovered the tumour was growing back and he is now receiving palliative care at home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Cancer Research UK handout Alex, who has brown hair and beard and Emma Davies, with long blond hair, standing outside the entrance to Manchester Cancer Research Centre wearing t-shirts which read Stand Up To Cancer. They are both smiling. It is a sunny day." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Cancer Research UK handout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Alex Davies, pictured with his wife Emma&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Mr Davies, who worked at Network Rail before his diagnosis, said he was relatively fit with no health conditions when he "collapsed out of the blue". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It took months to get to my diagnosis and my initial MRI scan didn't spot the tumour," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"My symptoms worsened over about three months including severe headaches, my speech became affected as well as my balance and I was getting confused."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The father-of-two continued: "If helping with this research could mean someone like me can be diagnosed sooner, it offers real hope for the future."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Mr Davies' wife Emma said it was a "really horrible time for us". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She said if a simple tear test could be used to bring a diagnosis forward it "would improve that awful time for so many others in the future".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Thanks to nearly £500,000 funding from Stand Up To Cancer - a joint fundraising campaign from Cancer Research UK and Channel 4 - the study led by scientists at the University of Manchester has expanded to include larger-scale trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Cancer Research UK handout Left to right: Prof Petra Hamerlik, Alex and Emma Davies in a lab in the Manchester Cancer Research Centre. They are all wearing white coats and smiling. " class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Cancer Research UK handout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Prof Petra Hamerlik (left) is leading the study&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Researchers have described the test as a "liquid biopsy" and said the "world-first approach" could pave the way for faster, cheaper and less invasive brain cancer diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;If successful, the test could be rolled out to GP surgeries which would allow patients to receive a diagnosis much earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Prof Petra Hamerlik, who lost her father to glioblastoma at a young age, is leading the project. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She said the research had not previously been explored to diagnose brain cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"My team is currently developing a tear-protein-based classifier that can differentiate brain cancer patients from healthy volunteers with high levels of accuracy," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"If successful, we'll seek further funding to develop a tool that can be rapidly deployed across health services, ultimately helping patients like Alex receive a timely diagnosis and better outcomes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 cnKFtO"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 06:20:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9UV3dlUGFOUnhtR1JUTnhEZWQybjlnaElkb01xXzNUNHE3WDlxcVV1alpLQk9XN1Item05VmN3RFZTUFpkMkE0WVpUZE55VHhPVGtUQnBKZTlwUdIBX0FVX3lxTE1SX2dxREFfaUdZME9meVRIOHhzRlJQOVVDWTNaNGZ4S3pkNnI1ZGdOU0dSaUZoOFBmSHFQNVFtMzdNLWQ2alBfRXl6UWVIMUFUcjk1LTl0TlBxX2RpUG1B</guid></item><item><title>60岁以上？训练师的这种力量锻炼将使您的肌肉强壮，平衡稳定，身体不受伤害-汤姆指南</title><link>https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/workouts/over-60-this-strength-workout-from-a-trainer-will-keep-your-muscles-strong-your-balance-steady-and-your-body-injury-free</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto"&gt;
&lt;p id="a82dd7cc-5a06-433a-80e7-088725468f64"&gt;Aging has its challenges. The body slows down, joints get stiffer, and holding onto muscle takes more effort than it used to. And while there’s plenty of fitness advice out there, much of it feels geared toward younger crowds rather than older generations looking to stay strong and steady.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s where Ed Gemdjian comes in. He’s a fitness coach and gym leader at &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.thegymvenice.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow" data-url="https://www.thegymvenice.com/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;The Gym Venice&lt;/a&gt;, specializing in pain-free, sustainable strength training for adults 40 and above. With more than two decades of experience, he knows what it takes to build strength safely while supporting healthy aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="a82dd7cc-5a06-433a-80e7-088725468f64-2"&gt;Coach Gemdjian has put together a six-move workout (with a quick warm-up included) designed to help you boost strength and muscle in a safe and effective way. All you’ll need is a pair of dumbbells and some comfortable activewear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gemdjian filmed the routine at the gym, but if you don't fancy training in a gym, we’ve rounded up the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/best-picks/best-adjustable-dumbbells" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/best-picks/best-adjustable-dumbbells"&gt;best adjustable dumbbells&lt;/a&gt; to keep you covered for strength building .&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-person-aC6KFra43sB4XaYEeNfMEN-x5a5jKryu9YgGtQ2jTTMJSegOQaoyZs1" class="slice-container person-wrapper person-aC6KFra43sB4XaYEeNfMEN-x5a5jKryu9YgGtQ2jTTMJSegOQaoyZs1 slice-container-person"&gt;&lt;div class="person person--separator"&gt;&lt;div class="person__heading"&gt;&lt;div class="person__name-socials"&gt;&lt;span class="person__name"&gt;Ed Gemdjian&lt;/span&gt;&lt;nav class="button-social-group person__social-buttons" aria-labelledby="button-social-group- person__social-buttons"&gt;&lt;p id="button-social-group- person__social-buttons"&gt;Social Links Navigation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="button-social   " href="https://www.thegymvenice.com/" target="_blank" aria-label="WEBSITE"&gt;&lt;span class="button-social__icon button-social__icon-website"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon-website" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 1000 1000"&gt;&lt;path d="M1000 500A501 501 0 0 0 503 0h-6A501 501 0 0 0 0 500c0 275 223 499 498 500h4a501 501 0 0 0 498-500zM529 936V765h133c-31 90-79 154-133 171zM337 765h134v171c-54-17-101-81-134-171zM61 539h176a899 899 0 0 0 22 167H110a439 439 0 0 1-49-166zM471 64v191H331c31-101 82-173 140-191zm199 191H529V64c58 18 109 90 140 191zm270 226H763c-1-59-7-115-18-167h155a438 438 0 0 1 40 167zm-235 0H529V314h156a857 857 0 0 1 19 167zM471 314v167H296a859 859 0 0 1 19-167h156zM237 481H60a438 438 0 0 1 41-167h154a921 921 0 0 0-18 167zm59 58h175v167H320a837 837 0 0 1-24-166zm233 167V539h175a831 831 0 0 1-24 167H529zm234-166h176a436 436 0 0 1-49 166H741a893 893 0 0 0 22-166zm104-285H731c-20-68-47-126-81-169a443 443 0 0 1 217 169zM350 86c-33 43-61 101-81 169H133A443 443 0 0 1 350 86zM148 765h127c20 59 45 110 75 150a442 442 0 0 1-202-150zm502 150c30-39 56-91 75-150h127a442 442 0 0 1-202 150z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/nav&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="person__bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;With 20+ years of experience, Ed Gemdjian is a Los Angeles based coach at The Gym Venice who helps adults over 40 build strength safely and sustainably.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a id="elk-what-is-the-workout" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-what-is-the-workout"&gt;&lt;span&gt;What is the workout?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id="98b1f875-ef03-4cda-b5a6-e3b978aa390d"&gt;Gemdjian explains: “This plan is built for adults 60+ who want safe, practical strength. You will train major patterns used every day: sit and stand, hinge, push, pull, brace, and get up from the floor.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The structure is simple: start with the warm-up, then move through all six exercises as a circuit, repeating two to three times per week on non-consecutive days. He also stresses the importance of listening to your body: “If a rep hurts sharply, stop and reduce the range or choose the easier option. And if you have medical concerns, speak with a healthcare provider before starting a new program.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now let's take a look at the exercises...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-warm-up" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-warm-up"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Warm-up&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a id="elk-c2c52e65-860d-45d6-ac3d-9d4a499b0a85" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="bird-dog-3"&gt;Bird Dog&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul id="5d85505e-75a1-4aed-b75b-c2e8c3a799ea"&gt;&lt;li&gt;5 slow reps per side with a 3‑second hold.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hands under shoulders, knees under hips. Reach opposite arm and leg long. Keep ribs and hips level. Move with the breath.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;a id="elk-21b09a0d-128f-4d4a-8bf8-a6976dc56127" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="prone-back-extension-superman-3"&gt;Prone Back Extension (Superman)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul id="e008e98a-bf57-4359-90df-deccc31c00cb"&gt;&lt;li&gt;5 slow reps with a 2–3 second hold.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Forehead or chin lightly down, arms forward or by sides. Lift chest and legs just an inch or two, keep gaze down, lower slowly.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;a id="elk-the-workout" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-the-workout"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Workout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a id="elk-e330c457-2aea-4439-b62b-ba5ceffc1831" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="1-box-squat-to-chair-goblet-optional-3"&gt;1. Box Squat to Chair (Goblet optional)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="3d9c8bea-8aab-48f8-a043-202d8c7daea4"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why it matters:&lt;/strong&gt; Trains sit‑to‑stand strength for stairs, toilets, and chairs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Equipment:&lt;/strong&gt; Sturdy chair or box. Optional light kettlebell or dumbbell held at the chest with elbows tight to the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-aC6KFra43sB4XaYEeNfMEN" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-aC6KFra43sB4XaYEeNfMEN slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get instant access to breaking news, the hottest reviews, great deals and helpful tips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="ff2363c1-6b62-4b6d-8366-b9ef2cf9b625"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to do it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol start="1" id="74bf84dd-52e3-4733-bb1c-8bc8c9c96fae"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stand with feet about hip to shoulder width, toes slightly out.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reach your hips back and sit to lightly touch the box. Knees track over mid‑foot.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Press through mid‑foot to stand tall. Squeeze glutes and stand tall without leaning back.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p id="cd84ff57-0e8b-4ca9-92e6-77cf9de8d71f"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sets &amp;amp; reps:&lt;/strong&gt; 2–3 sets of 6–10 reps. Rest 60–90 seconds. Aim for RPE 5–7 out of 10.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Form tips:&lt;/strong&gt; Keep chest proud, spine long, heels down. Exhale as you stand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make it easier:&lt;/strong&gt; Raise the box height, use a countertop or rail for light support, shorten range.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make it harder / Progression:&lt;/strong&gt; Remove the chair and squat until your elbows lightly touch your thighs to add depth and prepare for lower chairs or situations where you must stabilize in a deeper position.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-998eb046-61ff-4240-8292-8745c851ddf8" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="2-wall-hip-hinge-tap-back-3"&gt;2. Wall Hip Hinge (Tap Back)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="23718981-a7a5-48cc-9aff-5950a5ab174a"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why it matters:&lt;/strong&gt; Builds backside strength for picking things up and protecting the back.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Equipment:&lt;/strong&gt; Light kettlebell or dumbbells; a wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="d22cd6d9-cc88-48e1-95fb-1071bb457258"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to do it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol start="1" id="2cd89953-79d3-48c2-a51f-9619fbdf2dc1"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stand about 6 inches in front of a wall with feet hip‑width and the weight on the floor between your feet (or start without weight).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Soften knees. Push hips straight back until your glutes gently tap the wall, keeping your spine long.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If using a weight, slide hands down your thighs to grasp it, keep it close to your legs, and hinge back up by driving hips forward.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lower with control, tapping the wall each rep to reinforce the pattern.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p id="a9623215-5618-47fd-b4fc-fe770c83ef59"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sets &amp;amp; reps:&lt;/strong&gt; 2–3 sets of 8 reps. Rest 60–90 seconds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Form tips:&lt;/strong&gt; Think “close the car door with your hips.” Keep ribs down, neck neutral, and weight close.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make it easier:&lt;/strong&gt; Practice without weight, stand closer to the wall.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make it harder:&lt;/strong&gt; Step an inch farther from the wall or add a brief pause when your glutes touch the wall; progress to a standard hinge without the wall when ready.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-886ca68d-6fbd-4099-85e4-c6492bf37df4" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="3-supported-split-stance-row-3"&gt;3. Supported Split‑Stance Row&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="dd6f496b-891c-4f9f-a5d2-e71b0190e9ee"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why it matters:&lt;/strong&gt; Strengthens the upper back for posture and shoulder health.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Equipment:&lt;/strong&gt; One dumbbell. Support hand on a bench, box, or wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="d2878406-52dd-4e41-a69d-61fc8ff41f15"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to do it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol start="1" id="ff1e65f9-dffa-448c-81db-a40099d0b419"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Take a long split stance and hinge slightly. Place your support hand on the bench.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;With the other hand, row the weight toward your hip.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pause for 1 second, lower under control.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p id="bf03d62f-d5c3-492e-a18d-f3e311a0efb3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sets &amp;amp; reps:&lt;/strong&gt; 2–3 sets of 8–12 reps per side. Rest 45–60 seconds between sides.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Form tips:&lt;/strong&gt; Shoulder blades down and back. Do not twist. Elbow travels near the ribs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make it easier:&lt;/strong&gt; Lighter weight, shorter range.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make it harder:&lt;/strong&gt; Add a 2‑second pause at the top or slow the lowering to 3 seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-ebef785c-53eb-40d2-a599-a7a4fd8a85da" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="4-glute-bridge-3"&gt;4. Glute Bridge&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="54a2539c-bc41-47c4-99ab-faf18004dafa"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why it matters:&lt;/strong&gt; Builds glutes and hamstrings that support the lower back and hips.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Equipment:&lt;/strong&gt; Mat. Optional miniband above knees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="e4e4ed6c-38f8-488c-834f-70822ee9ac25"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to do it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol start="1" id="815e4036-5d5a-4659-9535-27ec62140318"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lie on your back, knees bent, feet hip‑width.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lightly tuck pelvis, press feet through the floor, and lift hips until shoulders, hips, and knees form a line.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pause 1–2 seconds and lower slowly.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p id="a128f806-9a63-4196-855c-8964f7983b85"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sets &amp;amp; reps:&lt;/strong&gt; 2–3 sets of 10–12 reps. Rest 45–60 seconds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Form tips:&lt;/strong&gt; Keep ribs down, do not arch the low back. Exhale as you lift.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make it easier:&lt;/strong&gt; Shorter range, hands pressing into the floor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make it harder:&lt;/strong&gt; Add a miniband and push knees gently out, or hold the top for 3 seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-a8e6e345-691e-4b82-baa7-aa1e409e0265" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="5-baby-get-up-half-turkish-get-up-3"&gt;5. Baby Get‑Up (Half Turkish Get‑Up)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="b89633f0-0357-4085-9b63-07dc92f96dfa"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why it matters:&lt;/strong&gt; Teaches you to get from the floor to a tall sit. Useful for fall recovery.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Equipment:&lt;/strong&gt; Mat. Optional very light weight or even a shoe balanced on the fist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="794561b1-d2e2-4528-ba2f-8749114b3672"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to do it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol start="1" id="bff84ca2-d591-4640-b741-ed233f21409a"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lie on your back. Right knee bent, right fist to the ceiling. Left leg long, left arm about 45 degrees from your body.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Roll onto your left elbow.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Press to your left hand. Sit tall with the right fist still vertical.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reverse slowly to the start. Switch sides.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p id="624f4b78-b8af-421a-9f11-cedfb65eb628"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sets &amp;amp; reps:&lt;/strong&gt; 2–3 sets of 3–5 reps per side. Rest 45–60 seconds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Form tips:&lt;/strong&gt; Eyes on the fist, keep the fist vertical, move slowly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make it easier:&lt;/strong&gt; No weight.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make it harder / Progression:&lt;/strong&gt; Hold a very light dumbbell or kettlebell. Over time, progress the sequence to the half‑kneeling and then full standing Turkish get‑up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-688c4e87-9a41-4bd9-aac3-e58638e5e165" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="6-incline-plank-hands-on-counter-or-bench-3"&gt;6. Incline Plank (Hands on Counter or Bench)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="c3203d8f-f551-47d6-b7ba-6215d8b37741"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why it matters:&lt;/strong&gt; Builds core stiffness for safer lifting and better balance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Equipment:&lt;/strong&gt; Stable counter, rail, or bench.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="66460a54-4bca-426a-bc07-f6c5242f45a6"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to do it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol start="1" id="0209132d-2ce3-4a4c-927c-b13da5cf1006"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hands under shoulders, body in a straight line from ears to ankles.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Squeeze glutes and lightly brace abs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Breathe through the brace.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p id="159b62f8-3ba7-4657-bdf8-d826d4a798e4"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sets &amp;amp; time:&lt;/strong&gt; 2–3 sets of 20–30 seconds. Rest 45–60 seconds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Form tips:&lt;/strong&gt; Do not let hips sag or pike.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make it easier:&lt;/strong&gt; Use a higher surface or wall plank.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make it harder:&lt;/strong&gt; Lower the surface or lift one foot for 5 seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-why-is-it-important-to-build-and-maintain-strength-as-you-age" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-why-is-it-important-to-build-and-maintain-strength-as-you-age"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Why is it important to build and maintain strength as you age?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id="16de9014-9298-4025-ac86-f6a4cf23e468"&gt;As we get older, our muscles, bones, and joints naturally lose strength and resilience. This can make everyday tasks like climbing stairs, carrying groceries, or getting up from the floor more difficult than they used to feel. Maintaining strength is key not just for mobility, but for balance, energy, and overall independence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gemdjian highlights why this matters so much in his work at The Gym Venice. He says, “Strength training is the single best antidote to age-related decline. After 30, we lose muscle and power each decade, which erodes balance, joint health, and independence.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He says it's a good idea to focus on compound movements as they engage multiple muscles in one movement. “These exercises preserve lean mass, strengthen bones, and improve insulin sensitivity, keeping energy and weight manageable.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plus, they build stronger glutes, legs, and core, making everyday tasks like climbing stairs, carrying groceries, or getting off the floor feel easier. “Strength work through &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/features/progressive-overload-what-is-it-and-how-does-it-help-build-muscle-and-strength" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/features/progressive-overload-what-is-it-and-how-does-it-help-build-muscle-and-strength"&gt;progressive overload&lt;/a&gt; also sharpens the brain via coordination and nervous-system adaptations,” he adds. “Add a little weight, reps, or range as your body adapts and loads gradually will begin to feel easier.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Follow &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://news.google.com/publications/CAAqKAgKIiJDQklTRXdnTWFnOEtEWFJ2YlhObmRXbGtaUzVqYjIwb0FBUAE" target="_blank" data-url="https://news.google.com/publications/CAAqKAgKIiJDQklTRXdnTWFnOEtEWFJ2YlhObmRXbGtaUzVqYjIwb0FBUAE" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tom's Guide on Google News&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=tomsguide.com" target="_blank" data-url="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=tomsguide.com" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;em&gt;add us as a preferred source&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; to get our up-to-date news, analysis, and reviews in your feeds. Make sure to click the Follow button!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-more-from-tom-s-guide" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-more-from-tom-s-guide"&gt;&lt;span&gt;More from Tom's Guide &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a id="elk-16003e2b-4bc7-4cbf-af5c-5f707d2d5d84" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;aside data-model-name="NordicTrack Select-A-Weight Dumbbell Set,Bowflex SelectTech 552i,Amazon Basics Adjustable Barbell Dumbbells,Ativafit Adjustable Dumbbells,Flybird Adjustable Dumbbell,,Core Home Fitness Adjustable Dumbbells &amp;amp; Stand,,Tespon Adjustable Dumbbells 66lbs" data-name="Buying Guide Multimodel widget" data-widget-title="multimodelWidgetTitle" data-widget-type="multimodelreview" data-render-type="editorial" class="hawk-base"&gt;&lt;div class="hawk-multi-model-review-container"&gt;&lt;div class="hawk-multi-model-review-retail-container"&gt;&lt;p class="hawk-title-container"&gt;Round up of today's best deals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Tom's Guide</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 06:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9wFBVV95cUxNTTRkVTBoc1J0QXpuRm5pMUxIZk9WLVhSVkg2Rnc5bjkyZnNjSHUwVzFTRmJJb2lLVzR1aDRGaFFZS21FelR2dHRfNjhjVUlpY1d0RzJ1UDk1MkU1WnAyOVM0cHlLejlpaHJtdlF4emFuNU1GVHRwaWRQTmZBckdNNjVBSkFUZWdmYzE0UkRqQWRtRnhhSFduRE1QVWdBZHFxQTRGY0UxX21jM0duTDBlQ1ZOUFlRUHBZNFFNNlZSRW5OSHRQdWV6VUxSVjlycnJBRl8tcDI0c1FVMC10Nmc0WjIxN0tDb0Foc3hXUkgwS2lYaUVoa284</guid></item><item><title>「我的车变成了救护车」--牙买加观察家</title><link>https://www.jamaicaobserver.com/2025/09/28/car-became-ambulance/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="image_caption"&gt;Aiden-Jon Amir Hall was diagnosed with sickle cell anaemia at four weeks old. He passed away in 2022 at the age of five.&lt;/p&gt;				&lt;div class="body content-single-wrap"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PARENTS who each carry the sickle cell trait have a one-in-four chance of having a child with sickle cell anaemia — a painful reality with which Latoya Minott Smikle has had to live.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During her fourth pregnancy, the now mother of five learnt that her four-week-old baby — Aiden-Jon Amir Hall — had sickle cell disease. At the time, she also found out that she, her partner, and their three other children were carriers of the sickle cell trait.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After five-and-a-half years of fighting courageously, Aiden-Jon passed away due to complications with the disease in 2022. Out of that heartache and the battle she waged on his behalf, Smikle established the Aiden-Jon Amir Hall Foundation, which is seeking to raise $1 million this year to provide financial support to six individuals with sickle cell disease. The foundation is also looking to raise awareness about the disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smikle recalled that before Aiden-Jon’s birth, she’d lived next door to a family who also had loved ones with sickle cell disease. She told the &lt;b&gt;Jamaica Observer&lt;/b&gt; that she became aware of their late-night hospital runs during a crisis and would hear the anguished cries of pain that echoed through the neighbourhood. Yet, she admitted, she’d never imagined that one day that would also be her reality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was after Aiden was diagnosed with the disease that the Sickle Cell Unit in Kingston, which was the unit that reached out to us, they were the ones that looked up my children’s medical records from birth, and then from there they would have discovered that all of them have the trait.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Imagine you’re learning that you have a baby with full sickle cell, then you’re finding out that yourself has the trait and all your living children also have the trait. I don’t think I have to tell you how jarring that was. It was very shocking and very jarring, and I think for a moment I became depressed because I would have been four weeks postpartum; that’s not the easiest kind of news to bear at that time,” she told the &lt;b&gt;Sunday Observer&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smikle said subsequent checks would later reveal that it was likely her mother who had the sickle cell trait.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sickle cell is a genetic blood disorder that causes red blood cells to become rigid, abnormal cells that block blood flow in small vessels, leading to severe pain. An individual can either have the trait or the full extent of the disease. If an individual is diagnosed with the trait, it means that they inherited one sickle cell gene. The full extent of the disease, sickle cell anaemia, occurs when an individual inherits two sickle cell genes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;September is recognised as Sickle Cell Awareness Month, an annual observance dedicated to raising awareness, understanding, and support for the inherited blood disorder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aiden-Jon was diagnosed with sickle cell anaemia, the most common and severe form of the disease that causes red blood cells to become stiff, crescent-shaped, leading to anaemia, painful episodes, and potentially severe organ damage as the sickle cells block blood flow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like her neighbours, Smikle said late-night hospital visits soon became the norm as she cradled her baby through multiple painful crises. Hospital stays were rarely fewer than seven days, and balancing finances, work, and caring for her other children alongside her husband proved an overwhelming task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At times she had no choice but to take Aiden-Jon with her to work, as her spouse served in the Jamaica Constabulary Force. She recounted one particularly difficult moment when she took him with her as she led a work event in St Ann, only for him to suffer a major crisis before it began — one that ended with another hospital admission. She shared that she was living in Clarendon at the time, but wanted her son to be treated at the specialised Sickle Cell Unit in Kingston to receive comprehensive care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My car had to become an ambulance. I had to be flying like a mad woman from St Ann to get back into town because when a child is in pain; it’s difficult hearing your child cry all the way from St Ann to Kingston. There is nothing that can soothe that pain but whatever is administered to him; for example, morphine and other drugs through IV [intravenous therapy], plus give him the requisite treatment that he needs at the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s very challenging. Sickle cell anaemia is a very challenging situation for parents, especially if you’re not somebody who has a job that pays well; it even becomes a greater challenge because, financially, it is a very stressful situation,” said Smikle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She told the &lt;b&gt;Sunday Observer&lt;/b&gt; that her experience has revealed the gaps that exist in the system as well as the lack of empathy in society for individuals living with sickle cell disease and for parents struggling with their children. While the Sickle Cell Unit, which is located at the University of the West Indies, Mona, serves as a vital pillar by providing testing, resources, and some level of support, Smikle does not believe it is adequately funded to deliver holistic care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She noted, too, that even with assistance from the National Health Fund to cover the cost of medication for loved ones with sickle cell disease, many parents continue to struggle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a country where approximately one in every 150 babies is born with sickle cell disease and one in 10 adults carries the trait, she stressed that greater support and resources are urgently needed. She is hoping the Aiden-Jon Amir Hall Foundation, launched last Saturday, will bring about some of that change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I believe that God would have known that this would have been my journey and that I would have needed all these life experiences as a tool to help me now to be better able to help other persons, and so, for me, the foundation is to let my son continue to live and continue to impact people, because even though he was five and a half years old, he was such a loving child; people were impacted by him. The testimonies that people shared at his funeral, one would have assumed that he was an adult, but he was just a child and very impactful in such a very small window of time,” she told the &lt;b&gt;Sunday Observer&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“As a Christian, some people would ask me if I don’t ask God why, and why God never healed him, but my faith tells me that God sacrificed his only son through a very brutal death to provide life for me. Whatever my son went through, whatever we all went through as a family with my son, I believe there was purpose behind it to help the forgotten, to help those that are being overlooked, to help those that can’t speak for themselves because they’re in too much pain and because nobody wants to hear anything from them,” she reasoned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smikle said she has identified six recipients for a grant — a number that reflects how old her son would have been if he had not passed away a month before his birthday in 2022. One of the recipients is the child of a single father who has to undergo surgery to remove his/her spleen. There will be a fund-raising dinner in October to raise $1 million for the recipients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s to build a community that can help others who are struggling; for them to understand, ‘You’re not alone.’ For me, most importantly, my child would not have survived, not because there wasn’t effort put forward to making him live the best life he lived, but I want to help someone else’s child to be able to live longer and healthier, and to reach the peak of all that they are able to achieve so that I can smile when I visit my son’s grave; I can smile and say, ‘I did it for him,’ ” said Smikle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="attachment_4435583" class="wp-caption alignleft"&gt;&lt;a href="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_1-591.jpg"&gt;&lt;img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-4435583" decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-4435583" ta-src="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_1-591.jpg" alt="Latoya Minott Smikle and her late son Aiden-Jon Amir Hall" ta-srcset="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_1-591.jpg 717w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_1-591-225x300.jpg 225w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_1-591-135x180.jpg 135w" sizes="(max-width: 717px) 100vw, 717px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="caption-attachment-4435583" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Latoya Minott Smikle and her late son Aiden-Jon Amir Hall&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="attachment_4435586" class="wp-caption alignleft"&gt;&lt;a href="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_2-348.jpg"&gt;&lt;img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-4435586" decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-4435586" ta-src="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_2-348.jpg" alt="A detailed shot of sickle-shaped red blood cells, illustrating the abnormal shape characteristic of sickle cell anaemia." ta-srcset="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_2-348.jpg 1434w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_2-348-300x200.jpg 300w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_2-348-1024x683.jpg 1024w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_2-348-768x512.jpg 768w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_2-348-180x120.jpg 180w" sizes="(max-width: 1434px) 100vw, 1434px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="caption-attachment-4435586" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;A detailed shot of sickle-shaped red blood cells, illustrating the abnormal shape characteristic of sickle cell anaemia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="attachment_4435589" class="wp-caption alignleft"&gt;&lt;a href="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_3-200.jpg"&gt;&lt;img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-4435589" decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-4435589" ta-src="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_3-200.jpg" alt="The Aiden-Jon Amir Hall Foundation is set to have a fund-raiser in October to assist parents and individuals living with sickle cell disease. The target is $1 million with six beneficiaries identified." ta-srcset="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_3-200.jpg 956w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_3-200-300x300.jpg 300w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_3-200-150x150.jpg 150w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_3-200-768x768.jpg 768w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_3-200-180x180.jpg 180w" sizes="(max-width: 956px) 100vw, 956px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="caption-attachment-4435589" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The Aiden-Jon Amir Hall Foundation is set to have a fund-raiser in October to assist parents and individuals living with sickle cell disease. The target is $1 million with six beneficiaries identified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Jamaica Observer</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 05:17:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE5vN3RBUHN3RzVvZ2xDcDhpT0p4TXlCeU9FMHRPOWdUa0N3M3A4V1VxdWkzWmJIQzhocXd0bG5iNmRKRU5UOVZyRUpPX2ZvMHJkUnBoV1FMeURfNkNaXy1UOFZFY1R3QTZ4Z2x1MURkTWt1dw</guid></item><item><title>如果有人随便说了这11个短语中的任何一个，他们的挣扎比他们想承认的要多- YourTango</title><link>https://www.yourtango.com/self/someone-says-any-these-phrases-casually-struggling-more-than-admit</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people silently struggle without asking for help. Maybe it's financial problems, relationship issues, or personal pain, but they often walk through life feeling alone. While their behaviors indicate there's a problem, their words sometimes speak louder. Whether it's saying they don't care or acting like they're busy, if someone says any of these phrases casually, they're struggling more than they want to admit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It isn't always obvious when our loved ones are going through things, but there will sometimes be telltale signs. It could be their tone of voice or dismissive words, but it's up to us to pay close attention. Because when a person is struggling, they may be crying out for help and their words will fall on deaf ears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;If someone says any of these 11 phrases casually, they're struggling more than they want to admit&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. 'I'm fine'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-i%27m-fine.png" alt="man telling friend he's fine but secretly struggling" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit i'm fine" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;loreanto | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If someone says "I'm fine" casually, they're struggling more than they want to admit. It's unfortunate, but most people who are struggling won't reveal that their mental health is in decline. Filled with guilt and shame, they'd rather cover it up by telling others they are fine, but this can be dangerous and hurtful to those who care about them most.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if they don't see it, their loved ones have a strong desire to connect and be vulnerable with each other. As the &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6125010/" rel="nofollow"&gt;American Journal of Lifestyle Medicine&lt;/a&gt; reiterated, "Humans are wired to connect, and this connection affects our health." So, while it might be tempting to push their feelings to the side, speaking to someone has a big impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/people-who-seem-they-have-their-life-together-often-hide-these-struggles"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People Who Seem Like They Have Their Life Together Often Hide These 11 Struggles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. 'It is what it is'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-it-is-what-it-is.png" alt="young man shrugging saying it is what it is" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit it is what it is" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Krakenimages.com | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some people have been let down so many times, they've learned to be nonchalant about their mental health. As a result, they may shrug and give up. But if someone says "it is what it is," they're struggling more than they want to admit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loved ones might be upset to hear it, but those dealing with mental or emotional health issues may not see it as a big deal. Maybe they were taught to just suck it up and deal with it, or are so tired of trying that they have nothing left to give.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holding everything in might make someone feel more isolated in the long run, causing them to pull away. But talking to loved ones can help and &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/most-powerful-phrase-for-someone-struggling"&gt;provide a safe space to open up&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/subtle-habits-tell-other-people-everything-they-need-know-about-you"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8 Subtle Habits That Tell Other People Everything They Need To Know About You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. 'I'm just tired'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-i%27m-just-tired.png" alt="tired woman overworked" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit i'm just tired" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;CrizzyStudio | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the number of people working overtime to make ends meet, it isn't uncommon to hear people complain about how tired they are. But when someone uses their tiredness as an excuse to avoid doing certain things, like socializing with friends or taking care of their daily responsibilities, it's not a good sign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who are struggling are shutting themselves out from seeking help, making their mental health issues worse. And according to a &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/1745691614568352" rel="nofollow"&gt;study published in Perspectives on Psychological Science&lt;/a&gt;, loneliness and social isolation are twice as harmful to someone's physical and mental health as obesity is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/truly-smart-people-usually-avoid-anyone-who-does-these-things"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Truly Smart People Usually Avoid Anyone Who Does These 11 Things&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4. 'I don't care anymore'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-i-don%27t-care-anymore.png" alt="woman telling friend i don't care anymore" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit i don't care anymore" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Pheelings media | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/subtle-signs-not-just-stressed-completely-exhausted-emotionally"&gt;Once someone is completely drained&lt;/a&gt;, everything comes in one ear and goes out the other. Due to their pure exhaustion, they may admit they don't care anymore, even if internally they're not doing well. Because despite how nonchalant they want to be, deep down inside, they're hurting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, due to their stubborn nature, it might be nearly impossible to have a one-on-one conversation about how they actually feel. So used to being closed off, they keep a lid on their emotions until they eventually explode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/wellness/proven-techniques-healing-brain-wound-humans-experience-trauma"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4 Proven Techniques For Healing The 'Brain Wound' Humans Experience From Trauma&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;5. 'It could be worse'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-it-could-be-worse.png" alt="struggling man telling friend it could be worse" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit it could be worse" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;fizkes | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If there's one thing to notice about a person who's struggling, it's that they'll always find a way to demean their own emotions. Like clockwork, they'll compare their issues to someone who is seemingly struggling more than them, downplaying their own pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But just because it isn't as severe as someone else's plight, doesn't make it any less important. As one &lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/doiLanding?doi=10.1037%2Fpas0001155" rel="nofollow"&gt;study from Psychological Assessment&lt;/a&gt; found, people who invalidate their own emotions feel more upset and are more readily activated emotionally. So, once someone is already closed off, it might take a professional to get them to open back up again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health/things-people-used-be-ashamed-of-now-considered-healthy"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Things People Used To Be Ashamed Of That Are Now Considered Healthy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;6. 'I don't want to talk about it'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-i-don%27t-want-to-talk-about-it.png" alt="mentally stressed woman saying don't want to talk about it" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit i don't want to talk about it" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;StratfordProductions | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When times get tough, it can feel impossible to open up and share what's on your mind. Whether it's from embarrassment or guilt, a person saying they don't want to talk about it is likely suffering in silence. It isn't always their intention to &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/things-people-hide-their-feelings-understand"&gt;shut people out or hide their emotions&lt;/a&gt;, but it might come from a place of fear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, just because it's hard doesn't mean they should give up. Even if it's something small like journaling their thoughts, actively finding a way to vent is the best way to figure out what to say or, at the very least, get those emotions out in a healthy and productive way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/habits-quietly-successful-people-miserable-people-overlook"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5 Habits Of Quietly Successful People That Miserable Folks Always Overlook&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;7. 'It doesn't matter'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-it-doesn%27t-matter.png" alt="upset woman telling partner it doesn't matter" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit it doesn't matter" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;simona pilolla 2 | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If someone says "it doesn't matter" casually, they're struggling more than they want to admit. Because the truth is, it does matter to them, they just don't want to express it for one reason or another. Perhaps they don't want to feel like a burden or are prone to overthinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And according to &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/the-mind-body-link/202504/the-hidden-cost-of-overthinking"&gt;psychologist Kyle Davies&lt;/a&gt;, "When we're constantly second-guessing or trying to outthink our emotions, we become disconnected from the deeper signals of clarity, insight, and instinct that reside within us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even so, it's their choice whether they want to share or not. Despite venting being good for their mental health, those who struggle will always do things on their own terms, despite it harming them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/money/people-who-never-struggle-financially-avoid-these-everyday-habits"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People Who Never Struggle Financially Avoid These 11 Everyday Habits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;8. 'I'll figure it out'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-i%27ll-figure-it-out.png" alt="woman thinking i'll figure it out" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit i'll figure it out" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;PeopleImages | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, people need to figure things out on their own. Despite how difficult the obstacle may be, they can't always depend on others to save them. But this doesn't mean they have to shut everyone out completely. Even if they can't always help, at the very least, people can offer the support needed to keep moving forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who don't bother asking for help are always going to struggle the most. Even if they can do it all on their own, isolation and the feeling of helplessness are only intensified when they shut down. This is why it's important to let people in. Because nobody does anything alone and comes out the other end successful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/notice-things-someones-house-struggling-more-they-admit"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If You Notice These 11 Things At Someone's House, They're Struggling More Than They Admit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;9. 'I can't complain'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-i-can%27t-complain.png" alt="man telling woman i can't complain hiding struggles" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit i can't complain" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;MAYA LAB | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people were taught not to complain from a young age. They were told that no matter how difficult life got, there was plenty to be grateful for. And while this might have been said with the best of intentions, never complaining isn't healthy. Holding everything in is bound to mess with a person's mental health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/the-addiction-connection/202312/how-to-stop-intellectualizing-your-emotions"&gt;clinical psychologist Rubin Khoddam&lt;/a&gt; explained, "&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/not-so-subtle-signs-you-might-be-intellectualizer"&gt;Intellectualizing emotions is a defense mechanism&lt;/a&gt; that serves as a shield against the overwhelming intensity of feelings. It's the process of suppressing emotions by overthinking, analyzing, or explaining them away. It can be rooted in our upbringing, societal expectations, or personal coping strategies."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/simple-daily-tasks-feel-impossible-when-body-stuck-fight-flight-mode"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Simple Daily Tasks That Feel Impossible When Your Body Is Stuck In 'Fight-Or-Flight' Mode&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;10. 'Same old, same old'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-same-old-same-old.png" alt="woman telling friend same old same old secretly struggling" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit same old same old" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;PeopleImages | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If someone says "same old, same old" casually, they're struggling more than they want to admit because despite wanting people to think that nothing has changed, they're secretly dealing with problems they believe others won't understand. So, they choose to portray everything as just fine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While they might not see anything wrong with this, shutting out others is hurtful. After all, feeling abandoned can hurt just about anyone's feelings. Does this mean people have to open up completely? No, but simply saying, "I'm going through something, but I'd rather not talk about it now" is a lot better than keeping them in the dark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/tiny-ways-people-can-tell-you-didnt-shower-even-when-try-freshen-up"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Tiny Ways People Can Tell You Didn't Shower, Even When You Try To Freshen Up&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;11. 'I'm just busy'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-i%27m-just-busy.png" alt="upset woman on phone saying i'm just busy" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit i'm just busy" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;fizkes | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether it's work or family, there's nothing inherently wrong with someone saying they're busy. Likely, it's true. But everyone needs a break now and then, and using being busy as an excuse is never a good sign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/your-body-has-something-to-tell-you/202412/the-cost-of-fighting-your-unwanted-emotions"&gt;psychologist Elizabeth Sadock&lt;/a&gt; put it,"Suppressing emotion is like denying hunger: It persists because it serves an essential purpose." So, even if they're not revealing how they truly feel, eventually, it will come back to bite them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/family/quiet-struggles-only-moms-who-financially-provide-for-their-families-will-understand"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Quiet Struggles Only Moms Who Financially Provide For Their Families Will Understand&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Marielisa Reyes is a writer with a bachelor's degree in psychology who covers self-help, relationships, career, family, and astrology topics.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="midcat-most-popular"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Related Stories From YourTango:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="rc-widget-c743d1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>YourTango</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 03:33:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxNYU1pQ1AtVkUyU0pIRUlwTHVick1jdW9vVjZnYWpxc1l6bS1hc05FY3IzTVBaS3IyNzFiV18yamJmSW94V25BNHJER0tuTHg2LXJ5eDJxNmNmLWlCaXlrWl9DMVZGcEVtZlNtcDZIRWZuMlRzZHdxOFpmcFJWb01IYTl4cWJWMGp2TlM1YnNKd1J3Y2g0b1RIS0dzeW5UUQ</guid></item><item><title>8个爱好婴儿潮一代发誓-科学现在说实际上可以延长你的寿命- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/things-to-do/z-8-hobbies-boomers-swore-by-that-science-now-says-actually-extend-your-life/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p data-start="432" data-end="555"&gt;It’s funny—some of the things younger generations teased boomers about actually turn out to have serious health benefits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="557" data-end="755"&gt;Science has been catching up with common sense in the last few decades, and research now shows that several of the hobbies boomers grew up with—or never let go of—are directly linked to longevity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="757" data-end="958"&gt;These aren’t high-tech, expensive pursuits. They’re everyday activities, woven into life without fanfare. And maybe that’s the point: the stuff that really sustains us isn’t flashy, it’s sustainable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="960" data-end="982"&gt;Let’s get into them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="989" data-end="1006"&gt;1. Gardening&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1008" data-end="1098"&gt;Ever wonder why so many boomers spent their weekends pruning roses or planting tomatoes?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1100" data-end="1410"&gt;Turns out, gardening isn’t just about curb appeal or homegrown produce. Studies link it to lower stress, better immune function, and reduced risk of dementia. Digging in the dirt exposes us to microbes that boost serotonin. Plus, gardening keeps you moving in a low-impact way that’s sustainable for decades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1412" data-end="1595"&gt;One meta-analysis found that gardening interventions had &lt;a href="https://systematicreviewsjournal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s13643-024-02457-9?.com"&gt;a moderate positive effect on well-being&lt;/a&gt; and mental health across multiple studies. It’s a habit that feeds both the body and the mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1597" data-end="1919"&gt;I’ve noticed this myself when I tend to my balcony plants. Even just ten minutes with my hands in soil resets my stress levels. The quiet focus of pruning leaves feels a lot like meditation—but with tomatoes at the end of it. If you’ve got a yard—or even a few pots—you’ve got a built-in therapy session waiting for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="1926" data-end="1941"&gt;2. Walking&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1943" data-end="2029"&gt;Boomers walked. A lot. They didn’t think of it as exercise—it was just part of life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2031" data-end="2373"&gt;Now, science says it’s one of the best predictors of healthy aging. Walking improves cardiovascular health, supports bone density, and even sharpens memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2031" data-end="2373"&gt;A 2022 genetic study of over 400,000 participants found that brisk walkers had significantly longer telomeres—and suggested that walking faster could&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420133538.htm?.com"&gt; slow biological aging&lt;/a&gt; by the equivalent of about 16 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2375" data-end="2651"&gt;The beauty of walking is its accessibility. You don’t need gear or a gym membership. Just shoes and time. It’s also underrated as a creativity booster. Steve Jobs was famous for his walking meetings, and research backs up the idea that &lt;a href="https://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/releases/xlm-a0036577.pdf?.com"&gt;walking helps with divergent thinking.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2653" data-end="2878"&gt;I learned this on a trip to Japan when I joined an older local group on their morning walk. Their energy was contagious, and it hit me: this is a habit you can keep doing well into your eighties. No extreme workouts needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="2885" data-end="2905"&gt;3. Volunteering&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2907" data-end="3002"&gt;Many boomers made volunteering a staple—whether at church, the library, or community centers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3004" data-end="3208"&gt;Research shows that giving your time doesn’t just help others; it extends your own life. People who volunteer regularly have lower mortality rates, better mental health, and a stronger sense of purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3210" data-end="3421"&gt;One prospective study found that adults over 50 who volunteered at least 200 hours per year were about &lt;a href="https://europepmc.org/article/PMC/3804225?.com"&gt;40 % less likely to develop hypertension. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3423" data-end="3669"&gt;Purpose is medicine. And volunteering gives it in spades. It satisfies the psychological need for relatedness, something self-determination theory highlights as essential for well-being. In other words, helping others reminds us that we belong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="3676" data-end="3712"&gt;4. Playing cards or board games&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3714" data-end="3799"&gt;Friday night poker nights, bridge clubs, Scrabble marathons. Boomers swore by them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3801" data-end="4078"&gt;Now science confirms that regularly playing games protects against cognitive decline. Social interaction plus strategy keeps neural pathways firing. In a French prospective cohort (the Paquid study), regular board game players had about &lt;a href="https://bmjopen.bmj.com/content/3/8/e002998?.com"&gt;15 % lower risk of dementia&lt;/a&gt; over 20 years compared to non-players.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4080" data-end="4321"&gt;Games do something else too: they create shared rituals. That weekly bridge night isn’t just entertainment—it’s community plus mental exercise. The anticipation of the game, the inside jokes, even the competition—all of it feeds longevity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4323" data-end="4532"&gt;I’ve mentioned this before, but when I lived in Spain for a summer, I saw older folks gather nightly in plazas to play dominoes. They weren’t just passing time—they were literally keeping their brains alive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="4539" data-end="4554"&gt;5. Dancing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4556" data-end="4648"&gt;If you’ve ever been dragged to a boomer wedding, you’ve seen the electric slide in action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4650" data-end="4938"&gt;Beyond the cheesy moves, dancing is insanely good for you. It combines aerobic activity, balance training, and social connection. Studies show that dancing lowers the risk of heart disease and improves brain health. Some even suggest it &lt;a href="https://montefioreeinstein.org/news/2023/01/05/social-dancing-improve-cognition-reduce-alzheimers-risk?.com"&gt;reduces the likelihood of developing Alzheimer’s.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4940" data-end="5174"&gt;Neurologists point out that dancing challenges the brain in unique ways: you have to coordinate movement, remember steps, and often improvise in rhythm with others. That blend of physical and mental effort is rare outside of sports.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5176" data-end="5359"&gt;Plus—it’s fun. Unlike forcing yourself onto a treadmill, dancing makes exercise feel like joy. No surprise it triggers dopamine release, which is linked to motivation and happiness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="5366" data-end="5389"&gt;6. Cooking at home&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5391" data-end="5445"&gt;Boomers weren’t eating out every night. They cooked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5447" data-end="5652"&gt;Science backs this habit big time. Home-cooked meals tend to be healthier, with fewer processed ingredients and less sodium. Cooking also engages creativity and gives a sense of control over your health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5654" data-end="5882"&gt;One study found that people in Taiwan and Australia who cooked up to five times a week had &lt;a href="https://www.bluezones.com/2018/04/want-to-eat-better-and-live-longer-learn-to-cook/?.com"&gt;a 47 % greater chance of being alive ten years later.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5884" data-end="6157"&gt;I still remember my grandmother teaching me how to make lentil stew. At the time, I thought it was just food. Now I realize it was one of the healthiest “hobbies” she could have passed down. Cooking ties health with tradition, creating a kind of resilience you can taste.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="6164" data-end="6179"&gt;7. Reading&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6181" data-end="6287"&gt;Bookshelves lined with novels, biographies, or how-to guides—that was a common boomer household feature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6289" data-end="6501"&gt;Reading isn’t just entertainment. It boosts empathy, reduces stress, and improves brain connectivity. A 2016 Yale study found that people who read books regularly&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0277953616303689?.com"&gt; lived almost two years longer&lt;/a&gt; than non-readers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6503" data-end="6679"&gt;Books are also a powerful way to practice “deep focus” in a world that constantly interrupts us. That immersion strengthens attention span, which is protective for the brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6681" data-end="6978"&gt;Personally, I find that reading grounds me in a way scrolling never could. I’ll pick up a behavioral science book and suddenly lose hours, not because I’m distracted but because I’m absorbed. That kind of focus is becoming rare—and it might be one of the healthiest mental workouts we have left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="6985" data-end="7024"&gt;8. Bowling and other social sports&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7026" data-end="7097"&gt;Bowling leagues were a thing. So were golf groups and softball teams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7099" data-end="7357"&gt;At first glance, they seem like just casual fun. But social sports combine three powerful life-extending elements: movement, community, and routine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7099" data-end="7357"&gt;One longitudinal study found that higher diversity in social activities (e.g. clubs, groups, sports) was linked to &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/psychsocgerontology/article/79/5/gbae021/7609169?&amp;amp;login=false"&gt;lower mortality risk&lt;/a&gt; even after adjusting for health and activity frequency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7099" data-end="7357"&gt;The game matters less than the connection. Whether you’re rolling strikes or gutter balls, you’re winning at health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7479" data-end="7817"&gt;What fascinates me is how these activities create “third places”—spaces outside home and work where people gather. Sociologists argue these places are essential for community health, and boomers knew this instinctively. A bowling alley wasn’t just about pins. It was about friendship, laughter, and rituals that kept people coming back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="7824" data-end="7843"&gt;Final thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7845" data-end="7946"&gt;The hobbies that keep us alive aren’t flashy. They’re simple, social, and woven into everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7948" data-end="8132"&gt;Boomers didn’t need wearables or biohacking apps to tell them what felt good. They trusted habits that gave them connection, movement, and purpose. And now the science backs them up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8134" data-end="8251"&gt;So the next time you’re tempted to dismiss a “boomer pastime,” maybe lean in. It might just add years to your life.&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 01:35:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxQbFUxdW05X1FTMlFBU19WdHlYNXg3eUlidUwxb0pxbGU2bE9va1ZWTUdHZUtELU9oOHRLTldxNmI3OWI5NFBkVTVlMTV1c1NGRkczUFEwZ2V6TUdhejNiSHBhRWVNbHRlX0JBaWZmUWxRUVdVLVdtczVvdUV0aTJtQTBXN0Z1XzB4dnprR21XTXEyZmI5TWxDZFZVenBuTUpzZEFpLVZTVks0bl9sVEZqMUFB</guid></item><item><title>这个简单的每周习惯可以使一个人的生物钟倒转7.5年！ -印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/this-simple-weekly-habit-can-rewind-ones-biological-clock-by-7-5-years/articleshow/124088774.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;While slowing down the aging process, expensive supplements and intricate exercise regimens are usually at the center stage. But new research suggests that the real secret might be much more straightforward — walking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study in the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32175820/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt; Annals of Human Biology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; assessed data from 5,823 American adults and determined that at least 150 minutes of walking per week was associated with longer telomeres in comparison to non-walkers. Telomeres are always-discussed protective caps at the ends of our DNA strands. They get shorter with age, and more rapid shortening has been associated with heart disease, cancer, diabetes, and premature death. I.e., longer telomeres are a marker for slower biological aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is in line with more comprehensive studies on physical activity and longevity. For instance, Harvard studies involving more than 650,000 participants found that consistently engaging in 150–299 minutes of moderate exercise each week assisted adults in living 3.4 years longer than their sedentary counterparts. In some instances, when combined with normal weight and dietary habits, the benefits extended up to 7 years of extra longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-type="in_view" class="  "&gt;&lt;div class="EEW3_ timeline_pollWrapper_as " data-scrollga="scroll#poll_view"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="hLnAH"&gt;Poll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="KEEGr"&gt;Do you believe walking can effectively slow down the aging process?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walking is effective because it's both accessible and potent. Walking increases circulation, lowers inflammation, improves insulin sensitivity, and decreases blood pressure, all of which affect how quickly or slowly our cells age. The telomere studies add richer biological complexity to this tale, demonstrating that walking doesn't just make us feel young but actually keep our DNA young, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The genius of this discovery is how easy it is. Just 30 minutes of walking briskly five days a week is all it takes to meet the 150-minute goal. You don't require a membership at a gym or expensive equipment. Even dividing it into 10–15 minute walks throughout the day can be beneficial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naturally, there is more to the equation than walking. Diet, sleep, stress reduction, and other types of exercise all enter the picture. But if one activity is simple and has proven efficacy, walking on a daily basis might be one of the most effective longevity methods out there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to add walking to our busy schedules&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can be hard to find time to exercise with busy work schedules and family obligations. The good news is that they are convenient and can be easily adapted to our busy lifestyles. Here are a few easy strategies to incorporate walking without throwing off our hectic schedules:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Break it down into chunks: Rather than taking a long walk, divide 30 minutes into two or three shorter periods of walking. Attempt to fit in a 10 minute walk before work, speedy one on lunch break and then a quick one after dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make active transportation a habit: Wherever possible, walk or cycle to the office, do errands on foot or park further away from locations to get extra steps&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Set reminders: Use phone alarms, or apps to remind yourself to move regularly, especially during long periods of sitting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bottom line: Science now establishes that walking 150 minutes a week doesn't just make one healthier — it may actually slow cell aging, protect your DNA, and add purposeful years to your life. Sometimes, the simplest steps really are the most powerful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7wFBVV95cUxNY3NrSDRyZjhnbXFEbWhzQTZ6RjdNRmlwVjRkcEdkVG5fOG5TN0laR2NBNXE2YmZWRGdzNlF6U1I3MDFxcHhGWDJ1YlFMWGh5elVSR3B6ZWZOREE3QVhtT2V3MU9saTBPT01HMVpPN2pBVk1MTUR1emRQLUNtSTI4SG02akt1Z1R6bWo2TmlMUmdIekVYcFlXWHN5MnNRSGk1Nzg5X0RoeUlPMkp3azdKUmx5SDZaYVhlNkZqQ29nUnhrekFaMWpFcXRXQmJ1R1hVRF9nazFTMHdJMzZON2dOSWt5dEczTzBjX3hMNVViMA</guid></item><item><title>这可能是人类第一艘飞往另一个太阳系的多代星际飞船吗？ - Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/possibly-humanitys-first-multi-generational-starship-chrysalis-to-another-solar-system/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new interstellar concept called Chrysalis sketches a 36 mile long rotating habitat designed to carry 2,400 people on a one way, 400 year trip. The destination is &lt;a href="https://www.nasa.gov/image-article/alpha-centauri-triple-star-system-about-4-light-years-from-earth/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Alpha Centauri&lt;/a&gt;, about 25 trillion miles from Earth, a distance that rules out resupply once the ship leaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The plan treats the vessel as a closed society that must feed itself, educate children, care for the sick, and manufacture what it needs while coasting between stars. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It proposes layered habitats for farms, homes, schools, industry, and storage, all made livable by rotation that supplies gravity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-chrysalis-plan"&gt;The Chrysalis plan&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://i4is.org/who-we-are/board-of-directors/#gsc.tab=0" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Dr Andreas Hein&lt;/a&gt; is executive director of the Initiative for Interstellar Studies (&lt;a href="https://i4is.org/"&gt;I4IS&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group convened experts to see whether architecture, engineering, and social systems could be woven into a practical multi-century mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team behind Chrysalis proposes a long training phase on Earth. Early generations would live in isolated Antarctic stations for 70 to 80 years to build the habits, culture, and mental resilience needed for life off planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chrysalis uses a nested shell layout around a central spine. Inner-zones grow plants, fungi, &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/living-microbes-found-sealed-inside-2-billion-year-old-rock/"&gt;microbes&lt;/a&gt;, insects, and some livestock in controlled farms, mid layers hold parks, clinics, schools, and libraries, and outer shells host workshops and storage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dwellings sit between community space and light industry to keep daily life close to work and services. The outermost storehouse would be robot heavy to cut human labor and risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-alpha-centauri-and-proxima-b"&gt;Alpha Centauri and Proxima b&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alpha Centauri is the nearest star system, which shortens the voyage by every realistic metric. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The likely landing zone is &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nature19106" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Proxima Centauri b&lt;/a&gt;, an Earth-size exoplanet reported to orbit in a temperate zone that could allow liquid water under some conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once the ship enters the system, shuttles housed in the central core would ferry crews and equipment to the planet. The design treats that arrival as the beginning of settlement rather than the end of the mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The proposal aims to arrive with full knowledge systems, from agriculture to medicine to materials science. It assumes no external logistics, so onboard manufacturing and repair are treated as basic survival needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-artificial-gravity-and-health"&gt;Artificial gravity and health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chrysalis relies on artificial gravity from steady rotation to keep bodies closer to Earth normal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://technology.nasa.gov/patent/TOP2-311" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Rotation-based gravity&lt;/a&gt; is a studied countermeasure for cardiovascular and musculoskeletal deconditioning, as summarized in a &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/physiology/articles/10.3389/fphys.2018.00716/full"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; that evaluated centrifuge experiments in humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spin introduces tradeoffs like &lt;a href="https://oceanservice.noaa.gov/education/tutorial_currents/04currents1.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Coriolis effects&lt;/a&gt; that can disturb balance if rotation is too fast. The nested layout helps tune spin and radius so living areas feel stable while still providing adequate effective gravity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Radiation exposure is another core risk for a centuries long voyage. The concept leans on structure and materials, using mass in the habitat shells to reduce particle flux rather than relying only on specialized shields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health care sits in the communal layer near schools and parks to keep services accessible. That placement supports daily routines and reduces travel time for patients and caregivers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-chrysalis-power-and-propulsion"&gt;Chrysalis power and propulsion&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For power and thrust, the team points to nuclear fusion as the long term energy source. Fusion plant concepts and timelines remain under &lt;a href="https://www.iaea.org/publications/15777/iaea-world-fusion-outlook-2024" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;development&lt;/a&gt; and have been mapped and evaluated extensively. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors propose a 20 to 25 year construction window once industry can deliver the required systems. They treat in-space manufacturing as a mission essential capability to replace worn parts and build upgrades during cruise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Energy production, recycling, and life support appear across multiple layers to avoid single points of failure. Heavy maintenance and logistics live at the outer edge where robots can operate with fewer human safety constraints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The population would be planned to hover near 1,500 to balance resources, education, and health. That cap sits below the ship’s maximum berth count to leave margin for emergencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-competitions-like-this-help"&gt;Why competitions like this help&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chrysalis won first place in the 2025 &lt;a href="https://www.projecthyperion.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;competition&lt;/a&gt;, and the jury praised both technical breadth and attention to people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Chrysalis impressed the jury with its system-level coherence and innovative design of the modular habitat structure but also overall depth of detail,” wrote the Project Hyperion &lt;a href="https://www.projecthyperion.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;jury&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Chrysalis is a living spaceship where humans, robots and artificial intelligent agents share information, experiences and decision-making processes,” stated the Chrysalis team, explaining that their starship was more than hardware. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We asked participants to integrate architecture, technology and social systems to conceptualise a functional society spanning centuries, and the outcome was beyond expectations,” said Dr Hein executive director of the &lt;a href="https://i4is.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Initiative for Interstellar Studies&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concept work cannot replace flight hardware, yet it shapes the questions future engineers must answer. It also documents social and cultural choices that matter as much as engines when people live their whole lives off &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/earths-atmospheric-rivers-have-shifted-towards-the-poles-causing-big-local-weather-changes/"&gt;Earth&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-chrysalis-would-prepare-for-arrival"&gt;How Chrysalis would prepare for arrival&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The core would carry compact shuttles sized for surface hops, cargo, and emergency evacuation. Pilots and maintenance crews would train during the cruise so landings do not depend on a single cohort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Food systems would keep a mix of biomes, from tropical to boreal, to preserve biodiversity and stabilize diets. That diversity lowers the risk that one crop failure cascades across the whole &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/ecosystem-attack-predicting-the-success-of-species-invasions/"&gt;ecosystem&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge transfer shows up in how learning is embedded in daily life. Schools would be near labs, workshops, and farms so students practice skills early and keep them across generations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Governance would be transparent, with planned births, shared resources, and collaborative decision tools. The aim is to prevent shocks to a small population where every loss hurts community resilience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 01:19:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxPM2UxR1NrNUdFWlItWDFNYzJHSzBPLWUwWW02OS1LUWJ5LW9XOWdDbFdVTGF2UnYxRGtieXBQc3hxUkRWUGdZLWlfeUJsazFqVU1EU0E0REY3VHB1V0FwMWE2cmd4VXh5RFJSX2FQc1JNLWlZbklxaHJPdFdjU1ZqTk53NWZXaVRUMktkRFc1VzNIUzJuR2Fra0RLZ09UWDVVUTZQSmFGQjd2WV9GVmg3MjNUR04</guid></item><item><title>缓解膝盖疼痛并避免手术的六个简单步骤- dailymail.co.uk</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15139739/ease-knee-pain-avoid-surgery-six-steps.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When keen runner Jon Reeves, 54, began struggling to get down the stairs in the morning, he knew his knee pain was more than just sports injuries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The father of two from Oxfordshire had gone from daily runs and regular badminton matches to strapping up his inflamed joints and dosing himself on painkillers just to get through the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2020 doctors confirmed the cause: &lt;a target="_self" href="/sciencetech/osteoarthritis/index.html" id="mol-7df044a0-9ba6-11f0-ac66-c563bb30a77b" class=""&gt;osteoarthritis&lt;/a&gt; – the degenerative joint disease that affects about ten million Britons. More than half of cases strike the knee, with 100,000 people a year ending up on the &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/nhs/index.html" id="mol-7dee96f0-9ba6-11f0-ac66-c563bb30a77b"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt; waiting list for joint replacement surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Getting the diagnosis was devastating,’ says Jon. ‘I thought it was an old person’s disease and I was worried it would only get worse.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Initially prescribed anti-inflammatory drugs and exercises that were painful and brought little relief, Jon’s condition worsened until doctors warned him that he would need a double knee replacement. But by combining acupuncture, weight training and a Mediterranean-style diet, he was able to slash his pain level and postpone surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I am now managing amazingly – largely pain-free and back to hiking, swimming, cycling and long walks with my dalmatian Oscar,’ he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts say thousands more like Jon could delay or even avoid surgery with simple lifestyle changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Jon Reeves was diagnosed wth osteoarthritis in 2020. By combining acupuncture, weight training and a Mediterranean-style diet, he slashed his pain level and postponed surgery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The degenerative joint disease affects about ten million Britons. More than half of cases strike the knee, with 100,000 people a year ending up on the NHS waiting list for joint replacement surgery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt; Last week, Mail on Sunday columnist Dr Ellie Cannon wrote she was ‘worried that not enough osteoarthritis patients realise there are steps they can take to avoid knee replacement surgery’. In response she had a flood of letters and emails from readers sharing their own remedies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One, Bill Ellis, 81, from Suffolk, who suffers from osteoarthritis in his knees, said a combination of supplements ‘has certainly made a difference in reducing my pain’ adding: ‘I also do 20 squats every other morning, not too deep I hasten to add, and it keeps the muscles stronger, which helps.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Eddie Boyle, 77, from Bedfordshire, swears by capsaicin cream – which contains extracts from chillis – for reducing his pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So from diet swaps to supplements that work and exercises to ease the agony, here is the experts’ guide to managing the pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;1. FOLLOW THE MED DIET &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Hailed as a key to longevity, a Mediterranean diet has also been shown to help reduce the symptoms of arthritis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The eating style, common in Greece, Italy and Spain, is focused on fresh fruit and vegetables, fish and chicken, whole grains and olive oil, while cutting back on red meat and sweets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2016 study of more than 4,000 people with osteoarthritis in their knees found those who stuck most closely to the diet were significantly less likely to suffer crippling joint pain. They also scored better on overall physical health and showed fewer signs of depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts say the diet’s anti-inflammatory properties can help soothe swollen joints, while also protecting heart health and supporting weight control – two key risk factors for arthritis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the Mediterranean diet won’t ‘cure’ osteoarthritis, scientists suggest it offers a simple, natural way to ease symptoms and improve day-to-day well-being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘The Mediterranean diet can be really beneficial for patients,’ says Dr Wendy Holden, medical advisor for Arthritis Action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘A diet rich in fruit and veg as well as fish and whole grains, in addition to cutting down on ultra-processed foods, is key to cutting inflammation.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A 2016 study of more than 4,000 people with osteoarthritis in their knees found those who stuck most closely to the Mediterranean diet were significantly less likely to suffer crippling joint pain&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Protein intake is another crucial part of the puzzle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘From the age of 40 our muscle mass declines by 2 to 3 per cent per year, so we need to take in more protein from different sources in our diet – ideally at least 40 grams daily,’ says Dr Lucy Donaldson, Director of Research at Versus Arthritis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘This can be a challenge for many of us, but fortunately our research shows that an essential building block for protein called leucine – found in fish, nuts and legumes – is very potent at stimulating muscle protein levels, helping to maintain skeletal muscle.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other experts argue that the type of diet matters less than weight loss itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘The real benefit to any diet, in relation to osteoarthritis symptoms, is maintaining a healthy weight,’ says Professor Philip Conaghan, an arthritis specialist at the University of Leeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘This is because it reduces the load on the joints, which in turn eases pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘But excess fat also drives inflammation, which makes symptoms worse.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Research backs this up. Studies show weight loss reduces levels of inflammatory chemicals released by fat tissue, and can slow cartilage damage even in non-weight-bearing joints such as the hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Anecdotally, doctors say patients who shed excess pounds often report less wrist or finger pain – clear evidence the benefits go beyond simply lightening the load on knees and hips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;2. TRY WEIGHT-LOSS JABS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mounting evidence suggests weight-loss injections may ease the pain of osteoarthritis – and in some cases this may be due to more than just losing excess fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For 54-year-old Sian Rios, who suffers from arthritis in her hip, a private prescription for Mounjaro has meant she can finally ditch her walking stick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Before starting the jabs, the care home manager from Swindon was in such severe pain she was unable to walk more than a few metres. At night the throbbing pain would wake her repeatedly, leaving her exhausted and sleep-deprived.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox floatRHS health" data-version="2" id="mol-e778e500-9bae-11f0-ac66-c563bb30a77b" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15139739/ease-knee-pain-avoid-surgery-six-steps.html"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;IT'S A FACT&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt; &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Women are 40 per cent more likely to get knee osteoarthritis than men, with an increase in cases during menopause. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Four months on, she has shed six stone to weigh just over 17st.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I feel like it has given me my life back,’ says Sian. ‘Within weeks of using Mounjaro I was suffering from less pain, but now I very rarely have flare-ups and use pain relief far less often.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I have lost a lot of weight since May, but what I have really gained is mobility, confidence and hope. I’ve gone from barely being able to walk to taking strolls around the lake. It’s night and day compared with the start of the year.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her hip replacement scheduled for later this year is now on hold thanks to her progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Research backs her experience. A 2025 Taiwanese study of nearly 1,000 patients with osteoarthritis in knees found weight-loss injections reduced the risk of needing joint replacement surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Preliminary studies have suggested there is a benefit to weight-loss injections beyond just weight reduction,’ adds Dr Holden at Arthritis Action. ‘It appears they can help protect cartilage from wear and tear, slowing the progression of disease. The benefits are increasingly being reported by patients, and we are likely to see greater use of the drugs for arthritis going forwards.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Currently, however, arthritis is not included in the prescribing guidelines for weight-loss jabs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;3. BUILD STRENGTH FIRST&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts say the key to managing osteoarthritis pain – and preventing it in the first place – is building strength.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Strictly Come Dancing star Joanne Clifton, 41, who was diagnosed with osteoarthritis in both knees in 2015, is one of those who credits strengthening exercises as preventing her from needing surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Professor Philip Conaghan regularly sees patients aged 40 to 75 with knee, hip or other joint pain, and says muscle weakness is “almost universal”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;His advice is simple: ‘First, get strong, then get fit. Just telling people to walk round the block is a bad starting point – because they are weak, they can’t walk at a brisk pace and they’re not getting any benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Strictly Come Dancing star Joanne Clifton, 41, was diagnosed with osteoarthritis in both knees in 2015, and credits strengthening exercises as preventing her from needing surgery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Once they’ve built some muscle strength, they can start on aerobic fitness, such as on an exercise bike or cross trainer, or swimming. Walking laps in a pool is a fabulous exercise for weak people.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He warns that difficulty undoing a jar, or struggling to get out of a chair or bath, are red flags – even before joint pain sets in – that muscles are weakening and putting too much strain on joints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The benefits are clear. A review last year in the Annals of Physical and Rehabilitation Medicine concluded there was ‘overwhelming evidence’ that strength training significantly reduces pain and improves function, performance and quality of life in people with knee and hip osteoarthritis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Exercise works because joints depend on the network of muscles and tendons around them. Isaac Selby-Burton, a personal trainer who specialises in arthritis coaching, says: ‘It can be hard for people to take that initial step with exercises, because of the pain the condition causes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I recommend starting with resistance bands, focusing on range of motion and muscles like the quads, which are vital for people with knee problems.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;4. USE ACUPUNCTURISTS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many patients swear by acupuncture to manage osteoarthritis pain, saying it allows them to do the strengthening exercises that bring long-term relief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The ancient Chinese therapy involves inserting fine needles into specific points in the body, and is said to encourage the release of natural pain-relieving chemicals, improve circulation and reduce stiffness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox floatRHS health" data-version="2" id="mol-08b1d6a0-9baf-11f0-ac66-c563bb30a77b" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15139739/ease-knee-pain-avoid-surgery-six-steps.html"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;IT'S A FACT&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt; &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists have found evidence of osteoarthritis in dinosaur fossils, making it one of the oldest known diseases.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The evidence is mixed, but growing. A review in 2025 of 18 studies involving 14,000 people found acupuncture was effective in reducing pain and improving function in osteoarthritis. Other research has shown modest short-term benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘For many people the pain of osteoarthritis has the greatest impact on their lives,’ says Dr Donaldson at Versus Arthritis. ‘Exercise can have very positive effects on pain but isn’t suitable for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Although National Institute for Health and Care Excellence guidelines do not recommend acupuncture for osteoarthritis, rheumatoid arthritis or other inflammatory forms of arthritis, we know many people living with chronic pain and inflammation use it. Our recent survey on complementary treatments found one in two people who tried acupuncture for arthritis reported some level of pain relief.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;5. USE SUPPLEMENTS THAT WORK&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Patients often swear by supplements to help ease arthritis pain – but experts say the evidence is thin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Among the most popular are turmeric (or sometimes just curcumin, the chemical compound that it contains), glucosamine sulphate (which is produced commercially from shellfish exoskeletons) and chondroitin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘There is very little evidence to suggest that these supplements will help relieve osteoarthritis,’ says Dr Wendy Holden, medical advisor for Arthritis Action, who is also honorary consultant rheumatologist at Basingstoke and North Hampshire NHS Foundation trust.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The only two supplements with any evidence behind them are cod liver oil and rosehip&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘The issue is that although the compounds themselves may have some benefit, supplements don’t usually contain enough of the key ingredient to make a real difference.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The only two supplements with any evidence behind them are cod liver oil and rosehip – though even here, results are mixed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cod liver oil is rich in omega-3 oils, which are thought to have anti-inflammatory effects, but trials in osteoarthritis have generally failed to show clear benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rosehip powder – which is made from the seed pods of a rose bush – has shown more promise, with several small studies and reviews suggesting it can modestly reduce pain and stiffness, though the effects are limited and further research is needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;6. SPECIALIST BRACES CAN EASE SYMPTOMS &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Specialist knee braces can also help to improve osteoarthritis symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2017 study followed 63 patients awaiting total knee replacement who were fitted with an ‘unloading’ or ‘offloading’ brace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After eight years, 40 per cent of those who had worn their brace consistently for two years said they no longer needed surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The brace, made of lightweight plastic and fabric, straps around the knee to apply a gentle sideways pull that helps realign the joint. A hinge on the side absorbs some of the downward force, reducing pressure and allowing patients to be more active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Patients in the trial initially wore the brace almost constantly, before using it selectively for activities needing extra support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Those who wore it for more than six months were half as likely to require surgery as those who gave up within three months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The same model – the Unloader One, made by Icelandic company Ossur – has even been worn by TV star Ant McPartlin, 49.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;McPartlin revealed he turned to it after his struggle with painkiller addiction following his ‘botched’ knee surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>dailymail.co.uk</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:32:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxPOUV4cENOblhOQjNSNWtQRWdtTjVnRFFrS1lXZnJROVRLWnNyV3hsS2F0RnhZSndjcFdPTlZ0RkpGbV9jTExwWTkwdWZVUThLTU42SjlRZ2VxUFhjbVJmQlRWTlZDOEJsc3NSTVpYX0NQTDNUZGswcHBXb3pXM1JHZHR6cndNMEEwMXdGeXByb2FwYVVCRXA3RUtCWQ</guid></item><item><title>N70,000艾滋病预防注射分裂尼日利亚人- Punch报纸</title><link>https://punchng.com/n70000-hiv-prevention-injection-splits-nigerians/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Punch Newspapers</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:25:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE55d0RQTWN3YVJ5LURqYVhSQTRYcnVJZS02TmhjTFZ6VHRzbjBNcWdMUnJXV01MOXFrUVcwSTdXY0xnbmFlUUJJakU5SUxhdXM2bVlZV2hCQUJocjIxTTFaVWltOHdLSnZiM0QwdVJENXpBZFJwME9HeA</guid></item><item><title>世界视网膜日：医生说，小习惯在保护你的视力方面每天都有很大的回报-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/world-retina-day-doctors-say-small-habits-pay-off-big-in-protecting-your-vision-daily/articleshow/124183315.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;World Retina Day is all about shining a light on the importance of eye health, specifically the retina, that tiny but mighty part at the back of your eye that makes clear vision possible. Without it, things like reading your favorite book, scrolling on your phone, or even recognizing faces would be a real struggle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;We at TOI spoke to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Yogesh Patil&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, Vitreo-Retina Surgeon, Dr Agarwals Eye Hospital, Sanpada; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Kalpana R&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, Senior Consultant, Ophthalmology, SIMS Hospital, Chennai; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Krishna Nagaradh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, Vitreo - Retinal Consultant, Dr Agarwals Eye Hospital, Bengaluru on common retinal conditions and how to take care of retinal health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Nutrition for healthy eyes: Here's what doctor recommends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What are the most common retinal conditions you see today, and are cases increasing with lifestyle changes like screen time and diabetes?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Yogesh Patil: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Age related vision changes are usually gradually progressive like needing reading glasses(presbyopia), scattering of light especially at night, taking longer time to adjust when going from bright to dark places, fluctuating vision. These are normal age related changes which can be treated with glasses, lubricant eye drops or better lighting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if vision changes are sudden in onset, asymmetric or associated with flashes, floaters, distortion or field loss are warning symptoms and are usually associated with Retina diseases. In such conditions an urgent dilated retinal check-up is needed with an expert. If proven Retina disease then it needs certain tests and immediate treatment as time is extremely crucial in these problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Krishna Nagaradh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common retina related conditions seen today are related to diabetes and are known as diabetic retinopathy. Yes the cases are increasing to a greater extent with a sedentary lifestyle which most of the middle-aged people are used to it nowadays. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Kalpana R: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common retinal conditions we see today are diabetic retinopathy, age related macular degenerations and Glaucoma and eye stroke. Lifestyle changes like prolonged screen time renders a person obese, enhancing diabetes. Diabetes mellitus could occur familial or secondary due to co-morbidities, bad dietary habits and sedentary lifestyle. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How can people differentiate between normal age-related vision changes and potential warning signs of retinal diseases?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Yogesh Patil: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prolonged near work and less outdoor time is leading to higher incidence of minus Glasses called “myopia epidemic.” In children, sustained near focus may accelerate myopia progression leading to gradual increase in glass power. Higher minus power (Myopia) increases risk of several problems like retinal tears &amp;amp; detachments and Myopic macular degeneration. Chronic stress and irregular sleep are risk factors for development of central serous chorioretinopathy, a retinal condition more seen in young and middle aged males. Sedentary lifestyle, obesity and low physical activity can lead to early development of diabetic, hypertension and raised cholesterol levels which secondarily leads Diabetic Retinopathy, Retinal vein occlusion like diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Krishna Nagaradh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The vision changes due to retinal conditions are usually sudden in onset and are more obvious like appearance of floaters in front of eyes, seeing flashes or beginning to see distorted images, at the same time vision changes related to normal ageing are usually gradual like difficulty in focusing near objects over a period of time like seen in presbyopia or gradual blurring of vision with glare like symptoms seen in cataract.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Kalpana R: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Normal age-related visual changes could be due to receding of reading distance (usually starts in late 30’s or early 40’s) called as presbyopia. Dry eyes causing blurred vision, cataracts causing blurred vision or effective vision. Eye fatigue is common after straining. People cannot differentiate between the normal aging of the eyes and vision disturbances due to retinal diseases unless they become severe and cause a significant amount of vision loss. Hence, regular eye check-ups are mandatory to identify and treat them at the earliest. Retinal diseases symptoms are such as seeing floaters, flashes, loss of vision, loss of central vision, and loss of peripheral vision. Individuals should be mindful that before these symptoms occur a significant amount of retina is affected beyond repair in certain conditions like diabetes, degenerative diseases, glaucoma., etc. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;We hear a lot about diabetic retinopathy—how big of a public health concern is it right now?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Yogesh Patil:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Currently India has the second-largest diabetic population in the world and Diabetic Retinopathy is the most common cause of vision loss in working-age adults worldwide. Approximately in India there are 12 million people suffering from Diabetic Retinopathy and 20% of these have variable degree of permanent vision loss. The worst part of Diabetic Retinopathy is no pain, very few subtle symptoms in early stages and by the time patients present with complaints its already advanced stage with some amount of permanent vision loss. Advanced stages of diabetic retinopathy require expensive treatments like lasers, intravitreal injections, surgery). The good news is up to 90% of vision loss from DR can be prevented with timely screening, sugar control and early treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Krishna Nagaradh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diabetic retinopathy is the leading cause of blindness in the middle aged population. Globally there were 12 crore people suffering from diabetic retinopathy in 2010 and this number can reach upto 20 crores by 2030. Diabetic retinopathy has the potential to cause blindness and with increasing prevalence of diabetes worldwide makes this condition a bigger public health condition which has to to be taken seriously and people should get screened so that the patients are diagnosed early and treated to prevent major vision loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Kalpana R: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diabetic retinopathy is of major concern in today’s world since the number of cases are increasing despite awareness. It’s a condition which affects the retinal blood vessels and in turn affects the layers of the retina at different stages causing blindness if not treated at the earliest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What role does early detection play in preventing severe vision loss from conditions like macular degeneration or retinal detachment?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Yogesh Patil: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Macular degeneration and retinal detachment are two separate diseases but if detected early treatment is simpler and more vision rewarding in both. In case of retinal detachment early detection involves screening for flashes and floaters, detecting peripheral Retinal degeneration/tears which can easily be treated with a quick outpatient laser via major surgery for retinal detachment. Early detection of dry macular degeneration means patients can start lifestyle changes (diet rich in antioxidants, stopping smoking, supplements in select cases) and monitoring which can slow progression of condition to more devastating disease like Wet Macular degeneration. Even in wet age related macular degeneration: If detected early, intravitreal anti-VEGF injections can preserve reading and driving vision whereas detected late (scarred macula), even the best treatment cannot restore useful central vision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Krishna Nagaradh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early detection is crucial in treating any of the retinal conditions as we can minimise the damage caused to the retina and slow the disease progression which in turn preserves the vision. In treating retinal detachment intervention done in hours to days of time will restore maximum vision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Kalpana R: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ingemination to prevent peripheral vision loss due to retinal diseases is a regular eye check up with an ophthalmologist (not optical) and following the investigations and treatment protocols suggested by the doctor without fail. The amount of retinal cells lost in the inadvertence cannot be reverted. All the attempts are to retain the viable tissue for a prolonged period to give some amount of quality of life to the patient. Retinal detachment is realized early by the patient (which is possible by noticing loss of vision suddenly or gradually, floaters and flashes) can be treated well and there is a possibility of patients getting a good quality of vision post-surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="86"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How important is diet and lifestyle in protecting retinal health, and what simple habits can people adopt?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="88"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Yogesh Patil: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have already discussed the role of bad lifestyle/ diet results in several retina diseases. Now let's see what rectification should be done. In terms of diets, foods rich in antioxidants (green leafy vegetables, coloured fruits) and Omega 3 fatty acids( nuts, chia seeds, fish) should be a regular part of one’s diet. Restrict refined sugars, processed food, alcohol and tobacco / smoking, regular exercise improves blood flow, lowers risk of diabetes &amp;amp; hypertension. Annual/ regular eye check-ups especially in diabetic, hypertensive or highly myopic. Balanced screen use and encourages outdoor activity in children to reduce myopia progression. Stress &amp;amp; sleep management - lowers risk of CSCR and helps overall vascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="93"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Krishna Nagaradh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diets rich in anti oxidants like vitamin A,C,E zinc, lutein and zeaxanthin play a vital role in protecting the retina. They are found in abundance in green leafy vegetables. Also foods like fruits and vegetables support the overall functioning of the eyes. To quit smoking is another major lifestyle modification needed to be adopted as it will reduce the oxidative stress over the retina and prevent its damage. Managing blood sugar and blood pressure levels. Protection of once eyes from harmful UV radiations by using protective glasses, keeping self hydrated, reducing screen time, getting enough sleep and avoiding frequent touching of eyes also plays role in maintaining eye health. Regular eye checkups which should include dilated eye examination for early detection of retinal pathology will avoid severe vision damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="101"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Kalpana R: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A well-balanced diet is the most important requirement for healthy eyes. Fruits, nuts, green vegetables are all essential for the function of the retina which carries the electrical impulses to the brain which is converted as an image for us to see. Without balanced nutrition the retina degenerates faster. A proper lifestyle is the quintessence of healthy eyes. Cutting down on screen time, having adequate amount of sleep, using the gadgets at a proper distance (60-70cm away) with anti-reflective screen, avoiding reading in dim lights or glaring lights, following the 20/20/20 rule which is only 20 minutes of attention to gadgets at a stretch, blinking every 20 seconds, and looking at objects 20 meters away; this is of utmost importance to prevent dry eyes and eye strain while working. Well balanced nutrition is mandatory, avoiding eye injuries (wearing protective goggles at necessary times) should be borne in mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="108"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What’s one myth about retinal health you wish more people understood correctly?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="110"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Yogesh Patil: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;People think that if their vision is good, their retina must be healthy. The truth is early retinal diseases are usually silent. Good vision does not equal a healthy retina. The only way to know is through a regular dilated retinal exam or imaging specially in at risk people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="114"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Krishna Nagaradh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The major myth which I have heard from many of my patients is that eye check ups need to be done only when they face a difficulty in vision. Regular eye checkups are must especially in diabetics cause early diagnosis and treatment can avoid major eye related complications in future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="117"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Kalpana R: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A common myth about absent retinal diseases is that they can be cured at any time. But the fact is in some individuals the worst outcome can be averted while in some it can be prolonged. Take good care of your eyes and see the colors of the world with a Duchenne smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="122"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This day is a reminder to check in on your eye health, because conditions like macular degeneration, diabetic retinopathy, and retinal detachment can sneak up without obvious symptoms at first. Regular eye exams are key. A quick visit can help catch problems early and protect your sight long-term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="124"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it’s not just about doctor visits, your lifestyle plays a role too. Eating foods rich in antioxidants (think leafy greens, berries, and fish packed with omega-3s), wearing sunglasses to block UV rays, and keeping your blood sugar and blood pressure in check all support retinal health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="126"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, on World Retina Day, give your eyes some love. Schedule that eye exam, grab a pair of good shades, and maybe even swap the fries for a salad, it’s a small step with a big payoff for your vision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="128"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 23:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwJBVV95cUxQTlVfVi14X19rWWYwQ2lPZzhVVmlvUkdhSmRNbS1abEktYzBhdDlYQmJ1ZGZPSlVaSzdQemJPQXdYLVpkdE9POWg3VzdKREFzZk5DOElzVW45SUo5Q2QzRTJneGNNamdKbS1WbzRXTmNnQ0hIMVJDclRDN2hpUTRDWEQxQmkzdzJBWUx6eFRfS2JiR1RPU1ZlRm5GQmdnSnZ1cVJpSjBEMWJ0OXhTZDlkQzBudzkxQ2dNOUhGajNYNEdFaXdZNzRCaDJHX0lqLXpnVzNpbGthQ2R5aHFmVG9rTHJiUi14SFZ2MEFwa21wYW53UG5zcjE1M2I3bWt4emg3bUdLZzZac2ZzU1RCd0ZEQTVOTdIBmAJBVV95cUxPeXNyY0ZtWU52UzJEVGlYazJuOXVZdHlWd01sNjlHRXJwVUZqTklmYllaQzRZSmtsSXBzb2xjM0tNVEJFaGMxbXAyNzAtY2plQ1RoT2x4cHdzODBfMVNaSV9FMXVUSkd3V1JSaWN4Vllwdy1pSGtPNW5NRkVNcXRTaXRIOG02NjRtX3dTcjl4bmVLalVoQ3BxSF9wUGgzdFVzTHNqTkd3c0xnWkNlUmFCX3MySlY2QkpjZGNScTJHak0ydTVVcV9NSnZibURTbHgwSEtyX1owTmxDTl9CN25YRFhhTllLTERvNVVQZ243dk5VUWF4Rzc4LVVQTHVYVm5XMldhOXF2azBOM0xIZTFZZ2VQblhfc0hI</guid></item><item><title>随着卡车驶入数百万只死鸡的潜在垃圾场，巴尔米拉社区感到震惊- TMJ4新闻</title><link>https://www.tmj4.com/news/jefferson-county/palmyra-community-alarmed-as-trucks-pull-into-potential-dump-site-for-millions-of-dead-chickens</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="RichTextArticleBody-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;PALMYRA, Wis. — After TMJ4's &lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.tmj4.com/news/jefferson-county/palmyra-neighbors-brace-for-second-mass-chicken-disposal-as-bird-flu-strikes-jefferson-county"&gt;initial story&lt;/a&gt; on Thursday, the Palmyra community in Jefferson County reached out to the news team concerned about the smell of millions of dead chickens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a class="Link" href="https://datcp.wi.gov/Pages/Highly-Pathogenic-Avian-Influenza-Confirmed-in-Jefferson-County.aspx"&gt;Wisconsin Department of Agriculture, Trade and Consumer Protection&lt;/a&gt;, a commercial flock of chickens were slaughtered after a case of bird flu was discovered in the county. Their bodies are believed to have been dumped in that community Saturday morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zion Rd and County Cl closed on Saturday, but large trucks could be seen driving in and out of the area where neighbor Lisa Eddy said a large egg farm owns property and previously dumped dead chickens in 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eddy said trucks have been driving to the dump site all morning, drivers can be seen wearing masks, something she said is a tell tale sign that soon, the smell of millions of dead chickens will once again plague the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="Figure" itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
    
        &lt;div class="Figure-container"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://ewscripps.brightspotcdn.com/dims4/default/e8c75ae/2147483647/strip/true/crop/4284x5712+0+0/resize/1080x1440!/quality/90/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fewscripps-brightspot.s3.amazonaws.com%2F84%2Fe6%2Fa368667d4e1db2d4458a2d97d6ea%2Fimg-1321.jpeg" alt="Lisa Eddy lives near chicken dumpsite in Palmyra" srcset="https://ewscripps.brightspotcdn.com/dims4/default/e8c75ae/2147483647/strip/true/crop/4284x5712+0+0/resize/1080x1440!/quality/90/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fewscripps-brightspot.s3.amazonaws.com%2F84%2Fe6%2Fa368667d4e1db2d4458a2d97d6ea%2Fimg-1321.jpeg 1x,https://ewscripps.brightspotcdn.com/dims4/default/d96de6c/2147483647/strip/true/crop/4284x5712+0+0/resize/2160x2880!/quality/90/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fewscripps-brightspot.s3.amazonaws.com%2F84%2Fe6%2Fa368667d4e1db2d4458a2d97d6ea%2Fimg-1321.jpeg 2x"&gt;&lt;p class="Figure-credit" itemprop="author"&gt;Marcus Aarsvold&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
        &lt;figcaption class="Figure-caption" itemprop="caption"&gt;Lisa Eddy lives near chicken dumpsite in Palmyra&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It's super frustrating, annoying and really impacts your quality of life. You can't be outside, you can't have the windows open and you can't enjoy walks with the dogs or anything," Eddy said. "We're also worried about the groundwater. This is the second time that they're dumping millions of birds. When is it going to stop?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She said the first time this happened, the smell lasted for an entire year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a class="Link" href="https://datcp.wi.gov/Pages/Highly-Pathogenic-Avian-Influenza-Confirmed-in-Jefferson-County.aspx"&gt;Wisconsin Department of Agriculture &lt;/a&gt;confirmed the bird flu case of a commercial flock in Jefferson County and that they're being depopulated, but did not name the specific farm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;"This story was reported on-air by a journalist and has been converted to this platform with the assistance of AI. Our editorial team verifies all reporting on all platforms for fairness and accuracy."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div class="Form"&gt;&lt;p class="Form-title"&gt;Let's talk:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class="Form-description"&gt;Hey there! At TMJ4 News, we're all about listening to our audience and tackling the stuff that really matters to you. Got a story idea, tip, or just want to chat about this piece? Hit us up using the form below. For more ways to get in touch, head over to tmj4.com/tips. &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
        
        
    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;It’s about time to watch on your time. Stream local news and weather 24/7 by searching for “TMJ4” on your device.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.tmj4.com/apps" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Available for download on Roku, Apple TV, Amazon Fire TV, and more.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.tmj4.com/reportatypo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Report a typo or error&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; // &lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.tmj4.com/news/submit-news-tip"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Submit a news tip&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TMJ4 News</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 23:22:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1AFBVV95cUxPcHdMYjVCTXo4ZkVQVjRfLTA5SUVmU01odkNmcmgwcDk1b1BZY3ZTZFFzRGhLR3FGcmo0ZmNMVDQtLVIxUWhBZGFuMHlrNjZLb2hVMkVUZXNzc2psc1VqWlJpM3NLMnF5Wng4RHNCYjZobWJya3NMUXBvT0d1dlZoak94SXRlSGVtQ3hMSkpnMFEtUk1RTXdmbkdaZXFEdVMzZmhDMmhqTmxNNjc2dGVRa3NVWlhMa2ZzQkJZU3BrTUhjM292LVNEcjBoU1VKbkN4OVNQcQ</guid></item><item><title>胶原蛋白补充剂是否有助于减少皮肤衰老的迹象？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cjr5zj12ye1o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Collagen: Do you drink it? Inject it? Rub it on your skin? And does it work?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-c4820dd1-0 cYDsPh"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-c4820dd1-11 bxdaHR"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;Ruth Clegg&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;Health and wellbeing reporter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 ERpRj"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Woman applying cream to her face" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;When it comes to collagen - how do you take yours?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;There are parties where people even drink shots of the anti-ageing supplement, often followed by a hefty tequila - though the latter is probably not recommended in the quest for youthful, peachy skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Collagen is the most abundant protein in the body, and forms the scaffolding that helps maintain the structural integrity of our skin and musculoskeletal system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In short, collagen helps to keep our skin plump, our joints and bones strong, and our hair and nails healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It's become so treasured that some dermatologists recommend "banking" it - investing in our collagen supply early so we have surplus when the inevitable happens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Yes. The inevitable. Ageing. Sigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Our collagen supply naturally starts to decrease, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.uclahealth.org/news/article/should-you-take-collagen-supplements#:~:text=The%20body's%20collagen%20production%20slows%2Cup%20the%20level%20of%20decline." class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;on average around 1% a year, as we reach our mid to late 20s&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The speed of its decline depends on factors like our exposure to the sun, diet, and stress levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But is there credible science to say supplements can replenish our dwindling supply? And if so, what's the best way of getting it into our bodies?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Kimberlie Smith Kimberlie Smith with long brown hair looking straight into camera" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Kimberlie Smith&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;As a sleep deprived mother, Kimberlie says collagen makes a difference to her skin&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Kimberlie Smith started taking collagen about six months ago. The 33-year-old began using it after a "traumatic year" in 2024. Her son was born prematurely, and as a result of stress, the mother-of-three says her skin took a "huge hit".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She uses marine collagen, the type derived from fish, in a tropical-flavoured gel she drinks every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"My skin definitely seems to be brighter and clearer, plus my hair has never looked better since I started taking it," Kimberlie says. "As a sleep deprived mother, it's definitely made a difference."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Emma Wedgeworth, a consultant dermatologist based on London's Harley Street, says while there is some &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.jafc.6b05679" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;research to suggest taking collagen orally has an impact&lt;/a&gt;, she remains sceptical.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She says the idea that collagen can make its journey through our body - not the easiest of quests - and land exactly where we need it to be is probably wishful thinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;For a start, it has to get through the gut without being completely broken down. Collagen is a large molecule so companies have now started to break it up into smaller pieces - collagen peptides - otherwise known as hydrolysed collagen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Even though this collagen - now in its smaller form - has a better chance of making its way through the intestinal wall and into the bloodstream, it still has a long way to go.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It has to reach the skin to have an impact, and it could just as easily slip off to support other organs in the body. It's a valuable resource.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"There is little reliable evidence on this, but there is a theory that because our skin is the organ with the 'fastest turnover' of cells, it might be more likely to use these collagen peptides above other organs."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;And that's when you might get an increase in collagen being made in the skin cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;'You can't risk stopping'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;That all seems very complicated - and uncertain. It may leave you asking: what about using collagen creams? They're going directly onto the skin, so won't they stand more chance of getting where they need to be?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"No," is Ms Wedgworth's simple answer. "The collagen will just sit on the outer layer of your skin, it won't reach the dermis - which is the middle layer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;There are three different types of collagen supplements: marine (from fish), bovine (from cows), and vegan. Of the three, the dermatologist recommends marine if you are taking collagen orally. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;This is because it contains more type 1 collagen - the most common of the five types and the one that gives structure to our skin cells, as well as playing a crucial role in the health of our bones, tendons and connective tissues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Vegan collagen is the least effective, says Ms Wedgeworth. Collagen is an animal-derived protein, so these products are not actually made of collagen, and instead contain a range of amino acids and vitamins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Matthew Montgomery Ali Watson at the gym, smiling at the camera and rubbing chalk on her hands 
" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Matthew Montgomery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Ali Watson, a keen weightlifter, originally started to use collagen supplements to help protect her joints&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I'm trapped," Ali Watson tells me as she points to packs of bovine collagen powder in her kitchen. "Yes, this one is for me and well, this one is for Tommy."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;I look at the slender brown hound next me, grey whiskers poking out round his nose. He lifts an eyebrow in acknowledgement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ali, a neuroanaesthetist who, by her own admission, "knows a lot about dosing", feels like now she's started taking collagen, she can't stop - and nor can she stop giving it to her dog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I started taking it as a powder a couple of years ago. At first, it wasn't about my appearance, it was about my joints, I wanted to protect them because I do a lot of weight-lifting."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ali's not sure that she's noticed any difference with her joints, but she has noticed a change elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"My skin feels like it glows more, my hair feels thicker and my nails feel stronger."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;I glance down at Tommy, who seems more interested in his dog bowl than any powdered supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I know, it seems mad," Ali says, "but Tommy seemed a bit slower, a bit less enthusiastic just before summer, so I thought I would try him on dog collagen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I wanted to see if it could help with his joints - he's getting old now. And he is a bit brighter, but that might just be because the weather's got colder again and he's less hot and lethargic."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ali's not completely convinced the supplement is making a difference, and it's costing her £60 a month to ensure she and Tommy get their daily dose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Tommy started on collagen a few months ago to help his joints&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But she says she now can't stop dosing them both up. "That's the thing with these supplements," the 46-year-old says, "life does have its ups and downs. You might take them when you're on a down, then things pick up again - and it might have very little to do with the supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"But by that stage, you can't risk stopping."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Professor Faisal Ali, a consultant dermatologist at Mid Cheshire NHS Trust, says one of the issues consumers and clinicians face is the amount of conflicting information and conflicting interests in supplement research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A recent, relatively small, study compared &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0002934325002839" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;research funded by the wellness industry&lt;/a&gt; to studies that did not have the same conflict of interest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;While industry-funded studies suggested collagen supplements significantly improved skin hydration, elasticity and wrinkles, those that did not receive funding from pharmaceutical companies revealed no effect on skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Prof Ali says industry-funded studies are not "inherently bad", it's just such a varied picture. But he says there is a lack of robust evidence to suggest oral and topical collagen have any substantial effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;So if I could turn back time and start drinking and banking collagen in my 20s, would I have smoother, more youthful skin now, I ask him? Probably not, he says. It doesn't stay in the body for that long - we haven't got a collagen store cupboard that we can just dip into.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Micro derma facial roller" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Microneedling makes small wounds in the skin which may trigger collagen production&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;However, Prof Ali believes we can potentially boost collagen output and maintain elasticity in our skin by using special techniques&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11499218/#fn-group1" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt; such as laser collagen stimulation and microneedling&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;This means using a number of tiny, specialist needles or a laser to make small wounds to our skin, which then encourage a repair process, triggering new collagen formation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But that's not cheap. You could be paying up to £300 for one session. Is there a less costly alternative?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"The best thing you can do for your skin," Prof Ali says, "is using decent sunblock. We know the sun has a huge impact on ageing our skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Sun cream, healthy diet, and if you smoke, stop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"These will have a far greater impact than collagen supplements."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 22:37:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5YYXJORjRDaWc5bXpCYnhia0s5YjVJTUNEMGxtUklhSy11ZnpTcHpsbW40UDZPOHZmYzdFMnd0Qkc3Y2hkaTJGUldGcDJIaWNXS0pmbXY2UUQzZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE9VUnkwTWhPQ0lSNDNRQTYySnIzc2VtSVpjLXdwcXNpUGJBM3g3SU0xdWp3bDJ0dl9DSENNTWk5NDU5UjBtbnlVTnZHbzY4ZUZlWDA5NTlMMXdFSUhfNVNZ</guid></item></channel></rss>