<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>蛋白质去年就是这样。为什么光纤是下一件大事- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/25/food/fiber-food-trends-2026</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                &lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/source/instances/cmkmf2hnv008m27nxe4qy98hq@published" data-component-name="source" class="source-elevate vossi-source inline-placeholder" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    &lt;cite class="source__cite vossi-source__cite"&gt;
      &lt;span class="source__location vossi-source__location" data-editable="location"&gt;New York&lt;/span&gt;
         — 
    &lt;/cite&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkny5w0x00053b6ts0n8m0vs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Move over, protein. Fiber is on pace to be the next “it” nutrient of the year.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkppujvw00003b6tk38cw2wj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Consumers — particularly Gen Z — are fixated on stomach health, leading to the &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/26/health/fibermaxxing-tiktok-trend-fiber-benefits-wellness"&gt;“fibermaxxing” trend&lt;/a&gt; taking hold on TikTok. As people try to maximize the fiber in their meals, major food companies are capitalizing on the trend with new, fiber-focused products.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmfbrfq000d3b6tv252g2ww@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “There is a consumer need in terms of digestion and gut health, and that’s something we’ve seen the last few years,” said Sherry Frey, health and wellness thought leader at NIQ. The younger generation, she added, understands that digestive health is linked to better skin and improved cognitive function.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmqvfyi00083b6t542z6qcg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dataessential, a food and beverage research firm, found that 52% of consumers were&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;interested in trying “fibermaxxing” after learning about the trend and that 42% of shoppers think food labeled “high fiber” is healthier.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmfv6nm000t3b6tp41iwanb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Fiber builds on previous wellness-focused consumer trends, Frey told CNN. First was hydration, as seen with the rise of &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/05/24/food/hydration-electrolytes-drinks-popularity"&gt;products like Liquid I.V. and Electrolit&lt;/a&gt;. Then protein, a trend that shows no sign of &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/06/11/food/starbucks-protein-cold-foam"&gt;slowing down&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpqx3ef0000356p72g590ce@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The natural next step is for fiber,” she said, calling the converging of trends a “perfect storm.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmfgspw000h3b6t0751bojr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Also, fiber has been proven to trigger “a naturally occurring GLP-1 in our bodies,” she added, referencing the appetite-suppressing hormone in weight-loss drugs like Wegovy that are flooding the market.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpo7jhe0000356peeunolpi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Consumers’ desire for fiber is already evident on grocery store shelves. Whole Foods’ &lt;a href="https://www.wholefoodsmarket.com/trends/the-next-big-things-our-top-8-food-trend-predictions-for-2026" target="_blank"&gt;forecast&lt;/a&gt; for 2026 said there are “more fiber-forward callouts on packaging” as well as more products with added fiber.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmujwpe00033b6timifv0j3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Thrive Market, a membership-based online supermarket, has seen fiber-related terms surge 30% over the past year with shoppers gravitating toward snacks, bars and supplements, a spokesperson told CNN.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmfxh3b00153b6t0yr07vi8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Major food companies have taken notice: PepsiCo CEO Ramon Laguarta said on its most recent earnings call in October that “fiber will be the next protein.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmg1uyg001e3b6tq1keljaj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Consumers are starting to understand that fiber is the benefit that they need. It’s actually a deficiency in US consumers’ diets, and that will be elevated,” Laguarta told analysts. (More than 90% of woman and 97% of men don’t get their recommended daily intake of fiber, the US government &lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2020-12/Dietary_Guidelines_for_Americans_2020-2025.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; in 2020.)
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmg0jlc001c3b6tr41r5zi6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            PepsiCo is already bolstering its soda portfolio with fiber-forward products. Last summer, it launched a gut-friendly soda following its &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/03/17/business/pepsi-buys-poppi"&gt;purchase of Poppi&lt;/a&gt; with “Pepsi Prebiotic Cola,” which &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/21/food/pepsi-prebiotic-soda-launch"&gt;includes added fiber.&lt;/a&gt; More products are on the way, including fiber-enhanced versions of its SunChips, Smartfood popcorn and Propel hydration packets.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkny5r0f00033b6tcu7t9foq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            McDonald’s CEO Chris Kempczinski also &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DTbEkDuEkAC/?hl=en" target="_blank"&gt;recently predicted&lt;/a&gt; on his Instagram account that fiber “is going to be big” in 2026, perhaps signaling that the fast food chain could dip its toes into the trend.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmgesb0001x3b6tsr4rk4du@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Snacks, such as chips and puffed crackers, will be the battleground for fiber, Frey predicts, notably products made from legumes and beans. But taste is a factor, especially if it’s made from plant-based ingredients.&lt;strong&gt;﻿&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmgun1900233b6t2rvty5en@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Consumers are willing to make a trade, but they’re not always willing to make the trade if the taste isn’t there,” Frey said. “Despite the economy, they’re willing to pay a little more for these kinds of products.”
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmh02d100293b6tqyytqq3d@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            That’s where private labels created by major grocery stores come in. They are also getting into the wellness sector with fiber-enchanced products, but without the premium prices.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmhkd2z002u3b6tfrtggx4y@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Aldi’s &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/24/food/aldi-label-changes"&gt;recently relaunched&lt;/a&gt; in-house line includes knock-offs of “better for you” sodas and meal bars. Walmart is expanding its Bettergoods lineup, which encompasses several foods that have plant-based ingredients.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmh5k4a002i3b6txe3pjbdb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The recommended amount of fiber is 25 grams per day for adult woman to 35 for adult males, &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/12/health/protein-fiber-explainer-wellness"&gt;according to medical experts&lt;/a&gt;, so “it’s a generally good healthy trend,” said Paul Kriegler, a registered dietician and senior director of nutritional products for Life Time Fitness.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmhzzzv00323b6t4dwr2itm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            However, the prepackaged products hitting shelves are not a panacea for this deficiency. He would rather consumers gravitate toward the produce and vegetable section at the grocer for their fiber needs.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkptxgje00003b6tupirhph6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The US government’s &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/07/health/dietary-guidelines-rfk-maha"&gt;newly released dietary guidelines&lt;/a&gt; also urge people to prioritize “real food,” including “fiber-rich whole grains,” as well as curtail their intake of highly processed foods.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkmi2hc200363b6tfrf27tss@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “What I’ve taught clients for a long time is to eat a pile of vegetables the size of your head every day,” Kreigler told CNN. “The irony is most of the foods that will help ‘fibermaxxing’ don’t even have labels and you have to go get them fresh.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:00:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE81VlVzN3pPVGN0TGliNTdDNW9BVW1XSHRQdkQyb28zcTRvZWtvQ3h6V0RjZnU1OEdrRXRxd1lnTlRVSHdDN0RqLXh5V2dxYzMzQjh1UE5pcGQyNFYtLWo1S0RLc2xWNHl1Z0E</guid></item><item><title>以下是儿童疫苗的“共同决策”如何限制疫苗接种-美国国家公共广播电台</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2026/01/25/nx-s1-5686622/cdc-childhood-vaccines-shared-decision-rfk</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-107237" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                A child holds a toy bear with a band-aid after receiving a flu shot during an immunization event in Los Angeles. Flu is one of six vaccines that will no longer be given routinely but now require a consultation with a doctor.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    PATRICK T. FALLON/AFP/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        PATRICK T. FALLON/AFP/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;In a major change in vaccine policy, the Trump administration &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2026/01/05/nx-s1-5667199/cdc-vaccine-schedule-children" target="_blank"&gt;recently dropped &lt;/a&gt;recommendations that all kids get six immunizations long considered routine. Instead, they're now in a category called "shared clinical decision-making."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That's when the patient (or the parents if the patient's a child) has a conversation with a health care provider to decide if a treatment is appropriate, says &lt;a href="https://law.northeastern.edu/faculty/parmet/" target="_blank"&gt;Wendy Parmet&lt;/a&gt;, who studies health care policy at Northeastern University in Boston.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"In theory, shared clinical decision-making sounds great," she says. But the approach is usually reserved for complicated medical decisions where the answer is often muddy, not for routine vaccines that have been clearly shown to be safe and effective.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Some examples include: Should someone get surgery or physical therapy for back pain? Which men need regular PSA prostate cancer testing?&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;But many doctors say there's no ambiguity when it comes to these vaccines, which protect against &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis-a/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;hepatitis A&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis-b/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;hepatitis B&lt;/a&gt;, the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/meningococcal/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;meningitis&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/rsv/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;respiratory syncytial virus (RSV)&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/rotavirus/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;rotavirus&lt;/a&gt;, a dangerous gastrointestinal infection.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"These vaccines have clear evidence of benefit for all children," says &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/profiles/jake-scott" target="_blank"&gt;Jake Scott&lt;/a&gt;, an infectious disease researcher at Stanford University. "So moving them to shared decision-making doesn't reflect the scientific uncertainty that the category exists for. It manufactures this sort of uncertainty where no uncertainty really exists."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The problem with shared decision making in this context, is "you're suggesting that both options are equally valid," says Dr. &lt;a href="https://www.urmc.rochester.edu/people/112363409-lainie-friedman-ross" target="_blank"&gt;Lainie Friedman Ross&lt;/a&gt;, a pediatrician and bioethicist at the University of Rochester School of Medicine. "And the fact is: Not getting vaccinated puts your own child at risk, puts you at risk and puts your community at risk. So it is not an equal decision."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Vaccine &lt;a href="https://childrenshealthdefense.org/defender/hhs-sweeping-changes-childhood-vaccine-schedule-cdc/" target="_blank"&gt;critics argue&lt;/a&gt; there's enough nuance about these immunizations to warrant moving them to the shared clinical decision-making category. And administration officials &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/cdc-acts-presidential-memorandum-update-childhood-immunization-schedule.html" target="_blank"&gt;say the change is designed to restore trust&lt;/a&gt; in vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But Ross and others argue that dropping these vaccines to a lower spot in the &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/fact-sheet-cdc-childhood-immunization-recommendations.html" target="_blank"&gt;new CDC vaccine hierarchy&lt;/a&gt; sows dangerous confusion and doubt, especially at a time when vaccine hesitancy is already on the rise and vaccination rates are already falling.&lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;"It's a huge embarrassment for U.S. public health and a disaster for public trust, and most of all for children," says Dr. &lt;a href="https://www.seattlechildrens.org/directory/douglas-j-opel/" target="_blank"&gt;Douglas Opel&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of pediatrics at the Washington School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;They also point out that doctors already routinely answer any questions parents may have, in addition to providing detailed handouts about each vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;New hurdles to vaccine access&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;And there are many practical implications that could become hurdles to kids getting the shots, even if their parents do want them, Scott says. That includes deleting automatic electronic medical record alerts when shots are due and canceling standing orders for nurses and pharmacists to vaccinate kids without getting a doctor involved.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Moving it from routinely recommended to shared clinical decision-making has a dramatic effect on the practical delivery of vaccination," Scott says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;And while the administration says the decision shouldn't affect whether government programs or private insurance pay for the immunizations, some legal experts say that may not be guaranteed.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The administration says that there's not going to be insurance implications. But there are a number of problems there," says &lt;a href="https://www.uclawsf.edu/people/dorit-reiss/" target="_blank"&gt;Dorit Reiss&lt;/a&gt;, who studies vaccine policies at UC Law San Francisco. "First of all they can change their interpretation later. Second, if a private insurer wanted to challenge this and say, 'This vaccine is no longer recommended. I don't have to cover it,' they probably have some good arguments."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Even with insurance, parents may now get hit with co-pays for those extra conversations with swamped pediatricians, according to Dr. Molly O'Shea, a Detroit-area pediatrician who serves as a spokesperson for the American Academy of Pediatrics.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Before, if it was a vaccination that we didn't have to have a conversation about, we could feel safe allowing families to schedule a vaccine-only appointment," O'Shea says. "Because shared-decision making is required now, that takes time and that now is going to be billed for."&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;New liability concerns for drugmakers&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Another one big question is: Does this make vaccine makers and doctors vulnerable to getting sued? Many lawyers don't think so.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"On a legal standpoint, nothing has changed," says &lt;a href="https://www.greenlegalteam.com/david-carney/" target="_blank"&gt;David Carney&lt;/a&gt;, a Philadelphia lawyer who's the president of the &lt;a href="https://www.vipbar.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Vaccine Injured Petitioners Bar Association&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But some lawyers argue that the change does open the door to more litigation over vaccine injuries.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The immunity under the National Childhood Vaccine Injury Act of 1986 (the 1986 Act), which shields pharma and physicians from liability when vaccines cause serious harms and deaths, only applies to vaccines that are recommended for routine administration to children and/or pregnant women," &lt;a href="https://www.sirillp.com/aaron-siri/" target="_blank"&gt;Aaron Siri&lt;/a&gt;, managing partner at Siri &amp;amp; Glimstad, wrote in an email to NPR.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Siri is a close ally of Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. and has been extensively involved in litigation against federal agencies and vaccine manufacturers.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Some legal experts say that this uncertainty is alarming. Without liability protection, vaccines could become unavailable, says Parmet.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We don't quite really know whether shared clinical decision-making will be considered as sufficient enough of a recommendation to provide the liability protection," Parmet says. "And if it doesn't do that, then there are real concerns about whether the manufacturers will continue to make vaccines."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;A chilling effect on prescribers&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Even if the change doesn't lead to an increase in successful lawsuits involving vaccines, just the possibility of lawsuits could be enough to intimidate doctors, some say.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"They're worried about stepping on a landmine if one thing goes wrong," Parmet says. "One kid gets sick. The next day — even if it has nothing to do with the vaccine — are they going to be the ones held responsible? And someone's going to say, 'You had the nurse do it without talking to the doctor?'"&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That could make doctors hesitant to recommend these immunizations, which means imposing shared clinical decision-making could leave more kids more vulnerable to dangerous infections.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"I do think many physicians will be chilled in their behavior around recommending vaccination," says &lt;a href="https://law.stanford.edu/michelle-m-mello/" target="_blank"&gt;Michelle Mello&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of health policy and law at Stanford. "We've got this change now that plunges us into a situation of chaotic uncertainty."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxPcGpUektENGNwYmxTMzU5a2FYcGZzaTNCN3FxdjJCMVkyX3p0NGlkOTF0TlFKX3J3NmlCZ3p3MHFTaDhEdzBNRW5XcDFSQVZKamFYS05sWmZoLVVVVGcwZ0g4M1Y0TS1ra3FRalNBTzZWQW91QWJERjBxcElvbFRXVlJxUUNHU3VpY1JNRDVwX1M</guid></item><item><title>妈妈分享5岁女儿的视频，询问有关慢性病患者生活的令人心碎的问题（独家） -雅虎生活（英国）</title><link>https://uk.style.yahoo.com/mom-shares-video-5-old-100000758.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Maygen Steed recently captured a video of her daughter asking if she would have diabetes forever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Steed tells PEOPLE her "heart broke" in that moment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The video, which she shared on TikTok, amassed over 550,000 views&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In December 2022, when Maygen Steed's daughter, Paisley, was still a toddler, she noticed the little one seemed under the weather and assumed she had the flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Although Paisley was drinking plenty of fluids, she seemed dehydrated, was noticeably lethargic and "could barely lift her own head."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"I remember cradling her in my arms as my husband drove us the 30 minutes to the nearest emergency room. I didn't even have her buckled in because she couldn't lift her head," Steed, 30, tells PEOPLE. "I was afraid she'd stop breathing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"When we arrived at the emergency room, they immediately took us back. They called in a careflight for her, and she was sent to a children's [hospital] in Dallas," she continues. "When she got to Dallas, they said her blood sugar was over 600, and her A1C was 12.8%."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It was in that moment that Steed learned her daughter's actual diagnosis, quickly realizing that she didn't have the flu, but was in diabetic ketoacidosis (DKA) — a "life-threatening complication of diabetes and undiagnosed Type 1 diabetes," &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/21945-diabetic-ketoacidosis-dka" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:per the Cleveland Clinic.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;per the Cleveland Clinic. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diagnostics/9731-a1c" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:to the academic medical center;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;to the academic medical center&lt;/a&gt;, an A1C test measures "the average amount of (glucose) sugar in your blood." For people without diabetes, a normal A1C is below 5.7%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maygen Steed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Paisley Steed in the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"The doctors told us that if we waited any longer to bring her in, she wouldn't be alive," Steed shares. "I still have nightmares about her diagnosis day."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While the family has learned how to manage Paisley's type 1 diabetes, it hasn't been easy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Recently, Steed shared a video of her daughter in the car, asking from the backseat if she would have to deal with diabetes her whole life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"When I grow up to be a mom, will I still have to have a Dexcom and [Omni]pod?" the now-5-year-old asked in &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@maygen_k1995/video/7578374722887355662" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:the clip,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;the clip,&lt;/a&gt; which went viral, amassing over 550,000 views.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Steed wrote atop the video, "I walk into a haunted house but instead of clowns &amp;amp; monsters it's just my baby asking me if she'll still be diabetic when she grows up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Steed shares that "in that moment, my heart broke."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"No 5-year-old should be having to think about whether or not they will continue to struggle with a chronic illness when they are a mom," she says. "As I fumbled with the words to say, I just softly said yes because I can't lie to her."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"This will be something that she deals with for the rest of her life. As long as I am her mom, though, I will take as much of the burden off of her as I can," Steed adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Steed has been inspired to share information about Paisley's diagnosis on her TikTok account as a way to "advocate and share about type 1 diabetes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maygen Steed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Paisley Steed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"While the actual diagnosis of type 1 diabetes cannot be avoided (it's an autoimmune disorder/genetic), a traumatic diagnosis can be avoided by knowing the signs and symptoms of early DKA," she shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Along with type 1 diabetes, Steed notes that Paisley "also suffers from thyroid trouble."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"I struggle with caregiver fatigue and anxiety over parenting a high needs child," she adds. "Every alarm that goes off on her phone, my chest tightens with worst-case scenarios, but I am working on that and trying to be positive."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Her Graves' disease is in remission, but we are currently struggling with hypothyroidism and all of the side effects from that. Her little body goes through so much," she shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Despite this, Steed tries to remain positive about Paisley's type 1 diabetes diagnosis, which she's had for a "little over three years."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Each year on her 'diaversary', we have a little celebration that we hit another year of surviving with T1D. She knows all about her condition and enjoys explaining to people why she wears a CGM and pump," she shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maygen Steed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Paisley Steed playing golf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She notes that Paisley loves playing with makeup, babies and golfing, but struggles with large crowds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"She used to participate in gymnastics and soccer, but when her peers would touch her devices (pod/Dexcom), she had trouble speaking up and setting boundaries," Steed says. "She is so full of personality, and sometimes I forget that she's only 5, not 15. She is witty and such a joy to be around."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Although I cannot trade places with her, I can educate myself on the best way to care for her and advocate for her needs," Steed adds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/woman-shares-heartbreaking-moment-daughter-asks-about-diabetes-exclusive-11889221" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Life UK</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE5zRU00aHlRUkwwdHVIM0k2WmRmaFlLdEpsNGFxYTF5Y1JVYUdmaFdyZnZrc2VIVjZPY3U4MDQycDdsS2tXck5KZkJoclROa3Q0MWdoVUJZTjdUTEJ1bFJNQmdxeXJCN3B0akRPMkt1RTFFQQ</guid></item><item><title>William H. Foege ，根除天花的关键人物， 89岁去世-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/24/us/william-h-foege-dead.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 02:21:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE5BQjBBWm5QTGRHX0s1Wk9JMGF6NjZDdzN5ZUp1VDBZMl83YnNzcWVTVEI4Zk5OOXktV2VTanVMWmNFZS1LeTRtbDl0MHdOVTE2dFFPR1ctRFNXdnU5cUdVQ1M0M0RGNVdIZTlSVXlZZGg</guid></item><item><title>意想不到的地方，你可以得到黑色素瘤，而不是你的皮肤......它与阳光无关-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15456909/unexpected-spot-skin-cancer-melanoma-eyes.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The signs melanoma, a type of skin &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-74a6f2f0-f7a8-11f0-b093-c11752a910bb"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;, are clear. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Moles that are either new or changed in appearance are the &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14639039/dermatologist-warning-6-signs-deadly-melanoma-skin-cancer.html"&gt;hallmark of the disease&lt;/a&gt;, which strikes more than 200,000 Americans every year, along with rough patches and color changes in the skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cancerous lesions can pop up anywhere on the skin, but experts warn melanoma may strike an uncommon area for thousands of Americans: the eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Melanoma has been known to pop up on eyelids, thin layers of skin that are often exposed to harmful ultraviolet (UV) radiation, which makes them prone to developing lesions. Left unaddressed, these cancers may infiltrate the inner layers of the eye and the brain, making them far less treatable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the cancer can begin in a place even without skin, such as inside the eye, in a form of the disease called ocular melanoma. Of ocular melanomas, there are several subtypes, including uveal melanoma and conjunctival melanoma.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The skin and eyes share the same cells called melanocytes, which produce melanin, the pigment that gives skin, eyes and hair their color. Damage and mutations in these cells lead to melanoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And while melanoma is commonly caused by sun exposure, uveal and conjunctival melanoma are not primarily associated with harmful UV light. Instead, people with lighter eye colors or pre-existing eye conditions like near-sightedness may be at a greater risk.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As melanoma, and skin cancer in general, is on the rise nationwide, eye doctors have urged Americans to keep up with regular eye exams every one to two years to detect potentially cancerous changes, and to be on the lookout for seemingly subtle changes like blurred vision, spots and irritation in or around the eye. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Experts warn melanoma, a type of skin cancer, is not always just on the skin (stock image) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Allison Dashow, pictured above in 2025, was diagnosed with ocular melanoma four years ago at 26 years old&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Jacqueline Bowen, an eye doctor and president of the American Optometric Association, told the Daily Mail: 'Skin cancer involving the eye can appear in several different ways. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Some start in or around the eye itself, while others spread to the eye from elsewhere in the body.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 1 million US adults are currently living with melanoma, the deadliest form of skin cancer, and about 212,000 will be diagnosed this year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The mortality rate from the disease in the US is about two per 100,000 people, resulting in around 8,000 deaths per year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And melanoma rates have surged over the past 30 years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;According to the American Academy of Dermatology, the rate of melanoma diagnoses in the US doubled from 1982 to 2011, and there was a 31.5 percent increase between 2011 and 2019, the latest figures available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In women over 50, there has been a three percent increase in melanoma rates per year, while men under 50 have seen a one percent dip yearly. Rates among women under 50 and men over 50 have remained stable. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Signs of skin cancer range from innocuous to obvious, but experts warn that treating cases early is key to making sure they do not spread or further develop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured: Dashow, now 29, after her surgery with a covering over the eye affected by ocular melanoma, which she wore for seven days&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Two forms of melanoma that grow in the eye, subtypes of ocular melanoma, are uveal and conjunctival melanoma. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are usually no symptoms in early stages of ocular melanomas, but as the diseases progress, patients may experience blurry vision, floaters or flashes in their vision and changes in pupil shape. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The exact causes are unclear, but experts believe the disease is more likely in people with lighter eyes and skin colors. The role of UV light in ocular melanomas' development is unknown. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are about 2,000 new cases of ocular melanoma every year, according to the Melanoma Research Foundation (MRF). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Conjunctival melanoma, developing in the conjunctiva (clear tissue over the eye), is exceedingly rare with roughly 130 cases per year in the US and fewer than one in 1 million worldwide. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Symptoms include irritation, redness or a sensation of something being stuck in the eye. As it progresses, it may lead to vision loss, blurry vision or a change in pupil size. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Uveal melanoma starts in the eye's middle layer, called the uvea. It is the most common eye cancer. Like the other forms of eye melanoma, the causes are unclear, but it is not thought to be influenced by UV light. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above graph shows the increase in melanoma cases since 1975. Deaths, however, have decreased slightly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bowen said: 'It’s important to note that some of the most serious eye cancers, particularly uveal or ocular melanoma, often cause no pain or vision changes in the early and even mid stages. Uveal melanoma is life-threatening because the retina is an extension of the brain, providing a direct pathway for cancer to spread if it goes undetected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This is why annual comprehensive eye exams are essential, even when no symptoms are present. During every exam, doctors of optometry carefully examine the eye using specialized microscopes that can detect very small or early precancerous and cancerous lesions of the eye and surrounding structures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Many eye cancers are found during routine exams before symptoms ever develop, which greatly improves outcomes.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While there are no definitive cures for ocular melanoma, patients can be treated with a specialized laser therapy or plaque brachytherapy. These treatments kill the tumor and while doctors don't declare patients 'cured,' they are considered to be what is called NED, no evidence of disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bowen urged anyone who notices changes in their eyes or vision to visit an eye doctor as soon as possible, especially if symptoms last for several weeks or worsen. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Early detection matters at every age, including in children, where rare but life-threatening eye cancers such as retinoblastoma may only be detected through a comprehensive eye exam,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 02:16:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxPbFlRMWdldHdzQU52SHdUd0pwOUgzTjd0cmZSZ2VrZkN1VXVVTEtRUlV4TjJ6dEJoZjlHQmw3dEYtZUlDeTM3b1A1bk9EbG9NUmxjdVQ2ckxkeXloZkQxeFZvZW5zRFI4Ylp0dGFiVlFQZ0hwNlhtZGprM0RMdDhkRHV6WjdsZldpZmZ0TjF0WldXRkZFMUVfTmRROFdCQWfSAaQBQVVfeXFMUFFHX1B5OENVcG1ETll4ZVItTF84MGp3QkJTcnhEdlRlT2RWcWpXS25KOVNxUXlpWlBLZ3NINkw2WHBNS2lES0h4b21yQ1Rock9lSFlwMDlaMTBTU3hDQzhuS1RpSjdqRXhUVWkwZUd3Z0tVWno5OFBlSXRfcGs0djJSX2QxWXQ0a2xITExzMFVQMTFrWHZValpETjVTZ1NWUjRmNWY</guid></item><item><title>官员报告爆发无法治愈的致命尼帕病毒- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/officials-report-outbreak-deadly-nipah-014841550.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;BIJU BORO/AFP via Getty&lt;/p&gt; Bats (stock image)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Authorities in India have confirmed that two cases of Nipah virus have been reported&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two nurses at a private hospital near Kolkata, West Bengal, were infected with the potentially fatal virus, and one is in a coma&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The most likely source of infection is a patient who had been admitted to the same hospital previously," a senior health official said&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Authorities in India have confirmed that two cases of the deadly Nipah virus have been reported — and health officials are putting quarantine and surveillance measures in place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to reports from the &lt;a href="https://www.thehindu.com/news/national/west-bengal/centre-steps-in-as-two-nipah-cases-detected-in-bengal/article70502064.ece" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Hindu;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hindu&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/global-health/science-and-disease/health-experts-scramble-to-contain-nipah-outbreak-india/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The Telegraph;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/asia/india/nipah-virus-outbreak-symptoms-signs-india-b2906226.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The Independent;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Independent&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, two nurses at a private hospital near Kolkata, West Bengal, were infected with the virus, which is zoonotic — meaning it spreads between animals and people.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Two nurses at a private hospital are infected with Nipah virus, and one of them is in critical condition," health official Narayan Swaroop Nigam told &lt;em&gt;The&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Telegraph&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two were working together from Dec. 28 to Dec. 30. Over the course of the next few days, from Dec. 31 to Jan. 2, both nurses developed high fevers and respiratory distress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two were admitted to the intensive care unit at the same hospital where they work on Jan. 4 after their conditions worsened, the outlet reported. One of the nurses is now in a coma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials said that an initial investigation suggests that both nurses caught the virus from a patient with severe respiratory symptoms. The patient died before they could be tested for Nipah.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The most likely source of infection is a patient who had been admitted to the same hospital previously," a senior health official involved in West Bengal's Nipah surveillance efforts told &lt;em&gt;The&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Telegraph.&lt;/em&gt; "That individual is being treated as the suspected index case, and investigations are ongoing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials said that 180 people in the region had been tested for Nipah as of Jan. 20, and 20 people who had high-risk contact with the two nurses have been quarantined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nigam told &lt;em&gt;The&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Telegraph &lt;/em&gt;that every test came back negative thus far, and the people in quarantine will be tested again at the end of their 21-day isolation period.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Given the serious nature of Nipah virus infection, which is a zoonotic disease with high mortality and potential for rapid spread, the situation is being handled with utmost priority," a senior Health Ministry official told the &lt;em&gt;Hindu&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both local and nationwide agencies, including the country's National Centre for Disease Control, are now involved in the incident, and the investigation is still underway.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Hindu &lt;/em&gt;reported on Saturday, Jan. 24, that officials were testing bats at Kolkata's Alipore Zoo to rule out infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers from India's National Institute of Medical Research collected blood and swab samples from bats at the zoo over two days, a State Forest Department official told the outlet. RT-PCR tests, which test for genetic materials from viruses, are also being conducted on bats across various parts of West Bengal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt; PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The team collected swab samples from bats. They have followed all the protocols during the process," Alipore Zoo Director Tripti Sah said. Other officials told the outlet that preventative measures were put in place, and there is "no reason for immediate panic."&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/health-topics/nipah-virus-infection#tab=tab_1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:World Health Organization;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt; (WHO), Nipah virus causes a range of illnesses from asymptomatic infection to acute respiratory illness and fatal encephalitis, or inflammation of the brain. It also causes severe disease in animals such as pigs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first recognized outbreak was detected in Malaysia in 1999. In that outbreak, 100 people died in both Malaysia and Singapore, and one million pigs were killed to prevent further spreading of the disease, which had severe economic consequences for farmers, according to the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/25085-nipah-virus" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cleveland Clinic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;NIH-NIAID/Image Point FR/BSIP/Universal Images Group via Getty &lt;/p&gt; Nipah virus particles&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The WHO states that Nipah transmission is thought to occur when people are exposed to secretions from animals or contact with the tissue of a sick animal. Some outbreaks were traced back to fruits or fruit products, such as juice, that were contaminated with urine or saliva from infected fruit bats. The illness can also be spread from human to human.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The virus has no vaccine or cure, and doctors can only treat the symptoms — which initially include fever, headaches, muscle soreness, vomiting and sore throat, before transforming into dizziness, drowsiness, altered consciousness, and neurological issues linked to encephalitis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pneumonia and other respiratory problems can also occur, and the virus has an incubation period of four to 14 days. No cases have ever been reported in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people who contract the virus make a full recovery, according to the Cleveland Clinic, but some patients have reported neurological conditions that result from encephalitis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India's Ministry of Health has advised the public to take precautions amid the outbreak. In a social media post, the agency recommended that those in the region wear protective clothing whenever handling or cleaning animals and sheds, wash fruit before consuming it, protect sap and juice collection from bats, and avoid exposure to bats by not visiting areas such as abandoned buildings, caves or mines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/officials-report-outbreak-of-deadly-nipah-virus-which-has-no-cure-11892039" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:55:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQSmp4WUNraE5kbU9qLTE3akw3ZEE1WnhkYWY0ZkdCTmxTX3FmUml6cldQUFBvTm1ybzhMbFFMSEVvQ2lWMU1pZmVyV2dPbnBsMlBRMHQ2RV9YVE15VUphTGxJSUwxRFVWS3UxWGdtSlFNdUFVQ2UzZUVrUXU0c0tZS2lsc1JBQl94SHc</guid></item><item><title>根据健身专家- EatingWell的说法，在50岁后进行6次平衡锻炼，以提高力量和稳定性</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/balance-exercises-to-boost-strength-and-stability-11891603</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Practice balance exercises at least two to three times per week to improve stability and balance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Start slowly, focus on form and use support as needed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;As your balance improves, try increasing the difficulty or frequency of the exercise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; You may recall a time when standing on one foot, walking along a curb or jumping around felt effortless. But as we age, our body changes, and so does our balance. Balance loss is common with age due to natural declines in muscle strength, reaction time, proprioception and spatial awareness. "Balance starts declining for everyone at age 40 and more rapidly after 60 so we need to combat that age-related decline and train our balance to maximize our retention," says &lt;a href="https://ariesphysicaltherapy.com/about-us-best-physical-therapy-fort-lauderdale" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Bill Kelley, D.P.T., ATC, CSCS, Cert. DN&lt;/a&gt;. These changes can make everyday tasks, like climbing stairs, reaching for items on a shelf or walking on uneven surfaces, feel more challenging or even dangerous. Nearly one in three older adults fall each year, with a quarter of those falls resulting in a serious injury such as a hip fracture.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-cite="7" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Although balance often declines after age 50, it doesn't have to be a given. Research shows that regular balance exercises can significantly improve stability in older adults.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "Balance exercises should be a vital part of anyone's movement practice as we all age," says &lt;a href="https://hubphysicaltherapy.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Paul Fath, PT, D.P.T., OCS&lt;/a&gt;. "Regularly practicing and performing balance exercises will help to maintain better balance and slow the decline of balance-related events and injuries."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To help you get started, here are six expert-recommended, beginner-friendly balance exercises to safely build strength and stability.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-supported-single-leg-stand"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Supported Single-Leg Stand &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These single-leg stands are easy to do at home and can transform your balance. "Most balance exercises work by challenging your stability, which trains your body to better sense its position in space. Single-leg stands are especially effective because your base of support is reduced, forcing your brain and muscles to work together to recalibrate your center of gravity," says &lt;a href="https://welltech.com/experts/molly-ruecker" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Molly Ruecker PT, D.P.T., SCS, ATC, CSCS&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "This exercise strengthens stabilizing muscles in the feet, ankles, hips and core, essential for daily movement and balance," she adds.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Stand near a counter, table, wall or sturdy chair for support.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Place your hands on your hips or lightly on the support if needed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lift your left foot off the ground, raising your thigh toward parallel to the floor or as high as you can without losing balance. Keep your weight on the other leg and engage your core.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hold for 20 to 30 seconds, or as long as you comfortably can.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly lower your left foot and switch to the right leg.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeat 2 to 3 times per leg.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Advanced Exercise:&lt;/strong&gt; Hold the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-exercises-for-aging-11866471" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;single-leg stand without support&lt;/a&gt; or close your eyes for 20 to 30 seconds.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-heel-to-toe-walk"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Heel-to-Toe Walk &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Heel-to-toe walks are a game changer for balance. "I stress gait mechanics a lot. How your foot lands, how your toes are placed and how your muscles respond during movement all matter," &lt;a href="https://www.msfitnessstudio.com/about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Melanie Sinclair, CPT, PES, CES&lt;/a&gt; says. "Heel-to-toe walking helps improve how you move forward efficiently, whether you're walking, running, lunging or just moving through daily life."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Stand tall and extend your arms out to the sides for balance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Place one foot directly in front of the other so the heel of your front foot touches the toes of your back foot.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continue stepping forward in this way for 5 to 10 steps, aiming to walk in a straight line.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Turn around and walk back to your starting point.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Advanced Exercise:&lt;/strong&gt; Walk heel-to-toe slowly, pausing briefly on each step to challenge balance and control.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-sit-to-stand"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Sit-to-Stand &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Getting up and down from a chair is a daily activity most people perform many times a day. But as balance changes, this simple movement can become more difficult. "Sit-to-stand is a functional activity that is done throughout the day in self care and in positional changes," shares &lt;a href="https://activecarephysicaltherapy.com/staffs/dr-karena-wu/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Karena Wu, PT, D.P.T., OCS&lt;/a&gt;. "It demonstrates proper loading of weight into the legs to slowly lower or to stand up and good &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/7-day-body-weight-training-plan-for-beginners-11744140" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;hip strength&lt;/a&gt; to stand up fully erect."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Sit on a sturdy chair with your feet flat on the floor and hands resting on your lap.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lean slightly forward, engage your core and push through your heels to stand up fully.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly lower back down to a seated position.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeat 10 to 15 times, resting as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Tip: Move slowly and deliberately. Standing and lowering slowly helps your muscles engage and improves balance.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Advanced Exercise:&lt;/strong&gt; Perform slowly from a lower chair or while holding light weights, or progress to traditional squats without a chair.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-supported-hip-hinge"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Supported Hip-Hinge &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Supported hip-hinges test what your balance is like while in motion. "As you hinge at the hips, your center of gravity shifts backwards and forwards, forcing the muscles to constantly adjust to keep you stable," shares Ruecker.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Hip-hinges are also good for balance because they strengthen the core and posterior chain muscles, including the glutes, hamstrings and back, all of which are key muscles for controlling posture and movement. The light support is perfect for those who need an added feeling of safety, allowing them to practice proper form without the fear of failing," she adds.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Stand about one foot away from a wall, back facing it, with feet hip-width apart.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Place your hands on your hips or lightly on the wall for support.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hinge at your hips, gently pushing them back while keeping your back straight. Your glutes may lightly touch the wall to guide you.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lower until you feel a gentle stretch in your hamstrings.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly push your hips forward to return to standing.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeat 10 to 15 times.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Tip: Avoid bending your knees or leaning forward. Focus on hinging at the hips and gently pushing your glutes back.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Advanced Exercise:&lt;/strong&gt; Place your hands on your thighs and slowly slide them down toward your knees or shins. Alternatively, progress to traditional Romanian deadlifts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-standing-side-leg-raises"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Standing Side Leg Raises &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Standing side leg raises help with lateral balance. "Standing leg raises improve your balance by shifting your weight onto one leg while the other moves outward, forcing your body to control side-to-side stability," explains Ruecker.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_63-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_64-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "The main working muscles are those on the outside of the standing hip, especially the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-exercise-for-better-blood-pressure-8619767" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;gluteus medius&lt;/a&gt;, which keep your pelvis level and prevent you from tipping or collapsing inward. At the same time, your core and supporting ankle muscles will make small adjustments to keep your body stacked over the base of support. This trains your body to manage lateral balance and alignment," she adds.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_67-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_68-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Stand next to a wall, counter or sturdy chair and place a hand on it for support.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shift your weight onto the leg closest to the support.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly lift the other leg out to the side, keeping it straight.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lower the leg back down without fully touching the floor, unless needed for balance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeat 10 to 15 times per leg.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_69-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_70-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Advanced Exercise:&lt;/strong&gt; Perform side leg raises without support or use a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/stretches-to-do-every-day-to-help-undo-sitting-11849140" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;loop resistance band&lt;/a&gt; just above your knees.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_71-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-step-ups"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_72-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Step-Ups &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_73-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_74-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Getting up and down the stairs can become a difficult task as we age, but step-ups can help you feel confident going up and down flights. "Step-ups are an important unilateral strength and balance activity that mimics stair climbing and descent," says Wu. "It emphasizes the use of multiple joints and muscles in the leg to step up and down with control and good kinetic alignment."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_75-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_76-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; She adds, "This can help reduce falls if someone trips and lands on a single leg. This is also an important &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7949443/best-strength-training-exercises/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;leg strengthening&lt;/a&gt; and balance exercise that assists in other activities like getting out of a car smoothly and with less effort."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_77-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_78-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_79-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_80-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Use a sturdy step, stair or step box about half a foot (6 inches) high.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stand facing the step, holding a railing or placing a hand on a wall for support if needed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Place your left foot on the step and push through your heel to bring your right foot up to meet it.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Step down with your right foot, keeping your left foot on the step.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeat 10 to 15 times per leg.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_81-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_82-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Tip: When you push through your heel, you should feel your glutes doing most of the work.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_83-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_84-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Advanced Exercise:&lt;/strong&gt; Use a higher step box or hold a dumbbell in the hand opposite the stepping leg to increase challenge.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_85-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-to-practice-balance-safely"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_86-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How to Practice Balance Safely &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_87-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To reduce the risk of falls or injury, keep these safety tips in mind:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_88-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_89-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use Support When Needed.&lt;/strong&gt; Keep a wall, sturdy chair or counter nearby to hold onto until you feel stable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clear Your Space.&lt;/strong&gt; "To reduce the risk of tripping, ensure the area is tidy and free of clutter," says Ruecker.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wear Proper Shoes.&lt;/strong&gt; Supportive, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/podiatrist-approved-non-slip-shoes-11829338" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;non-slip footwear&lt;/a&gt; can prevent slips and improve stability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start Slow.&lt;/strong&gt; Perform exercises at a controlled pace, as rushing increases the risk of losing balance. "Starting simple, listening to your body and slowly increasing the difficulty are also great ways to stay safe while still making progress," shares Ruecker.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engage Your Core.&lt;/strong&gt; A strong, engaged core helps support better balance and control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Progress Gradually.&lt;/strong&gt; Increase the difficulty only when you can perform the exercise confidently and safely.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus Your Gaze.&lt;/strong&gt; Looking at a fixed point ahead, such as a picture on the wall, can help improve stability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seek Professional Help.&lt;/strong&gt; A physical therapist or certified &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/the-best-exercise-combo-to-lose-visceral-fat-11880936" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;personal trainer&lt;/a&gt; can provide personalized recommendations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_90-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-often-should-you-do-balance-exercises"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_91-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Often Should You Do Balance Exercises? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_92-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Research supports this recommendation, showing that older adults who practice balance training three times per week experience improved stability and a lower risk of falls.&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "The best frequency for performing balance exercises is the frequency that you can perform consistently," says Fath. "When included in your regular exercise program, I would suggest at least 2 to 3 days per week."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_93-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_95-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_96-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_97-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Maintaining and improving balance is important at any age, but it becomes especially important after 50. Adding balance exercises to your routine can help strengthen muscles, prevent falls and make everyday movements feel easier. Focus on slow, controlled movements and proper form, and progress to more challenging variations only when you can perform each exercise confidently. For best results, aim to practice balance exercises a few times per week.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOSWxsdlFHc3Y1cTdBTEM4NVNvejZJZmp0NmF4TlJTVEU0NTVWdmZOMExzQWxuZVNMTVM2eXpHaVdsdVBySnZ0b3FIdUhwTzYyenVVczJzbmR0LWpRZVRlT1l0ajVkTGxNSnpUMGttR09EMEgzdnFsRkxjNEhYblhOT1RSdnpMNEpjWlhpRnNB</guid></item><item><title>小RFK声称他在20天内减掉了20磅，在极端饮食中获得了精神上的清晰度- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/rfk-jr-claims-lost-20-191230378.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. revealed the details of his extreme, highly restrictive diet centered on meat and &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/digestive-health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:fermented foods.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;fermented foods.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I’m on a carnivore diet," Kennedy said during a recent interview on USA TODAY's "The Excerpt" podcast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy said he follows the diet the "whole day," every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink/doctors-divided-diet-trend-has-babies-licking-butter-gumming-ribeye-steak" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Doctors Divided Over New Diet Trend That Has Babies Licking Butter And Gumming Ribeye Steak;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doctors Divided Over New Diet Trend That Has Babies Licking Butter And Gumming Ribeye Steak&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That may not be right for other people, but I lost 40% of my visceral fat within a month," he said &lt;a href="https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2026/01/22/usa-today-sits-down-with-hhs-secretary-rfk-jr-for-an-exclusive-the-excerpt/88287278007/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:on the podcast,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;on the podcast,&lt;/a&gt; referring to the fat that surrounds internal organs and is linked to higher risks of cardiovascular disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Robert F. Kennedy Jr. says he eats a diet centered around meat and fermented foods.&lt;span class="caption-credit"&gt; (Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also claimed improved mental clarity and said he lost 20 pounds in 20 days after switching to the diet. He acknowledged some of the benefits could be due to the placebo effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS/mvaj7wvj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read On The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Read On The Fox News App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The carnivore diet is a meal plan that includes consuming only animal products such as meat, dairy and eggs, Fox News Digital has &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/8-carnivore-diet-myths-debunked-researcher" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:previously reported.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;previously reported.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink/ancient-fermented-dish-linked-immune-changes-amid-devastating-flu-season" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ancient Fermented Dish Linked To Immune Changes Amid Devastating Flu Season;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ancient Fermented Dish Linked To Immune Changes Amid Devastating Flu Season&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The health secretary, who turned 72 this month and celebrated with a hefty steak, pairs the diet with &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:foods that are fermented,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;foods that are fermented,&lt;/a&gt; typically meaning they are soaked, salted or cultured to let natural bacteria or yeast break down sugars over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cabbage, for example, becomes sauerkraut when it’s salted and left to ferment; milk turns into yogurt or kefir when live cultures are added; and soybeans become miso through a long fermentation process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts say fermented foods can support gut health, boost immune function and reduce inflammation by increasing beneficial bacteria in the gut. Some also note the fermentation process may produce compounds linked to better mood, energy and sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink/healthiest-red-meats-eat-how-cardiologist-says-prepare-them" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Healthiest Red Meats To Eat — And How A Cardiologist Says To Prepare Them;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Healthiest Red Meats To Eat — And How A Cardiologist Says To Prepare Them&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy is known to eat steak with fermented vegetables for breakfast and even bring his own sauerkraut to restaurants — a habit his wife, actress Cheryl Hines, joked about with &lt;a href="https://www.thecut.com/article/cheryl-hines-isnt-loving-rfk-jr-s-carnivore-diet.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The Cut.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;The Cut.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I’ll have my little clutch, one of my good bags that I only take out every once in a while because I want to keep them nice, and he’ll hand me a bag of sauerkraut and say, 'Can you put this in your bag?'" Hines told the outlet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;The health secretary is known for bringing his own sauerkraut to restaurants, according to his wife, Cheryl Hines.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"People will say, 'Ew, what’s that smell?'" she added, saying she responds, "'Don’t worry about it, it’s my husband’s dinner.'"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Sign Up For Our Lifestyle Newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here To Sign Up For Our Lifestyle Newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy’s comments come amid the Trump administration's updated federal dietary guidelines, which place more emphasis on protein and whole foods while easing decades-old restrictions on saturated fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy’s &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/nutrition-and-fitness/diet-trends" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:personal eating habits;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;personal eating habits&lt;/a&gt; are more extreme than the updated guidelines he helped unveil and experts have warned that the carnivore diet, in particular, is highly restrictive and needs more research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;The carnivore diet consists of eating only animal-based foods, including meat, dairy and eggs.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We don’t have gold-standard, evidence-based medical research to support the carnivore diet’s long-term health claims," Dr. Mia Kazanjian, a board-certified radiologist in Connecticut, told Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here For More Lifestyle Stories;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here For More Lifestyle Stories&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Eliminating &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/food-drink/food/healthy-foods" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:fruits, vegetables and whole grains;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;fruits, vegetables and whole grains&lt;/a&gt; is dangerous because it deprives people of essential vitamins, minerals, fiber, phytochemicals and antioxidants," Kazanjian added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fermented foods like sauerkraut and kimchi have less fiber than plants, so they are not a replacement for plant nutrients, she noted, and a diet centered on animal foods can also increase LDL cholesterol, raising the risk of heart disease and stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Kennedy says fermented foods are a daily staple alongside meat-only meals for him.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other potential risks associated with the carnivore diet include kidney stones, gout and bone loss, according to experts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/lifestyle/quizzes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Test Yourself With Our Latest Lifestyle Quiz;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Test Yourself With Our Latest Lifestyle Quiz&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kazanjian recommends speaking to a doctor before starting any new diet. "As a physician focused on cancer prevention, I recommend a Mediterranean diet, largely plant-based, with whole grains, fruits, vegetables and lean proteins, for optimal health and longevity," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Later in the interview, in response to a question about peptides and supplements, Kennedy reiterated, "I don't want to make myself a role model for what people should do and shouldn't do."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS?pid=AppArticleLink&amp;amp;af_dp=foxnewsaf%3A%2F%2F&amp;amp;af_web_dp=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.foxnews.com%2Fapps-products" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Download The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here To Download The Fox News App&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also said "gold standard science," not his personal opinions, influences the &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/maha" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:administration's public policy.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;administration's public policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Kennedy did pullups after a conference at Ronald Reagan Washington National Airport in Arlington, Va., in December 2025.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fox News Digital has reached out to the HHS Department for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Additional reporting by Fox News Digital's Melissa Rudy and Andrea Margolis.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Original article source:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink/robert-f-kennedy-jr-only-eats-meat-fermented-foods-heres-what-experts-say" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:RFK Jr. claims he lost 20 pounds in 20 days, gained mental clarity on extreme diet;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;RFK Jr. claims he lost 20 pounds in 20 days, gained mental clarity on extreme diet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 21:16:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE9icnlyWGlMQjhZS2lDYVNvU1UxemJXb2VvOG1ES2puREJSakhibjVDMGJQZkRFekNCUUhjQUE1Sy1iOVhubEpHczdXUlRDOUtxblM1bk05ZUwyOHloX3pFc1Q4Q0JHRWdpZ2ZDWV84dmp2SUU</guid></item><item><title>猛禽可以缩小30%的大脑。以下是他们如何恢复增长。- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/shrews-can-shrink-their-brains-by-30-heres-how-they-grow-it-back</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;In preparation for winter, the common shrew (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Common_shrew"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sorex araneus&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-animal-can-shrink-its-brain-and-we-finally-know-how"&gt;shrinks its brain&lt;/a&gt; by 30 percent to conserve precious energy. Then, come spring, the shrew miraculously 'regrows' its shrivelled brain, neurons fully intact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists have now traced the evolutionary origins of this rare adaptation and the genes that likely enable it. While fascinating in its own right, this information may also spark new approaches to understanding and treating &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/just-one-gene-may-be-responsible-for-over-90-of-alzheimers-cases"&gt;human brain degeneration&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-stem-cell-secrets-of-this-tiny-worm-could-help-unlock-human-regeneration"&gt;The Stem Cell Secrets of This Tiny Worm Could Help Unlock Human Regeneration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The unusual adaptation is known as &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cub.2021.04.006"&gt;Dehnel's phenomenon&lt;/a&gt;, named for Polish zoologist &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/August_Dehnel"&gt;August Dehnel&lt;/a&gt;, who first described the shrew's remarkable brain-shrinking ability, a method of coping with the seasonal energy shortage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dehnel's phenomenon is rare, but shrews aren't the only practitioners: European moles (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/European_mole"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Talpa europaea&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;), common weasels (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Least_weasel"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mustela nivalis&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;), and stoats (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stoat"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mustela erminea&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) also reduce their brain size with the seasons. These mammals all have fast metabolisms, and they don't hibernate, which may explain why they take such drastic measures to reduce their energy needs when food is short.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ecologist William Thomas, from Stony Brook University in the US, led a study to map the common shrew's entire genome, comparing it to those of other mammals who also exhibit Dehnel's phenomenon to see what genetic tricks they have evolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study builds on the team's &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-animal-can-shrink-its-brain-and-we-finally-know-how"&gt;previous work&lt;/a&gt;, which looked at seasonal changes in gene expression in two parts of the shrew's brain, and determined which sections of DNA were more active – and therefore possibly involved – during these massive bodily shifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_189566" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-189566" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/original-1-642x428.jpeg" alt="a tiny brown shrew is peeking out of a biologist's 'trap' box, held up to the camera with a blue gloved hand about four times the size of the shrew." class="size-medium wp-image-189566" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/original-1-642x428.jpeg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/original-1-1012x675.jpeg 1012w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/original-1-768x512.jpeg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/original-1-1536x1024.jpeg 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/original-1-2048x1366.jpeg 2048w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/original-1-600x400.jpeg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-189566" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;In 2025, researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cub.2025.08.015"&gt;discovered&lt;/a&gt; that the shrew's seasonal brain shrinkage is caused by water loss, and yet brain cells survive. (&lt;a href="https://www.ab.mpg.de/764426/shrews"&gt;© Christian Ziegler / Max Planck Institute of Animal Behavior&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Putting that data together, the researchers found genes associated with the creation of brain cells were upregulated across multiple species that exhibit Dehnel's phenomenon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shrew specifically had amped up expression of &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vascular_endothelial_growth_factor_A"&gt;&lt;em&gt;VEGFA&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a gene associated with blood-brain barrier permeability (which may improve nutrient sensing in the brain). Its genome was also enriched with genes associated with DNA repair and longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Water-regulation genes were also active, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cub.2025.08.015"&gt;supporting theories&lt;/a&gt; that shrews achieve reversible loss of brain volume &lt;a href="https://www.mpg.de/25258209/0827-ornr-rare-seasonal-brain-shrinkage-in-shrews-is-driven-by-water-loss-not-cell-death-987453-x"&gt;by losing water&lt;/a&gt;, not net brain cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/castingcall?utm_source=SA_website&amp;amp;utm_medium=article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=casting_call"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg" alt="Audition now for ScienceAlert's Casting Call" class="alignnone wp-image-189354 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-1200x509.jpg 1200w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1.jpg 1266w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="p1"&gt;The findings point to "a finely tuned system that enables common shrews to reversibly regulate brain shrinkage while avoiding the detrimental effects typically associated with neurodegeneration," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/molbev/msag006"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cell biologist Aurora Ruiz-Herrera from the Autonomous University of Barcelona &lt;a href="https://www.uab.cat/web/newsroom/news-detail/-1345830290613.html?detid=1345974943963"&gt;adds&lt;/a&gt;: "The role of genes related to energy homeostasis and the blood-brain barrier points to possible biomarkers and therapeutic targets for &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-may-start-at-the-brains-borders-scientists-discover"&gt;neurodegenerative diseases&lt;/a&gt;, always with the necessary caution when extrapolating to humans."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/molbev/msag006"&gt;Molecular Biology and Evolution&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 21:01:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxQZ3lDQUVqYkFSdnFqVlhEY1FQUmVjbGtfRTVzOV9iWGRNUGZjTk51VmRkcnVKWERaRUkwd3FoY2lmUVp6dGJFYk1DMG9NckdfOWpfcnljaHdDMWpqM0l2eHZkcFFIUUVPX1RWeDkyZGlyUXEwb3ZHdHozNU9qTS10Q0hjVnFvRUxRTlhuYUhzWU1IQnpwWEVZWA</guid></item><item><title>根据大脑研究员Yoram Yovell的说法，父母的幸福悖论- ynetnews.com</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/culture/lifestyle/article/hy26qqz8bg</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-contents="true"&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="1ks5o-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1ks5o-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1ks5o-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;A happy relationship is an elusive concept. We tend to think marital happiness depends on personality, luck or years of careful maintenance. But when the data is examined, a less romantic and far more intriguing picture emerges. Paradoxically, the years in which we expect to feel most fulfilled, the years of starting a family and raising children, are precisely the years when relationship satisfaction declines. Only much later, when it seems the hardest part is behind us, does it begin to rise again. Why does this happen?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="eo1hm-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="eo1hm-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="eo1hm-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The question of whether children truly bring happiness to a relationship is not new. Yet research accumulated over many years paints a consistent, and not always intuitive, picture. Large-scale studies conducted over recent decades point to a recurring pattern that appears again and again, almost regardless of a couple’s personality or social background.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="ciuo0-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide firstImageInArticle firstImageInArticleBody"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.ByeH0oqzLZe" id="image_ArticleImageData.ByeH0oqzLZe"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;6&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.ByeH0oqzLZe" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/19/S100fZjjHbl/S100fZjjHbl_4_71_851_1024_0_x-large.jpg" alt="פרופ' יורם יובל" title="'Contrary to the common perception, happiness actually increases at older ages', Prof Yoram Yovell  (Photo: Eric Sultan) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.ByeH0oqzLZe" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/19/S100fZjjHbl/S100fZjjHbl_4_71_851_1024_0_x-large.jpg" alt="פרופ' יורם יובל" title="'Contrary to the common perception, happiness actually increases at older ages', Prof Yoram Yovell  (Photo: Eric Sultan) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;'Contrary to the common perception, happiness actually increases at older ages', Prof Yoram Yovell &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Eric Sultan&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="7fakc-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7fakc-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7fakc-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;‘I think the interesting question is why this happens. It is not one study, but many studies, and together they increase our confidence that we are dealing with something real,’ says Prof. Yoram Yovell, a psychiatrist and brain researcher. ‘Many studies conducted in the Western world, in countries like Israel, industrial, capitalist, modern societies, show that couples’ happiness over the course of their relationship rises and falls according to a fairly clear pattern. ‘From the birth of the first child until the children leave home, both partners’ levels of happiness and satisfaction are lower. The lowest point is roughly when the first child reaches adolescence. These are the data. Of course, this is an average. There are couples who manage to avoid this, but they are not many.’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="8sia9-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="8sia9-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="8sia9-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;‘Before children are born and after they leave home, happiness is higher. In the years before having children and in what are commonly called the “empty nest” years, when children have left home, couples’ relationship satisfaction and personal happiness are higher, exactly the opposite of what we tend to assume. ‘Contrary to the common image, happiness actually increases at older ages. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="2a1q8-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.S1xbMCcM8bg" id="image_ArticleImageData.S1xbMCcM8bg"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;6&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.S1xbMCcM8bg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/19/SJGJReiiH11e/SJGJReiiH11e_1_0_1000_563_0_x-large.jpg" alt="גיל ההתבגרות" title="'The lowest point comes during adolescence, it is interesting to ask why'  (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.S1xbMCcM8bg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/19/SJGJReiiH11e/SJGJReiiH11e_1_0_1000_563_0_x-large.jpg" alt="גיל ההתבגרות" title="'The lowest point comes during adolescence, it is interesting to ask why'  (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;'The lowest point comes during adolescence, it is interesting to ask why' &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="ra0j-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="ra0j-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="ra0j-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;As people grow older in the Western world, they become happier on average. There are exceptions, of course, but when you look at the averages, the best is still ahead of us. Most of us will be happier later in life, and that is good news. The problem is that most of us are now deep inside what I call the “valley of death”, meaning most of us have children, and we are asking ourselves, “What happened to us?”’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="68ogp-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="68ogp-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="68ogp-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;If this pattern repeats itself among so many couples, the obvious question is not only what happened, but how it happened. Prof. Yovell shifts the discussion away from individual psychology toward the broader social structure, suggesting that the decline in parental and marital happiness is not a personal failure but the result of a deep historical shift in how we live, raise children and build families.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="1otgt-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1otgt-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1otgt-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;‘I think it happened without any bad intentions, but we are in the middle of a very large social experiment,’ he says. ‘Until the Industrial Revolution, almost all human beings lived in extended families, which is probably how our species evolved. When you look at the animals closest to us, the apes we evolved from, and when you look at early human societies, everyone lived in three-generation extended families, with grandparents, parents and children living together. To this day, that is how people live in traditional societies. That was the default for all humans everywhere.’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="8jnkk-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="8jnkk-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="8jnkk-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The Industrial Revolution, he explains, changed the rules of the game. ‘Several things happened. Mobility increased. Until then, people lived more or less where they were born. They were born in a village and lived there their entire lives, and even if they left, they usually returned. From this emerged a new way of life that we now take for granted, but simply did not exist 200 years ago: the nuclear family, a two-generation family of parents and children.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="3n1d5-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.H1ei1ysfIWl" id="image_ArticleImageData.H1ei1ysfIWl"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;6&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.H1ei1ysfIWl" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/19/S1WCgsir11x/S1WCgsir11x_0_0_1000_668_0_x-large.jpg" alt="זוג לא מאושר" title="'Most of the time we feel guilty, and rightly so'  (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.H1ei1ysfIWl" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/19/S1WCgsir11x/S1WCgsir11x_0_0_1000_668_0_x-large.jpg" alt="זוג לא מאושר" title="'Most of the time we feel guilty, and rightly so'  (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;'Most of the time we feel guilty, and rightly so' &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="9j3ln-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9j3ln-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9j3ln-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;‘Why does this matter? Because in nuclear families, raising children becomes a zero-sum game. In traditional societies, there is always someone who can step in when the father is at work and the mother is at the end of her rope: an aunt, a grandfather, a neighbor, someone who is not one of the two parents, who is available and can help with the children. Today, we no longer have that.’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="bdv0q-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="bdv0q-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="bdv0q-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The shift from extended families to nuclear families was not the only change brought by industrialization. At the same time, the way children grow up, and the amount of time they spend with their parents, also changed. ‘Before the Industrial Revolution, children spent most of their time with their parents. Boys went out to the fields or hunted with their fathers and learned their trade from them. Girls stayed with their mothers, helped with household tasks and learned how to be mothers themselves. They were with us, we raised them, and they learned how to function from us,’ Prof. Yovell explains. ‘Once we started sending them to schools and we were no longer with them, we began to feel guilty, and rightly so. All parenting guides and psychologists tell us how important it is to be with our children, which is true. Then every free moment outside of work comes with enormous pressure to be with them all the time. ‘This is especially true in Israel. We are a society that sanctifies children more than other Western societies. We constantly feel guilty that we have not done enough and that we need to do more for them.’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="64s0l-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="64s0l-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="64s0l-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;In other words, the daily reality of modern parenting places an extreme psychological burden on parents. ‘If you look at your children and mine, who are they with? Either with their father, their mother, or with someone we pay: teachers, instructors, educators, kindergarten teachers, caregivers. Someone on the payroll. This creates a very heavy mental burden for parents. ‘I will say something extreme. The role of parenting, which has always been difficult throughout history, has become almost impossible in recent years. Those who pay the highest price are mothers, women, because they have taken on an entire new set of responsibilities and challenges, without any meaningful reduction in the load placed on them by raising children. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="text_editor_block_quote" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="7fh86-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7fh86-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7fh86-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;'Because the country is small and because we still retain traces of a traditional society, grandparents here are more involved in raising children and grandchildren than in other Western countries, particularly the United States. This is likely one of the key reasons Israel’s happiness levels are genuinely among the highest in the world'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="2pej6-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2pej6-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2pej6-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;‘Many fathers have their work, and work becomes the ultimate mistress. A person works long hours and is not at home, and he says, with some justification, what do you want from me? I am providing. Someone has to keep this whole thing going. If the mother is the primary breadwinner, and the father still goes to his job and does not stay home, and there are no active grandparents and no paid caregiver whose job it is, then the mother is left with an impossible burden.’ This burden is not merely theoretical. It is a daily reality Prof. Yovell has encountered in his clinical work. ‘I no longer do this, but for many years I worked as a therapist in New York. I had a patient who was a senior executive at one of the major Wall Street firms. One day she came into my office, sat down, looked at me and said, “Dr. Yovell, I need a wife.” That is where many women find themselves today.’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="5fj2c-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.HyxBFljGIZe" id="image_ArticleImageData.HyxBFljGIZe"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;6&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.HyxBFljGIZe" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/19/SJmyClsoBbe/SJmyClsoBbe_0_67_1000_563_0_x-large.jpg" alt="הורות" title="Mothers are coping with an impossible burden  (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.HyxBFljGIZe" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/19/SJmyClsoBbe/SJmyClsoBbe_0_67_1000_563_0_x-large.jpg" alt="הורות" title="Mothers are coping with an impossible burden  (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Mothers are coping with an impossible burden &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="7pm75-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7pm75-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7pm75-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Still, this picture is not identical everywhere. Much of the research informing our understanding of parental and marital happiness comes from countries where family structures are even more fragmented and distant than in Israel. ‘Most of the studies we have come from Western countries, especially the United States. These are very large countries, where people often see their grandparents only during the holiday season, between Thanksgiving and the New Year,’ Prof. Yovell says. ‘The situation in Israel is better, because the country is small and because we still retain traces of a traditional society. Compared to other Western countries, grandparents here are more involved in raising children and grandchildren than in the United States, where grandparents may live in Florida while the family lives in Los Angeles and see each other once a year. ‘That is probably one of the important reasons why happiness levels in Israel are genuinely among the highest in the world. But we are still a Western country, with all the caveats, and it is still very hard to be a parent here.’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="f6rj8-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="f6rj8-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="f6rj8-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Another feature that slightly distinguishes Israel from other Western societies, he says, is the attraction to community-based living. ‘Until October 7, communities near the Gaza border had far more people wanting to live there than they could actually absorb. Parents are looking for a community where children can function in the afternoons without parents having to provide transportation and entertainment, or without children being stuck in front of smartphones, which we know is not good for them.’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="3jgm6-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="3jgm6-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="3jgm6-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The shift in family structure and parenting has not only weighed heavily on daily life but has also had a direct impact on the intimate core of the couple’s relationship. “What are the variables that predict how satisfied both partners are with the quality of their romantic lives?” Prof. Yovell asked, before offering the answer. “The striking finding is that it is most strongly correlated with the number of hours the father spends with the children. That is fascinating, it explains a great deal, and it also offers hope, because it tells you exactly what you need to do to make things better,” he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="9ggl3-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9ggl3-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9ggl3-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;This link between couplehood, parenthood and children’s well-being also lies at the heart of the extensive research conducted by Prof. John Gottman, one of the world’s leading scholars on relationships and family life. Over decades of research, Gottman sought to examine not only what people say about their relationships, but what actually happens inside them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="4uepd-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.SkgsKzozLZx" id="image_ArticleImageData.SkgsKzozLZx"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;6&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.SkgsKzozLZx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/19/Skb1RejiHZg/Skb1RejiHZg_0_0_1000_563_0_x-large.jpg" alt="זוג לא מאושר" title="We have to find a way, somehow, to preserve romantic love between partners  (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.SkgsKzozLZx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/19/Skb1RejiHZg/Skb1RejiHZg_0_0_1000_563_0_x-large.jpg" alt="זוג לא מאושר" title="We have to find a way, somehow, to preserve romantic love between partners  (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;We have to find a way, somehow, to preserve romantic love between partners &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="4dsba-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4dsba-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4dsba-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“Prof. Gottman’s research found that romantic love between parents is the child’s true cradle,” Prof. Yovell said. “Couples who did not abandon their relationship in favor of total focus on the children were not only happier themselves, their children were happier as well.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="4j0t4-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4j0t4-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4j0t4-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;One reason Gottman’s work is considered particularly reliable, Yovell explained, is his unusual methodology. “He did not settle for what people told him. Instead of relying solely on self-reporting, as most psychological research does through questionnaires, he also measured actual behavior over time. “As part of his research, he invited couples, and later entire families, to what was known as the ‘Love Lab,’ a fully equipped apartment owned by the University of Washington in Seattle, located in a pleasant neighborhood overlooking the harbor. They stayed there for a weekend at the university’s expense. It was very much like ‘Big Brother.’ They gave full consent to be filmed and recorded everywhere except the bathroom and bedroom throughout the weekend.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="text_editor_block_quote" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="6ssbb-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6ssbb-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6ssbb-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;'All couples who divorce began with immense love for one another and a genuine desire to give everything to each other. The question is how you move from point A to point B, from the person you chose above all others and were truly willing to do anything for, to a place where you cannot stand them and feel you must separate, despite the enormous social costs'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="41mum-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="41mum-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="41mum-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;This process was repeated over many years. “He took a young couple in the first year after marriage, then followed up five years later after their first child was born, and then another five years later with two or three children, and compared the results. Much of what we know today comes from these findings, especially the insight that the amount of time parents spend with each other has a major impact.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="aig8r-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="aig8r-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="aig8r-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The conclusion, Yovell stressed, is not romantic but practical. “Couples must actively protect their love. What happens naturally and effortlessly at the beginning later requires care and intention, because it no longer happens on its own. Life’s wear and tear is simply too great. “Parents who hover over their children 24/7 under the belief that this is what is best for them are mistaken. The love between the two of you is what gives your children their deepest sense of security.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="9r827-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9r827-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9r827-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;From there, he said, the path to relationship breakdown can be short. “There are situations in which separation is truly the right choice, cases where the conflicts are simply too severe. But it is important to remember that every couple who divorces began with enormous love for one another and a genuine desire to give everything to each other. “The question is how we move from point A to point B, from the person we chose above all others and were willing to do anything for, to a situation where we cannot stand them and feel we must separate, despite the enormous social costs.” Here, too, Gottman’s research offered an answer. “He found that what we usually think of as the causes of divorce, such as an affair that comes to light or a shocking financial secret, are actually just triggers. What happened beforehand was a gradual erosion of romantic love over many years. “Then something occurs that, had it happened at the beginning of the relationship, the couple could have survived.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="bh251-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="bh251-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="bh251-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Gottman compares romantic love to a bank account. “We begin with a large positive balance. But the challenges of raising children lead to repeated withdrawals, and if we do not make regular deposits, small and frequent investments, we can end up overdrawn. “One of Gottman’s strongest recommendations is to strengthen the couple relationship, for example by going on a weekly date, once a week. It sounds very small, but it is critically important. At the beginning we did this often. Later we are simply too tired, busy with the children, and we say, ‘Let’s just watch something on Netflix.’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="8l0pc-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="8l0pc-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="8l0pc-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“But if we stay at home, we remain wrapped in all the habits of the household. We do not return to the romantic, couple-centered space we once had, the place that felt good and that is what keeps the flame of love from going out.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="1sliq-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.HJlwFEizUWx" id="image_ArticleImageData.HJlwFEizUWx"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;6&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.HJlwFEizUWx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/19/rJ10goiHZl/rJ10goiHZl_0_0_1000_667_0_x-large.jpg" alt="זוג צעיר ומאושר" title="Do you remember when you were once a young, happy couple?  (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.HJlwFEizUWx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2026/01/19/rJ10goiHZl/rJ10goiHZl_0_0_1000_667_0_x-large.jpg" alt="זוג צעיר ומאושר" title="Do you remember when you were once a young, happy couple?  (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Do you remember when you were once a young, happy couple? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="84vut-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="84vut-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="84vut-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Ultimately, after all the data, studies and diagnoses, Prof. Yovell seeks to distill these insights into one simple principle that, in his view, summarizes the entire discussion of relationships, parenting and emotional responsibility: Make time to invest in your relationship, even if at times it comes at the expense of the children. You are not being selfish. You are also taking care of them. “You simply have to put on the oxygen mask,” he said, invoking the familiar airline safety instruction. “We all know the announcement before every flight, that if there is a drop in cabin pressure and oxygen masks fall, you should put the mask on yourself first and only then on your child. Every mother hears this and says, ‘Are you serious? Me first and only then my child?’ “The answer is that this is exactly what you should do.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="6kdba" data-offset-key="ebo0q-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="ebo0q-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="ebo0q-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“Imagine the moment it actually happens. There is a loss of cabin pressure, the masks drop, and the plane eventually makes an emergency landing on water. Now everyone has to get out quickly before the plane sinks. Who has a better chance? A fully alert child wearing a mask, lying in the arms of an unconscious mother? Or an unconscious child in the arms of an alert, clear-headed mother wearing a mask, who can lift the child and get out of the plane in time? “First take care of yourselves and of each other, so that together you can take care of the children,” he concluded. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ynetnews.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 20:02:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibkFVX3lxTE9mdDEwNjV4NDl6VzVWaWRUTFhCSmc5SVRRckF2Y0VhN0o5dXhseGp5NVpYRkdIb09kb2hfVUhONDVSQjRuSUJaaVFnalROamF4Snc3bl9LSFpGU3BGV21DaU9VN0NkTU10Wk9zS29B</guid></item><item><title>在堪萨斯州社区废水中检测到6种高浓度病毒- hayspost.com</title><link>https://hayspost.com/posts/737cea8b-a085-43e3-a2ab-b59cc43b3eea</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="p-4 text-lg text-gray-800 leading-loose"&gt;&lt;figure class="py-8"&gt;&lt;img class="mx-auto w-full sm:w-full md:w-1/2" src="https://media.eaglewebservices.com/public/2022/12/1671049425198.jpg" alt="Image Pixaby"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="text-center italic text-gray-700 text-sm pt-2"&gt;Image Pixaby&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Lawrence sees early flu peak as some health care providers require masking&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;By:&lt;a href="https://kansasreflector.com/author/mayasmith/"&gt;Maya Smith&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://kansasreflector.com/2025/02/24/gov-laura-kelly-skeptical-kansas-houses-anti-tenure-legislation-will-reach-her-desk/"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Kansas Reflector&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LAWRENCE — Six viral diseases — including COVID-19, the flu and norovirus — have been found at high concentrations in Lawrence wastewater as Kansas communities face peak flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;COVID-19, influenza A and B, RSV, human metapneumovirus, and norovirus have all been detected at high concentrations in Lawrence &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/4niF8mr" target="_blank"&gt;wastewater&lt;/a&gt; within the last three weeks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wastewater data indicates trends of illnesses spreading within a community but does not correlate to exact case numbers, with doctors saying it’s normal to see high concentrations of respiratory illness during flu season. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Wastewater data does not measure individual cases, but it provides a reliable picture of how much virus is circulating in a community,” said Veronica White, preparedness and epidemiology coordinator for Lawrence-Douglas County Public Health. “This data captures viral genetic material shed by everyone using the sewer system. One factor that may be contributing to the higher concentrations of respiratory viruses seen in Lawrence’s wastewater is its larger population.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lawrence is also seeing an early peak in influenza B compared to the rest of the country. Positive flu tests spiked the last week of 2025, with 32% of total flu tests coming back positive, according to data from the University of Kansas Health System.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some health care providers such as Watkins Health Center at the University of Kansas are requiring masks for all visitors, patients and staff due to a “record surge in respiratory illnesses,” according to a sign at the front door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;White said early rise in the flu doesn’t indicate a more dangerous flu season, but rather earlier circulation of the virus than usual. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Identifying this trend early through wastewater data allows people to take preventive steps, such as getting vaccinated, monitoring symptoms, and staying home when sick,” White said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wastewater data also indicated that a newer strain of COVID, known as the XFG or the Stratus variant, has accounted for 82.5% of positive COVID samples, with concentrations increasing by 25% in the last month. The variant has also been increasing nationally, White said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dana Hawkinson, medical director for Infection Control and Prevention program at University of Kansas Health System, said there are still large populations of people across the state who have not received a flu shot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There have been a large number of people ill and circulators too in our communities. But (the flu) still remains at a high level at this point in time,” Hawkinson said. “There have been extremely low numbers of people not getting the vaccine. We know that we can help prevent this and people’s chances of severe illness and death with it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steve Stites, chief medical officer at the University of Kansas Health System, said that &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/p7chEnUW0EI?si=2KN1bC2byLQI_f0H&amp;amp;t=678" target="_blank"&gt;vaccines&lt;/a&gt; are incredibly safe and effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hawkinson said flu symptoms include fever, cough, congestion, body aches and a sore throat rather than stomach bug symptoms, with the definitions often getting mixed up during flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wastewater data has also indicated that Salina is seeing medium concentrations of the same illnesses, except for influenza A, which is considered to be at a high concentration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Based on the data, we expect viral activity to continue in both Lawrence and Salina over the next few weeks,” White said. “As we move through flu season, we anticipate seeing elevated influenza activity reflected in the wastewater, especially as the season approaches its typical peak.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical experts continue to advise washing hands, covering coughs and not going into large public spaces when sick to prevent illnesses from spreading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You can still go get the flu vaccine,” Hawkinson said. “It’s still recommended, and you can do it now to protect yourself from infection.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>hayspost.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 19:04:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE9KN2lSbVhfVkxHa1M5VUVPZnhKVjRwNUczeTg4TGJ6emVtbm9jSVp2QnFNWTRSVlJSWVNSdkpDdUhrN3Z3ZmJtVlhMekFwYVNpTzNzXzdfRmlxeWRjdlBGX0Y2VzBsZnhuR0ZRTE5oODU</guid></item><item><title>拔出向内生长的头发，然后有4%的机会从昏迷中苏醒过来的男性- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/texas-man-coma-sepsis-brain-dead-removing-ingrown-hair-recovery-593066-20260124</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Moving footage captured the moment a man woke from a coma a month after his loved ones were told he was likely brain dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Doctors feared the worst for &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/us-news"&gt;Texas&lt;/a&gt; dad Steven Spinale after he was rushed to hospital, as they had initially 'couldn't figure out what was wrong with him', according to his sister Michelle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;She explained that he was admitted in 2022 after weeks of being 'pretty sick', but all medics were able to determine was that he was 'bleeding internally from somewhere'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Little did we know that would be the smallest worry," Michelle wrote in a &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/help-steven-fight-for-his-life"&gt;GoFundMe&lt;/a&gt; post at the time. "He declined fast until he crashed and was put on life support."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Steven's organs then started to shut down and doctors realised he was suffering from &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/sepsis-warning-signs-andrea-mclean-nearly-died-379552-20251204"&gt;sepsis&lt;/a&gt;, which is a life-threatening reaction to an infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;According to the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/nhs"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt;, the deadly condition takes hold 'when your immune system overreacts to an infection and starts to damage your body's own tissues and organs'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Steven Spinale battled a rare bacterial infection, sepsis, influenza A and double pneumonia among other complex medical issues (GoFundMe)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It turned out that Steven developed sepsis after contracting a 'rare bacteria that was ravaging through his body'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The then-36-year-old got the infection shortly after &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/ingrown-hair-remove-advice-nhs-716053-20240322"&gt;attempting to remove an ingrown hair&lt;/a&gt; from his groin, his family said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Steven then subsequently caught influenza A - a viral infection that mainly affects the nose, throat and lungs - and double pneumonia while he was in hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Michelle told social media users who had been intently following her brother's story that doctors had also diagnosed him with acute respiratory distress syndrome (ARDS).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;This is another potentially fatal illness which 'is usually a complication of other serious conditions' and means that the lungs are not working properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Miraculously, he defied the odds and woke up from a medically-induced coma (GoFundMe)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;In an &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.tiktok.com/@michellebell111/video/7345167428386639134?lang=en"&gt;update&lt;/a&gt; shared to &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/tiktok"&gt;TikTok&lt;/a&gt; in November 2024, Michelle explained that the bacterial infection caused 'severe damage' to her siblings heart, while noting that he also suffered a 'stroke'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;She said that medics had also found massive blood clots in legs and heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Steven was &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/ingrown-hair-sepsis-man-brain-dead-510163-20240322"&gt;placed in a medically-induced coma&lt;/a&gt;, with doctors saying he was likely 'brain dead' - giving the dad just a four percent chance of surviving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"They told us no brain activity, but they were wrong," Michelle captioned the clip, explaining his family had fought to keep the ventilator that was keeping him alive on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;After four weeks of being in a coma, Steven &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/ingrown-hair-sepsis-man-coma-brain-dead-update-731931-20260123"&gt;miraculously woke up&lt;/a&gt; - and his sister caught the incredible moment he began to regain consciousness on camera.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take a look at it here:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Michelle captioned the heartwarming clip: "What it looks like to wake up from a coma after Drs said you didn't have brain activity. Boy were they wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"This is one of the many reasons I know God has the final say. They told us my brother was brain dead, he wasn't!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;In the comment section of the clip, she explained that the marks on Steven's face were 'pressure wounds' which he sustained after spending such a long amount of time &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/steven-spinale-ingrown-hair-sepsis-spinning-bed-728723-20240322"&gt;in a rotating hospital bed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;In another TikTok &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.tiktok.com/@michellebell111/video/7347155858708548894?lang=en"&gt;video&lt;/a&gt; shared during Steven's recovery, his sister explained that his family 'never lost hope', while poignantly adding: "And luckily he is alive today."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Steven has since gone on to make a miraculous recovery after being discharged from hospital, while Michelle has been sharing regular updates on &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/social-media"&gt;social media&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;She has shared several videos showing him hitting 'milestones' such as sitting up in bed eating food, learning to walk again and taking part in physiotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Other snaps show Steven going fishing and spending time with family members - while sporting a huge smile on his face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:04:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxNU21PX2VaV2J2Uy1Qc3RlSnVQWE9PQlpJV3lPeGxGRkNiNGJQYU1DZ1lwelBRSnIwLXdLSDVuU2t0TzhGQXNfTlgwb29KcWJRS1pFRE5URWVQay0yWHB6YUdtMWdmRjJQeEJHaDhVVkZnWFVxejAxTGdqVEZKYzMxU25fMGFHajRlLXVKYXBLbEZhX0t5WjhpVzdPZlNBbDNtS0VfZ25QeXNMbDVYZjVQMjdyeFdkOWc</guid></item><item><title>在肠道中发现的一个隐藏的警告标志可能会增加癌症风险- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/a-hidden-warning-sign-discovered-in-the-gut-may-increase-cancer-risk</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-unique-set-of-gut-bugs-might-be-centenarians-secret-to-a-long-life"&gt;As we get older&lt;/a&gt;, chemical marks on our DNA slowly shift. Now, a study reveals this 'drift' in gut  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/stem-cells" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73034" data-postid="188904" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;stem cells&lt;/a&gt; is fueled by inflammation and disrupted cell signaling, and it may help explain why our risk of colorectal  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="188904" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; rises with age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The international team of researchers has called this process Aging and Colon Cancer-Associated (ACCA) drift, and it involves shifts in &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DNA_methylation"&gt;DNA methylation&lt;/a&gt; that can 'switch' genes on or off without altering the DNA – called &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/epigenetic-changes-"&gt;epigenetic changes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this case, the drift leads to the gradual silencing of genes that help suppress tumor formation, allowing cancer risk to build up in more and more cells across the gut, long before tumors appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/just-3-days-of-binge-drinking-triggers-rapid-gut-damage-in-mice"&gt;Just 3 Days of Binge Drinking Triggers Rapid Gut Damage in Mice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We observe an epigenetic pattern that becomes increasingly apparent with age," &lt;a href="https://www.leibniz-fli.de/news/as-our-gut-age-new-study-finds-out-why-important-genes-go-quiet-as-we-get-older"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; molecular biologist Francesco Neri, from the University of Turin in Italy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting with what was known – that &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41580-018-0020-3"&gt;epigenetic drift&lt;/a&gt; has been &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2217/epi-2015-0017"&gt;linked to cancer&lt;/a&gt;, and that colorectal cancer risk rises with age – the researchers studied tissue from both healthy human colons and colon cancer tumors, looking for common methylation patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They found similar patterns of gene silencing in older individuals and in cancerous tissue, suggesting a common underlying process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further experiments on mouse models and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-an-organoid" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="106655" data-postid="188904" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;organoids&lt;/a&gt; (mini-guts grown in the lab) helped the researchers establish what was driving the drift and how it was spreading, and confirmed that it was unique to the intestines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_188907" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188907" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/GutCrypts.jpg" alt="Intestinal crypts" class="size-full wp-image-188907" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/GutCrypts.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/GutCrypts-600x255.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-188907" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The researchers identified how crypt stem cells changed and spread. (Krepelova et al., &lt;em&gt;Nat. Aging&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The focus was on intestinal crypts, small pockets in the gut lining that house stem cells that renew the intestinal lining. Experiments showed that ACCA drift originates within these stem cells and then expands as crypts divide and spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here's what's happening: increased inflammation, reduced &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wnt_signaling_pathway"&gt;growth signaling&lt;/a&gt;, and reduced iron levels in intestinal crypt stem cells combine to disrupt the processes that tidy up methylation, leading to genes being deactivated – in a way that potentially allows &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/targeting-the-cancer-stem-cell-could-be-key-to-better-treatments"&gt;cancer to develop&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Over time, more and more areas with an older epigenetic profile develop in the tissue," &lt;a href="https://www.leibniz-fli.de/news/as-our-gut-age-new-study-finds-out-why-important-genes-go-quiet-as-we-get-older"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; molecular biologist Anna Krepelova, from the University of Turin. "Through the natural process of crypt division, these regions continuously enlarge and can continue to grow over many years."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When there's not enough iron in the cells, faulty markings remain on the DNA. And the cells lose their ability to remove these markings."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As stem cell-driven crypts divide and multiply, patches of tissue with older, cancer-prone epigenetic profiles gradually expand. This creates more unhealthy pockets throughout the gut over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/castingcall?utm_source=SA_website&amp;amp;utm_medium=article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=casting_call"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg" alt="Audition now for ScienceAlert's Casting Call" class="alignnone wp-image-189354 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-1200x509.jpg 1200w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1.jpg 1266w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inflammation, iron imbalance, and lower growth signaling can accelerate epigenetic drift, meaning the aging process and increased vulnerability to cancer can happen earlier in the gut than previously thought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These danger zones will vary between people, as does &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/walking-daily-linked-to-lower-risk-of-13-cancers-major-study-finds"&gt;cancer risk&lt;/a&gt;, but now we know more about how &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-common-medicine-may-stop-colorectal-cancer-from-returning"&gt;colorectal cancer&lt;/a&gt; gets more opportunities to start as we age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Encouragingly, in organoids, the researchers were able to slow and even partially reverse epigenetic drift by boosting iron uptake or restoring specific cell growth signals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This means that epigenetic aging does not have to be a fixed, final state," &lt;a href="https://www.leibniz-fli.de/news/as-our-gut-age-new-study-finds-out-why-important-genes-go-quiet-as-we-get-older"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Krepelova. "For the first time, we are seeing that it is possible to tweak the parameters of aging that lie deep within the molecular core of the cell."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s43587-025-01021-x"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature Aging&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:01:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxNR25TS3NpU2RFcmdnY2VMUUxUNzF2Qkl1Z18xN25FeEo3WjU2enBDUll1SDQzNmtnMDhZZHJpVllKbmZUOTVCOW4yQWptS0tGTll2UXhoakE4ZnNnUnUwVmpNbEptRE16TUFaUjN3WnBmelo3MjEwUi1yMlJVOG9UWWdlMTlCV3lESGtDTmY3cVlWSEd2NGI5MWJVMmJsQQ</guid></item><item><title>我的朋友被吸入了育儿社区最黑暗的群体之一。我受不了她-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2026/01/parenting-advice-friend-baby-vaccination.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="22" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkseajw40029cvkkcm75wycu@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is a newsletter bonus question. Care and Feeding is Slate’s parenting advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a question for Care and Feeding? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://forms.gle/4BXEw8Wtcd7aAyXh9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submit it here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkseajw4002acvkk8tjb2xnz@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Care and Feeding,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="52" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksealum000a3b7bywgye87z@published"&gt;My friend, “Angela”, who is in her 30s, is the first of my friends to have a baby. Her circle is small, and so is her fiancé’s. He is new to the state. They decided to try for a baby after just six months of dating, and will be wed this summer.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="59" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksealwz000b3b7bwo2w5sxf@published"&gt;Angela is a hippie, and a victim of abuse at the hands of her father, brother, and past partners. One partner in particular was conspiratorial, and as a result, she has never received a COVID vaccine. In 2022, I was unable to see her before my abortion in the case that I might need surgery—I couldn’t risk contracting COVID.&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="41" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksealz6000c3b7blcr322gu@published"&gt;During her pregnancy, we talked about vaccination, and Angela told our friend group she intended on getting the baby vaccinated. She also told us she would get the Tdap shot during her pregnancy, though she never confirmed actually having done so.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="84" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkseam1g000d3b7bgapsqsxl@published"&gt;Angela is now a stay-at-home mom with a four-month-old baby. I love this baby. I love the title of “auntie.” But Angela is becoming overprotective and delusional. She has no media literacy and is sharing anti-vaccine posts on Facebook. When challenged, she thanks me for my help, but it rings hollow. She talks often about “hating Trump,” but is now parroting a lot of his ideals. I can’t be friends with someone who doesn’t vaccinate their baby! How can I get through to her?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkseam68000f3b7bvzjsk7cd@published"&gt;—Vaccinated&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksecyl2000p3b7bwu8lwwt8@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Vaccinated,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="83" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksed31r000u3b7be07orskk@published"&gt;Few things going on here! But the most glaring is that your friend’s baby is &lt;em&gt;four months old, &lt;/em&gt;meaning your friend is just &lt;em&gt;four-months postpartum. &lt;/em&gt;This is a hard, hard time for her—she’s isolated, she’s sleep deprived, her body and hormones are still doing strange things, and she’s got this living creature to take care of. You call her “overprotective and delusional,” but another way to put that might be “suffering from postpartum depression.” (Not a doctor! Just musing here, but like, c’mon.)&lt;/p&gt;

  



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="86" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkskwx3q003p3b7bliufjnyr@published"&gt;Right now, the best thing you could do for your friend would be to encourage her to speak to her doctor about how she’s feeling. And the next best thing would be to just be there for her, listen to her, be compassionate, and supportive, and yes, offer one IRL data point of dissent on the vax front (e.g., when she brings it up or posts about it, simply reply: “I’ve read the same stuff you have. And I still believe vaccinations save lives,” or whatever).&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="84" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksg8olw003g3b7bm4qyhb60@published"&gt;As for “getting through to her” beyond that—good luck. We live in an information hellhole right now. Her media illiteracy and vax hesitancy is the result of societal failure, not her own personal or moral shortcoming. Her baby’s pediatrician will have many opportunities, and some authority, to talk her about vaccines. And there will (likely, probably, definitely, depending on where you live) be many checks in the future that could spur vaccination: daycare registration, school registration, camp registration. This isn’t your problem to solve.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="59" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksl0frn003t3b7b3smdcrrm@published"&gt;But if this is a red line for you, then sure, tell her that and peace out. It sounds like you might be looking for a reason to do that anyway—judgment for your pal is just oozing from your letter, before you even mention vaccines. Your friend could definitely use a friend, but it doesn’t have to be you.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkseajw4002ccvkka4ghvgn9@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Logan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmkseajw4002dcvkkaubsb3st@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Classic Prudie

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="122" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkseajw4002ecvkkc88h50gq@published"&gt;I’m a personal assistant to a highly accomplished woman a few years older than me whom I admire and respect a great deal. I’ve worked with her for five years, and we have a close professional relationship. This weekend, we were together late one night when she confided in me how lonely she was; the long hours we work make it difficult for her to maintain a relationship, and she has few friends nearby. Then she told me how good it was to have someone she could confide in and how grateful she was that she could speak to me in confidence. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2016/01/dear-prudence-im-falling-in-love-with-my-boss.html"&gt;She gave me a look that under any other circumstance I would have taken as an invitation to kiss her. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmkseajw5002gcvkk4txv9xbq@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxPeExpYmZnN2tiZkZZSVdZdGNkWEZncDIwOW1kN0E1T3BpOG5IQXpsck9ZRkJNaXh2NFBVX1FBWm5hX3VOdWJoOHRBM0pUMDU5eS1qSnFhb0Q2aUg3SjF6VW0tRV9lNDJsSXBLYW9JM0RCNXp1cFIyMXlOWlZEYjZ5WHo1cDU</guid></item><item><title>这种类型的运动在减少老年人体脂肪方面最有效- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/this-type-of-exercise-is-most-effective-at-reducing-body-fat-in-older-adults/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:54:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxQY1hmeTFHYWdMVThaaHNBejgwbGt5bW53aFhZVU1NQmNVXzBSOG1qTHNqX3pYMDFfWHVaaGxDLUNlanhjWWhUc1dsdFFxQjlycVZ3UE9aNnZSM2RvMHE3dnJ2S0x1Y3kyalBQSE4xMWk0LWo1a0MwVzRkd29qaHdHUTNDUGNlY25IOGVIWElXWXhEZWFwVzhOU1lEMXNIeEdPWTRyWg</guid></item><item><title>我的粗鲁，爱管闲事的婆婆只是“不得不”走进我们做爱。我们的性生活永远不会是一样的。- Slate</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2026/01/sex-mother-in-law-advice-erectile-dysfunction-treatment-options.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkslb2nz003orzmcfjk3izo0@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Stoya and Rich here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkslliz000213b7cqya7d1pl@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="43" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleobt00173b7cu526hkp1@published"&gt;My husband and I went over to his parents’ for the Christmas holiday. His mother has never been particularly respectful of boundaries, but we thought we were safe to go at it at nearly 3 a.m. There’s no way she’d be up, then, right? Wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

    


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="95" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksllz6c00233b7c4l8qdomg@published"&gt;My MIL decided there was something she just HAD to ask us that couldn’t wait until the next day, and she walked in on us. Things were rather awkward in the morning, but I thought it was just one of those dumb things and that would be the end of it. Instead it’s been the end of our sex life, namely the fact that my husband hasn’t been able to get it up since the incident. I’ve tried everything—pussy shaving, sexy lingerie, sucking his dick—nothing works. Both of us are extremely worried and don’t know what to do. Help!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleofp00183b7cd50j256p@published"&gt;—Trying to Raise the Dead&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="6" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleoit00193b7clrxkepxb@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Trying to Raise the Dead,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="54" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleoly001a3b7ciz8qjcqf@published"&gt;Please relax. Not a lot of time has passed, and you’ve pinpointed a cause for the E.D. Plenty of people with non-working dicks and their partners write into this column having no idea why it’s happening. You at least have a leg up. It’s not the &lt;em&gt;dick up t&lt;/em&gt;hat you desire, but it’s something.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="190" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleop4001b3b7ckpe56478@published"&gt;Here’s what I would try: Work on eliminating the intrusive thoughts of this incident. This could be accomplished via therapy and/or a meditation practice. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/11/wife-secret-sex-toy-advice-tracking.html"&gt;I went into my practice in a previous column&lt;/a&gt;, so visit that page for tips. I have found that building the meditation muscle gives me the ability to pick and choose what my mind focuses on. It’s not 100 percent (I have not completely eliminated being haunted by disturbing thoughts or images) but I am doing much better than I did before, and I didn’t even know it was possible to not think about things that were bothering me. Your impulse to do whatever you can to help the matter is heartening and logical, but this issue may be above your pay grade. This is especially so if the root of the cause is, as it seems to be, that he feels “caught,” ashamed, like his boundaries were crossed, or like he’s somehow now associating sex with his mom. This is where working with a therapist/coach could really help. Couples counseling could be an option, but this may be something he mostly handles on his own.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="79" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleotl001c3b7curxc3zf7@published"&gt;I would also get your husband some kind of wood-boosting assistance. Physiologically, he may not really need a PDE5 inhibitor like Viagra and/or a cock ring, but just having them can allay the anxiety that comes with and further exacerbates erectile dysfunction. Boner pills tend to be well-tolerated, and while some guys experience side effects (to the point of making the drugs off-putting), I think trying them is worth the small risk here—just to get him over the hump.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="76" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleoxs001d3b7c4suc4f9y@published"&gt;Also, try focusing on sex that doesn’t require his penis to be hard. Maybe that means he focuses on you orally/manually or that you introduce toys. Play in that space for a bit. Allowing him to get comfortable with this kind of contact may take the edge off and he may find himself able to perform. Again, this boner-killing event was fairly recent so giving it some time is also likely going to be useful. Patience!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleqjr001i3b7cphfykdj7@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Rich&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmkslivws001v3b7ccilb43mj@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="106" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkslj14l001y3b7cfe5pdf8m@published"&gt;I’m in a polyamorous relationship with my boyfriend. It’s not really my thing, but I agreed to give it a shot because I really like him. We’ve had our ups and downs, but our biggest hangup is that he doesn’t want to give me “veto” power over who he sleeps with. That hasn’t been a problem, really—until now. Recently, he told me he’s very attracted to my friend, and wants to hook up with her. I, um, hate this. For some reason, it’s making me super jealous, but I agreed to a relationship structure where he gets to do what he wants. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2022/10/boyfriend-relationship-rules-friend-sex-advice.html"&gt;What should I do?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmkslb2nz003rrzmc6ai43tch@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:51:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQQ3o2SUkyUUl4UHdTeFBaWUtXWG03RWR3M1drQjhsbHNYZEJ2YnJ0MFMzNE1mUmdkR1R3MGtxZ005eGN2aFV5UXFDdEd1NG13RFAzZm43RWRlMDE3bDFBWlQ5ZzlLUGhybzlkUGZ5akVSbl9jVE4xYWhadzRhYWZzUVZ1V2xuYVRjcGUtTlRucDlNVnBFUnZzZDQwM25LeG1aYmM4</guid></item><item><title>非洲顶级卫生官员抨击特朗普政府在非洲进行人体实验的计划-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/vaccines-africa-trump</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="article-featured-image-figure"&gt;
			
			
	&lt;p class="article-featured-image-caption-container"&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="article-featured-image-caption"&gt;
			Illustration by Tag Hartman-Simkins / Futurism. Source: Samuel Corum / Getty Images 		&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/figure&gt;
	
	
	
	
	
	&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;Last week, officials at the Africa Centres for Disease Control and Prevention (Africa CDC) announced that health authorities in Guinea-Bissau had moved to &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/health-medicine/trump-rfk-africa-vaccines"&gt;halt a controversial study&lt;/a&gt; which would have used unvaccinated infants as lab rats. The US Department of Health and Human Services (HHS), however, insisted the trial was still on.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;That wasn’t all US health authorities had to say. In a bizarre outburst, the HHS &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/health-medicine/trump-hhs-africa-cdc"&gt;told &lt;em&gt;Futurism&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that the Africa CDC was a “fake and powerless organization,” and insisted that it was “not a reliable source” for information. During a &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2jhDb-r2jDc" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;press meeting&lt;/a&gt; on Thursday, director-general of the Africa CDC Jean Kaseya hit back.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Let me tell you: we are not an NGO,” Kaseya said defiantly. “We are not a UN organization. We are the convening power in Africa. The mandate [is] given to us by all 55 African heads of state and government.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“People can meet in the US, people can meet in Europe,” Kaseya continued, likely referencing &lt;a href="https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-news/danish-vaccine-study-emails-hhs-rfk-jr-1235498456/" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;leaked emails&lt;/a&gt; between HHS officials and Danish researchers to push the vaccine trial in Guinea-Bissau. “If we are not there, they are wasting their time.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Kaseya also made it clear that no government has the right to impose experiments on the people of Guinea-Bissau.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Africa CDC is respecting and supporting the sovereignty of the country,” the official continued. “It’s not Africa CDC that will say, ‘this clinical trial will take place or not.’ It’s not any other international body that will come to say, ‘this clinical trial will take place or not.’ It’s not a foreign country that will come and say, ‘this one will take place.’ It’s the sovereignty of the country.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Though the HHS evidently thinks it has the power to push dangerous vaccines experiments on African countries, the reality isn’t so simple. According to the &lt;a href="https://africacdc.org/news-item/africa-cdc-guidance-for-any-clinical-trial-to-be-conducted-in-africa/" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Africa CDC’s guidelines&lt;/a&gt;, any vaccine trial that doesn’t receive a written authorization from the country’s National Medicines Regulatory Authority is illegal. Likewise, it must have approval from the National Ethics Committee, as well as a local institutional review board at each site where the trial is to take place.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;On top of all that, any trial must also have explicit approval from the country’s Ministry of Health — granting officials in Guinea-Bissau the power to functionally veto any experiment the government doesn’t support.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Kaseya emphasized the importance of exercising sovereignty over African public health. “Our vision is not coming from Western countries,” he said. “Our vision is coming from Africa, shaped by African leadership, based on African realities.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;In an &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2026/jan/23/guinea-bissau-hepatitis-b-vaccine-study" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;interview with the &lt;em&gt;Guardian&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Abdulhammad Babatunde, a doctor and global health researcher in Nigeria, said that it’s “very important to fund research that Africans actually want.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Africans want to solve Africa’s problems, not satisfy the curiosity of the funders,” Babatunde said, referring to the HHS, which announced the &lt;a href="https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/12/18/2025-23245/notice-of-award-of-a-single-source-unsolicited-grant-to-fund-university-of-southern-denmark-sdu#page-59125" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;$1.6 million funding package&lt;/a&gt; for the study in December. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Once up and running, the vaccine trial would have given 7,000 newborn children a vaccine for hepatitis B, while 7,000 more infants in the control group wouldn’t receive the vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;As the &lt;em&gt;Guardian&lt;/em&gt; notes, nearly one in five adults and 11 percent of children in Guinea-Bissau have hepatitis B — which carries a significant risk for debilitating illness and death. In such a health environment, there’s no justification for purposefully leaving infants unvaccinated for any length of time.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“This is not acceptable,” Babatunde told the paper. “To prevent things like the Tuskegee study and others, the control group has to get the standard of care, and the intervention group should get [potentially] better care.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Asked whether the HHS’s comments would affect future collaboration with Africa CDC, Kaseya said he’s putting the strange episode behind him.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“I was briefed that they don’t know anything about any statement against Africa CDC,” he said. “I could tell you about a statement that could be somewhere, made by someone. But officials from HHS just yesterday — senior people — said they don’t know anything about the statement. I trust them, I’ve closed the chapter.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on Africa: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://futurism.com/artificial-intelligence/ai-companion-chatbots-kenya"&gt;AI “Companion Bots” Actually Run by Exploited Kenyans, Worker Claims&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTFBXT1FhSnNmeE1oU1RvMGJmbktBWUJaM3BnOHJ5MkdueG8yV09WcU5YZmlzWXlqcW9MRExuOTF4THdfdmRrNlhRTXhXQ3lSdDJ5SHJzRm9USlU0N3pSQzRuZmRydk5QUzIwYmc</guid></item><item><title>由于官员发出严重警告，印度报告了无法治愈和“潜在流行病”的致命病毒爆发- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/india-nipah-virus-outbreak-symptoms-deadly-illness-no-cure-who-warning-577116-20260124</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Indian health officials are currently battling to contain an outbreak of a deadly virus which has no vaccine or cure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;There are currently least five confirmed cases of Nipah virus (NiV) in the eastern state of West Bengal, which is the fourth most populous state in the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Three nurses, a doctor and a member of &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/health"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; staff - who all share links to the same private hospital - have been infected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;One of the patients is currently in a 'critical' condition, the West Bengal health department said. Experts are still working to determine how the five people contracted the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;But according &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/global-health/science-and-disease/health-experts-scramble-to-contain-nipah-outbreak-india/"&gt;to&lt;/a&gt; The Telegraph, one of the nurses who was first infected caught Nipah virus while treating a patient with severe respiratory symptoms - who later died before testing could be carried out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Almost 100 people who have been in close contact with the infected have been quarantined and are under observation, state officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"All of them are asymptomatic and tested negative," said Narayan Swaroop Nigam, who is the Principal Secretary of the Health and Family Welfare Department in West Bengal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;The virus is contagious, deadly and has no cure (C. K Thanseer/DeFodi images via Getty Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"We will again test them before their 21-day quarantine ends," Nigam added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The World Health Organisation (WHO) classes Nipah virus as a high-risk priority pathogen, meaning it has the potential to cause an 'epidemic'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It has earned itself a spot on the organisation's Research &amp;amp; Development Blueprint &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.who.int/teams/blueprint/nipah-henipaviruses#:~:text=Nipah%20virus%20is%20one%20of,human%20transmission%20have%20been%20documented."&gt;list&lt;/a&gt; of epidemic threats as a result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;With no approved vaccine or cure to remedy the zoonotic illness, the WHO previously &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.who.int/india/home/emergencies/nipah-virus-infection"&gt;warned&lt;/a&gt; that 'urgent' research and development is needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;There have been no known cases of Nipah virus reported in the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/uk-news"&gt;UK&lt;/a&gt; to date, however, the Health Security Agency (UKHSA) is now intently monitoring the situation in &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/world-news"&gt;India&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;According to the WHO, the illness is transmitted to people from &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/animals"&gt;animals&lt;/a&gt;, although people can also get struck down by it after eating contaminated &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/food-and-drink"&gt;food&lt;/a&gt;. It can then spread directly from person-to-person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Guidance from the UK government also &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.gov.uk/guidance/nipah-virus-epidemiology-outbreaks-and-guidance"&gt;explains&lt;/a&gt;: "Close and direct, unprotected contact with infected patients, especially those with respiratory symptoms, has been implicated as a transmission risk."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;A health worker seen wearing protective gear disposes biohazard waste from a Nipah virus isolation centre during an outbreak in India in 2023 (AFP via Getty Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Those who have been infected usually begin to experience symptoms which are comparable to the flu or a fever - but it can later trigger fatal brain swelling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Signs of Nipah virus include a temperatures, headaches, myalgia (muscle pain), vomiting and sore throat, as well as dizziness, drowsiness, altered consciousness, and &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/mental-health"&gt;neurological&lt;/a&gt; issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The WHO states: "Some people can also experience atypical pneumonia and severe respiratory problems, including acute respiratory distress."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;In severe cases, patients may develop &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/community/encephalitis-lethargica-explained-symptoms-cause-149011-20250803"&gt;encephalitis&lt;/a&gt; - the life-threatening inflammation of the&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;brain - or seizures, which the WHO says can then lead on to 'a coma within 24 to 48 hours'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;According to the WHO, 40 percent to 75 percent of cases of Nipah virus end in fatalities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The virus was first recognised in 1999 during an outbreak among pig farmers in Malaysia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It is thought to have been transmitted to humans via exposure to secretions from the animals, or unprotected contact with the tissue of a sick pig.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Bats have been blamed for previous outbreaks of Nipah virus in India (Soumyabrata Roy/NurPhoto via Getty Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Nipah was also found in Bangladesh in 2001, and nearly annual outbreaks have occurred in that country since.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Evidence of the virus has also been found in bat species in a number of countries, including Cambodia, Ghana, Indonesia, Madagascar, the Philippines and Thailand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Subsequent outbreaks in India have been attributed to infected fruit bats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;India's Ministry of Health and Family Welfare shared a post on &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/social-media"&gt;social media&lt;/a&gt; encouraging people to 'follow essential precautions to prevent infection'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;People are being urged to wash fruit and vegetables thoroughly, clean their hands with soap and water and to wear protective clothing when in contact with animals, among other advice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The government also warned people to avoid eating 'contaminated and half-eaten fruits from trees' as well as raw date palm juice and toddy-like liquid kept in open pots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:54:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxPc0JyUlgwVUx4eG0yUDZuN29mVlBHdU1YSFVDSndGRnktcDFubFlPenRsUWRFcVA2am5xVk5QR3VScXlsSEhyN2NEOG5OaWxEdlc0Q0FWVkI3VVpQVTYySml4ejcyVWwtQ1ZuOU1manV0aVVyMEZqU2hpSnZtYU5ESDY1Vkp6MFdRYW1hV2JVT19sYTJVMUhZYmJmSzFaU0F3WUdJOVBMV0V3UnhhaTZpUXVkclAyaElxMDVzR1czMWs</guid></item><item><title>癌症肿瘤可以通过清除蛋白质团块来预防阿尔茨海默氏症- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-cancer-tumors-alzheimer-protein-clumps.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:30:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxPdFBMWlRwSUl0N3BNbWp5RjhhSWZaYUhJV19YVXV6UHRpamJ1VzVGWmU5akRGdFY3ckZubEcwMDYzY0JHTXE2WldBZS00dHpqVUJlMFZrNXc0TmlXS0hXeWp1d1ExOHg4b3RBTDI2dWRQWEhjYmxZUzJFSHlON1FteWVIemZDRERLWWc</guid></item><item><title>当您每天服用欧米茄3补充剂时，您的血糖会发生什么？ - Verywell Health</title><link>https://www.verywellhealth.com/omega-3-supplements-and-blood-sugar-11865218</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="health-sc-page_1-0" class="comp health-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content article-content expert-content right-rail__offset lock-journey" data-sc-sticky-offset="60" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[400, 1400, 1400, 1700, 2000, 2200, 2400, 2600, 2800]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="health-sc-block-callout--key-takeaway_1-0" class="comp health-sc-block-callout--key-takeaway health-sc-block-callout-base mntl-sc-block-callout mntl-block theme-key-takeaway theme-key-takeaway" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block-callout-heading_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-heading mntl-text-block"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block-callout-body_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-body mntl-text-block expert-content"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is insufficient scientific evidence that daily omega-3 supplementation lowers blood sugar (glucose) levels.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;An elevated blood sugar level is a hallmark feature of diabetes, a lifelong condition that is typically managed with a combination of medication, nutrition therapy, and physical activity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you are considering taking an omega-3 supplement, speak with your healthcare provider first to avoid medication interactions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Omega-3 supplements, also called fish oil supplements, contain a type of fat found in shellfish and cold-water fish like salmon, mackerel, and tuna.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Results from scientific studies on whether taking a daily omega-3 supplement impacts blood sugar (glucose) levels are mixed, with emerging evidence leaning towards minimal to no effect.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-omega-3s-inconsistent-effect-on-blood-sugar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Omega-3's Inconsistent Effect on Blood Sugar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Elevated blood sugar levels due to defects in insulin production or action are characteristic of diabetes.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Without careful management, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/type-2-diabetes-complications-5120942" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;diabetes can lead to serious complications&lt;/a&gt; involving the eyes, kidneys, heart, and nerves.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Due to the seriousness and chronicity of diabetes, scientists have launched an extensive and ongoing investigation into the potential role of supplements, like &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/benefits-of-omega-3-11772277" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;omega-3 fatty acids&lt;/a&gt;, in both preventing diabetes and serving as an adjunct to traditional diabetes medications.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Despite substantial scientific investigation, results regarding the effect of omega-3 supplementation on blood sugar levels have been inconsistent.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Specifically, while some studies have found that &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/how-to-choose-omega-3-supplement-11845012" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;omega-3 supplementation&lt;/a&gt; lowers blood sugar levels, others have reported little to no impact.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-do-the-scientific-studies-show"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What Do the Scientific Studies Show? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One example of a study reporting conflicting results on the impact of omega-3 on blood sugar is a 2024 study in &lt;em&gt;Current Nutrition Reports. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Basics of the study include the following:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This study&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;reviewed 30 randomized controlled trials involving participants, primarily adults, with one of three forms of diabetes: &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/type-2-diabetes-7371634" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/type-1-diabetes-7971457" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;type 1 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/glucose-tests-in-pregnancy-5115077" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;gestational diabetes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participants received omega-3 supplements of varying types and doses for six weeks to 12 months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The trial found that some participants experienced a reduction in fasting blood glucose levels with omega-3 supplementation, whereas others showed no change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Investigators noted that such differences in trial results could be attributable to factors like:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Number of participants in each trial&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trial duration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participants' age and, specifically, how long they have had diabetes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dosage of the omega-3 supplement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Other examples of studies addressing the uncertain role of daily omega-3 supplementation on blood sugar levels include:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;A 2022 study reviewed 30 randomized controlled trials involving participants with and without diabetes&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Results revealed that omega-3 supplementation led to a significant reduction in fasting blood sugar levels. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A 2020 study reviewed 12 randomized controlled trials involving just over 800 adults with type 2 diabetes. &lt;strong&gt;Results revealed that&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;omega-3 supplementation did not affect blood sugar levels&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A 2019 study reviewed 83 randomized controlled trials involving more than 120,000 individuals with and without diabetes.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The average trial period lasted nearly three years. &lt;strong&gt;Results revealed that increasing omega-3 intake, whether through supplements or foods (fish or plants), had minimal to no effect on blood glucose levels&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-should-i-take-an-omega-3-supplement"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Should I Take an Omega-3 Supplement? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Overall, there is insufficient evidence to support the claim that omega-3 supplements can improve blood glucose control.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The American Diabetes Association (ADA) does not universally recommend omega-3 supplementation for individuals with diabetes.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Omega-3 supplementation is also not formally recommended for individuals with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/pre-diabetes-4014095" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;prediabetes&lt;/a&gt;, a common health condition marked by high blood sugar levels that are not yet elevated enough to fulfill a diagnosis of diabetes.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; All said, there is some evidence, albeit mixed, that omega-3 supplements may improve cardiovascular health in individuals with diabetes and risk factors for heart disease, like high cholesterol.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Given this potential link, your healthcare provider may recommend omega-3 supplements based on your personal heart disease risk factors.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="health-sc-block-callout--takeaway_1-0" class="comp health-sc-block-callout--takeaway health-sc-block-callout-base mntl-sc-block-callout mntl-block theme-takeaway theme-takeaway" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block-callout-heading_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-heading mntl-text-block"&gt;Speak to Your Diabetes Healthcare Provider&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block-callout-body_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-body mntl-text-block expert-content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Always consult your healthcare provider before starting an omega-3 supplement to ensure it's safe and appropriate for your care. Omega-3 supplements may interact with certain medications, like blood thinners.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If your provider recommends an omega-3 supplement, side effects are generally mild, with common ones being:&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Unpleasant supplement taste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bad breath&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gastrointestinal disturbances (e.g., discomfort, nausea, diarrhea, heartburn)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-using-diet-to-improve-blood-sugar-control"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Using Diet to Improve Blood Sugar Control &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For those with prediabetes or diabetes, the ADA recommends adopting a healthy eating pattern to optimize blood sugar control and prevent diabetes-related complications.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While no single diet suits everyone, the &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/mediterranean-diet-for-beginners-8709362" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt; is a good fit for many. First, check in with your healthcare provider.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The Mediterranean diet is nonrestrictive, offers tasty choices, and has been found to reduce blood sugar levels.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It consists of nutrient-dense foods like fruit, vegetables, and lean protein, as well as foods rich in omega-3s from both animal and plant sources, such as fatty fish, olive oil, and walnuts.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="post-article_1-0" class="comp post-article mntl-block"&gt;
&lt;div id="sources_1-0" class="comp sources mntl-block"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-article-sources_1-0" class="comp mntl-article-sources mntl-expandable-block" data-scroll-offset="70"&gt;&lt;div class="loc expandable-content"&gt;&lt;div id="source-guidelines_1-0" class="comp source-guidelines mntl-text-block"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verywell Health uses only high-quality sources, including peer-reviewed studies, to support the facts within our articles. Read our &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="/verywell-editorial-process-4777042"&gt;editorial process&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; to learn more about how we fact-check and keep our content accurate, reliable, and trustworthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-article-sources__citation-sources_1-0" class="comp mntl-article-sources__citation-sources mntl-citation-sources mntl-sources" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;ol class="mntl-sources__content"&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;National Center for Complementary and Integrative Health. &lt;a href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/health/omega3-supplements-what-you-need-to-know" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Omega-3 supplements: what you need to know&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;National Center for Complementary and Integrative Health. &lt;a href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/health/providers/digest/type-2-diabetes-and-dietary-supplements-science" class="pseudoStyle" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Type 2 diabetes and dietary supplements: what the science says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-4"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bayram SŞ, Kızıltan G. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s13668-024-00561-9" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;The role of omega- 3 polyunsaturated fatty acids in diabetes mellitus management: a narrative review&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Curr Nutr Rep&lt;/em&gt;. 2024 Sep;13(3):527-551. doi:10.1007/s13668-024-00561-9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-12"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Delpino FM, Figueiredo LM, da Silva BGC, et al. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/10408398.2021.1875977" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Omega-3 supplementation and diabetes: a systematic review and meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Crit Rev Food Sci Nutr&lt;/em&gt;. 2022;62(16):4435-4448. doi: 10.1080/10408398.2021.1875977&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gao C, Liu Y, Gan Y, et al. &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1186/s12944-020-01214-w" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Effects of fish oil supplementation on glucose control and lipid levels among patients with type 2 diabetes mellitus: a Meta-analysis of randomized controlled trials&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Lipids Health Dis&lt;/em&gt;. 2020 May 8;19(1):87. doi:10.1186/s12944-020-01214-w&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-11"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brown TJ, Brainard J, Song F, Wang X, Abdelhamid A, Hooper L; PUFAH Group. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1136/bmj.l4697" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Omega-3, omega-6, and total dietary polyunsaturated fat for prevention and treatment of type 2 diabetes mellitus: systematic review and meta-analysis of randomised controlled trials&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;BMJ&lt;/em&gt;. 2019 Aug 21;366:l4697. doi:10.1136/bmj.l4697&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;ElSayed NA, Aleppo G, Aroda VR, et al. 5. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2337/dc23-S005" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Facilitating positive health behaviors and well-being to improve health outcomes: standards of care in diabetes-2023&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Diabetes Care&lt;/em&gt;. 2023;46(Supple 1):S68-S96. doi:10.2337/dc23-S005&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-9"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhatt DL, Steg PG, Miller M, et al. REDUCE-IT Investigators. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1056/NEJMoa1812792" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Cardiovascular risk reduction with icosapent ethyl for hypertriglyceridemia&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;N Engl J Med&lt;/em&gt;. 2019;380(1):11-22. doi:10.1056/NEJMoa1812792&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-7"&gt;&lt;p&gt;National Institutes of Health. &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Omega3FattyAcids-HealthProfessional/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Omega-3 fatty acids: fact sheet for health professionals&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-10"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Martín-Peláez S, Fito M, Castaner O. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu12082236" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Mediterranean diet effects on type 2 diabetes prevention, disease progression, and related mechanisms. a review&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Nutrients&lt;/em&gt;. 2020;12(8):2236. doi: 10.3390/nu12082236&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="author-bio_1-0" class="comp author-bio"&gt;

&lt;p class="author-bio__bio-text"&gt;
&lt;span class="author-bio__bio-title"&gt;By &lt;a href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/colleen-doherty-md-4021130"&gt;Colleen Doherty, MD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Dr. Doherty is a board-certified internist and writer living with multiple sclerosis. She is based in Chicago.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="trust-ribbon_1-0" class="comp trust-ribbon trust-ribbon-expandable-block"&gt; 
&lt;div class="loc expandable-content"&gt;&lt;div id="trust-ribbon__feedback-block_1-0" class="comp trust-ribbon__feedback-block article-feedback mntl-article-feedback"&gt; 
&lt;div class="article-feedback__success-section js-success-section is-hidden"&gt;
&lt;p class="article-feedback__heading"&gt;Thanks for your feedback!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="article-feedback__feedback-section js-feedback-section is-hidden"&gt;
&lt;p class="article-feedback__heading"&gt;What is your feedback?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;button id="helpful-button_1-0" class="comp helpful-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Helpful
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;button id="report-error-button_1-0" class="comp report-error-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Report an Error
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;button id="other-button_1-0" class="comp other-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Other
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-x close-button"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-x" href="#icon-x"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Verywell Health</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:13:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxPU2lnU0FmSjNKeUhZcjJPcHd5ckwtelJHV1JvdndQQkVwRzIzajRFNy1JMzVxUFlMZU5KaS1zcDFjdG9Id3dwU2pXNjNEWGxZTGdHYUg1eHhDaWM1ZS1kYy01NXZpVldUdXZyNE5Fek5uX2czV1B0SHdwVWZFbUhJbA</guid></item><item><title>病毒在表面上存活多久？科学家发现关键细节- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/how-long-do-viruses-survive-on-surfaces-scientists-uncover-crucial-details/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;What lingers on the objects people touch every day can quietly shape how infection risk increases or decreases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That insight matters for how spaces are cleaned, built, and judged for safety when outbreaks emerge and when life feels routine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-surfaces-affect-viruses"&gt;How surfaces affect viruses&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To understand what happens once a virus is left behind on a surface, researchers recently tested two well-studied laboratory viruses on common materials under controlled conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What they found suggested that surface conditions influence risk in ways standard cleaning rules may not fully address.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. C. Brandon Ogbunugafor led the effort at &lt;a href="https://www.yale.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Yale University&lt;/a&gt;, where his team investigates how pathogens spread and change over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-testing-virus-survival"&gt;Testing virus survival&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Temperatures were chosen to reflect everyday indoor settings and the human body. Instead of tracking who might be exposed, the study focused on what happens to viruses once they land on a surface.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using simplified viral systems helped the team isolate how surface material and heat interact, without interference from immune responses or human behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bacteriophages, viruses that infect bacteria, made that isolation possible by allowing physical effects on viral survival and function to be tested under controlled conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-surface-spread-raised-concerns"&gt;Surface spread raised concerns&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2020, a research &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMc2004973" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;letter&lt;/a&gt; tested how long the pandemic coronavirus stayed infectious on copper, plastic, steel, and cardboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That kind of work fed worries about &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/viruses-can-spread-on-non-respiratory-particles-like-dust/"&gt;fomites&lt;/a&gt;, objects that can carry germs through touch, even when close contact seemed avoidable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A separate &lt;a href="https://wwwnc.cdc.gov/eid/article/29/10/23-0636_article" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;investigation&lt;/a&gt; by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention found that the monkeypox virus remained active on household surfaces for at least 15 days, reinforcing concerns about indirect contact during outbreaks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those reports showed that survival alone can mislead, and they left open what happens to a virus that survives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-viruses-that-infect-bacteria"&gt;Viruses that infect bacteria&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To keep the experiments controlled, the team used &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/bacteriophages-use-selfish-genetic-elements-as-weapons/"&gt;bacteriophages&lt;/a&gt;, viruses that infect bacteria rather than people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These viruses are widely used in research because their behavior is predictable and easy to measure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If surface and temperature effects appear in viruses with different shapes and life cycles, those effects are more likely tied to the environment itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That makes bacteriophages useful tools for testing physical rules that can later be examined in human pathogens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over several hours, the researchers tracked how quickly each virus lost the ability to infect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those counts captured survival, but the next step tested whether the remaining particles could still multiply once they met fresh bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-copper-and-heat-destroy-viruses"&gt;Copper and heat destroy viruses&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;On copper kept at 99 degrees Fahrenheit, both viruses lost the ability to infect quickly, making the combination the toughest setting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For phiX174, one of the two test viruses, half of the remaining &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/hidden-viral-dna-may-control-human-embryonic-growth/"&gt;active particles&lt;/a&gt; were gone in just over 30 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;T4, the second test virus, fared even worse under the same conditions. Because copper reactions speed up with warmth, even small differences in indoor temperature could change how fast contamination disappears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 2015 &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4659470/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt; showed copper ions can wreck a coronavirus’s genetic material and outer coat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-cold-slows-viral-decay"&gt;Cold slows viral decay&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At 39 degrees Fahrenheit, the same particles lasted longer on each surface, and some settings showed little drop over hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lower temperature slowed the chemical wear that snaps proteins and genetic material, so fewer particles reached a damaged state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stainless steel and plastic stayed comparatively friendly at 39 degrees Fahrenheit, hinting that contact chemistry matters less when heat-driven damage slows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That pattern helps explain why cold rooms and refrigerated transport can extend the window for indirect spread in some &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/93-of-earths-land-flagged-in-new-outbreak-risk-map-pr25/"&gt;outbreaks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-some-viruses-still-multiply"&gt;Some viruses still multiply&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After surface exposure, the remaining viruses were given new host cells to test whether surface damage affected their ability to multiply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Growth depended on whether a particle could still hijack a cell, meaning tiny surface damage could block reproduction without killing it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On plastic, phiX174 sometimes climbed more than 100-fold within 1 hour, even when survival measurements looked weak earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That result showed that staying intact on a surface and thriving in a host were related but not the same trait.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-same-surface-different-risks"&gt;Same surface, different risks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Links between survival and reproduction changed across conditions, so the same surface could reward persistence but punish growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At 99 degrees Fahrenheit on copper, survival and reproduction rose together for both phages, but plastic at that temperature showed the opposite trend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results showed that which virus lasts longer outside a host depended on the setting, because surface stability and the ability to multiply did not always align.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These mismatches show why surface survival alone cannot fully describe how risky a contaminated object may be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-copper-is-used"&gt;Why copper is used&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Designers have tried copper touch points in clinics because they can keep microbial buildup lower between routine cleanings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an intensive care unit &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/23571364/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;trial&lt;/a&gt;, rooms with copper surfaces had fewer infections and fewer patients carrying drug-resistant bacteria than standard rooms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The value is greatest on high-touch items that many people share, because copper keeps working between wipe-downs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even with that promise, copper cannot replace handwashing, disinfection, or fresh air, and it works best as one layer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-temperature-and-surfaces-interact"&gt;Temperature and surfaces interact&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Numbers from this experiment showed that temperature and surface acted together, meaning simple one-factor rules can miss real outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some settings, temperature amplified surface effects, while in others it reversed them. That kind of interaction means one factor cannot be understood without the other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many infection models assume germs fade from surfaces at a steady pace, but this work suggests that pace changes with both material and temperature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If planners ignore those pairings, they may overclean low-risk spaces or underprepare where a warm, durable surface keeps viruses active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taken together, the results showed that surface conditions can influence both how long viruses persist and what they can do afterward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future tests with more temperatures, humidity, and human viruses should clarify where these patterns hold, and where they break down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2025.11.16.688743v1.full?et_rid=1135089731&amp;amp;et_cid=5851869" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;bioRxiv&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:03:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxNNmQ4SHVPbWNWbWZsT2RkVmhTby1FdEU0YXp3ZUw0N01BdVNoOW1jeUJ5emNTRVBCN2tDTlpUbDBDNjZGa18zQTllbmxRTHp3RkFPb3RBX1ZnTG1sZVpWdFVBeTFHU2ZFMFllSTRRY2s5VHJWUE1GNnprZ0xMS2VsMmtvVUVSdTFJN1VNRVVrOVlsRkloZEdiMWFjWWJJXzNoS2VFNw</guid></item><item><title>一位烹饪书作者连续6年每天吃巧克力蛋糕。现在她分享她的食谱- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/24/health/everyday-chocolate-cake-recipe-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1pxwu004e26p2h8rc0rym@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Go ahead, eat chocolate cake every day. One healthy cookbook author gives us permission — and a recipe that’s protein-packed.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c0006356p1iwz1hx4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Rachel Riggs’ signature unfussy cake asks for just one bowl, a single whisk and 10 minutes to get the oven ready. The result is a chocolate dessert that contains 18 grams of &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/04/15/health/how-to-eat-more-protein-diet-wellness"&gt;protein&lt;/a&gt; per slice and tastes so amazing that Riggs ate a piece as part of lunch daily for six years straight.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c0007356pn407f9a7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            No wonder she named it The Everyday Chocolate Cake.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c0008356pngjnttr2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This is a legit dessert. I think it’s virtually indistinguishable from any mainstream chocolate cake,” said Riggs, who included it in her debut cookbook, “&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Good-Health-Uncomplicated-Allergen-Aware-Nourished/dp/1773272780" target="_blank"&gt;In Good Health&lt;/a&gt;: Uncomplicated, Allergen-Aware Recipes for a Nourished Life.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c0009356p4h09y2d3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “In this cake, the almond flour provides healthy fats, and the pure maple syrup, cocoa powder and unsweetened chocolate deliver antioxidants. Eggs are nutrition powerhouses, too,” Riggs explained.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000a356pz4e1uhav@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Each serving of this cake has as much &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0031938420304376" target="_blank"&gt;appetite-taming&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/nutritionreviews/article/79/1/66/5936522" target="_blank"&gt;muscle-building&lt;/a&gt; protein as three large eggs, which is courtesy of the almond flour, eggs and cocoa powder. (The cocoa powder alone adds about &lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/169593/nutrients" target="_blank"&gt;4 grams per ¼ cup&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;Each egg tacks on 6 grams, and each cup of almond flour layers on 32 grams more protein.) Keep in mind that it also has 39 grams of sugar per slice (including the ganache), courtesy of the natural sweetener maple syrup, so you can determine how often you’d like to slot this into your diet.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000b356p56d96yat@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The inspiration for this cake came from a not-so-sweet place. Riggs has been passionate about food for as long as she can remember.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000c356pyqexetzo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Cheese is where my deepest passion was, so I opened a specialty food shop in 2006. Within four years, there was a substantial shift in my health, so I was forced to close my shop,” the author recalled.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000d356pp0u6wsdf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The symptoms started off subtly but grew over time to the point that the profound fatigue they triggered resulted in “punishing payback for hours, days — or sometimes weeks,” she said. “Like so many people with chronic illness, I went from doctor to doctor, then started broadening my scope and traveling for medical care. It remained a mystery.”
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000e356png00a6nx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            During her mission to try anything that might ease the pain and fatigue, Riggs embarked on a doctor-approved, strict elimination diet.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000f356pit343apj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I went three months without this whole swath of ingredients,” Riggs said. “Eventually, I was able to start adding those things in, and that’s how you identify if something isn’t a good fit for your body.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000g356p8swkc1o9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Riggs  discovered she felt better eliminating her original potential triggers, including  grains (not just gluten), dairy, refined sugars, legumes, peanuts, shellfish  and nightshades (a class of vegetables that includes tomatoes, potatoes,  peppers and eggplants). She still finds plenty  of different   foods to   eat, such   as meat, fish, seafood, fruits, many nuts, most vegetables, seeds,  herbs and spices.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000h356psee1lqwi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Looking to cook with a limited ingredient   list, Riggs found inspiring options lacking and started  developing  her own recipes “to feed myself and my husband food that didn’t  feel punitive,” Riggs said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000i356px9b8y2a0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The result was her first cookbook, “In Good Health.” When pulling together those recipes, the nonnegotiables, she decided, were nourishment, deliciousness and ease.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000j356p19t1onch@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “There aren’t any adaptations or faux foods here,” Riggs said. Instead, “it’s really just whole, nutrient-dense food. These are the recipes that I’ve been relying on for years.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000k356pd3x28q76@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Yes,  berries, sweet potatoes and salmon are on the menu. As is ahi tuna, roasted  almonds, rotisserie chicken and more. “Even if somebody doesn’t have their own restrictions, we’re all cooking for people that do these days,” she said. “This book is a great resource for when you’re cooking for friends or relatives who have dietary restrictions, say, for a holiday, which can be very daunting.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000l356prdh44wnt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Start with The Everyday Chocolate Cake&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;and   soon you’ll be trying Morning Glory Muffins,  Zesty Herbed Tahini Dip and Savory French Onion Beef.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000m356pkar5yrq5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Serves 6
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000n356p6gvu0nl8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Prep time:&lt;/strong&gt; 20 minutes
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000o356pfvvd9sg4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Bake time:&lt;/strong&gt; 25 minutes
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000p356psh8an5o6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Cool time:&lt;/strong&gt; 20 minutes
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000q356pd06r6p9c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Total  cooking time:&lt;/strong&gt; 1 hour 5 minutes
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000r356p4r46y4wq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            One of Riggs’ most beloved cures  for her cravings is this cake, which gets its decadent crumb from the cocoa powder.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000s356pqv19y67i@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            She uses a premium cocoa powder with a higher fat content that gives it a richer flavor. “When you’re cooking with so few ingredients, the ingredients matter,” Riggs said. (That’s why she includes her product picks in the cookbook.)
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000t356p25uauhtc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Once you’ve mastered this version of The Everyday Chocolate Cake, Riggs gives you permission to mix things up. Try adding ⅛ teaspoon of mint extract to the ganache for a minty chocolate cookie vibe, she said, or add a drop or two of orange oil instead. Or bake the same batter in a cupcake pan for a single-serving dessert.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000u356pfo4iwkd7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “My book also includes a birthday cake variation on this with a thicker, more spreadable ganache, because nobody should have to celebrate a birthday without a birthday cake,” Riggs told me.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/list/instances/cmkh1znv0002m356pozqlrn0l@published" class="list-elevate vossi-list_elevate" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
  &lt;ul data-editable="items" class="list__items list__items--ul vossi-list_elevate__items vossi-list_elevate__items--ul"&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.0.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Virgin coconut oil, for greasing
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.1.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            2 ½ cups (260 grams) superfine blanched almond flour
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.2.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            ¼ cup (30 grams) cocoa powder, preferably Valrhona
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.3.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            1 teaspoon baking soda
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.4.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            ¾ teaspoon Himalayan pink salt
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.5.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            ¾ cup (235 grams) pure maple syrup
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.6.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            3 large eggs, room temperature
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

  

  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/list/instances/cmkh1vv1a002g356p5m87h0s3@published" class="list-elevate vossi-list_elevate" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
  &lt;ul data-editable="items" class="list__items list__items--ul vossi-list_elevate__items vossi-list_elevate__items--ul"&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.0.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            ¼ cup (60 grams) canned full-fat, additive-free coconut milk (see note)
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.1.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            2 ounces (57 grams) 100% unsweetened chocolate (see note)
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.2.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            2 tablespoons pure maple syrup
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.3.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            ⅛ teaspoon Himalayan pink salt
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

  

  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/list/instances/cmkh1rv7s001p356pj7f0j3au@published" class="list-elevate vossi-list_elevate" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
  &lt;ol data-editable="items" class="list__items list__items--ol vossi-list_elevate__items vossi-list_elevate__items--ol"&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.0.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Make the cake: Preheat oven to 350 degrees Fahrenheit (177 degrees Celsius). Thoroughly grease a 9-inch (23-centimeter) nonstick springform pan with coconut oil and line the bottom with parchment paper.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.1.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            In      a medium mixing bowl, whisk together almond flour, cocoa       powder, baking soda and salt, breaking up any      lumps. Add the maple syrup and eggs,      and whisk until smooth and combined well. Pour the batter into the springform pan. Using a rubber      spatula, spread it toward the edges and tap the pan on the counter to      level the batter.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.2.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Bake for 25 minutes on the center rack. Cool for 20 minutes, then transfer the cake to a serving plate.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.3.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Allow      the cake to cool completely before making the ganache.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.4.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Make the ganache: Combine all ganache ingredients in a small glass or porcelain      bowl and microwave for 30 seconds. Using a small whisk, whisk gently for 2      to 3 minutes, until the chocolate is melted, smooth, glossy and slightly      thickened but still pourable.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.5.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Pour the chocolate ganache onto the top (center) of the cake. Using an offset spatula or the back of a spoon, carefully spread the ganache over the cake, nudging it gently over the edge and allowing it to drip down the sides as much as you like.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.6.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Refrigerate the cake, uncovered, for 30 minutes so the ganache can set.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.7.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Cover      and store at room temperature for up to three days, or in the fridge for up to a week.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d0016356p0sjkhxyg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;em&gt;Note: Look for a baking bar that contains only cacao beans, such as baking bars by Guittard. Use full-fat coconut milk that&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;does not contain additives or thickening agents&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;— Riggs likes Trader Joe’s Organic Coconut Milk or Native Forest Organic Coconut Milk Simple.&lt;/em&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmkh1tl5o002a356p3xrmrl8g@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note_elevate inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://karlawalsh.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Karla Walsh&lt;/a&gt; is a Des Moines, Iowa-based freelance lifestyle writer with more than 16 years of editorial experience.
&lt;/p&gt;

  

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:00:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxOeXJBZWpaVUhPQlZFVXBleEVEdXZEUkNWWmRUMFhrV1ZuRDBOWW1rU3FlTG1YdDBhaUhiRkx3UXNDRVlacmFvWFhzUUVTVW4ta2pqWTFycmZ4eUFReFJ5YWVhQzhSeDVVY0c3TjRKYk1XcC1rT0I5TlJtZU50N2Z3eU5udw</guid></item><item><title>一旦被枯萎病消灭，成千上万的美国栗树在缅因州生物学家的土地上蓬勃发展-好消息网络</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/once-wiped-out-by-blight-thousands-of-american-chestnut-trees-are-thriving-on-biologists-land-in-maine/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_228669" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228669" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-228669" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew.jpg 1400w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew-326x175.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew-1024x550.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew-768x413.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew-696x374.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew-1068x574.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew-782x420.jpg 782w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew-530x285.jpg 530w" sizes="(max-width: 1400px) 100vw, 1400px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-228669" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Dr. Bernd Heinrich – The Wild American Chestnut&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wild American chestnut trees, deemed “functionally extinct” decades ago, may already be quietly mounting an unexpected comeback in the northern forests of the US.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thousands of naturally thriving, wild trees in Maine contradict decades of assumptions about the species’ extinction—and how genetic engineering is the only solution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever since the accidental importation of an Asian virus in 1904 killed this majestic tree—once abundant along the U.S. East Coast and Canada—ghostly gaps left in the landscape haunted biologists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But a new documentary (&lt;em&gt;watch below&lt;/em&gt;) brought to light a remarkable and little-known success story: thousands of wild, healthy American chestnut trees are flourishing on the Maine forest land of renowned biologist and author Dr. Bernd Heinrich.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He bought 25 saplings for $10 from a nursery 44 years ago. They grew tall and their numbers multiplied as bluejays and squirrels plucked their seeds and buried them in fields as far away as a mile, and today there is no hint of blight in any of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These chestnuts are really taking off,” said the 85-year-old professor, who climbed to the top of one of the trees to fetch a sample of the fruit for the videographers. “And it could very well be that these are blight resistant.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The vigorous natural growth—which shows up in thousands of thriving grandchildren of the original trees—directly counters long-held beliefs that the iconic species survives today only as scattered, doomed sprouts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_228674" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228674" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-228674" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-%E2%80%93-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation.jpg 1400w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation-326x148.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation-1024x465.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation-768x349.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation-696x316.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation-1068x485.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation-925x420.jpg 925w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation-530x241.jpg 530w" sizes="(max-width: 1400px) 100vw, 1400px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-228674" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Historical American chestnut trees – Courtesy The American Chestnut Foundation&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Heinrich, professor emeritus of the Biology Department at the University of Vermont and author of more than 20 books on biology and 100 scientific papers (including the celebrated memoir &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/4r9hMRj" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Year in the Maine Woods&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;), has spent more than four decades observing the chestnuts on his hundreds of acres.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ANOTHER CHESTNUT DISCOVERY:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/towering-chestnut-tree-found-in-maine-could-help-save-the-nearly-extinct-species/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Giant Chestnut Tree Found in Maine Could Help Save a Near-Extinct Species&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with University of Vermont students, Heinrich’s &lt;a href="https://bioone.org/journals/northeastern-naturalist/volume-29/issue-3/045.029.0302/The-Continued-Spread-of-a-Wild-Population-of-American-Chestnuts/10.1656/045.029.0302.short" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;team has documented&lt;/a&gt; well over a thousand thriving chestnut trees—some now representing three generations of natural regeneration. Each has been mapped via GPS during a long-term field study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new short film, The Wild American Chestnut, produced by &lt;a href="http://TheWildAmericanChestnut.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Global Justice Ecology Project&lt;/a&gt;, also captures Heinrich discussing projections that the American chestnut is shifting its range northward due to climate change, opening new opportunities for survival beyond its historical geographic limits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_228673" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228673" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-228673" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license.jpg 974w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license-326x232.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license-768x547.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license-100x70.jpg 100w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license-696x496.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license-589x420.jpg 589w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license-530x378.jpg 530w" sizes="(max-width: 974px) 100vw, 974px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-228673" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;American Chestnut Nuts with Burrs and Leaves – Credit: Timothy Van Vliet from his Orchard in New Jersey in 2004 -GNU Free license&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These acres of thriving chestnuts magnify the major setbacks for the biotech-based tree restoration strategies of the past three decades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In December 2023, The American Chestnut Foundation withdrew its support for a genetically engineered chestnut that was decades in development, after multiple documented research errors revealed the tree to be genetically defective. Discouraging field performance rendered them, in the Foundation’s opinion, unsuitable as the basis for species restoration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MORE FLOWERING SURPRISES&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/look-worlds-largest-prehistoric-flower-preserved-in-amber-is-stunning-reminded-of-natures-beauty/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;World’s Largest Prehistoric Flower Preserved in Amber is Stunning Reminder of Nature’s Wonder–LOOK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This film presents some good news about the wild American chestnut and is a stark contrast to claims by some researchers that genetically engineered trees are the only path to restoration,” said Anne Petermann, Executive Director of the Project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was stunning to see so many robust trees—three full generations growing naturally—while the efforts to engineer blight-resistant chestnuts have produced nothing but failures.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ebywGe-J730?si=An6NOiQ9KcLGmyfR" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPREAD SEEDS OF GOOD NEWS By Sharing a Chestnut With Tree Lovers on Social Media…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:51:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0AFBVV95cUxPekxKeWoyVTkxMlg3STBVeDVsRFNCVVdqMFhVVzNjcy15OFZvTFJBU3JuUFJ2aWNQYTI2dTZ6YnNtY0VXMzZLUTJHWjN5NE1Vd19vSFFHTEhyVjVYeFJaZlctTHM1V1hEaDY0R19ScUdLMXUzWjhlaEdGUEZ5WExNamZZSVUtYmVzVEVkc1Q0aTRyR3R6Y0VuQ1NaYmlwUmZyLWlyMC1KTUg1TmFGUVdHVnVMWU1sUE5lbGp2bXlLdjdfMjJkVlZTZTI2bVE4ODZX</guid></item></channel></rss>